♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Okay!
Impact!
Odd, take Aelita to the tower! Yumi’s in trouble!
Okay, here we go!
Hang on, Yumi, you can do it.
There!
Aelita!
Okay, Princess, the home stretch!
Odd! Two more Bloks are coming at you!
No sweat! Be back in a second, Aelita!
Laser arrow!
Yeah!
He is amazing, how-
Odd!
--the crowd is going wild--
Odd, cut it out, will you?
--thank you!
There’s a third Blok!
Huh? A third one?
Odd!
Oh no!
Odd, you’ve lost too many life points!
Odd, what are you doing? Take cover!
It’s too risky!
Odd, one impact and it’s game over.
You’ve only got ten life points left, that’s all!
Ten’s more than enough! Here we go!
You see, what did I tell you?
Great, Odd!
Congratulations!
Hey Jeremie, next time, just enjoy the show
and let the real pros get the job done, okay?
(LAUGHS)
Huh?
I’ll go and take care of the tower.
Hey, take it easy, I was just kidding!
I didn’t mean it! Hey, Einstein, you hear me,
it was a joke!
Return to the past now.
Valerie?
Present.
Benjamin?
Herb?
Present, ma’am.
Nicolas?
Here.
Sissi?
Present.
Jeremie?
Hey, great work, guys.
You were better than ever!
No hard, feelings, Odd, it was--
Odd?
Huh?
Odd? Odd? Odd’s absent?
Well, and so is Ulrich.
Herb?
Present, ma’am.
Nicolas?
Here.
Sissi?
Present.
Jeremie?
Dylan?
Present.
Hey, that was great work, Einstein.
You were never better! No hard feelings, huh?
Caroline?
Present
After what you said to him before,
it’s no wonder he’s sulking.
Odd! Ulrich!
Here, ma’am!
I know that you’re here.
What I do not know is what you have to say
to each other that’s so interesting!
They asked me if I noticed,
that with all due respect, ma’am,
the Brauer equation you wrote
on the blackboard is wrong.
What?
It’s not wrong from a mathematical
point-of-view, but it fails to take into account
Bronski’s theories on the
phenomenon of compared masses.
You should treat the second unknown element
as a squared mass, not a factorial.
Hmm…
Why yes, you’re…
you’re absolutely right!
I’m sorry about that!
Jeremie, would you know where
Ulrich and Odd are?
This is weird, I don’t believe it!
Yumi’s gone, too!
Nobody here?
Aelita?
Aelita, Ulrich, Odd, and Yumi…
Tell me that they’re with you.
Why? Didn’t they come back from Lyoko?
No, Aelita, I’ve lost them!
Something must have gone wrong
on the return trip!
Calm down, Jeremie, they couldn’t have
just vanished. Go and check the scanners
while I look around Lyoko.
Good idea, I’ll go and see...
Hmm…
You mind telling me what you’re doing here?
Uh…
You guys okay?
As okay as two guys can be
with two hours of Bio ahead of them.
Anyone know why he’s sulking?
He’s angry at Odd.
Listen, uh, something
really strange happened in English class.
All the world’s a stage,
and all the men and women merely players.
They have their entrances and--
--and all the men and women merely players.
Like a broken record,
but it only lasted a second.
And what?
You’re thinking that it could be XANA?
I really don’t know, Ulrich,
but it sure wouldn’t hurt to keep an eye on things.
Nobody.
Pulsations?
XANA!
Jeremie, this is serious.
Everyone is very concerned.
Now, for the last time,
do you know where Yumi, Odd, and Ulrich are?
No, sir, I--
As I’m sure you can imagine,
their parents are worried sick.
I already told you,
I don’t know where they are.
Jeremie.
Think about it, please.
The smallest clue could prove to be a great help,
you four are always together!
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Alright, sir, I’ll think about it,
but I need to be alone.
You have an awful lot of nerve,
young man.
However, if it’s the only way
to bring you to your senses...
I’ll give you three minutes.
Thank you, sir.
I felt your message. What’s new?
I’m sorry, Jeremie,
but they’re not on Lyoko.
There’s an activated tower, though...
only I can’t seem to locate it.
I need your help. Go to the factory.
Impossible, I’m stuck in
the principal’s office.
You are? Don’t worry, I’ll help you
get out of there.
Yes, Jeremie, just like XANA, I can operate
on the school’s network as well.
Listen closely now.
I’m sure Jeremie knows more
than he’s saying.
Should we call the police?
I’ve thought it over.
I'll tell you where they are.
Pass the peas!
-No, you can reach them yourself!
Thanks!
-Did you hear Rockout’s new single?
Didn’t I tell you?
No, go on.
Well, I needed new wheels,
because I broke them on a ramp.
So, I call over the guys selling them--
Hey, Sissi, did you use canary feathers
in the washing machine instead of soap?
That is so dumb! I’ll have you know
that yellow is the “in” color this year! Hmph!
(LAUGHS)
What a dolt!
Pass the peas!
-No, you can reach them yourself!
Thanks!
-Did you hear Rockout’s new single?
Huh?
Hey, did you hear that?
I sure did.
That is so dumb! I’ll have you know
that yellow is the “in” color this year! Hmph!
I didn’t say anything that time!
We’ve got a problem, guys.
But there’s nobody here!
We have to wait a little while.
Hm?
They’ll be here any minute now.
Hmm...
Well, where are they?
(COUGHING)
Jeremie!
It’s impossible…
he couldn’t have just disappeared!
Aelita!
Yes, Jeremie?
Thanks for giving me a hand!
I hope you realize that if…
that if you don’t detect anything alive
on the scanners, it’ll mean that…
Yes, I know. We’ll find out soon enough.
Empty.
They aren’t there.
I don’t get it. If they’re not here, and they’re
not on Lyoko, either, where are they?
Jeremie! Just before you got here,
I captured this sound byte! A sort of…
radio or TV station transmission.
But be careful, Jeremie, it was really bizarre.
Let me show you.
Alright, let’s go.
Huh?
We’ll start with a little stretching.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, that’s crazy!
And one, and two, and one,
and two, and one, and two.
That’s it!
Hey, watch what you’re doing, huh?
You did that on purpose, I saw you!
And one--
Hey, watch what you’re doing, huh?
It happened again!
I’ll show you what it feels like!
And it’s happening all the time!
Keep going on your own!
Jeremie?
What am I looking at?
They didn’t come back to Earth, did they?
What if what we’re seeing is a recording?
But how can that be, Aelita?
I’m in the picture!
There are weird things happening,
any news from Aelita?
I’m having difficulty contacting her,
I have no idea if there’s an activated tower or not,
but at the slightest alert, we’ll have to move in.
Hey, how come you’re not doing
Phys Ed, Jeremie?
Jim agreed to excuse me.
He did? That’s weird.
You’re not exactly his star athlete.
You’ve gotta know how to handle him.
--twenty-six, twenty-seven,
keep going, twenty-eight--
Not like them.
Huh?
Incredible.
It sure isn’t a tape. It’s happening somewhere,
right now. They’re neither in Lyoko nor
in the real world. They’re somewhere else…
Yes, I know, but I checked all the
transfer protocol data, and unless
a sort of parallel world exists somewhere,
there’s no such thing as an intermediate space.
Unless XANA has manufactured one!
That’s it! A world parallel to Lyoko!
And he must’ve modeled it after the school!
He couldn’t have made a better trap!
Yumi and the others think they’re in reality,
but it’s only an illusion.
They’re living under XANA’s control, completely at his mercy.
We’ve gotta rescue them!
Find out where the signal is coming from!
I’ve been trying to, but it’s been masked.
The signal is scrambled. All we have is a soundwave
and not the signal itself.
Then that’s what we’ll have to use.
We’ve gotta program it to guide the scanner
and dive towards the source using
a trial and error system.
But that’s crazy and you know it!
And besides, who could do it?
We’re all alone, Jeremie, and--
It’s gonna have to be me.
If you take over the controls,
then I’ll be able to go.
It’s too dangerous.
But we can’t leave Ulrich and Yumi and Odd
at the mercy of XANA! Think about it.
If I’m here in front of you…
...who’s the other Jeremie?
Aelita
There’s something I wanna tell you.
I’d much rather be entering a virtual world
to find you there waiting for me.
So would I.
Here we go.
It’s okay, Jeremie,
I’ve prepared the transfer procedure.
You can get into the scanner.
Scanner Jeremie
Virtualization!
Woah!
Aelita, can you hear me?
Of course not, that would be too easy.
Hmph. There he is at last.
We’ve got a visitor, Jim.
That’s gotta be it!
I’d better go now and have a closer look.
Yeah, Yumi’s what you might call intuitive,
but she can be wrong sometimes,
and let’s face it, Ulrich, any girl with a crush on you
can’t be what I call absolutely normal.
Well, what about Jeremie?
Don’t tell me you don’t find him a bit strange.
Well, yeah, he has been acting a bit weird lately,
but to think that he’s been hiding a huge secret--
Yeah, hello? Yumi, is that you? What’s the--?
It’s started again, but this time,
it’s a lot worse than ever,
this time it’s at my own home!
What’s going on, Yumi?
It’s my parents, they’re acting so…
I don’t know, so strangely!
They keep making the same gestures,
and they act as if I’m not even there!
It’s as if they were phony imitations of my real
mom and dad, we’ve gotta do something!
You better not stay there, I’ll see you in the park,
okay? We’ll go to the factory, I’ll warn Jeremie.
No, not Jeremie. Just Odd, you, and me, okay?
Let’s leave Jeremie out of it this time,
I-I have my doubts. See ya.
Let’s hope they’re in their room.
Ungh…
Oh…
(GROWLS)
I’ve got you.
Soon, I won’t have any more obstacles.
I only hope it’s not too late.
What about Jeremie?
We didn’t tell him.
But, you know, once we’re at the factory,
we can’t get to Lyoko without him.
We’ll see when we get there,
but I’m afraid he can’t be trusted.
(LEAVES RUSTLE)
Must’ve been a squirrel or something.
C’mon, let’s go.
Oh no, too late!
Out of my way!
For a program, you’re a pretty good imitation!
I don’t understand, there’s no link,
it’s like Lyoko didn’t exist anymore.
And that might be exactly what has happened.
Huh?
Jeremie!
Jeremie? But what are you doing here?
I got a message from Aelita that
a tower’s just been activated.
She said something about about a program
to erase Lyoko. I haven’t heard from her since.
Okay, we’ve gotta check this out, Yumi.
Hey, wait a minute, if the link has been cut,
how do you intend to send us there?
I’ve created a new access protocol.
All we need now are the scanners.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Hmph.
Hold it, Odd, I’m not too sure of this.
Ngh…
What’s wrong with you? Look, it’s Jeremie, Yumi!
We’ve gotta get moving!
What if Lyoko does get erased, huh?
Have you thought about Aelita?
Look, you’ve gotta believe me,
but if you have any doubt,
let Ulrich and Odd be transferred before you.
Yumi, you’re right, it’s a trap!
Don’t go!
XANA, is that the best you can do?
A cheap imitation to delay us?
He’s lying. The phony is there, it’s him!
Everything you hear is phony!
Huh?
You never came back from your last trip.
You’re in a virtual world created by XANA!
That would explain all the inconsistencies!
Of course it would, XANA can make mistakes, too!
He only has theoretical knowledge of the real world.
What he wants is to get you into the scanner
to get rid of you once and for all!
That’s totally absurd, XANA.
It’s true, we have no proof that he’s
not the one lying to us, right?
He could have created the inconsistencies, too.
Exactly. To hold us up while Aelita and Lyoko
are being erased forever.
The only proof is the fact that I’m here with you.
You have to decide which one of us is lying.
And it’s not me! Assuming, as you claim, that
this world is virtual, you mind telling us how you got here?
We’re listening, XANA.
I got in here via the scanner,
I’m here in virtual form.
You gave yourself away! Everybody knows that
the real Jeremie wouldn’t step foot in the scanner!
He’d be much too frightened!
Hah…
Huh?
And I’m sure he would go into the scanner,
if his friends were in danger.
No doubt about it.
Absolutely none.
But it’s not logical, don’t you see?
He’s much too scared to even try.
I’m much too scared! If not,
then why haven’t I already done it?
I told you why, because he’s not infallible.
XANA’s knowledge of people is only approximative.
That’s right, and as far as friendship goes,
it’s not approximative, it’s double zero.
Good to see you again, Einstein.
No! It’s not logical!
No!
NOT LOGICAL! NOT LOGICAL!
Woah!
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
You are going to die!
Aelita!
No!
(LAUGHS)
(CELESTIAL SINGING)
Jeremie! No!
Aelita, here I am, are you okay?
Yes, fine. Don’t worry.
Phew.
I got them back, all of them, safe and sound.
The parallel world bubble has disappeared.
I don’t remember anything,
but I feel just great!
Aelita? What happened to us?
XANA created a replica of where you live
so you’d think it was reality.
He locked us up in a virtual prison.
But Jeremie and I did all we could
to set you free.
What? Jeremie came to Lyoko?
Mhmm.
Fantastic, Einstein!
Join the daredevil heroes club!
Thanks Odd,
no hard feelings, huh?
Look, it’s XANA’s welcoming committee!
No need to worry, Jeremie, we’re used to this.
It’s a piece of cake! Here we go!
I’m with you!
Yeah!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS