♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Huh three day weekend,
that’s fantastic. Isn’t it?
With a little luck,
I just may have the house to myself.
Yeah, but knowing your parents
it’s not going to be easy.
I’m betting on Yumi.
I didn’t tell you, but I’ve got a lot
of homework this weekend.
Of course I’ll stay home and look after things.
And if you’ve nothing against it,
I’d like to have a little gathering.
Gathering to do homework together,
or to wreck the living room?
Well… uh...
Go on answer your father.
Well I thought I’d invite my friends over
for a quiet evening at home.
Hmm…
You mean those three clowns?
But daddy! You hardly
even know them!
They seem nice enough.
I wish you’d trust me a little more.
Hm…
Alright!
They can come.
That is so great!
You won’t regret it. You’ll see!
Thanks mom.
You are the greatest!
Have a nice weekend!
Hey I’ve got great news guys,
tonight we have the house all to ourselves.
You did it!
We better get organized.
No problem.
Anything wrong, Jeremie?
I’m trying to localize Lyoko,
it shouldn’t take this much time.
Don’t worry!
If there is a problem,
Aelita will contact you.
Yeah well,
we can always hope.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Time for physics!
Hm. Class dismissed.
And don’t forget Monday’s quiz
on seismic phenomenon better known as earthquakes.
Theo and Benjamin said they would come,
But what are we gonna do about Sissi?
Wouldn’t break my heart if she didn’t come.
She and that horrible music she’d bring with her.
Hey, leave the music to me.
Wait till you see the surprise I’ve got in store for you.
We’re gonna have a real DJ, guys.
You’ll see, no dumb music for us, we’re gonna rock.
Great, see ya later.
We’ll go shopping after class.
Ok, in the meantime I’ll try and contact
Aelita and warn her to be careful tonight. You never know.
And now it’s time for Ulrich to get ready and enter the starting block.
Tensions are high, ladies and gentlemen,
as he zeros in on his objective.
The timekeeper is about to signal the departure.
Bang!
And he’s off and running!
What grace! What agility! And what great speed he’s got!
And here we go, he’s ready for the sliding phase!
With perfect knee coordination!
Ready?
Stop!
Oh, he beat me.
Really? Ulrich went farther than you?
Well then, how did I make out?
A new dorm record!
What’s all this racket about?
(GROWLING)
Gotta hang up!
Secret code Big-Fat-Clown
Gotcha, ok, talk to you later.
Come on, Jim, we’re just a little bored,
there’s nothing to do here.
I really don’t understand, every long weekend,
you kids stay at school, you never go anywhere!
If for once you guys took a vacation,
I’d have some peace and quiet!
That just goes to show you how much we love this place.
Oh yeah? I bet that’s cause at home your parents are sick of ya!
I sympathise with them.
And now, let’s go, I want all of you to
go back to your rooms on the double!
Awww...
Right away, Jim.
Your turn, Odd.
We’d better hurry, huh?
Bang!
You ok, Odd?
Hey didn’t I beat the record?
Is this your surprise disc-jockey? Huh?
Yeah-you mean you don’t recognize her?
She goes to school here, her name’s Samantha.
Uh see ya later, I’ve got some work to do.
Hm, you're not gonna introduce us to her?
That must be her.
Hello?
I don’t believe it.
That’s the fifth time
I’ve launched the localization program.
The network must really be blocked,
I can’t into contact with Lyoko.
Uh, hello?
Hi.
How are you?
Did you have any trouble getting in?
No, no trouble, the gates were really easy to climb.
When can you show me what you’re gonna do?
When I’m finished, I wanna add a little
more stuff, but I haven’t found anything I like yet.
You should try the old vinyl records,
there’s lots of really great stuff on vinyl.
If you want, I’ll lend you some.
Can’t we stop talking about music?
We’ve got better things to do, don’t you think?
Ready for a big thrill session?
Uh, yeah I guess.
Well, then take me to the computer room, Odd.
I think this time I’ve got it!
One more operation and...
Aelita? Aelita, it’s Jeremie! Do you read me, Aelita?
Hey, Aelita!
Hello Jeremie. How are you?
Eh, So-so--
Why? What’s wrong?
I had such a tough time contacting Lyoko!
That’s nothing new. Lyoko is constantly
changing its access points on the network.
Hey, you feel like playing some chess?
Be right there.
Wow, what kind of powers this one got?
Oh, I dunno, two gigas?
Hey, cut that out! Put that down, you hear?
What are you doing?
If I’m gonna make music, I need a powerful computer, but I’m broke, so I have no choice but to rip this one off.
Your school’s insured, so everybody's happy, right?
Wrong! Insurance or not, stealing’s a crime!
And besides, nobody--
Does that around here.
Hey, you’re r--
Shhh!
Hmm?
I would never have believed it of you, Odd.
I wasn't going to steal it, Jim, I swear!
Huh, what were you gonna do with it, then?
Uh.
You've got some explaining to do, follow me.
Checkmate!
Can I maybe try beating you at...
Like, karate?
Go on, keep moving.
Looks like trouble.
Well Odd, this time you are in one
heck of a jam, that’s for sure kid.
Caught in the act stealing a computer that is school
property isn’t like not doing your homework.
Listen Jim!
What the?
This is crazy, whenever Odd needs a
computer, I lend him mine, I’ve done it lots of times.
Go on, tell him, Odd.
Yeah, although, this time I needed a really
powerful laptop, and that one was just perfect.
And why didn’t you ask permission to borrow it?
It seems to me that would have been a lot more simple.
Well, I was afraid that you would say no.
What do you think I am? An idiot?
I want the truth right now.
You stole it, didn’t you?
This time it’s the school disciplinary council,
and you might just get expelled!
Huh? No wait, you can’t do that to me, Jim!
(PHONE RINGS)
The use of cell phones is strictly forbidden on school grounds!
Hand it over, confiscated!
Jeremie! Jeremie!
I just spotted an activated tower.
Jeremie, Xana’s launched an attack.
Jeremie, answer me!
Gotta get outta here.
Huh?
Ok, tell us what happened, come on Odd.
I’ve got nothing else to say.
See you later, I got things to do.
Alone!
Do you see what I see?
Xana!
Hey, they’re getting really deep,
everything’s gonna be swallowed up.
(PHONE RINGS)
Ok, I’ll see you at the factory.
Hold it!
Look, I can’t go with you now.
Samantha’s locked in the
science building’s computer room.
Ok...
Let’s go back to the beginning,
cause I think you lost us, Odd.
She’s the one who stole the computer.
I really tried to stop her, but...
Well, she’s already got a lot of problems
at her school, so I didn’t tell Jim.
No matter what happened, we gotta get her outta there.
Right, I’ll run over and meet Yumi at the lab.
Ok, step number one,
we pay a little visit to the gymnasium.
Let’s hope we’re the only ones at school.
Must be in here.
Bingo!
So which way do we go now?
There!
Oh no, I don’t believe it, I’m never going to get out of here!
It’s at least a twenty meter drop down there.
Well, make sure the rope is attached securely.
What’s going on?
Connection!
Connecting to Lyoko.
Jeremie! You're there, at last!
Xana’s activated a tower!
That’s what we thought, we’ve already been affected.
Take your time and concentrate.
Go!
Ok, here we go.
Hurry! The stairs!
Yumi, you’re off to the mountain region.
I’ve got problems connecting to Lyoko,
the landing could be rough.
So be careful.
Transfer Yumi.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization!
Hey!
Get me outta here, get me outta here!
Let’s hope we don’t get there too late.
I’ve gotta get out.
I’ve gotta get out of here!
Samantha!
Sam, we’re on our way!
Don’t worry Sam, we’re gonna get you out.
Are you ok? It’s over now, Sam.
Oh Odd, I’m sorry.
I hate to bother you guys, but we’ve
gotta get outta here, and fast, too!
Yumi, your hand, give me your hand.
Thank you, Aelita, you got here just in time.
Now we’ve got to hurry, Xana’s monsters
aren’t here yet but they’re bound to come.
The tower’s not far from here, in that direction.
Well, this promises to be a charming stroll.
It’s not as hard as all that.
If you jump at the right time.
I see what you mean.
Ready?
46, 47.
48, 49.
What’s going on?
We’re almost there.
You were right, Aelita, it wasn’t all that hard.
Watch out, three hornets approaching fast!
Stay behind me.
They’ve disappeared from my control screen.
Where did they go?
I don't know.
In this territory, they have the advantage.
Can you hear me?
Listen, I’m calling from the junior-highschool.
I work here at the school and I need your help.
Listen it’s a real emergency, I’m stuck in a
closet with tons of mud, so get here fast!
No, lady, this is not a practical joke!
No, I can’t wait any longer!
Help me!
Yumi, the hornets are coming straight at you!
Jeremie, I’m caught in a crossfire,
I can’t hold out much longer!
Hang on, Odd and Ulrich are on the way!
I hope so, anyway.
Aelita!
Yumi no!
Try using your creativity, Aelita, we need a little time!
Wow, this place is wild, what is it?
Huh, you’re finally here!
Yumi’s been devirtualized, Aelita’s fighting three hornets all alone!
Odd, I don't understand any of this.
What’s going on, huh?
Sorry, there’s no time to explain.
You keep Jeremie company, and I’ll see you later.
What?
Oh, girls!
No time to lose!
Destination, the mountains.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization!
We made it, Einstein.
Great.
The path in front of you leads
to the platform where you’ll find Aelita.
Get outta here, you monster!
Sorry we’re late, Aelita.
This will convince you to forgive us.
Laser arrow!
You missed your target, Odd.
Ulrich, careful!
Watch out, Odd!
So, you wanna play, huh?
Laser arrow!
Hey what’s my problem today, huh?
They’re coming back!
Laser arrow!
Nice going, Odd.
It’s about time.
Triplicate!
It’s just us now!
Help!
Where are they?
Odd!
Hurry, Aelita! Let Odd handle it.
Help me!
I don’t wanna die!
Return to the past, now!
Psst.
Ok, he’s gone!
Where is he?
He should be here by now.
(KNOCKING)
Hey, I thought you said no one else knew.
It’s ok, they’re my pals.
This is Ulrich.
And this is Jeremie.
The genius who’s gonna help you rock!
Have a seat, Sam.
I'll show you what
you can do when you’ve got great equipment.
Thanks, Odd.
Now if you don’t mind, let’s focus, ok?
(LAUGHTER)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS