♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
It’s now or never!
Go on, Aelita! Go!
Odd’s on his way, Aelita.
Impact!
Megatank approaching!
Hold it.
Come and get me, you bowling ball.
Laser arrow!
Phew.
It’s okay. Aelita’s in the tower.
As usual, guys, great job!
That’s right!
Another XANA attack chalked up,
another tower gone!
Okay, get ready for the return trip to the past.
And so this equation,
which you weren’t able to solve,
would have enabled you to--
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Class dismissed, and don’t forget
your chemistry exercise for tomorrow.
Actually, I prefer Odd. He’s funny, too.
I got bonus points for making level five.
Well, guys, how was class today with Missus Hertz?
Was it fun?
The same exact lesson
as before the XANA attack,
so it was twice as boring.
Once, twice, it doesn’t matter.
You’ll never be any good in physics anyways.
Well, if it isn’t Sissi.
“Hello, Ulrich dear, can we talk for a minute?”
Hello, Ulrich dear, can we talk for a minute?
(LAUGHS)
First of all, I’m not your Ulrich dear,
Second of all, I will not go to your room
to explain Exercise B, page 52.
But, how did you that I--
A Sissi attack is almost as bad as a XANA attack,
and ten times as boring.
That’s for sure.
So, anyone feel like sneaking out
and going into town for a while?
Count me out. I’ve got a heavy date with my pillow.
And I’m gonna work on my program
for materializing Aelita!
One of these days, I’m gonna do it!
How about you, Yumi?
Wanna go into town and have an ice cream?
No, not tonight. I’ve got to do a little studying.
I’m way behind thanks to all these XANA attacks.
See you tomorrow!
Ciao, Yumi, see you tomorrow!
Another exciting evening.
Ciao!
Ulrich, you ought to take a shower,
it really relaxes you!
Tell me what your day was like.
Oh, nothing special. Let’s see, now…
Oh, I had the embarrassment
of my life in gym class.
My shorts tore, you can guess where.
Then I lost my pencil case in the library,
and to finish the day, I had a fight with Marcie.
And that’s what my day was like.
No, what I mean, Odd, is
don’t you feel you’ve already had
the exact same kind of day?
Well yeah, but that’s normal.
Don’t forget, we had the same
French, English, and physics class twice,
and on Lyoko, it was “Yoohoo, it’s us!”
for the seventh time.
“Yoohoo, it’s us?”
That’s what I call our game plan,
y’know, the one we use to help Aelita
reach the tower safe and sound.
Why all these questions, hm?
No reason, I’ve…
I’m fed up with all this school, Lyoko,
back to school, back to Lyoko,
and this is XANA’s fifth attack in a week.
I’m also fed up with what’s happening
to Yumi and me.
Once in a while, I get the feeling that…
that she doesn’t really like me,
that she doesn’t have…any feelings for me.
(SNORES)
Oh, hi Emily.
Hello, Ulrich. I’m looking for Jim.
Have you seen him?
No, sorry.
That’s okay, goodnight.
I don’t believe it.
Does she have a thing for me, huh?
Ulrich, if you’re gonna sleepwalk,
do it in your room!
Oh, hi Jim.
By the way, Emily’s looking for you.
Hm?
Hm, Ulrich?
What’s he doing with Emily?
They sure don’t look bored.
Hello.
What kind of a game does he think he’s playing?
He’s just talking to her.
What are you, jealous?
What, me jealous of Emily?
You’ve gotta be kidding.
Besides, she’s a year older than him,
and that’s a lot.
Guess what. You’re also a year older than him.
I guess you just forgot.
Yeah, well it’s not the same thing!
I’m Ulrich’s girlfriend! I-I mean,
I-I’m his good friend.
You know, Ulrich’s been
kinda down in the dumps,
so if he wants to talk to another girl,
don’t make a big deal about it.
Who says that I am?
Oh, this machine is gonna drive me bananas!
Hey, that’s double big news.
Ulrich without Yumi, and Ulrich with Emily.
Emily? How dare she!
The nerve of her going after him!
If Yumi’s out of the picture, I’m next on the list!
Speaking of Yumi, she’s not taking it too well.
Neither are you, Sissi.
Oh, shut up!
I’ve just got a really great idea
that’s bound to make Ulrich all mine!
Quite a romance going on there.
(LAUGHTER)
Two months already, that’s not bad.
What?
Oh, I thought you knew!
Doesn’t Ulrich tell you everything?
I mean, you two are so close,
I’ve decided to give up on him.
There’s no hope. I’ll have
to do my best to forget him.
And if I were you, I would do the same.
You’re not me, Sissi,
so save your advice if you don’t mind.
What a pest…
You mean you didn’t know?
Sissi, do you mind explaining your strategy?
Jeremie!
XANA’s launched another attack!
Are you feeling pulsations?
Yes, in the desert region,
they’re really strong.
I’ve never seen him so active as he is now.
Sorry, guys. You gotta go back.
And right away, too!
Well, as they say,
when you gotta go, you gotta go.
Ulrich has shut off his cell phone.
Yeah, he’s much too busy with Emily,
hang on, I’ll go get him.
Yumi, no, wait!
Wanna go for a walk, Ulrich?
It’s nice to relax and not think of--.
Hey Ulrich!
Huh?
Come here for a second.
Hello, Yumi.
I’ll be right back, okay?
I hate to disturb you, Romeo,
but Jeremie’s been trying to reach you.
XANA’s just woken up!
XANA, again?
Go on, I’ll be right there.
What do you mean, go on?
Cool it, huh, Yumi?
Okay, I’ll cool it.
First, tell me what’s going on with
you and Emily.
Nothing’s going on.
I like her, we get along really well.
I don’t understand the problem,
unless that bothers you.
Bothers me?
No, it’s just that…
that you could’ve told me about it!
Like a buddy, huh?
Oh, I get it.
You think of us as buddies.
I’ve wondered what you thought of us, and now I know.
That’s right, a couple of pals, and nothing more,
and besides, that’s the way you want it!
Not like Emily, huh?
Oh, Ulrich!
Okay, what do I really mean to you?
And be honest, huh?
Me be honest?
You and Emily have been together
for two months without a word
and you tell me to be honest?
Where did you get that? Emily and I are not-
Oh, forget it. I’m not gonna...
defend myself to you. Ciao.
Yeah, right, ciao,
that’s all you can think of to say!
Ulrich?
Oh, Jeremie.
Yeah, I told him, he’s on his way there.
Me too, yeah, I’ll be right there.
Now that act two is over,
the final act is all mine.
All yours? But what about Emily?
Oh, for a pro like me, Emily is no problem.
Huh?
In exactly thirty seconds,
Ulrich will be in my arms.
See you later!
Ulrich, dear, I have to tell you something!
It can’t wait any longer!
Sissi, dear, under normal conditions,
I would take the time to tell you to go fly a kite,
but this time, I’ll be less polite and just ignore you.
(LAUGHS)
Well, your thirty seconds are up.
No, everything’s quiet here.
No short circuits, no giant bug invasion,
no earthquakes…
how about you?
Well, I’m almost at the activated tower,
but none of XANA’s monsters have appeared yet.
If not for the pulsations,
there’s no other sign that XANA’s woken up.
I wonder if this is a new tactic of his.
What if the attack is aimed at us directly?
For example, this argument between Yumi and Ulrich.
Suppose that XANA is just using Emily to mess with our heads.
I got a better idea, he’s using your ridiculous theories
to distract us.
What’s the matter with you? I was just trying to help.
Give us a break, Odd, will you?
Stay out of this.
Hey, stay calm.
I think one of you should do a little reconnaissance on Lyoko.
Well, who wants to be first?
Don’t all of you answer at once.
Send Ulrich, Jeremie. He needs to be entertained,
he’d love to go to Lyoko!
Ladies first, get her out of our hair.
Look, I’m getting tired of all this quarreling,
Aelita needs us and that is what I call an emergency,
so head for the scanners, all three of you are going!
Aelita.
Help is on the way.
I better warn you, Yumi and Ulrich are a bit...
well, you might say “buggy.”
You mean to say that they’ve been fighting,
don’t you?
You guessed it, Aelita.
I’m gonna transfer you to the desert region.
Don’t forget, you have to protect Aelita, all three of you.
Okay, here we go.
Transfer Yumi
Transfer Ulrich
Transfer Odd
Scanner Ulrich
Scanner Yumi
Scanner  Odd
Virtualization!
Hi!
Hello, Aelita.
Hey, Aelita!
Huh?
There was a bug at the moment of transfer,
are they all--?
Don’t worry, everyone is accounted for.
Safe and sound and ready to go.
I don’t know what it was. I’ll scan the program,
we’ll see what happened.
What is this mess?
Aelita!
I think the Supercalculator’s been infected with a virus!
So that’s the XANA attack…
But that’s crazy.
Why would XANA want to infect himself?
Well, you never know what XANA’s got
in his head until it’s done.
Unless...
He’s using it to modify a program
that he doesn’t have access to.
Yeah, but which one?
I don’t know, but it look like he wants to
change the rules on Lyoko.
I got a funny feeling about this.
We’ve got to take a closer look into this.
There has to be a deactivated tower not far from you.
Okay, I’m off.
I hope you’re not gonna kill each other
if I leave you two alone.
Jeremie.
Okay, I’m here.
I have access to the transfer program.
This is very strange.
Usually, the program doesn’t include
any of XANA’s creatures. It’s really weird.
You go, you’re the closest.
Now I understand, Jeremie. It’s a trap!
XANA’s sabotaged the devirtualization program!
Huh?
Odd, watch out for lasers! This monster could kill you for good!
Laser arrow!
What’s going on?
XANA’s monsters can prove fatal to you.
Can’t be  devirtualized or you’ll disappear forever!
Oh no! Odd’s lost 50 life points already!
Calm down, Jeremie, Odd’s still here with us.
But you don’t understand,
he just got hit by a laser,
that means he’s only got-
Listen, Jeremie.
Aelita takes the same risks all the time.
Nothing’s changed for us.
We have to be more careful, that’s all.
One thing is sure, XANA’s really trapped us,
and we’d better not make a mistake this time.
It’ll make the fight a lot more exciting.
I’ve got to deactivate the tower fast,
before XANA has a chance to concentrate all his strength on-
That’s the safest solution.
Hurry, but watch out for monsters!
Meanwhile, I’ll try to get rid of the virus.
Listen XANA...
if you think you can impress me with your cheap,
two-bit virus, you are mistaken.
I’m never gonna get it to work!
XANA has completely wrecked the circuits!
There’s only one possible solution.
Work directly on the hardware.
There’s gotta be an access around here somewhere.
All I gotta do now is find it.
Here?
Uhh, nope.
Must be in the Supercalculator room.
Hmm, no way.
On this floor, everything’s locked up tight.
Now what?
Oh no!
XANA, you’re even more evil than I thought.
Jeremie, how are you doing?
Jeremie?
The access base!
If I adjust the winch,
I should be able to get down.
The tower! It’s there!
(MACHINE WHIRS)
You don’t scare me, XANA!
Just gotta replace the circuits you messed up,
and you’ll fail again like all the other times!
It’s all over.
If we try to get through all this, we’re done for.
You never know.
We’ll just have to hang on until
Aelita enters the code.
It’s “Yoohoo, it’s us” time.
Yumi, you take the Krab.
Odd and I will take on the Megatanks.
Aelita, go on, run!
Ulrich, I, uh…
Be careful, Yumi.
You too, Ulrich.
Keep rolling! Laser arrow!
Yumi!
I’m coming!
Bingo!
You were just-- aaah!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
Yumi, no!
It’s okay, I’ve got you.
Ulrich, you…
Yeah...
Actually, I prefer Odd. He’s funny, too.
I got bonus points for making level five.
Quite a romance, don’t you think?
Two months already, huh?
Really, two months? That long?
There’s Yumi.
So long now, Emily.
So long! Ain’t love grand…
Hi, I was waiting for you.
So was I. Two months is a pretty long time,
but Sissi was here to keep me company.
Hm?
Thanks.
Bunch of creeps…
Yumi?
Y’know, about what happened on Lyoko…
I mean, uh, what nearly happened…
Uh, now that you mention it, um…
I’d rather you didn’t talk about it to Odd and Jeremie.
At least, not right away.
Yeah.
I agree, not a word.
C’mon, Ulrich!
Don’t forget, we’ve got
Mrs. Hertz’s classes to go to one more time!
Well, it wasn’t all that boring on Lyoko,
was it Ulrich?
You’re right, Odd, and I learned something too.
Something super important.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS