(SQUEALS)
You’re wrong, I tell you!
JEREMIE: But I didn’t say that Kiwi was stupid.
Oh, no. You said he was brainless.
JEREMIE: Yeah, well if you throw him a stick, he won’t run and fetch it.
Well, neither would you.
ODD: Does that make you brainless?
Franks and beans or ravioli?
TAMIYA: Hey, what’s he doing there?
If Jim sees him,
Odd’s gonna be in big trouble.
TAMIYA: I’ll take him back to his room.
I’ll meet you in the showers.
TAMIYA: Good doggie.
Come on, Kiwi.
KIWI: (GROWLS)
Ow!
MILLY: ♪ (HUMMING)
(SCREECHES)
MILLY: (SCREAMS)
So, you’re not gonna be
finishing your chocolate pudding?
AELITA: Isn’t that your fourth one?
Odd is like a cow.
ULRICH: He has more than one stomach.
The better to pig out with, my dear.
MILLY: Help me!
Tamiya came after me!
MILLY: She looked so strange--
and-and her eyes
were completely white!
MILLY: They were horrible!
She looked like Doctor Shrank!
JEREMIE: Who’s Doctor Shrank?
The psycho TV brain surgeon
in Hospital of Horrors.
AELITA: Smells like XANA, doesn’t it?
I’m launching a super scan.
ROSA: Calm down. It’ll be alright.
You must’ve had a bad dream.
MILLY: No!
I didn’t! It was real!
JEREMIE: Activated tower.
Let’s head for the factory.
ULRICH: I’ll let Yumi know.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
YUMI: Ulrich?
Uh-huh.
YUMI: I understand.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
YUMI: Okay. No problem.
Was that Ulrich?
HIROKI: Your boyfriend?
Hiroki, for the hundred-thousandth time,
YUMI: he is not my boyfriend.
♪ Yumi’s in love! ♪
HIROKI: ♪ Yumi’s in love! ♪
MR. ISHIYAMA: Hiroki, leave your sister alone.
You are such a pain!
YUMI: I’m going to bed.
I think it’s serious.
ROSA: Sissi, go get your father please.
We’ll go with you.
SISSI: Hey, Jim!
There’s a problem with Milly Solovieff.
SISSI: Jim?
W-a-a-a-h!
ULRICH: Sissi, come back!
Meet up at the factory!
ODD: Wha-a-h…
Through there!
ODD: About face, everybody!
Hey, what’s going on?
ODD: Oh, nothing.
We’re surrounded by zombies, mam.
ROSA: Zom--
(GROANS)
SFX: (MOANING)
(GASPS)
SISSI: Help me!
Cool it, maggot-faces.
ULRICH: Come on.
There! You see!
MILLY: I wasn’t dreaming!
I’ll bet they’ll be back with reinforcements.
NICHOLAS: The problem with the living dead
is that you can’t kill them.
Because they’re already dead!
NICHOLAS: (CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
WILLIAM: No, I’m not joking!
Hello?
WILLIAM: Zombies. That’s right. Like in Out of the Tomb.
I hope Ulrich got away alright.
ODD: Don’t worry. He’s probably
at the factory by now.
And we’ve got to join him ASAP.
WILLIAM: Hey, where do you think you’re going?
Uh, outside.
WILLIAM: No way--it’s too dangerous.
That’s our problem, William.
WILLIAM: Sorry.
I’m the oldest one here,
WILLIAM: so I’m the one responsible for the group.
And I’m telling you you’re
staying here and waiting for help.
WILLIAM: I don’t want the zombies to get you,
and what’s more, if they
attack the cafeteria again,
WILLIAM: we’ll need as many of us here as possible.
Anyone who tries to get out
WILLIAM: has got to get past me first, understand?
Oh, great. William thinks he’s Bruce Willis.
ODD: That’s all we needed.
What do I do now?
ULRICH: Can’t get through.
Hey Sissi, listen,
we’ve got to get to a safe spot.
ULRICH: Let’s get back to the lunchroom fast.
And get some help, okay?
SISSI: Okay.
(MOANING)
SFX: (HOWLING)
A supercomputer that lets you
go into a virtual universe
WILLIAM: where you have to battle
an evil enemy called XANA?
Uh, yes.
JEREMIE: When you put it that way,
I admit it sounds a little weird.
If you want to stop this zombie attack,
AELITA: Odd, Jeremie, and I have to
get to the factory right now.
Look, I’m sorry, but I don’t believe you,
so we’re all staying together.
ODD: Okay. Plan B.
I’ll distract him and you take off with Aelita.
ODD: Hey, Jackie Chan,
so you think you’re the boss
around here or something?
WILLIAM: Yes, and I want us all to
get out of this unharmed.
You’ve got to stop watching
those superhero films!
ODD: It’s getting into your head!
Look, they’re getting away!
AELITA: Jeremie!
Hey, you!
WILLIAM: Sorry, but it’s for your own good.
You’ll thank me when you
get out of this safe and sound.
JEREMIE: Safe and sound, yeah. Thanks a lot.
Oh, fantastic. No one.
OFFICER #1: Hello? Anybody here?
Uh, yes?
OFFICER #1: Uh, good evening.
We got a call alerting us
about an attack,
OFFICER #1: uh, by…by…well, anyway,
You haven’t seen anything suspicious
OFFICER #1: going on around here on the campus?
Uh, zombies? Living dead?
MR. ROUILLER: Huh?
No, uh, but I haven’t
been out of my gatehouse.
MR. ROUILLER: As far as I know, everything’s normal.
I told you it was just another
stupid kid’s prank, right?
OFFICER #1: Let’s go. Thank you. Good night.
Hey, Jeremie, it’s me.
ULRICH: Are you at the factory?
Still not there.
JEREMIE: This joker William won’t let us out.
Right. I’ll see what I can do.
MR. ROUILLER: Hey, Jim!
You heard this thing about some zombies?
MR. ROUILLER: It’s completely nutty!
Look!
SFX: (MOANING)
Well, so much for the way out of here.
SFX: (CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yumi?
YUMI: What in the world have you guys been up to?
I’ve been waiting for you at the factory.
ULRICH: Haven’t you heard?
It’s a living dead convention over here.
ULRICH: I’m trying to find a way
to get Aelita to the factory,
but it’s not gonna be easy.
YUMI: Okay. Be careful.
They’re coming from all sides.
ODD: Wait, there’s Kiwi! Look!
He found me!
ODD: See how smart he is?
My little diggity dog!
MILLY: Hey…
That’s the same dog
we saw in the hallway
MILLY: just before Tamiya got zombified.
Wait, Odd!
ODD: Ow!
Kiwi, what’s wrong with you?
ODD: XANA.
William, quick.
JEREMIE: We have to tie him up.
Hurry up!
ODD: (GROANING)
You got a plan?
ULRICH: Yeah.
But I’m not sure you’re gonna like it.
WILLIAM: So, you’re saying that Kiwi
is possessed by this--this XANA?
Right. But now, thanks to you,
JEREMIE: Kiwi’s somewhere ready to bite us.
What’s more, we’re surrounded
by an army of the living dead.
JEREMIE: If you had let us out before,
we wouldn’t be in this mess.
Listen, if you had gone out,
WILLIAM: you might be a zombie
yourself by now, idiot!
I’m getting tired of hearing about
this factory and your supercomputer!
SFX: (MOANING)
Are you ready?
SISSI: Uh-huh.
Kill the zombie-e-e-e-s!
ULRICH: Come on, you dead-heads!
Open up!
SISSI: It’s me—Sissi!
Hey! Open up, I said!
SISSI: I’m not one of them!
She’s lying.
HERB: Prove it.
Um…I, uh…
SISSI: I have a subscription
to Pretty Girl,
and I still sleep with Ninin,
my stuffed moose.
HERB: That has nothing to do with it.
That just proves you’re a lame-o.
SFX: (MOANING)
You open this door, you
bunch of pea-brained dorks!
NICHOLAS: Okay, that’s Sissi alright.
Come on! It’s now or never!
WILLIAM: (GRUNTS)
That one’s on me.
YUMI: Hiyah!
Uh!
YUMI: Hurry up. Let’s get
back to the factory.
Get into the scanners.
JEREMIE: I’ll start the virtualization process.
Okay, ladies.
JEREMIE: We’re ready to roll.
Transfer Yumi.
JEREMIE: Transfer Aelita.
Scanner Yumi.
JEREMIE: Scanner Aelita.
Virtualization.
JEREMIE: And here’s the overwing.
Wow, you’re getting better, Jeremie.
YUMI: Soon, we’ll be landing
right on top of them!
Okay. On your way.
JEREMIE: And watch out for nasty surprises.
What are they doing?
ULRICH: If you ask me,
they’re preparing a final assault.
(CRYING)
SISSI: It’s okay.
Activated tower in sight.
AELITA: Krabs also in sight.
XANA’s played his cards right.
JEREMIE: He wanted to bring you onto Lyoko,
but with the fewest bodyguards possible.
JEREMIE: That’s why Kiwi bit Odd,
but not you or me.
Be careful.
JEREMIE: But now XANA doesn’t
need me anymore.
What do you mean?
JEREMIE: You’ve got to deactivate the tower fast.
If I get zombified, I won’t be able
to launch the return in time,
JEREMIE: And then…I don’t want to talk
about the mess we’ll be in!
Ready, Aelita?
AELITA: Mhmm.
Okay!
YUMI: We’re gonna try to push our way through.
That’s suicide!
JEREMIE: If you don’t make it, Aelita will be
alone with the scyphozoa!
Okay, guys. This is it.
ROSA: Oh, I think I’m…
(GROANS)
AELITA: They’re on our tail.
Ladies, I hope you know what you’re doing.
YUMI: Yeah. So do I, Jeremie.
Aah! Help!
HERB: No!
Take my fan.
YUMI: Hurry!
Now!
AELITA: Hiyah!
(ENGINE STALLING)
YUMI: Miserable kankrelat.
We’ll have to go on foot.
YUMI: Go ahead. I’ll take care of it.
Don’t drag your feet!
YUMI: Oh, no.
Jeremie, the tower has disappeared.
YUMI: Maybe we went the wrong way.
No, the tower is there.
JEREMIE: I can see it on my screen.
You’re right, Jeremie.
AELITA: It’s straight ahead.
How are we gonna get to it?
YUMI: I can tele-transport Aelita.
You’re crazy!
JEREMIE: If you fail, she’ll fall
right into the digital sea!
You have a better idea?
AELITA: I trust her, Jeremie.
Yumi!
JEREMIE: Yumi!
Behind you!
AELITA: Aah!
(SCREAMS)
KIWI: (GROWLING)
Yumi!
AELITA: Aah!
(GROANS)
AELITA: A-a-a-a-h!
It’s one of XANA’s tricks.
JEREMIE: Aelita…
(PANTING)
AELITA: Jeremie, a krab!
Keep going.
JEREMIE: Normally, it wouldn’t dare fire at you.
Yes!
JEREMIE: Hah-ha! Nice job!
Ow!
JEREMIE: Oh, no.
Don’t you touch Milly, you hear!
ULRICH: Odd?!
Jeremie, did you program
the return to the past?
AELITA: Jeremie?
Tower deactivated.
JEREMIE: Aelita!
(MOANS)
JEREMIE: Return to the past now!
You see? I didn’t even get that.
MILLY: Sissi, what do you think
about your father’s decision
to set up a language exchange
program with France?
MILLY: Our readers want to know.
My dear Milly, your paper
doesn’t have any readers.
SISSI: And anyway, I don’t need the whole school
knowing what I think, understand?
SISSI: Coming?
Oh, I hate her.
ULRICH: It’s true that she’s a pain,
but you know, deep down,
I think she really likes you.
AELITA: And I really think that
she can be very brave
and a real nice person
AELITA: when she wants to be.
What?
JEREMIE: Yeah.
In fact, you never can guess
a person’s true colors, can you?
♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
(SINISTER MUSIC)
(GROWLS)
(BELL RINGING)
Hi.
So, how did the Italian test go?
I couldn’t string
two words together.
Sei veramente nullo in
italiano mio caro Jeremie!
Hm?
It means you’re really lame
at Italian, Jeremie, old buddy.
You see? I didn’t even get that.
Sissi, what do you think of your father’s decision
to set up a language exchange program with France?
Our readers want to know.
My dear Milly, your paper
doesn’t have any readers.
And anyway, I don’t need the whole school
knowing what I think, understand?
No danger of that, Sissi.
ODD: You’d need a brain to think!
Good old Odd as unfunny as ever.
Shut up, will you?
Oh, I hate her.
ODD: You’re not the only one.You’re wrong, I tell you!
JEREMIE
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS!