♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Ok pass it
C’mon guys, you haven’t even worked up a sweat
Let’s go, go, go!
Ready!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
(GRUNTS)
Hmmn.
Huh?
(CHEERING)
Ok guys, good warmup session.
Play like that and you’ll whip Lincoln Jr. High
with no problem this afternoon’s final
I’ll see you all at the stadium after lunch for a final briefing
and always remember, a soccer team is like an army,
it needs a good general who can lead it. Right?
(MURMURING AGREEMENT)
Now, break ranks.
(LAUGHTER)
Hey Ulrich
Working out to stay in shape?
Hey listen, kid, I’m gonna be honest with ya,
you’re my key to winning this afternoon’s game.
I know we’ve got a good team
but Lincoln’s got this striker, his name is Matt.
He’s nasty, I know
but don't worry, Jim, I won’t disappoint you.
I’m counting on you, kid.
We’re gonna pulverize em
Massacre em, we’re gonna make mincemeat outta them.
We’re gonna gobble em up and spit em out, maybe.
Hey there, champion, if Lincoln never gets the ball,
we’re gonna be bored out there.
It’s nice of you to come.
We were here this morning and we’ll be here this afternoon
Not for you, of course, we can’t wait to see Sissi
cheerleading with her baton and all.
That’s why we’re coming.
One, two, three, four,
Come on team, give us heart.
Five, six, seven, eight,
Lincoln we’re gonna seal your fate!
Wooohooo
Tada!
Huh?
Oh?
(DING)
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
Huh?
Hm?
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
Yes, it disappeared, I tell you,
it never came down.
It just-just flew away.
Yeah sure, it’s up in the sky somewhere, right?
Or maybe it came down and landed on someone’s head.
Oh, but it’s true, I tell you, I swear,
my baton just disappeared into thin air!
We believe you Sissi.
Even if scientifically it’s impossible.
Listen, if I said that a supernatural thing happened to me,
it’s because it’s true!
You hear me, knucklehead?
A baton that flies up has to come down
and if it doesn’t, there’s something wrong.
Something seriously wrong
and I wanna know exactly what it is.
Huh?
Look, it’s the mysterious baton twirler.
Hey Sissi, eat your steak and french fries fast,
before they fly away.
(LAUGHTER)
Uh oh.
(x2) We’ve gotta talk right now!
Yes Jeremie, I’ve just spotted an
activated tower in the mountain region.
Why? Have you noticed anything strange
going on in your world?
Oh, just the usual things, batons that into the air and don’t come back and Yumi just suddenly airborne.
It was so weird.
The lights all started to blink and a second later,
I was floating in the air, I couldn’t believe it.
A break in the field of gravity causing spontaneous and localized weightlessness.
what’s the connection between electricity and weightlessness?
The magnetic field, it could be the
effect of a very powerful electromagnet--
that Xana’s using to offset the magnetic--
--attraction of the earth. You see?
How dangerous is it?
It’s not. If it’s within the limits of space and time
But if it’s on a larger scale, look what happened to Sissi,
her baton never came back.
We can’t afford to take the risk,
we have to go to Lyoko and deactivate the tower.
Well count me out.
Hm?
Huh? You;ve gotta be kidding.
No, I said count me out. I’ll go when the game’s over.
You’re going to abandon the ship for a soccer game?
I don’t believe it. Wake up, Ulrich, this is about saving the world--
--not to mention Aelita who’s surely in danger
but you would rather kick a-a ball around?
You heard what I said,
I can’t go and that’s that. Okay?
Somebody else say something, will you?
He’s dropping us like a smelly sock.
Look, I’m really sorry.
That’s all you can say? You’re sorry?
You’d rather please the crowd, huh?
All those admiring fans are more important than your friends.
Leave him alone, he’s got his reasons.
His parents are coming to the game this afternoon.
Have you ever met Ulrich’s dad?
If you’re not first in everything,
then you’re nothing in his book.
And since Ulrich’s report cards are kinda disastrous,
the only way to make his dad happy is--
--When he plays soccer.
Yeah exactly.
That’s why he’s been training so hard for weeks now.
He’s gonna play today’s game as if his life depended on it.
Mhm.
Why couldn’t he have just told us the reason?
Ulrich? Give away a secret?
Anyway, why worry?
Ulrich’s going to win the game and in the meantime,
we’re going to save the world.
We’ll just have to do without him this time
and besides, you’ve got me, don’t you?
Alright guys, the big day is here.
Huh?
Yeah!
Testing one, two, testing, one, two.
Here we go.
Hello everyone, this is Milly and Tamiya,
reporting to you live from the stadium.
It’s a big day today, the ninth grade
inter-school final is about to begin.
Although our school is favored to win,
a lot is going to depend on kadic striker, our own Ulrich.
We’re really counting on him today
and now, everybody, it’s soccer time!
(CHAIR WHIRRING)
(VARIOUS MACHINES BEEPING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Come on
Aelita, do you read me?
Aelita.
I’m here Jeremie
Aelita, it’s Xana, he’s attacking,
he’s trying to take over the city’s electrical network.
But why?
I don’t know but I’m gonna try to find out.
I’ll get the spy program started.
With the dataflow so dense,
there ought to be traces of it on the network.
Bingo! That’s Xana alright.
Heavy and predictable.
(CHEERING)
Incredible,
we knew that Ulrich was in great form
but what’ he’s showing us today--
--is beyond even our wildest dreams.
MATT: Hey!
Yaaah!
A fantastic goal and the Kadic team makes it one to nothing
after only three minutes of play.
Lincoln’s going to find a way to stop Ulrich
if they’re going to win this game.
Heavy but very fast.
We don’t have much time. Ready to go?
No problemo.
We’ve gotta hurry up because if we don’t,
Xana will be able to create much more powerful magnetic fields.
Transfer, Yumi.
Transfer, Odd.
Scanner, Yumi.
Scanner, Odd.
Virtualization!
The tower is situated at 30 degrees west.
Hurry up, huh?
I see it, Jeremie.
Over here!
Kadic! Kadic! Kadic!
There’s no stopping Ulrich!
He’s amazing to watch!
It’s two-nothing and the score may
get out of hand if Ulrich keeps this up.
He looks so handsome  when he runs.
Well thanks, Tamiya,
for that expert commentary on the game!
Oh no! He’s ready to attack the school.
Now I understand.
Fill us in, Einstein.
If not for what happened today,
with Yumi and Sissi, we’d have all gone to the game
and that’s where Xana wanted to
trap us because it was his plan.
To concentrate all of the energy on the science lab
and if we don’t make it fast
there’s a good chance Ulrich’s gonna finish the game
outside of the stratosphere!
No monsters for the time being
but we’re still far from the tower.
Oh, this is awful.
I gotta find a way to gain some time.
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
You asked for it Xana, I can hack a network,
you’re not the only one.
Go on, now! Stop Matt!
He’s getting away!
Fantastic, Ulrich’s as good on defense
as he is on the attack.
Go, Ulrich, go, go!
This program will help me counter--
--any of Xana’s attacks on the science lab.
Ulrich, do you copy?
That’s the end of the first half.
Kadic has a commanding two-nothing lead.
Let’s see if we can get some comments first-hand.
Ulrich? I imagine you’re confident after--
--dominating Lincoln for the past 45 minutes.
What do you think?
Uh, Lincoln’s in the finals,
that means they’re a good team.
In the words of our coach, Jim,
It’s our motivation that’ll make us winners.
And I honestly think that--
--Ah, I’ve gotta go not, talk to you after the game.
I better relax a bit before the second half.
And see what Jim has to-- Uh--
(PHONE RINGING)
Answer your phone, Ulrich, please!
What do you want?
Ulrich, I’ve been trying to reach--
--you for a quarter of an hour.
I can’t play with a cellphone in my hand.
Sorry.
Listen, I know about- well,
Odd told me why this match is so important to you
but there’s an enormous and serious problem.
I can’t go into all the details, there’s not enough time
but Xana’s gonna put the school into orbit.
What was that?
It’s true, I swear, he doesn’t have enough power yet--
--But--
--But he’s gonna try and get it from the science lab’s generator.
You’ve gotta make sure that nobody is in the building.
Hey, Ulrich!
Second half’s starting.
Be right there!
No problem. Everyone’s at the game.
Are you absolutely sure?
(CHEERING)
Oh, Mrs. Hertz isn’t here.
Oh no, she’s probably in the chemistry lab.
You’ve gotta go and get her out.
(LIQUID POURING)
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Ulrich!
Don’t ask me to do that.
Jeremie, anything but not that!
Oh! What’s wrong?
What’s wrong?
Look, I’m sorry, Ulrich,
you've got to leave the game.
You’re the only one who can do it.
You’ve gotta save her.
Oh, everyone is just numb, the crowd,
including yours truly, simply doesn’t understand.
It must be the pressure.
(CONFUSED MURMURING)
Oh!
MRS. STERN: Oh.
Hmmn.
It’s a matter of life and death, Ulrich.
Oh, it’s unbelievable,
the Lincoln team have just cut our lead in half.
Matt, himself, can hardly believe
that Ulrich let him score.
Ulrich! What are--
--Please, shut up, Jeremie, just shut up.
I’m gonna stop you!
We’ll see about that!
Ahhgh!
Oh no, it can’t be!
What awful luck for the kadic team.
Ulrich looks hurt after that violent tackle by Matt!
Oh come on,
I didn't even touch him.
Yes, it’s true!
(AGONIZING GRUNTING)
Ulrich! Oh no! I don’t believe it.
You- you can’t do this!
Leave me alone, Jim.
Oh, wow, absolutely incredible!
Our superstar striker is leaving the field with a knee injury.
Our one irreplaceable player is out of the game!
I don’t believe it for a minute
and I’m gonna check this out.
I’m leaving as well.
Tell me everything that happened while I’m gone.
Sissi, you’re our cheerleader!
There’s not gonna be a lot of cheering without Ulrich
and if we do score a goal you can replace me.
The crowd will love it.
Just dance your head off.
Jeremie, objective in sight,
the welcoming committee looks manageable.
I’ll take care of them in no time at all.
Ok, I should be able to neutralize--
--Xana but only for a few minutes.
So you’ve gotta work fast.
We’ve gotta move.
Ten seconds to attack time.
Ok, Yumi, go!
(LASER SHOTS)
Ahh!
Pretty sharp mosquitos,
since when do they grow brains?
But there’s only one left.
Negative, a new swarm of hornets is on the way.
Ok, change of tactics, this time we’ll try diversion.
Odd, I’ve reloaded 20 arrows for you
but that may not be enough!
Laser arrow!
Ahh!
Your turn, Yumi.
Laser arrow!
They just keep coming,
there’s no end to them.
Jeremie?
I just left the stadium.
Oh, thanks Ulrich.
What you’re doing is--
Yeah I know,
I’m on my way to the chemistry lab.
What do we do now?
The best defense is an offense, right?
Right but it depends on the number of enemies.
It’s ok, Ulrich, I made my own--
--electric field to create a short circuit.
But Xana’s bound to get ahead of me again soon,
so be very careful.
I don’t know how long it’s gonna last.
I just walked in,
there’s nothing at all happening.
Uh?
Huh?
Whoa!
Looks like I spoke too soon.
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
Whoa!
You have to hang on for just a few seconds.
As soon as you've secured Ms. Hertz, I can move into action.
You’ve gotta hang on now so Aelita can get through.
Yumi, Odd, are you ok?
Yeah, yeah, we’re cool.
(LASER SHOTS)
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
Ahhh!
Jeremie, it’s ok, I’ve got Ms. Hertz!
Go on, do your stuff.
Here we go.
The reverse circuit is working.
Ulrich?
Um, sorry to be so familiar with you Ms. Hertz.
Yoohoo, Ulrich?
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
Jeremie, what’s happening?
I don’t know, everything is becoming--
--impossible to control. Be careful!
(SCREAMING)
Ulrich, where are you?
I’ve gotcha!
Ulrich, what’s happening? What’s going on?
It’s too complicated.
Jeremie, where are you at now?
Ok, I’m back in control.
ULRICH: Ready!
It’s gonna rock!
(ELECTRIC LIGHT PULSING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Hey do me a favor, ok Jeremie,
tell me it’s going to calm down.
Not for the time being, it may get worse,
so hang on tight any way you can.
Odd, Yumi, what’s happening?
It’s horrible, I’m almost out of arrows,
telekinesis has exhausted Yumi
and the more hornets I kill,
the more there are.
Here I go.
Ulrich, do you mind telling me exactly what’s going on?
Yeah, I do mind, so keep quiet.
Huh?
Oh hey, Jeremie, what’s that sound?
I, um, I don’t know.
(RAPID BEEPING)
Oh no!
Xana has managed to take over 50 power stations!
Ulrich, whatever you do, don’t leave the building.
You understand? Stay inside.
(LASER SHOTS)
Hang in there, Yumi, we’re almost there.
No, not now, concentrarte.
Give us just a few more seconds.
(GASPING)
I can’t do it, Odd. I’m sorry.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Aelita! It’s too soon!
Well, Matt has a chance to tie the score with his penalty shot.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(SCREAMING)
The stadium!
Ahh!
(SCREAMING)
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Hey, Aelita, you’re crazy!
Ulrich, what are you doing?
Oh, no, no, no!
I don’t believe this!
(SCREAMING)
Noooo!
Aelita!
As soon as you’re finished crying,
just let me know.
Aelita, oh no!
Oh, you were just luring them.
Ofcourse.
Aelita, you are the greatest!
Ulrich?
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Goodbye, Ulrich.
I’m proud of you, really I am.
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
No!
Nooo!
(SCREAMING)
Return to the past now!
It’s a big day today, the ninth grade
inter-school final is about to begin.
Although our school is favored to win,
a lot is going to depend on kadic striker, our own Ulrich.
We’re really counting on him today
Let’s rock, Ulrich! Come on, world champion!
Yeah but which world?
Why both of them, Jeremie, both of them!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)CLOSED CAPTION
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS