♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
I'm sure it's gonna work this time!
Time for plan Alpha.
(RINGTONE)
Yumi? Yumi, it's me.
Okay, I just launched plan Alpha.
My five dry runs have all worked.
Okay, tomorrow I'll talk to my parents.
That's great! I'll tell Odd and Ulrich.
See you tomorrow.
(HUMMING)
Jeremie?
Can you hear me Jeremie?
Jeremie, wake up!
Jeremie…
Aelita!
Uh, Mom and Dad, can I talk to you for a second?
It's about my penpal, uh...
You haven't changed your mind about her living here for a while?
No, but tell us a little bit about her Yumi.
Where, we don't even know her name.
Aelita.
Aelita what?
It's Aelita...
Lyoko!
Is she Japanese?
Well, yes, she is.
What do her parents do, dear?
They uh, they work with computers.
Well, alright then.
She's welcome to stay with us.
That's fantastic!
I adore you!
You won't regret it, she's really so nice!
Bye now, see you tonight!
(CHUCKLING)
Very well then, what is your cousin's name Odd?
Aelita.
Hm, Aelita. And where does she come from?
She's from... Holland.
Hm…
Well, her papers are in order,
and your parents have recommended her highly,
so I see no reason why she can't attend school here.
Let me know when she arrives.
Yes!
Great!
Fantastic!
Okay, what are you two up to, huh?
You know this building is off-limits to students,
‘specially at eight in the morning.
We had an appointment with the Principal, Jim,
about Odd's cousin attending school.
Oh what a lame excuse!
What do you think I am, huh? An idiot?
Well...
Quiet!
Yeah, and I'll bet you think I'm not
on to your pranks with Jeremie and Yumi!
You disappear in the park like
some sort of magic, you plot in your rooms.
Hey, it's not a crime.
Maybe not. Now you listen up.
One of these days I'm gonna find out
what the four of you are hiding.
And now, to the cafeteria. Hurry up!
Hm
You know what I think? We’d better be careful about Jim,
if he keeps playing detective, he’s gonna find our secret passage.
Hey!
Hey, guys!
Great news, my parents said okay.
So did the principal!
Odd, that was a pretty good letter you faked from your parents.
I can’t say I’m proud of what I did, but it was for a good cause.
(RINGTONE)
Ooh, Jeremie, what’s up?
Okay, be right there.
That’s it, we’ve got it this time!
It works! It works!
I can hardly believe it.
(CHEERING)
It’s fantastic, you can find any kind of music you want!
I can’t wait for vacation, wow!
You’re not the only one.
Hm
Hey, Sissi, have you seen Ulrich and his gang this morning?
Well, yeah.
Where, in the cafeteria?
No, I saw them going to their rooms, Jim.
Yeah? Thanks for the tip.
It is pretty strange to go to their rooms at this hour.
I said to myself, now why would they be in their rooms now
with someone who isn’t even a boarder?
You mean Yumi Ishiyama is with them?
Mh hm.
You’re meaner than I thought.
Okay, tell me what the good news is.
Aelita, I don’t know how to tell you this,
but believe it or not, we’re waiting for you here.
Really?
Really!
The materialization’s gonna work?
Yep, it’s all in here.
And I can tell you it was really complicated,
defragmenting the inertial matrix wasn’t enough,
and so I had to start to recompile all of the DNA correlations and-
Time out Einstein.
(YAWNING)
To make a long story short, it works.
Oh Jeremie, that’s so great!
I can’t believe it’s true!
Better get used to it fast,
because it’s time to take the big jump.
And then it’s bye-bye XANA!
Hold on…
It’s not that simple. First I’ve got to
set up the program in the supercalculator.
Then Aelita will have to get to the passage tower
in Lyoko’s forest region.
That’s where she’s gonna get devirtualized,
before she appears in the flesh
for the first time inside one of the scanners.
In that case, I’m off to the forest right now.
Okay, and we’ll go to class in the meantime.
And afterwards, the factory.
I’ll see you later my friends.
We’ll be five for dinner tonight.
What’s wrong? Up to no good again, aren’t you?
No, we were just studying together.
My foot! I’ve had enough of your lies, you hear?
We’re gonna stay right here
until you guys tell me the truth.
Jim?
What is going on here?
I’m glad you’re here, sir.
I don’t know what’s going on, but...
but these little devils are up to good
and I intend to find out what it is.
Yes Jim, another one of your absurd stories
about secret plots and passages.
What do you mean, absurd?
You heard what I said, absurd, Jim.
(STAMMERING) But…
Now listen, your paranoid behavior and your one track mind
concerning these children are getting on my nerves.
You’re a physical education teacher, not a detective, Jim.
Um…
(FUMING)
What are you waiting for?
You have class now, so get going!
There it is!
Animals live in all land, air, and sea regions,
thanks to their varied respiratory organs.
It won’t be long now.
And so in Italian, the noun “città”,
which of course means “city”, is invariable.
Who can give me another example?
Jeremie, I’m gonna need help.
When animals and humans breathe,
they take in oxygen and emit carbon dioxide.
(BEEPING)
What are you doing?
It’s Aelita, she’s in danger.
Obviously this phenomenon depends on certain factors.
Who can tell us which ones? Jeremie?
Go ahead, we’re listening.
Uh...
The the... The frogs!
(LAUGHING)
(BELL RINGING)
About time that Jeremie gets a wrong answer.
Excuse me, sorry, excuse me.
Well, who would like to answer?
(BUZZING)
Anybody?
Yumi?
Yes, Ulrich?
What’s new?
Yumi, come to the park, it’s urgent.
Okay, be right there.
Sir, can I please go to the infirmary?
Mh-hm…
Mind telling me what’s going on?
XANA’s at it again!
He knows the end is near,
and he’s not going down without a fight.
(PANTING)
Oh?
Hm…
Where’d they go?
Yeah!
Aelita, can you hear me?
It took you such a long time. I’m at the passage tower,
but three Bloks won’t even let me get close.
Okay, I’ve got you localized, don’t worry.
Help is on the way.
Better hurry up.
Once the coast is clear, go to the center of the tower
and I’ll launch the program.
I’m transferring you to the forest region,
a little south of where Aelita is now.
Here we go!
I’m counting on you.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner, Ulrich.
Scanner Yumi.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Okay, Jeremie, we’re here!
That’s great.
Get ready guys,
I’m launching the materialization program immediately.
Break, break dance! Break, break, break dance!
Break, break, break dance, here we go!
Break, break, break dance! Break, break, break dance!
Break, break, break dance...
Oh no, what have I done?
Problem Jeremie?
I inserted the wrong CD!
One of Odd’s dumb videos instead of the program.
(SINGING CONTINUES)
Stop!
I’ve gotta go back to the dorm.
Okay, but hurry!
(SIGHING)
You made a video?
Well yeah, it’s pretty good, too!
What’s the title?
Break, break, break dance.
Okay, that’s enough fooling around.
We’ve got some cleaning up to do.
Sir, yes sir!
Okay, let’s get started.
This time, I’ve got him.
Go!
This is too easy.
Aelita, the passage is clear, you can go.
Wow, just think, this could be the last tower.
Playing hooky, huh?
Uh, no.
I uh, left something in my room, I…
Uh huh…
(STAMMERING) I gotta go back to class now, Jim.
Not ‘til you tell me what you’ve been plotting
since the beginning of the year.
And this time, the principal’s not here
to come to your rescue.
Oh you miserable little brat!
Get back here!
Ooh, wait ‘til I get my hands on you!
Jeremie, stop! That’s an order!
Hey!
Jeremie…
Oh no.
Oh, my ankle!
What are you, crazy, Jim?
Hey, this is your fault!
My ankle…
Jeremie, can you hear us?
Jeremie…
We’re in the tower.
Jeremie?
Where can he be?
Forty-five minutes is a long time to go pick up a CD.
I sure hope nothing happened to him.
Come on, stop being so gloom and doom.
Don’t panic. I’m sure everything’s cool.
And now, does it still hurt?
No, it’s okay now, I can- I can walk fine Dorothy.
If there’s one thing you’d
better not do yet it’s walk.
You’ll have to wait a week
before putting that foot on the ground.
A week?
And if you complain,
I won’t give you crutches to get around with.
Jim.
This time, you’ve gone too far.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
This time, your paranoia has caused an accident.
I’m sorry sir, I really am.
So am I Jim.
I’m going to have to let you go.
(ECHOING) Let you go
What was that?
Can I go to the bathroom?
Sorry, the doctor insists you stay off your feet.
I’ll go and get you a basin.
Jeremie, listen, I…
I wanted to say I’m sorry.
I was so sure that you guys were up to something...
that I guess I got carried away a little.
I deserved to get fired.
I went a little crazy ‘cause I thought you and your friends
had a lot of secrets that you were hiding.
Anyway.
I’m gonna miss you guys.
Hold on a second, Jim.
You’re um... not as crazy as you think.
My friends and I, we do have a secret.
But that means I was right after all!
Well let’s hear it.
Look, Jim, if you help me,
I’ll tell the principal everything.
You’ll be off the hook, and he’s bound
to give you your job back, right?
Great! Shake on it.
Go!
I’ve got your basin. Oh!
Over there!
Behind the oak tree.
Stop!
In front of you.
Oh.
(LAUGHING) Yeah.
I was right, I was right!
Take that!
Oh no!
And this super powerful virtual thing
called XANA wants to destroy us.
Only Aelita can deactivate the towers.
And our job is to help her as much as we can.
And she’s on this place called, uh, Loco?
No, it’s Lyoko.
The only way to destroy XANA is to unplug him.
But first, we have to materialize Aelita.
And that’s what we’re gonna do today.
Here we are.
Whoa.
Huh.
Well what do you know.
Who’d have believed it?
Aelita, is everything okay?
Jeremie, at last! What happened to you?
It’s a long story. Too long. But I’ve got the program.
Now let’s cross our fingers and hope it works okay.
I’m launching it.
Follow me, Odd.
Oh no.
Take that!
Okay, Ulrich, it’s up to you.
Hey, you piece of junk!
Nobody messes with my friends!
Triangulate!
Go on Ulrich, get him!
Show this XANA thing who’s the boss!
Jeremie, Ulrich is…
Jim?
Yes, Jim. Don’t worry, he’s one of the gang now.
Impact!
Ulrich, watch out behind you!
Huh?
You’ve got to protect the tower.
The tower’s not gonna hold much longer.
Leave it to Ulrich.
Hold on Ulrich, just a few more seconds.
I’m almost ready Aelita.
Get into position on the platform.
Okay.
Well, ready to take the big jump?
Ready.
Then here we go.
Code Earth.
She’s here at last!
Welcome to Earth.
(CHEERING)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS