Just a few more missions
like that on sector five,
and I’ll have all the elements
I need for Aelita’s antivirus.
See you tomorrow, Yumi.
Yeah, I’ll see you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, uh, later.
Well, what?
Hello! Anyone home?
What are you waiting for, anyway?
You know they’re right, Ulrich.
You really ought to go for it.
Like now?
No, wait ‘til she starts
going out with another guy
because she’s sick of waiting
for you to make a move, right?
Hmph.
A-And what if Jim
notices that I’m missing?
We’ll cover for you.
Yeah!
William?
What are you doing here?
Are you crazy?
Yes. I told you I was.
I go totally crazy when I like a girl.
Ah--no, wait!
Sorry, I-I’m
a little confused.
It’s Ulrich, isn’t it?
Goodnight.
So, then I told her I was gonna order
a T-shirt on the internet.
And she asked if it was
gonna come out of the printer!
(LAUGHS)
Here’s our hero.
Hey, champ. How’d it go?
Well, then.
I think I’m gonna
go to bed. I’m tired.
Yeah, me too.
Well, what happened, huh?
Leave me alone.
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Some of you are
already riding scooters,
and at this stage I don’t think it would
be a waste of your time
to go over the rules of the road.
This training day
will familiarize you
with the correct way
to drive a vehicle.
Assistant warrant officer
Garaig, here,
has agreed to take you
under his responsibility today
as part of the exchange program
between the police force
and the board of education.
Our physical education teacher, Jim,
will assist you as well.
Corporal Jim Morales!
Seventh engineering battalion!
Serial number nine-two-twelve-one!
At ease…you were in the army?
Uh, I’d rather not
talk about it, captain.
I’m only a warrant officer.
Oh, excuse me, lieutenant.
Yes, well, um, I’ll turn
operations over to you,
uh, Jim.
Can I count on you?
Affirmative, Mister Delmas!
Driving any vehicle
is serious business.
Caution, concentration and safety…
Hey! Hey,
Ulrich, what’s wrong?
Are you sulking or what?
(SCOFFS)
What is it with him?
Last night when we said goodbye,
he was in a great mood.
Yeah, but what about after?
What happened after he
followed you back to your place?
He followed me?
(GROANS)
Oh, no.
Now, I’m gonna
call you one by one
to take a drive
around the circuit.
The rest of you can
go back to your seats.
Delmas, Elizabeth.
I prefer Sissi to Elizabeth.
What about you?
Do you have a nickname?
(LAUGHTER)
Work it, Sissi!
Della Robbia, Odd.
Yea-a-a-a-a-h!
Ishiyama, Yumi.
(GRUNTS)
Pichon, Herb.
Wh-whoa!
Stones, Aelita.
Let’s go.
Aah!
Hey, you’re not
any better than I am.
What a morale booster!
Hey, will you just shut up?
Hey, it’s not Odd’s fault
if you drive like a dork.
Stern and Dunbar!
Where do you think you are?
Get up!
Straight to the principal’s office!
Your behavior is unspeakable!
Violence is no way to
sort out your differences!
Next time, I’ll suspend you both!
Understood?
Jim, take them to the library.
Yes, general!
Uh, I mean,
right away, Mister Delmas.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Don’t worry, Aelita.
It’ll work out.
They’re not the first guys
who have ever fought over a girl.
How about you?
Would you fight over me, Jeremie?
I fight for you every day, Aelita.
Against XANA.
Oh, that's so beautiful!
Huh?
Speak of the devil.
I’ve got an activated tower here.
Let’s head for the factory.
The sooner we deactivate it, the better.
What about Ulrich?
We’ll manage without him.
You’re home early, dear.
The meeting with (INDISTINCT) was moved up.
How’s you dictionary coming along?
Well, my editor called and--
(CRASHING)
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Who could that be?
Aah!
There! Look out!
Well, now we know what
XANA has in store for us.
Hello, Hiroki?
Yumi, there’s a big monster outside the house!
No, I swear!
And the monster looks like
the one in Ultimate Blaster!
Daddy’s outside.
I’m coming.
XANA has virtualized another krab.
It’s at my house.
My parents are in danger.
Go help them.
Odd and I will manage on Lyoko.
Take care of yourselves.
You too.
We’re gonna need some backup.
Uh, that might be important.
Ah! There we go.
But--
What?
You think I confiscated your
telephone so I could use it?
(LAUGHS)
I got his voicemail.
What bad luck.
We’ll have to do without Ulrich.
Right. I’ve got a plan.
Okay, this is the gallery,
which I’m going to call “G.”
This is where we are.
This is the elevator landing,
which I’m going to call “E.”
We’ve go to get to point E
without being spotted
by the krab, “K.”
You get it?
No, but I’ve got another plan.
What is it?
Bansai!
Odd!
What are you waiting for?
An invitation?
Get into the elevator!
I’m coming!
Hurry up!
Get to the scanner room.
I’ll start up the virtualization process.
You can’t come through here.
There’s a dangerous animal on the loose.
But I live right there.
I have to get to my parents.
Sorry, Miss. We have our orders.
You okay?
Are you there, Odd?
Uh, yeah, but uh…
we've got a little problem here.
Our friend Mister Krab
has busted all the scanners.
Not all of them.
This one still works.
Okay.
I'm gonna virtualize Aelita first.
The activated tower is
in the mountain sector.
35 degrees north.
Scanner Aelita.
Transfer Aelita.
Virtualization.
I've programmed the overboard.
Your turn, Odd.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Jeremie, we’ve got another problem.
What kind?
Well, it’s a big banquet.
XANA has sent us
an entire seafood platter!
(SCREAMING, LASER FIRE)
What’s all that ruckus?
(SCREAMING)
You two stay put if you
know what’s good for you.
Huh?
What is that thing?
Krab.
Hm?
(CRASHING)
What was that?
The very last scanner getting
destroyed by a krab.
Aelita is on her own now.
Okay, then.
There’s no time to lose.
You’ve got to believe me!
I’m the one that
the creature is after!
I already told you, miss.
Orders are orders.
Calling all cars.
The animal has just been spotted
in the vicinity of Kadic Academy.
I repeat, the vicinity of Kadic Academy.
Whoa…
Whoa!
The activated tower is
15 degrees more to the west.
Be very careful.
Don’t worry, Jeremie.
I learn fast.
You’d better.
Jeremie?
Ah, Ulrich!
Not a moment too soon.
What’s going on?
XANA has materialized three krabs.
One of them is at Yumi’s
and Odd’s playing upstairs with the second
so that it won’t do
any more damage outside.
A third one is here
at the academy.
I’ll deal with it.
With William.
(SCREAMING)
Geronimo!
(GROANS)
Jim!
Looking for me?
Come on! Over here!
Anybody home?
Daddy?
Mom?
Hiroki?
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Ulrich, I’m at the groundkeeper’s shed.
Ulrich!
Hiya-a-a-h!
(GROANS)
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
You’re lucky. I wasn’t gonna save you.
Hey, what are you, crazy?
What’s the matter with you?
Stay away from our group!
You got that?
Listen, man, you’re the
one who doesn’t get it.
In the race for Yumi, I’m not in first place.
Or didn’t you know?
Wha-hah!
Aah!
Wha-oh-ah!
Daddy?
(CHUCKLES)
These krabs are just as bad as on Lyoko.
Aelita!
Behind you!
Squadron of four hornets coming in!
They’ll do everything
they can to slow you down.
That’s for sure.
They’ll want to give the krabs time
to take care of Yumi and the others.
Ulrich.
Jeremie, we took out one of the krabs.
Finally some good news.
Aelita’s doing everything she can
to get to the tower and deactivate it,
but nothing had better happen
to Yumi and Odd in the meantime.
I’ll take care of it.
We’ll take care of it.
(GASPS)
Aah!
Well done, Aelita!
Odd would be proud of you.
They’re catching up with you!
I’ve got an idea.
It isn’t dangerous, is it?
Uh, no.
Odd showed it to me!
Is that supposed to
make me feel better?
Let’s go.
(SCREAMS)
Yumi!
Yah!
H-i-i-i-yah!
Ha!
Yagh!
(GROANS)
You’re about to arrive
at a hollow mountain.
Jeremie, could you
dematerialize the overboard
when I give you the signal?
Yeah, sure, but why?
Oh, no!
Ulrich!
Make my day, shrimp.
(GRUNTS)
Wow! Too cool!
(ECHOS)
Now!
Thanks, Jeremie.
Nice job.
I’m sending you the overwing.
What do we do now?
Well, I’ve got a slightly crazy idea.
The activated tower
is not much further.
Dead north!
Aelita?
Aah!
William, go!
Now!
(CRASHING)
Good job, man.
How many times have I told you
this is the guy you
should go out with!
(GRUNTS)
Ulrich, you’re the greatest!
Hiroki!
Hiroki, no!
Aah!
Ulrich!
(GASPS)
Aelita, get out of there!
Aelita!
Huh?
A decoy!
(SCREECHES)
I hope it’s not too late.
Oh, they did it!
You were great, William.
But you won’t remember any of it.
Hm?
Hey…
Tower deactivated.
Return to the past now.
Hey, you really do know
what you’re doing, Ulrich.
Thanks!
You want to come with me to my go-kart club?
We’d have a great time together.
Sure! Why not?
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS!