(SINISTER MUSIC)
(GROWLS)
(SQUEALS)
Hi.
So, how did the Italian test go?
I couldn’t string
two words together.
Sei veramente nullo in
italiano mio caro Jeremie!
Hm?
It means you’re really lame
at Italian, Jeremie, old buddy.
You see? I didn’t even get that.
Sissi, what do you think
of your father’s decision
to set up a language exchange
program with France?
Our readers want to know.
My dear Milly, your paper
doesn’t have any readers.
And anyway, I don’t need the whole school
knowing what I think, understand?
No danger of that, Sissi.
You’d need a brain to think!
Good old Odd as unfunny as ever.
Shut up, will you?
Oh, I hate her.
You’re not the only one.
You’re wrong, I tell you!
But I didn’t say that Kiwi was stupid.
Oh, no. You said he was brainless.
Yeah, well if you throw him a stick, he won’t run and fetch it.
Well, neither would you.
Does that make you brainless?
Franks and beans or ravioli?
Hey, what’s he doing there?
If Jim sees him,
Odd’s gonna be in big trouble.
I’ll take him back to his room.
I’ll meet you in the showers.
Good doggie.
Come on, Kiwi.
(GROWLS)
Ow!
♪ (HUMMING)
(SCREECHES)
(SCREAMS)
So, you’re not gonna be
finishing your chocolate pudding?
Isn’t that your fourth one?
Odd is like a cow.
He has more than one stomach.
The better to pig out with, my dear.
Help me!
Tamiya came after me!
She looked so strange--
and-and her eyes
were completely white!
They were horrible!
She looked like Doctor Shrank!
Who’s Doctor Shrank?
The psycho TV brain surgeon
in Hospital of Horrors.
Smells like XANA, doesn’t it?
I’m launching a super scan.
Calm down. It’ll be alright.
You must’ve had a bad dream.
No!
I didn’t! It was real!
Activated tower.
Let’s head for the factory.
I’ll let Yumi know.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Ulrich?
Uh-huh.
I understand.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Okay. No problem.
Was that Ulrich?
Your boyfriend?
Hiroki, for the hundred-thousandth time,
he is not my boyfriend.
♪ Yumi’s in love! ♪
Hiroki, leave your sister alone.
You are such a pain!
I’m going to bed.
I think it’s serious.
Sissi, go get your father please.
We’ll go with you.
Hey, Jim!
There’s a problem with Milly Solovieff.
Jim?
W-a-a-a-h!
Sissi, come back!
Meet up at the factory!
Wha-a-h…
Through there!
About face, everybody!
Hey, what’s going on?
Oh, nothing.
We’re surrounded by zombies, mam.
Zom--
(GROANS)
(MOANING)
(GASPS)
Help me!
Cool it, maggot-faces.
Come on.
There! You see!
I wasn’t dreaming!
I’ll bet they’ll be back with reinforcements.
The problem with the living dead
is that you can’t kill them.
Because they’re already dead!
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
No, I’m not joking!
Hello?
Zombies. That’s right. Like in Out of the Tomb.
I hope Ulrich got away alright.
Don’t worry. He’s probably
at the factory by now.
And we’ve got to join him ASAP.
Hey, where do you think you’re going?
Uh, outside.
No way--it’s too dangerous.
That’s our problem, William.
Sorry.
I’m the oldest one here,
so I’m the one responsible for the group.
And I’m telling you you’re
staying here and waiting for help.
I don’t want the zombies to get you,
and what’s more, if they
attack the cafeteria again,
we’ll need as many of us here as possible.
Anyone who tries to get out
has got to get past me first, understand?
Oh, great. William thinks he’s Bruce Willis.
That’s all we needed.
What do I do now?
Can’t get through.
Hey Sissi, listen,
we’ve got to get to a safe spot.
Let’s get back to the lunchroom fast.
And get some help, okay?
Okay.
(MOANING)
(HOWLING)
A supercomputer that lets you
go into a virtual universe
where you have to battle
an evil enemy called XANA?
Uh, yes.
When you put it that way,
I admit it sounds a little weird.
If you want to stop this zombie attack,
Odd, Jeremie, and I have to
get to the factory right now.
Look, I’m sorry, but I don’t believe you,
so we’re all staying together.
Okay. Plan B.
I’ll distract him and you take off with Aelita.
Hey, Jackie Chan,
so you think you’re the boss
around here or something?
Yes, and I want us all to
get out of this unharmed.
You’ve got to stop watching
those superhero films!
It’s getting into your head!
Look, they’re getting away!
Jeremie!
Hey, you!
Sorry, but it’s for your own good.
You’ll thank me when you
get out of this safe and sound.
Safe and sound, yeah. Thanks a lot.
Oh, fantastic. No one.
Hello? Anybody here?
Uh, yes?
Uh, good evening.
We got a call alerting us
about an attack,
uh, by…by…well, anyway,
You haven’t seen anything suspicious
going on around here on the campus?
Uh, zombies? Living dead?
Huh?
No, uh, but I haven’t
been out of my gatehouse.
As far as I know, everything’s normal.
I told you it was just another
stupid kid’s prank, right?
Let’s go. Thank you. Good night.
Hey, Jeremie, it’s me.
Are you at the factory?
Still not there.
This joker William won’t let us out.
Right. I’ll see what I can do.
Hey, Jim!
You heard this thing about some zombies?
It’s completely nutty!
Look!
(MOANING)
Well, so much for the way out of here.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yumi?
What in the world have you guys been up to?
I’ve been waiting for you at the factory.
Haven’t you heard?
It’s a living dead convention over here.
I’m trying to find a way
to get Aelita to the factory,
but it’s not gonna be easy.
Okay. Be careful.
They’re coming from all sides.
Wait, there’s Kiwi! Look!
He found me!
See how smart he is?
My little diggity dog!
Hey…
That’s the same dog
we saw in the hallway
just before Tamiya got zombified.
Wait, Odd!
Ow!
Kiwi, what’s wrong with you?
XANA.
William, quick.
We have to tie him up.
Hurry up!
(GROANING)
You got a plan?
Yeah.
But I’m not sure you’re gonna like it.
So, you’re saying that Kiwi
is possessed by this--this XANA?
Right. But now, thanks to you,
Kiwi’s somewhere ready to bite us.
What’s more, we’re surrounded
by an army of the living dead.
If you had let us out before,
we wouldn’t be in this mess.
Listen, if you had gone out,
you might be a zombie
yourself by now, idiot!
I’m getting tired of hearing about
this factory and your supercomputer!
(MOANING)
Are you ready?
Uh-huh.
Kill the zombie-e-e-e-s!
Come on, you dead-heads!
Open up!
It’s me—Sissi!
Hey! Open up, I said!
I’m not one of them!
She’s lying.
Prove it.
Um…I, uh…
I have a subscription
to Pretty Girl,
and I still sleep with Ninin,
my stuffed moose.
That has nothing to do with it.
That just proves you’re a lame-o.
(MOANING)
You open this door, you
bunch of pea-brained dorks!
Okay, that’s Sissi alright.
Come on! It’s now or never!
(GRUNTS)
That one’s on me.
Hiyah!
Uh!
Hurry up. Let’s get
back to the factory.
Get into the scanners.
I’ll start the virtualization process.
Okay, ladies.
We’re ready to roll.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Aelita.
Scanner Yumi.
Scanner Aelita.
Virtualization.
And here’s the overwing.
Wow, you’re getting better, Jeremie.
Soon, we’ll be landing
right on top of them!
Okay. On your way.
And watch out for nasty surprises.
What are they doing?
If you ask me,
they’re preparing a final assault.
(CRYING)
It’s okay.
Activated tower in sight.
Krabs also in sight.
XANA’s played his cards right.
He wanted to bring you onto Lyoko,
but with the fewest bodyguards possible.
That’s why Kiwi bit Odd,
but not you or me.
Be careful.
But now XANA doesn’t
need me anymore.
What do you mean?
You’ve got to deactivate the tower fast.
If I get zombified, I won’t be able
to launch the return in time,
And then…I don’t want to talk
about the mess we’ll be in!
Ready, Aelita?
Mhmm.
Okay!
We’re gonna try to push our way through.
That’s suicide!
If you don’t make it, Aelita will be
alone with the scyphozoa!
Okay, guys. This is it.
Oh, I think I’m…
(GROANS)
They’re on our tail.
Ladies, I hope you know what you’re doing.
Yeah. So do I, Jeremie.
Aah! Help!
No!
Take my fan.
Hurry!
Now!
Hiyah!
(ENGINE STALLING)
Miserable kankrelat.
We’ll have to go on foot.
Go ahead. I’ll take care of it.
Don’t drag your feet!
Oh, no.
Jeremie, the tower has disappeared.
Maybe we went the wrong way.
No, the tower is there.
I can see it on my screen.
You’re right, Jeremie.
It’s straight ahead.
How are we gonna get to it?
I can tele-transport Aelita.
You’re crazy!
If you fail, she’ll fall
right into the digital sea!
You have a better idea?
I trust her, Jeremie.
Yumi!
Behind you!
Aah!
(SCREAMS)
(GROWLING)
Yumi!
Aah!
(GROANS)
A-a-a-a-h!
It’s one of XANA’s tricks.
Aelita…
(PANTING)
Jeremie, a krab!
Keep going.
Normally, it wouldn’t dare fire at you.
Yes!
Hah-ha! Nice job!
Ow!
Oh, no.
Don’t you touch Milly, you hear!
Odd?!
Jeremie, did you program
the return to the past?
Jeremie?
Tower deactivated.
Aelita!
(MOANS)
Return to the past now!
You see? I didn’t even get that.
Sissi, what do you think
about your father’s decision
to set up a language exchange
program with France?
Our readers want to know.
My dear Milly, your paper
doesn’t have any readers.
And anyway, I don’t need the whole school
knowing what I think, understand?
Coming?
Oh, I hate her.
It’s true that she’s a pain,
but you know, deep down,
I think she really likes you.
And I really think that
she can be very brave
and a real nice person
when she wants to be.
What?
Yeah.
In fact, you never can guess
a person’s true colors, can you?
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO