♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Time to launch the program.
Oh no, I don’t believe it, not again!
I- Darn it, I’m so useless, I’m never gonna do it!
And I’m sure you will Jeremie.
Thanks for the encouragement,
But I’m useless I tell you.
Jeremie, do you think we’d get along well
in the real world?
I mean, as well as we do now?
Yeah, of course, why?
Well because I’m not so sure
I’d like to have a best friend who’s useless.
You understand?
Ha ha, very funny.
Hey get a move on Jeremie,
you’re going to be late for school again.
Wow is it that late already?
Ok I’ll be right there Odd.
Anyhow useless or not I’m going to try one more thing.
Ok I get the picture, see you later.
(SCREAMS)
This whatever it is of yours weighs at least a ton!
It's not a whatever,
it’s been in my family for hundreds of years.
So when are you going to unveil your thingamabob?
At the very end of my report.
You’ll see it's gonna be smash hit, a real showstopper!
Worth an A I hope.
Well you sure wouldn’t find a thing like that at my house.
First of all your whatchamacallit
doesn’t go with the drapes in the living room.
Whatchamacallit? Whatever?
What I like most about you Ulrich is your rich vocabulary.
Don’t look now Tamiya, but I smell a big juicy scoop!
So do I!
Ok, rolling, go ahead.
Fellow middle school students, hello, this is Milly
and Tamiya of the seventh grade reporting the school news.
You may not know it, but just behind your backs,
something strange is hatching,
and this my friends, is a part of it.
In our constant quest
to be the first to report the latest news,
we are bringing you this exclusive expose
of what's hidden under this drape.
Tamiya, listen,
is there any reason for your filming your feet?
Hey, Tamiya!
I’m sorry, it scares me a little.
(BELL RINGING)
Oh no, time for class already?
(YAWNS)
You know Jeremie most people use the night hours to sleep.
I was trying a new program for materializing Aelita.
With this last one I was trying I almost succeeded,
I was nearly there.
And what are you going to say to her when you do succeed?
You never knew how to talk to a girl!
With Aelita, it's not the same.
You’re right it's not the same.
Good morning everyone.
Before the start of your first class this morning,
I would like to introduce your new classmate.
Come in Taelia,
I’m sure your fellow students are anxious to meet you.
Okay here’s your chance, imagine she’s here in front of you,
right now in flesh and blood, what are you going to say?
Oh wow! (STAMMERS)
Beep! Sorry your time is up!
You could do with a few pointers in flirting.
Oh wow, this is- I don’t believe it!
You’re right, she sure does look like her,
but if it really is her,
she ought to be able to recognize us don’t you think?
Not necessarily, she may
of lost her memory when she was materialized.
Well talk to her,
it's the only way you can find out.
What if it's not her?
Hm?
Hm.
(SIGHS)
Go on!
Hey! Wait- (STAMMERS)
Okay watch an expert at work, and learn.
Hi there Ae- I mean Taelia.
My friends and I were, uh,
we thought you looked familiar like we’d seen you before.
Come on, that’s the oldest pick up line around.
Huh? Hey who said that I wanted to pick you up?
I was just making conversation.
Uh, by the way do things like the virtual world, or Krabs,
or buzzing monsters mean anything to you?
Uh, well yeah.
It means that I'd better be moving along.
Hey wait a minute, don’t go!
Where are you from? Do you have a family?
I’m not in the mood to talk.
Well?
It’s not her.
He’s only saying that
because he just got the brush off big time!
Watch an expert learn huh?
Anyway if it is Aelita, its for sure she’s got amnesia.
Wait a second, hold on.
Lets say its her, if it's really her, I mean for sure,
Then she can’t still be on Lyoko!
You can check it out later.
Right now we have a date with Mrs. Meyer.
Wish me luck for my report everybody!
Thanks for caring, guys...
Now we have here a simple equation with two unknowns-
I have to check out Lyoko now, I can’t wait any longer!
Okay, we’ll go together.
Uh, Mrs. Meyer, excuse me?
Yes, what is it?
I’m sorry but I need to go to the infirmary.
I-I don’t feel too well, I feel uh- I feel really sick.
Yes, of course, Jeremie, go ahead.
Uh, I’ll take him there! I mean uh, you never know, huh?
We’re just about connected.
Jim’s going to catch us if you don’t hurry up.
Aelita do you read me? It’s Jeremie, Aelita.
She doesn’t answer but she might be in one of Xana’s traps,
like in a storm or snow bound, so you can’t pick her up.
What if the last calculations I tried were the right ones?
You know, you could really use a good night's sleep.
Odd, it’s her.
And I say you’re nuts!
I’m positive, I did it, I did, Taelia is Aelita!
Well, of course it’s just a glimpse of my country's culture.
To explain it all would take me hours, and I’m not sure
you’re ready to put up with me for that long right?
(LAUGHTER)
To end my report, I’d like to show you something
that’s been in my family for centuries.
It’s a living symbol of Japan,
and it's a- (STAMMERS) a drape?
Xana.
Hey you! What are you doing here? Huh?
What kind of a costume is that?
Huh?
Hey, what wrong with you, huh?
Are you out of your head?
Maybe one of the kids took it?
Don’t forget the electric plugs!
Yeah, look if Xana is in on this,
we better not count on Aelita. We can’t reach her on Lyoko.
Odd we can’t reach her on Lyoko
'cause she isn’t on Lyoko!
Hm?
Sorry you guys, but I can’t believe
that that that girl is Aelita.
Well I know somebody who's dying to believe it.
Children please give me your attention.
Several of your fellow students as well as our own Jim,
whom you all know, and whom you respect I know,
have been attacked.
Let’s not go overboard, huh?
Their attacker was a person who uh,
well a person who was wearing armor, the armor of a Samurai.
(CLEARS THROAT) And this individual is still at large.
(SIGHS)
Any information you can contribute to the police
would be more than welcome.
We can't wait any longer.
We have to go to Lyoko, find Aelita,
and deactivate the tower.
When are you gonna get it into your thick heads that if
the samurai is controlled by Xana, that he's after Taelia?
It makes sense, doesn't it? Huh?
Because Taelia is Aelita.
(SIGHS)
Wow, he's really flipped his lid, huh?
Excuse me, Miss.
It seems that this armor belongs to you.
(STAMMERS)
Aelita! Listen to me, Xana's launched a new virus.
(SIGHS)
He's managed to take control of a samurai's armor.
You're his sworn enemy. He's after you.
You have no choice, you absolutely have to hide.
As a pick up line, that's a lot more original
than the one your friend tried.
Aelita, please listen to me.
It's definitely the materialization that gave you amnesia.
The shock made you lose your memory.
But you have to trust me! You have to, Aelita.
Hey, get your hands off of me.
I don't trust anyone who's stark raving mad.
(GASPS)
(CLANKING FOOTSTEPS)
No Xana! You won't get her, I won't let you, you hear?
(GASPS)
Come on, follow me! Hurry!
Faster, Taelita!
(GASPS)
It's not true.
Anyway, this samurai's armor does belong to you?
Well yes, to my parents.
And you have no idea who might have stolen it?
Look, we can't do anything here for Yumi, Ulrich,
we have to tell Jeremie to meet us at the factory.
Jeremie's voice-mail is on now.
Wow, this place is weird.
Follow me.
Come on.
That's Lyoko.
The virtual world where you once lived.
Doesn't that ring a bell at all?
And this, um, this Xana you talked about,
does he also live in the same world?
Yes
He's got total control.
But if he's so dangerous, why don't you destroy Lyoko?
Because you're part of-
(STAMMERS) Because you were part of this world.
You're totally crazy.
(SIGHS)
This whole story is crazy.
You know what I think? If all this stuff is so dangerous,
it's time you destroyed it, once and for all.
Do you... do you really think so?
Mh hm.
(SIGHS)
Jeremie, stop.
Huh?
Have you gone mad or what, Einstein?
What if Aelita is still on Lyoko?
But she isn't, I tell you.
Look, she's there, she's right in front of you.
Jeremie, I know you've dreamt of
seeing Aelita in reality for months,
but please come down to Earth, you can't be sure.
And what if you were mistaken?
You mean you're ready to take the risk of destroying Aelita
by destroying Xana, huh?
We've got to make sure.
You've got to let us go to Lyoko.
And if Aelita's not there,
who's going to deactivate the tower?
We have to take the risk.
Huh?
The last time I saw Aelita,
she was in the mountain area.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Can you see anything?
Yes, Jeremie. Mountains, lot's of 'em.
I'm starting the scan
to trace the tower that Xana activated.
You have to understand Taelia,
if you're not Aelita, then we've got to- Taelia?
Boy oh boy, finding someone around here is gonna be
harder than finding an idea in Jim's head.
Huh?
(SIGHS)
Ulrich, I just saw Aelita.
Hm? Where?
In a kind of flash vision.
Aelita.
Oh, hi, Yumi.
Well, is everything okay?
Yes, they finished questioning me,
but I just saw Taelia, and she looked like she
was in a hurry to go and see the principal.
Oh, that can't be, this is awful, horrible.
Yumi, I took Taelia to the factory.
You what? She's gonna tell the cops everything!
Be right there.
(MOANS)
Odd, Ulrich, the tower Xana's activated has been localized
at thirty degrees north in- in the forest area.
Without Aelita, that's not gonna do us a lot of good.
Look there! That ball of fire.
That's exactly what I saw before. Aelita's inside it.
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
Jeremie, we found her!
(SIGHS)
That ball is what's blocking the communication with Aelita.
It's a Guardian, the same monster that imprisoned Yumi.
Right, and Aelita saved her by convincing the monster
he had the wrong prisoner.
Yeah, but Aelita is the prisoner this time.
So now, the only solution is to use force.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Is anyone there?
I know you're there! Show yourself!
(GRUNTS)
Laser arrow!
Jeremie, nothing's working.
It's like this machine's invincible.
(SIGHS) Wow, Xana has- Xana must have designed a program...
right, it's a program.
And if it's a program, I should be able to-
Hey, what are you mumbling about?
You've got an idea, I hope?
Maybe, but give me a couple minutes here.
Okay, no problem, man, we've got all the time in the world.
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Already? To think I blew our whole cover
by talking to a perfect stranger.
That means the samurai wasn't after Taelia at all,
he was after us. Yumi!
Just a little more time.
Hey, how about that idea of yours?
It's ready. Here goes.
Making a clone of Aelita?
Well personally, I'm a bit skeptical, Jeremie.
Patience, Odd.
A decoy! Jeremie, you're the greatest.
Get Aelita to a tower,
she's got to regenerate herself.
Everything's okay, Aelita's got her life points back again.
(SIGHS) You found me at last.
What about the Guardian?
You mean that big, fat fire bubble?
Ha, he won't bother you anymore.
We're off Jeremie. Destination, the forest.
Jeremie, we're here.
Look guys, you better hurry, I can't reach Yumi.
I'm afraid she's having problems with the samurai.
There's no time to lose, let's go.
While you're at it, you got any other good news?
Oh yeah, plenty.
Taelia saw me punch in the access code to the lab,
and the principal and the police are here now.
Um, and Xana's monsters are around.
Two Bloks.
Watch out for their laser gel guns, or it's game over.
Hey, Bloks, cool, my favorite monsters.
Laser arrow.
(SIGHS)
There, it was this computer right here.
There was this Xana thing, I don't know how, but--
It seems he wants to destroy the planet.
Jeremie, I think you owe us an explanation.
Odd, take care of Aelita.
I'll stay here and cover you. Alone. Well, almost alone.
Triangulate.
Impact.
Your turn, Princess.
Come along now.
I'm sorry sir, but my friends are in danger
and I can't abandon them.
No, don't! Stop!
You can't do this, let me go!
You always pick the wrong time, huh?
Now!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
(GASPS)
(YELPS)
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMS)
Oh no!
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Return to the past now!
And this is Taelia, your new classmate.
I'm sure your fellow students are anxious to meet you.
I heard Sissi say that the new girl was an orphan.
That's why she didn't want to talk about her family.
Well anyway, if you look closely,
you can see their eyes aren't the same.
The nose is different, and so is the hair,
they're not similar at all.
How could you have possibly thought she was Aelita?
Did you just say that we thought?
You sure did.
You'd have to be blind to think that.
And now, to finish my report, I'd like to show you something
that's been in my family for centuries.
It's a living symbol of Japan. Here.
(SCATTERED APPROVAL)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS!