♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Tell me what the good news is, I can’t wait.
We’re waiting for you here.
I don’t know what those kids are hiding, sir,
but I intend to find out!
Me and my friends, we do have a secret.
Your paranoia is beginning to get on my nerves.
I’m sorry Jim, but I’m going to have to let you go.
Look Jim, if you help me, I’ll tell the principal everything.
Shake on it.
I’m ready for the big jump, Jeremie.
Okay, Aelita, I’m launching the program
for your materialization.
Code Earth.
(GASP)
Come on, let’s go.
Hey, relax Aelita, don’t worry, it’s just a history class.
I’d feel a lot better if it were in computers.
I don’t know anything about history.
That’s just it, you’re here to learn.
If it were a computer class, you could be the teacher.
Take your seats so we can begin.
(SIGHS)
Hmph
Just who does that new girl think she is?
All she cares about is having boys around her.
Actually, I think she looks worried.
Obviously Nicholas, you don’t know
the first thing about girls.
Acting frail and helpless will work every time.
Boys love that, it’s the best way to attract them.
Hm?
We have a new student in our class. I’ll let her introduce herself.
Hm.
(STUTTERING)
Aelita’s her name. And she’s my cousin.
She’s very shy.
Hm, well Aelita, let me welcome you to Kadic Junior High.
We all hope that you’re going to like it here very much.
You see, everything’s cool. There was no reason to worry.
I guess not. And besides, I really like history.
But you’ve got to admit, you fight a lot here,
there are wars all the time.
Hey guys! Well how’s our new Earthling doing?
Oh, I’m fine.
I’m trying to adapt to so many new sensations.
Like the air that you breath here,
all the colors and the smells. But I’m fine.
It’s about time we deactivated the supercomputer,
don’t you think?
Well I wouldn’t wait for Xana to send us an invitation.
And who feels like going back to Lyoko
now that Aelita’s here with us?
You’ll think this is silly, but it scares me a little.
Lyoko after all, was my home.
And I’m not really sure what effect
destroying it might have for me.
There’s nothing to worry about, I’m sure.
Come on.
(SNORING)
Hi, Jim!
Huh?
Well did you have a good sleep?
Oh yeah, great.
And I really appreciate everything you’ve done for me.
But I was getting a little bored, I have to admit.
How’d you like to watch us deactivate Xana?
I wouldn’t miss that for the world!
You haven’t forgotten your promise, Jeremie.
I haven’t, Jim.
As soon as Xana’s deactivated, I’ll tell the whole story
to the principal and you’ll get your job back!
That’s great.
I can’t wait ‘till all this is settled.
I honestly never imagined that I would
miss being your PE teacher so much.
Uh, from now on, call me Jimbo, eh?
Thanks, so are you ready to go, Jimbo?
Here we are.
(WHIRRING)
(MISC BUZZING AND BEEPING)
Are you okay, Aelita?
If you want to wait a day or two…
No, the sooner the better.
Okay. I think you should have the honor.
No, I… I’d rather you did it.
Sure, Aelita.
Xana, you gave us a lot of grief. But thanks to you,
we met Aelita. So goodbye and good riddance.
(WHIRRING DOWN)
(GASPING)
Aelita!
Put the power back on, Aelita’s not well, hurry up!
(WHIRRING UP)
What’s wrong with her?
Let’s hope Xana doesn’t rear his ugly head.
(GROWLING)
(HEART THUMPING)
Her pulse seems back to normal again.
I don’t know… what happened?
I--
You fainted, Aelita. It’s a little bit like sleeping.
A really deep sleep.
Oh I liked the way it felt.
Maybe you did, but you passed out, and that’s not normal.
I modified the scanners’ program while you slept.
Do you mind if I examine you?
Uh, no.
Launching program.
Data recovery.
Don’t tell me you really understand all that.
It’s not very complicated.
Hm.
We’re ready to begin the analysis.
Uh, that’s fine, Aelita, you can come back now.
Okay, let’s try to see what the trouble is.
(SIGHS)
That’s just what I was afraid of.
It looks like Xana infected me with a virus.
Hm.
That’s it!
Huh?
He must have done it during the transfer.
Hm.
There was a sudden drop in the voltage for a very short time.
I remember that.
Because I had a strange feeling at that moment.
For a few seconds I felt Xana’s presence,
as if he was trying to hold me back.
(HEART THUMPING)
And that’s probably the reason why you fainted a while ago.
Xana implanted a virus inside you because
he wanted you to be linked to him. And if we kill Xana…
Then I get destroyed as well.
(SIGHS)
Uh, is there anything we can do?
Yeah, try to find an antivirus.
But it could take a long time.
I’m starting up an analysis program.
The computer will work autonomously on it
until tomorrow morning.
I’ll take you back to Yumi’s. It’s kinda late.
(CHUCKLES)
What a strange sensation.
You shivered, that’s all.
It’s a reaction you get on account of the cold.
I like the feeling of being a little chilly.
And the sounds and the smells are all different at night.
Yeah, it’s quiet and peaceful,
and the plants, they breath differently.
Here, smell this.
Mmn
Wow, It’s wonderful to be alive!
And it’s thanks to you that I’m here.
(STAMMERING) Well, I didn’t do it alone.
What’s that? A scanner?
No, not exactly. Follow me!
(LAUGHING)
(MORE LAUGHTER)
Well your castle awaits you, Princess.
Thanks for walking me back.
In spite of the virus,
I still had the most wonderful night of my life.
Good night.
(STAMMERING)
See you tomorrow!
Aelita’s… wow!
(WHISTLING)
So do you have any idea how to get rid of
this miserable virus?
No, not yet. I hope the calculations
my computer made will help me.
Here come the girls.
Well how was your first night on earth?
Sleeping is really wonderful!
She would have slept all day
if I hadn’t shaken her a little.
(LAUGHING)
You’re just like me, Aelita.
And you’ll see, sleeping in class isn’t too bad either.
(HEART THUMPING)
(SNORING)
Huh? What’s going on?
Who can give us the definition of a pair of prime numbers?
Uh, Sissi?
Uh, mn, well...
Uh, uh, a pair of prime numbers is um…
Two numbers that are both the same.
(LAUGHING)
Thank you, Sissi. Well, can one of you
give us a less hare-brained answer?
Aelita?
A pair of prime numbers occurs
when their highest common denominator is one.
Very good, although--
In a principal ring, it’s equivalent to the fact
that their direct sum is equal to one
but of course with a non-principal factorial ring,
that is not the case.
Uh...
That is, according to the theory of Bézout, you see...
Bézout?
(SCREAMING)
Calm down, children.
Get back!
Take cover!
Xana’s changed tactics, he sent one of his monsters
to Earth for the first time! How did he manage that?
Who cares?
The problem is...
How do you suggest getting rid of him?
Like we always do, we fight them!
You three head for Lyoko and deactivate the tower.
Yumi and I will stay here and defend the home front.
Oh no, that’s crazy, Ulrich.
You know very well that if there’s a victim
that going back in time won’t bring it back to life.
Yumi? Yeah, we already know. We’ve got to find weapons.
Okay, I’ll meet you outside of the math class.
Well, let’s go, guys.
(SCREAMING)
I’ll handle him. Get going!
Let’s see how good you are.
Ow!
A few more seconds, and the coast will be clear.
What would you do without me?
Hurry up!
Come on!
Wow, Jim gave them a good run for their money.
Jim?
That way.
Huh?
Looks like they got their sights set on us.
Okay, let’s show ‘em what we can do.
Hey, over here!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
You miserable monster!
I’ll make you think twice before
you leave your world again!
Oh no!
Hang on, Jim!
I told you to call me Jimbo, remember?
Jeremie, you have to transfer me to Lyoko.
What?
Have you forgotten Xana’s virus, Aelita?
What if Xana stops you from deactivating the tower?
Or from returning to Earth?
That’s a risk we’ve got to take.
The priority is to stop Xana.
You know as well as I do that we have no choice, Jeremie.
Think of all the other monsters Xana could materialize.
Okay, get into the scanner. I’ll send you to Lyoko.
I’m deactivating the infected scanner.
Get ready, Odd.
(RAPIDLY INCREASING BEEPING)
Nice going, kid.
I’ve located the activated tower.
It’s in the glacier region,
that’s where I’m sending you.
By the way, where are Ulrich and Yumi?
At school, fighting monsters.
I’m off. I’ll be a lot more useful there.
Here, it’s like a swiss army knife.
See you later!
Transfer, Odd.
Transfer, Aelita.
Scanner, Odd.
Scanner, Aelita.
Virtualization.
It’s strange being virtualized.
Yeah, but you get used to it.
No air to breathe, no smells, no warmth, nothing.
I miss the real world already.
Let’s go, Aelita.
Ulrich, we’re never gonna make it!
Bonzai!
Yah!
(TRIUMPHANTLY LAUGHING)
Take that, you cockroach!
Yeah! Got one!
Say your prayers!
There’s something I gotta admit, Jim...
This is the first time I’m glad you caught us by surprise.
My friends call me Jim...bo.
Got it?
Squadron approaching at nine o’clock.
Three hornets.
Here they come now.
Watch out!
They’re coming back!
Head for the tower, I’ll hold them off!
You’ve got forty life points left, Odd.
Jeremie.
What is it, Ulrich?
Where are you?
Odd and Aelita really need your help.
We haven’t finished the job here yet.
Odd’s only got forty life points left.
If Aelita’s left all alone, she’s headed for disaster.
Okay, we’ll hurry up.
You two had better high-tail it to Lyoko.
I can handle these bugs on my own.
Am I right to say that the sooner you deactivate the tower--
--the safer the world’s gonna be? Is that it?
Mh hm.
Well then what are you waiting for?
Go on now and get the job done.
It takes a lot more than a few ugly monsters
to beat your friend Jimbo!
Take that!
You’re losing too many life points, Odd!
(YELLING)
You gotta hang in there.
Jeremie!
Yumi! It’s about time.
Odd’s only got twenty life points left.
We’re heading for the scanner.
Don’t worry about Odd, he can hold on a while,
twenty points is enough for him.
Laser arrow!
Come on, I’m waiting for you!
Oh, I don’t believe it!
I’m out of arrows.
Bye bye.
There it is.
Watch out, Aelita!
Aelita!
(SCREAMING)
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
So, still haven’t had enough, huh?
(LAUGHING)
Ah!
Oh?
(RAPID BEEPING)
(GRAONING)
Hey, you creeps! Over here! I’m ready, come on!
Aelita’s taking cover in a cave back there.
Oh no!
You can do better than that!
Sorry.
That way!
Uh huh.
Now, Yumi!
There, that’s more like it!
It’s all in the wrist. I’m a great frisbee player.
That was close!
Come on, Aelita, you know
we would never let you go it alone.
Hey, we can’t let the school go it alone either.
Right.
Yeah, take that! And that!
(SCREAMING AND WAILING)
Well don’t just stand there, go on, run!
Leave those kids alone!
(GRUNTS)
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Come on, you bed bugs, gimme all you got.
Go on, huh?
Is that all you got?
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
What are you waiting for?
Come on, you think I’m all washed up?
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Return to the past, now.
Aelita, we’re restarting the materialization program
immediately.
We’ve got to wipe out Xana
before he launches another attack.
Jeremie, it’s impossible.
The virus is still in me, I can feel it.
We’ve still got to try it.
Maybe you can be treated here on Earth.
No, Jeremie. You know that as well as I do.
As long as this virus is inside of me--
you can’t destroy Xana without destroying me at the same time.
We could materialize you for an hour or two.
So you could pay us a little visit, huh?
Why not?
But the rest of the time, I’ll have to stay here on Lyoko--
--to fight Xana. Until the day you find an antivirus.
Aelita...
I, uh…
Hm.
Jim. We forgot all about him.
So, you kids are at it again.
No Jim, we were studying.
Studying, my eye, I’ve had enough of your lies.
You’re gonna stay right here until you tell me everything.
Jim?
What is going on here?
Ah, you came by just the right time sir.
I was just about to find out exactly what
these children were up to again.
Oh, another one of your absurd stories
about mysterious meetings and secret passages, eh?
I’ve had about enough of this, Jim, and I’m going to have to-
He’s right sir, we really were plotting.
We were. We were going to play a little joke on
Nicholas and Herb.
Hm.
Huh?
In fact, sir, if Jim hadn’t caught us,
we would have been late for school for sure.
Well then, I’ll look the other way this time--
--since you admitted what you’ve done.
Now, off to class, children. Go on, now!
Well you made up one heck of a story, kids.
Why did you get me off the hook?
Well it’s just that you never know--
--maybe one day you’ll do the same for us.
And you know, we never get the time to thank you
for all you’ve done for us. So thanks a lot, Jimbo.
Yeah, thanks!
You’re a hero.
And a fantastic PE teacher, Jimbo!
Oh, well uh, you oughta tell the principal that!
Okay now, go to class!
Huh, a hero… Wow.
(LAUGHING)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS!