<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ECHOES</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[children chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dribbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chair rocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, do you want my croissant?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I've got my own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm not that hungry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita, Jeremy, Ulrich] Me neither.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] How're you doing, losers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it looks like the lame-o club</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is all depressed today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That always happens when </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>show up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Very funny, Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, honey, if there's anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can do to cheer you up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-just say the word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[GPS locator beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, disappear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem. Bye now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys. Well, today's the day I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's go and shut down the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[GPS locator beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo! Thanks to this mini GPS,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am going to find out what Ulrich and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his dorky little gang's secret is at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it'll all be over this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do any of you want to say something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've had our share of ups and downs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hours of detention, hours of glory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The five of us have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gotten used to life with Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now's it's time for a new life without it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fans swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope I'm not going to regret this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screen beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's all this, a video game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Who… who are you? Where am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA? What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A super dangerous program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a virus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which can control electricity,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that activates towers on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to gain access to your world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Only Aelita can counter it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by deactivating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower that it uses</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for attacks in the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is linked to XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to find a way to materialize her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] And this is your room. It's not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>very big, but you'll like it here, Miss…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stones… Aelita Stones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I've already seen this house</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a dream.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you're the daughter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Franz Hopper, the creator of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> XANA's escaped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With this virtual submarine, we'll be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>able to track XANA on the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's another virtual world just like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko, a replica created by XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>But for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like some sort</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of factory assembly line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but what do they assemble here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's plan is to take control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of hundreds of Supercomputers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all over the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in order to make an army of robots</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take over all of humanity!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our only hope of destroying XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is my multi-agent system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, we've done it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's been destroyed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, but I can't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Are you out of your mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't shut it down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't, Jeremy, or you won't?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, it's very simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We destroyed XANA, and now we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to shut down this horrible machine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are the rest of you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is wrong with all of you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's just that we all feel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little shook up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can see that! Any suggestions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got one. Why don't we take a vote</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see who does or doesn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>want to shut it down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Who votes for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So that's where they hang out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The old abandoned factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is their secret hiding place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go there now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not right away, dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we go now, we'll run right into them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'll go over there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during gym class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you guys are going to have to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some excuse for my being absent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you want us to say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know. Just say the first thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that pops into your head!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not in the mood to talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it's me who wants to talk to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to explain why I voted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against shutting down the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not in the mood to hear </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>that </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you remember me when I came here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The big brain of Kadic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>straight A computer genius,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not one single friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I discovered Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and everything changed for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I became a hero who could save the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you expect us to keep playing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>super hero until we were 80?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It had to end some time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but I don't want to lose</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what we've got together, our friendship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to do everything we can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find your dad, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fighting against XANA is my job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>our</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our friendship is directly linked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm afraid that if we shut it, it'll also</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shut down our friendship down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later. I've got gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hold on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I understand what you're feeling,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you're wrong. Our friendship</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is too strong to shut down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Abulabbas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Abulabbas] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim shouting] Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Present!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where were you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-With Yumi. I'll tell you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting] Elisabeth Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Does anyone know where Sissi is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She ran into some aliens</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and went totally crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you nuts or are you just dumb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aliens? And little green men like you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poliakoff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After class, we'll go tell the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that his daughter's crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if she's not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's detention on planet Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was the first thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that popped into my head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Right. Today's lesson is in RSG.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, RSG does not stand for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Rough Sports Games" or for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Raunchy Slobbering Gorilla"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or for "Reeking Stink of Garlic."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>RSG means "Rhythmic Sportive Gymnastics,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>known today just as "Rhythmic Gymnastics."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, can I ask you a question?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About RSG?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, about the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why'd you vote not to shut it down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I was afraid of missing--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Missing what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The fighting, the adventure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the heroics…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all that fun stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Lyoko, life's going to be awfully</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>boring, don't you think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boring?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finally having the time for music and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sports is not exactly what I call boring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Way to go, Odd. Nice one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, point for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true, I know how to have fun</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I have the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you'll also have more time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find new girlfriends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All the girls are crazy about me already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't need any extra time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I thought I told you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>never to talk to me again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Magali clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How dare you lie to everyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and say that I'm love with Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Magali slaps Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Magali] Try that again and even your dog</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't recognize you next time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know all about Claire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are so despicable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! I know all about Magali!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You sneaky rat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that you mention it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little extra time wouldn't hurt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right. That's two points for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Stern! Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If this lesson is disturbing your little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>private conversation, please let me know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're sorry, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, my first demonstration…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My sciatica! I'm stuck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't straighten up and it hurts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rusty squeaking gym teacher.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that's what RSG stands for, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining] Stern, Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the principal's office right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] By the way, Ulrich, what about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why didn't you want to shut</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't give Jim's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I'd rather not talk about it" routine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tire skids]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like being a hero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what this is all about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Let's see now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Diary of Jeremy Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screen beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Diary of Jeremy Belpois</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, student at</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic Academy, eighth grade, October 9th.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A few weeks ago, I was looking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for parts to finish my miniature robots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screen distorts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I discovered a sort of data processing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>complex with a lab and scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Most of all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a totally incredible computer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distortion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight, even though I'm scared stiff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I‘ve decided to start up the computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope everything goes okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Yumi, wait up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it a done deal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you shut it down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not yet. The others aren't ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… That's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Did they forget how dangerous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course they know how dangerous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it is, but they're just too nostalgic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I think life without Lyoko's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going to be different, but okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you're exactly like me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're an eternal optimist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not when it's a lost cause.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you around, pretty boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA managed to broadcast</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this deadly music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita deactivated the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before everyone in the city was wiped out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The principal was possessed by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But everything turned out just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Interesting anecdote: Sissi helped us out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and kissed Ulrich on the bridge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attacking all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're too busy to think about school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I suggested that we recruit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William Dunbar into our group,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Yumi absolutely refuses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fast forward]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were able to save Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but William is gone, and I think for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Today XANA possessed Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his new victim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She almost killed my cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are giant roots in the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Krabs are attacking the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to save Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Earth is in danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just have to wait for Delmas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to finish chewing out Ulrich and Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I wanted to talk to you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No need to explain, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know exactly why you voted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the way you did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we shut down the machine,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means saying goodbye to my past…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and to my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going up to my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Man in black] Come out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] See you in a minute, honey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you in a minute, Daddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You mustn't forget me…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>ever. Never forget, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[animals howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've so much catching up to do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and there's so little time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screen beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of this was so terrible…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and great at the same time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But now, it's time to move on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to something new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes… Something more carefree.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting to think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that way too, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know it's really crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you think of all we did, and no one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is ever gong know anything about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and wait until I tell my father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so, if I understand correctly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you said that RSG stood</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for "Rusty Squeaking Jim."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gym teacher with a "G," not "J" for Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you for the clarification</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but that's… just as bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth, you've already had an eighteen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>month advance on your allowance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I refuse to give you another cent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you interrupted me as I was scolding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern and Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You shouldn't scold them, you should</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lock all of them up! They're lunatics!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They put the whole world in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[woman] You can't go in there…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Jeremy] We have to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aha! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the smart one now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that I'm onto your little secret!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't feel like making fun of me now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth, that is enough!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to me, I'm serious!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For months, they've been fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a dangerous computer program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a virtual universe! They put</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>their own lives in danger and ours' too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Because of them, the school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-was invaded by swarms of hornets,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>killer crows and even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a deadly giant teddy bear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even you, my sweet little daddy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were possessed by the program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You even fought against Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the bridge to the old factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Luckily, I was there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I was able to knock you out that time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but other times, I could have been killed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was violently attacked by electric</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cables! I almost drowned in the elevator,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then, a crazy teacher possessed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my body</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so he could have a long</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>conversation with them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I'm trying to say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screaming] No, not the infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me go. You have to go to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes darling, later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now, you obviously need some rest…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A great deal of rest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA and his robot army are going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy the planet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like that poor kid, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really is off her rocker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I apologize, Poliakoff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters sarcastically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where'd you run off to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are the others?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the factory. Jeremy's got to launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a return to the past. The last one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about you, Ulrich? Still against</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shutting down the Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I honestly don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes you do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here. A little birthday gift.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[romantic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Ulrich. That's very sweet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't forget that Yumi and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are just good friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well actually, I'm not sure at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you thought that maybe if we had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a fight, I'd think about you all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't need that to get my attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's been so great,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just don't want it to end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There'll be plenty of other good times,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even without Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Promise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey lame-os, what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want my croissant, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather kiss your dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich honey, how's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Better without your GPS locator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, cut it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>have </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>any secrets.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you want to stay friends with us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just stop trying to mess us up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean… We're really friends?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Why sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>school would be so boring without you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh… Well see you later, good buddies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for you, don't let me catch either</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of you dorks trying to mess my friends up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, nice to see you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, are you guys ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, who's in favour of shutting down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Well, if it isn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the fantastic five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of trouble are you up to now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, nothing at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just closed the book</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on an unforgettable,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>adventure-filled life</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of heroism and danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've all been there, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, one fine day, I also gave up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my teenage dreams to become an adult.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No kidding! You're actually an adult?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So long!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>