<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DOUBLE TAKE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] So then, the guy gets up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and starts to scream:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Oh no,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my canoe just sprang a leak!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, that's hysterical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The guy thinks his canoe sprang a leak.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You guys have no sense of humor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We do. That's the problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sense of humor comes with growing up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, I'm the funniest guy in school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, if I wasn't me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would be president of my own fan club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that's what I call funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but the problem is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't mean it to be funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Do you mind making</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little bit less noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Some of us are trying to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've already spent a lot of sleepless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nights recreating the rest of Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and improving the digital equipment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for all of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now I've gotta figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what to do about William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't forgotten that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while you're doing your bad standup act…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't me. It was him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…that William is stuck on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under the control of XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if we don't do anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>people are gonna start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>noticing his absence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So keep it down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Delmas Academy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre Kadic here…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic Academy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre Delmas speaking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through the phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is James Dunbar, William's father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm calling to say that my son</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't be able to attend school this week.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got a very high fever,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he has to stay in bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I hope it's not game over for him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is to say, nothing too serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a very bad flu.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that's a relief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please tell your son that we all wish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>him a speedy recovery, Mr. Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good-bye, and thanks for calling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hangs phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs in relief]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I honestly don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what we'd do without my voice synthesizer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, now that we handled Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe we can go to more important stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, like what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Meatballs and spaghetti!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I know that you're a walking stomach</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I haven't got time to go to lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to get to the factory to test out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the latest codes for your new equipment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you program me some bell-bottom</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pants with an orange stripe on the side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will ya! I need a little thinking time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What you need is to hear a good joke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't laugh enough. Lighten up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman] It doesn't look that hard, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman] There we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[woman chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Nicole,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you have some work to finish up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicole doubts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[man] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>James Dunbar speaking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm calling you, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I'm getting worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't heard from my son,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, for several days</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and whenever I try to contact him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on his mobile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he doesn't pick up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, isn't that a shame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I assure you I'll do everything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I possibly can to find your son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call the army, the FBI,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even the President. So don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[James Dunbar] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no need to go that far for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now listen, Mr. Whoever alias Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You would do better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to think about your own fate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not that of your so-called son</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once I discover who</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it is that's calling. So there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hear that, Nicole?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>is the way you have to talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to practical jokers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who enjoy playing tricks on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's one thing I don't get.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you know that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>was the practical joker</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not the person you spoke to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the phone before?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in disbelief]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't want your banana?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's for Einstein. The walking stomach has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to look out for our local genius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh… Delmas and Incredible Hulk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at eleven o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Hello, Yumi. I was wondering,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have you had any news</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of William Dunbar by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim said that you were close friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Somebody told me that he was sick</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in bed with a very high fever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me handle this, Jean-Pierre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Yumi, be honest with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know perfectly well that William isn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any more sick than I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim sneezes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bless you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you. If you wanna know what I think,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think William is somewhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and something tells me that somehow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you know exactly where that somewhere is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that sometimes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's better to be honest with someone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>uno</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, somebody should tell William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we know he's around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>doso</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, he oughta get back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, Mr. Delmas, our beloved principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will call some police.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That oughta do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means I'm gonna have to slog away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all afternoon trying to finish a program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get William out of XANA's clutches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And who knows if it'll even work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-uh, that's impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got track this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't keep cutting PE all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you're gonna be in a lot of trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll get back to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Improvise… As usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Problem: being here and in class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the same time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vendor machine working</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and suddenly stopping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanism jamming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow, he sure got ready fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everybody wow]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Two points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey, everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've already finished all you had to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Piece of cake, sweetie pie, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think? Sure I'm done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're looking at the man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going kid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must've got all dolled up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for me today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't believe the vibes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm feeling right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, go back to being Jeremy, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[playfully]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just that… Whenever I see you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't feel like I'm myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hello, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy? But then…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think of me, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on. You mind explaining this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean you haven't figured out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I made a double of myself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A digital copy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by activating a tower on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way, I can work on the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for finding William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and be in gym class at the same time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You might have warned us about it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, guys, but I was in a big hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, you oughta know that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your double has gotta be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the biggest flirt I've ever met.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Must be some kind of emerging quality</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that appeared unexpectedly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, guys, I may not have hit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a home run with it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but a double is still pretty good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Abulabbas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Abulabbas] Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, this has gotta be a dream.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy Belpois in person has finally</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>decided to honor us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with his presence, in the flesh,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>although there's not a whole lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After holding the world's record</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for absences from every single sport</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're all going to watch Mister Skin</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Bones make up for lost time by</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>throwing his lack of weight around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His lack…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so it was in 1671 that Isaac Newton</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>created his famous reflection telescope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and as I'm sure you can see on this very</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rare and precious model of it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let me get out of the line of fire</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before I give you the signal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Newton and his law of gravity?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The apple that fell?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing noise]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holy Toledo, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Whew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I mean… Incredible, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could you throw that thing so far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with arms as scrawny</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as the wings of a chicken, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, well you see, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's been working out a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Suzanne]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim! You're worse than those barbarians</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who burned down the Alexandria Library!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you're gonna participate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the interschool competition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against the top student gymnasts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those dodos at Central Prep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't know what hit 'em!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music crescendoes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go on! You too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhaling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, champ. Now let's see how well</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you throw the javelin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, this better be important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure it is. XANA's attacking the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If it keeps up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA will be able to activate it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in red and use it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for his own evil purposes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods in approval]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get the idea. How can you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get the process to stop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] To buy a little time I can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>channel some of Sector Five's energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to shore up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower's resistance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy's double shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] Hey! What do you think you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo! Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna be your personal manager,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait 'til they get a load of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and me, we're gonna go far. Trust me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna taste the thrill of victory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna breeze through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the championships, the nationals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the planetaries, the interplanetaries,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the intergalactics!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Stern, Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, pick yourselves a lane</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and let's see how you run</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the 400 meters against Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] You ready, champ?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] On your marks. Get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Set… Bang!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't get me that easy, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy crashes against the floor]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better be careful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to rough up my champion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay, kid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm good, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK. Better safe than sorry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is what I always say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any volunteers to go with Belpois</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Ulrich nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm off to the factory with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Isolate Jeremy two and watch him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, right. Easy for you to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ma'am, can I please leave the room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Suzanne] Ouch! Yes, go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't seen any pieces</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of mirror around, have you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] If the Olympic champion would be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so kind as to enter…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lockers dragging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hurry up! I've hardly got enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>energy to protect the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're ready, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] OK. I'll start the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twin blades.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect for getting a close shave.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love your skirt, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Thanks. Those shoulder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pads aren't bad either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! You two can discuss fashion later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is north by northwest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh great, here we go again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lockers screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, stop pushing, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you like it in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] What is going on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just where do you think you are, Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No big deal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's just a little bit edgy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, try to calm down, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Don't you think that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>talking it out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would be much more constructive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than lashing out blindly and violently?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts ]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot for the psychology lesson,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sir. Now I've gotta catch him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, your evil XANA possessed copy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is on his way to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He's too fast for me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to catch up to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're on your own, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, Odd. I'll see what I can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did these wings come from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You like them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're just a little surprise I invented</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my spare time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you are the wind beneath my wings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you're an angel!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I can be just as resourceful as you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pal, you'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both exhale]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swords clash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triplicate…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He leaves an impression wherever he goes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, watch out! You've lost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>forty life points already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi's weapon spinning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yoo-hoo, Jeremy one and two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may be his evil twin,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you fight like a Bobbsey Twin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not too late</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take back what I said, is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[real Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy's double grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[real Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explodes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep your hands off my buddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ring beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explodes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's trying to push me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the Digital Sea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you back in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Oh no, it's not working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What do you expect?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Everything's breaking up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Only one thing left to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You didn't think I'd let you down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did ya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what do you think of my new outfit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's what I think too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So there's no way of bringing him back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not for the time being.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Have you got a plan B?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well… We haven't got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any other choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to make a copy of William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to replace him here at the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that a little risky?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yep, but it's the only way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to calm Jim and Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, but don't ever ask me to take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the copy to the infirmary, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopefully, William's copy hasn't developed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>emerging qualities</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like someone else I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-From this distance, he looks normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But up close?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Dunbar, my boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad to see that you fever has broken</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you're feeling well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, did I break anything else?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget to keep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>taking your medicines, eh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we're not out of the woods yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>