<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DOG DAY AFTERNOON</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, I'm coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't wear socks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get a better feel for the track?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot to put 'em on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, am I gonna have blisters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The way you sweat, you'll probably</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have to chuck your sneakers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd hums] Nice one, Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you see that? Kiwi opened the door</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he managed to find me all the way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the other side of the campus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He followed the smell of your feet. Easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your jokes stink worse than my feet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] On your marks… Get set… Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Yoo-hoo, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, how do I look?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure you really wanna know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[watch beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I say go, it means go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two letter words aren't hard, are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Either his ears need washing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or he's totally out of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look completely lost, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not. We're at the track, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Trouble at twelve o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're off your rocker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go talk to the nurse at the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's nothing serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a little out of sync</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because he's in love.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a second. Are you trying to say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you and William are…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They say that love is like getting drunk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-William doesn't drink, he's just…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-…just a complete half-wit, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tenth graders, that's it for today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ninth graders, get on your marks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think something weird is going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was a close call with Sissi today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think she bought the love story.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't we upgrade the clone's quality?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. His stupidity is an unforeseen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>emergent factor beyond our control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To fix it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have to reprogram everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's keep improvising.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi's getting very suspicious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happens</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if she tells her father about William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, the only solution I can see is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Keep pretending you're in love.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect. If you're always together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no one can get near him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got a vital mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to keep our secret safe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lively chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've improved the security program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the tower that runs his clone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, would you like to go to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to install it after class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No problem. Who's going with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do all of us have to go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one of you will be enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep an eye on things with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I volunteer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And I also have a great idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we take Kiwi to Lyoko this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your brainless dog? But what for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-First of all, my dog is not brainless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Secondly, our talents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are multiplied on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine Kiwi, and his sense of smell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He could sniff monsters from miles away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He might sniff out William on the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi's such a coward,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'd take off soon as he saw a Kankrelat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As fast as you did</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the time you went to Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[the others laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy and Aelita grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Looks like bikers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>used our factory for training.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] They aren't here anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] The coast is clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, we've gotta talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This thing with you and Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is baloney, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone knows she's mad about Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's mad about me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich Stern?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a nice guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like him a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you think he is a nice guy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then you are not well at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are weirdo things going on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I my father ought to know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, what are you doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my boyfriend's room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't think you can snow me, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What has your gang done to William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing. You're imagining things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, if you don't mind,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're gonna take a little walk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great guy Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Odd, are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on. Don't rush me, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready to go, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, is that you making that racket?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My tummy's rumbling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you believe it? I'm still hungry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. This won't take long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once you're on Lyoko, you'll be a star.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The tower we want is behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Expecting someone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get ready for a big surprise, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nothing. I was kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Head for the tower, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] On my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stand guard here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting the installation process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hope I didn't mess up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where are we going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Never mind. Just keep running.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I hear some kind of noise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two Tarantulas just appeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're at the other end of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I send you the overboard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just in case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Knock it off, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Tarantulas are far away, but still…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't seem to keep my balance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy, the program's operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, where did Odd go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He's busy clowning around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that you're done,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you both in. Materialization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Having trouble standing up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way I could've been… Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No biggie, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd missed his snack time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it doesn't seem to agree with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a pest that Sissi is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I can't get rid of Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I've got to go home right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bring him back to school. We'll take over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, come on, Romeo. We're going home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is Romeo a nice guy, too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go. I'll explain on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is something the matter, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, something serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm looking for my watch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must have fallen off after phys ed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sniffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Della Robbia, have you gone mad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums] Is this it, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Everything all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, no sweat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sniffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Except that Odd's acting really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You only just noticed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gross! Odd, I know you'll eat anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you're hungry, but that's ridiculous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh, come on, get real!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, this is getting worse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut that out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's really…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got this thing near my backside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think… I think… I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm growing a tail!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've gotta hang out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with William's clone a little longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a slight problem. Here's Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Talk to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, according to my diagnosis,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd absorbed Kiwi during virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is it serious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Pretty much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His human metabolism is still dominant,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if we don't do something,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we use the scanners to separate them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to send him… them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Count me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've still got that leech on my tail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call you back from the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've wasted enough time. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But can't we eat first?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna eat dog food all your life?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't look back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a stray dog is following us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna bit your leg</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't shut up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Just what we need right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know those guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uninvited visitors who use the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a practice track!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you kids doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beat it, right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me handle them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, gentlemen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just wanted to go in, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We didn't see your names on the door,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so get going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't waste energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've got motor oil for brains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll take care of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think you're in a Kung Fu flick?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's mean. Better be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll bite you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Rocky, what's wrong with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bikers shout]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What do we about them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll worry about them later on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now let's take care of Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I'm gonna virtualize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as you are onto Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then, I'll restore your two DNA sequences,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which should then return</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to their original molecular state.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, dog-man, go to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He unscrambles you and dog's DNA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and dog come back separated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You very clever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like I've got the hiccups.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This gonna take long, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I can't tell you in dog years.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So don't distract me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't go anywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you devirtualize before I finish,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be a dog forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, I feel better now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure that we can't help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's to concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] No! Activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] We're on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least we didn't miss dinner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for nothing. Cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, XANA just activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a tower in the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Aelita will handle it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stay put, understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get it. "Sit," "Heel," "Roll over."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Aelita gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice. The locals came to welcome us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about a little overbike action?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You got it. Be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Relax,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't run any red lights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Einstein, do you see what I hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three Bloks just showed up! Better hide!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call Yumi for backup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's about time you called.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My day has been just thrilling!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Major trouble on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get the feeling you forgot about Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me a minute, and then come over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Dad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Elisabeth…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[imitating her dad's voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't you home? You have homework!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you understand? Hurry on home!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… But… Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's finally out of my hair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know the way back. Ciao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bike engine]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gong striking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser bullets swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser bullets swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts and shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wheels grinding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantula groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oops!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, come on. My front paws</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't just for running, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser bullets swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why isn't the elevator working?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I shut it off because of the three goons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are they gone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What? There's nobody up here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sign of XANA trouble in town?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll switch the elevator on right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in a sec!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bikes engines]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser bullets swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I just hit a pedestrian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No time for jokes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's in a big jam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, if you get hit one more time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be in the doghouse for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to see you down here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The program almost finishes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Yumi? Wasn't she my backup?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Up there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd barks and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Quit spinning will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William pants and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Yumi is not answering.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Something is not right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bike grinding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bikers scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bikers and Yumi grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd, I've reconstructed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your separate DNA sequences.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to load it into the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three seconds, and you're back to normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to devirtualize yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About time! My paws are really killing me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And these guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't let sleeping dogs lie!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't miss me guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to be my old self again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, Odd, get out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Any more surprises on the way?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry, I didn't delete</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the old DNA from the memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I did, it would have bugged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, we'll be back online right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I sure hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are the others doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could be better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No news of Yumi and Aelita's alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fighting William and his pals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you want me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to hang out here scratching fleas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, I'm not done yet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too dangerous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you're about as obedient as Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bikers pant and groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[biker groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd pants and shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sparks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energetic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd barks and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, the DNA data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't finished yet, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanners hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's Odd's little diggedy dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a good boy! Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans and bikers grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bikers moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A bit shaken, but not stirred.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, all's well with Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Kiwi good too? That's great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time to celebrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotta move those bikers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before they wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with that dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Has he got rabies, or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not worth taking any chances.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's roll!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engines starting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi. Sleep well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, I didn't sleep a wink!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd was so glad to see Kiwi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they played all night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With Kiwi's talent and my idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of having him foam at the mouth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with toothpaste, you gotta admit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're a great team.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With us on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA won't stand a chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wouldn't try that again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, do you always carry toothpaste?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you never know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you'll run into a pretty girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His feet smell awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine him with bad breath as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I know you're the reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's all messed up, I'll prove it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't bother, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I broke up with him today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be surprised if he stays messed up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a long time. He took it hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You kidding me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's still a little of Kiwi in me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've still got a tail?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, his sense of smell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We are having beef stew</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Brussels sprouts for lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I can smell it from here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>