<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>IS ANYBODY OUT THERE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] "A horrible tragedy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>may explain the rumor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that there's a ghost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the heart of Kadic Academy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Back in 1905,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while the building was under construction,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of the workers, Leon Courbet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is said to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>been buried alive in the foundations…"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"…in the boiler room, to be precise!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now do you believe me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Bridgette] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Emily: 77! Good work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeanne: 87… Very good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth! A quadrilateral is not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a quadrant you do later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ten.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! I deducted two points for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the ketchup stain on your diagram: 98!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! There's some good but not enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make up for what's bad: 58.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb: 93. Excellent! Not as good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as Jeremy, but excellent nevertheless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Bridgette] Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"Meet me in the boiler room at midnight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] May I remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that in the evening,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>girls and boys are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>prohibited from straying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from their respective floors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For any of you who might be thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of trying to pull anything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>remember that the floors are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>different from each other</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that they are either upstairs from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or downstairs from the one above.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Girls are upstairs and boys, downstairs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Comings and goings</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from upstairs to downstairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and from downstairs to upstairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-are strictly forbidden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I ever catch anyone going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from downstairs upstairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or anyone going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from upstairs to downstairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he or she is really going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to regret it stairs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've been warned. Dismissed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Password?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You didn't give me one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Correct! Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't this a bit square for you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] It's a not a square.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a "tempagram"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Pentagram!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Whatever…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to this, and my psychic powers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to conjure up the spirit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of that poor Leon Courbet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure if we communicate with him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he can finally rest in peace!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to see this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, now stand in the pentagram with me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will bring together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our Ping and Pong energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And summon up the dead man's ghost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you forgot the paddles!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! And now, let the ceremony begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De profundis tenebrae!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I summon you, Leon Courbet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Leon, I'm listening…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't step out of the pentagram, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It protects us! Um… Leon Courbet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darn it, he's gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He doesn't want to speak to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Behind you, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go, quick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It was horrible, Jim. I swear it's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] No, let me tell you. I mean…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, you two, calm down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The ghost of Leon Courbet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>came after us in the boiler room, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If anyone is after you two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's a gym teacher in a track suit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>holding a red pen which he's gonna use</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give you four hours of detention!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We'd better go upstairs fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, you'd better go back to your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! Don't leave me all by myself, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shh… Alright. Come in then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aw!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait for me here. I'll be back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I dreaming or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm scared, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind if I sit near you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh! It's just a nightmare</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and soon I'm gonna wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think that XANA has launched an attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Laptop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We'll know in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… There are no activated towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks we've got a real ghost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on our hands then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone around here is gonna be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in real trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Leon's ghost came out of the boiler</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he was so ugly that even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas and Herb started screaming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah! Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You OK, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans] Yeah, yeah, I'm alright.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What's that noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's getting closer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gaps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You saw right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The monster depixelized when I hit it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gotta be one of XANA's!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So why didn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Super-scan pick it up then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew. We'd better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>head for the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers in fear and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi whimpers in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams, whimpers and cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's me! There's a big emergency!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Meet us at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi through phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathing heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, this is not time to hang around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry! It's coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What took you so long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA's attacking us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the Superscan didn't detect anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you believe in ghosts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wrong answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, that's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's managed to corrupt the Superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's an activated tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it can't detect it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, so what do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Aelita, get to Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as quickly as you can,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and try to fix the Superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich, in the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can check out the other Sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With a little luck, you'll be able to spot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Negative!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The spectre will strike back soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm staying with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'll launch the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles] Nice to see you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without your pajamas on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice of you to notice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm gonna need a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Can you bring up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Transporter, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] The countdown has started.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, you only have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>three minutes to find the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What do we do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] The desert looks normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll move on to another Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants] Can't shake him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] There's no point running.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll catch us every time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Huh, you've got a better idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too good to be true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, how much time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do we have left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] This is getting creepy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, that's all we needed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darn it, still no activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans] That must be jinxed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait. I have an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alright, I kind of get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shouldn't something be happening here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's still time to get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I would like a little help</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Where there's smoke…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Yumi. You can make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we didn't get the key,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[spectre roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy and Ulrich screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, man, he was a tough one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others probably need us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I've found the tower. Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tarantula roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tarantula roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keeps groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic, I'll get you out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like the look of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is all alone in the Arena.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[pants in fear] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How does this thing work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Fritz Ungelbert has done it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His third straight title.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a champ. It's amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! He even has TV on his computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? No, it's not Jeremy. It's Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, type in the code: "Scipio." Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah… I'd love to, but… how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Third window on the second screen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] S-C-I-P-I-O. There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I've spotted the activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the North-West part of the Ice Sector!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I'll go, but… where is Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hmm… No idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go look for them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tarantulas roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa! Not feeling so cocky now, are we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You OK, guys? Say something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Something."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, no stealing my jokes, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since we didn't fix the Superscanner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to return in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, let the ceremony begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De profundis tenebrae!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>De profundis tenebrae!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De profundis tenebrae.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I summon you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leon Courbet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spooky voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Who dares call my name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spooky voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Beat it, Miss Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You don't know who you're dealing with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spooky voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scram!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb and Nicolas scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You can come out now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think she's gonna try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to wake the dead again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spooky music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spooky roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>