<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko will be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>LOG BOOK</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich, what are you looking for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm hungry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... you go have breakfast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something I have to find.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] Eight slices of toast</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and three bananas! Not bad, huh? Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you skipping gym class again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yep! It gives me time to work on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's materialization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong? Afraid the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wall's gonna crumble?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha! Very funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can we talk for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hi Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hello!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, look over there, it's Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But... What's he doing with Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hey Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, that's blackmail!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why do you expect me to give into that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First of all, because it's hard to say no</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a pretty girl like me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and second of all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not going to give you any choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] Come on, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[history teacher]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the seventeenth century,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all European states were governed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by either a king or a prince.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They ruled over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mainly peasant populations...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's going on with them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm seeing things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Sissi, that's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] On the brighter side,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>check out how jealous Herb is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[history teacher] Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you listening to me, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have some important things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk about, Sissi. C'mon! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you mind explaining?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, but it's really important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, here goes. I'm in a...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in a jam, big time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For years I've...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been keeping a diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Sissi found it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and now she's blackmailing me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to go out with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If she thinks she'll win me over that way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In this diary of yours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you talk about XANA or Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah. And if I don't do what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi says, she's gonna tell everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't worry, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>While you're all at the pool,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and I'll look around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll find your diary, you'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] The answer is no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the last time, I did not have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a nose job, so stop asking, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Cut it out, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave her alone, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nothing. I'll explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take a look, Odd! Not bad, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This bus is the latest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in modern technology.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's electricity driven,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so it's non-polluting but powerful too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Electric and powerful too, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you this crate goes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about as fast as a snail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[driver] What the... huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Come on, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All aboard now! Go sit down, kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. What's the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sit back down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stay there till we get to the pool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bus engine starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh... Sissi is blackmailing him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. Incredible, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What matters now, though, is to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's diary before she starts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>blabbing about Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go through her room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll call you if I need any help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Good luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Jeremy here, Aelita! Do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid whooshes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm here, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was waiting for you to call.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was studying your world a little more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are so many strange things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to discover.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what's up? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something strange? What bus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car honks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't this nice and cozy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're zipping along at two miles an hour!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[driver] I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got it floored,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it just refuses to move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll launch a scan on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call you if I find something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, got you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo! Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is not Ulrich's handwriting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, wow! It's Sissi's!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm tired of his acting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if I don't even exist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't stand watching him pay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so much attention to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So while he was in the lunchroom,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I went looking around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just wanted a picture of him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I found much better than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now he can't possibly turn me down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what I'm doing isn't very nice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's the only way I can get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>him to stop ignoring me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of all the nasty tricks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, did you find Ulrich's diary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] No, but guess what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found Sissi's. You were right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She knows about Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She doesn't really understand what it is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-but she's ready to use what she knows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, you've gotta find Ulrich's diary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before they come back from the pool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I know how to get hold of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bike bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what if I ask my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we can go to a movie tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That'd be cool, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Eh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? I'm being nice to you right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you keep ignoring me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it just might not last! You hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] A little friendly advice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pay attention to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or the whole school's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gonna read your diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay, you don't have to threaten me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know exactly what I'm risking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? You really think so, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cell phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi. What do you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, uh... I wanted to tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how much I like your style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[imitating Sissi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I ran into that dipstick Jim today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What an idiot he looks like in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that sweaty gym suit of his!</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay! What do you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me where you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's diary hidden,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and hurry up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or all your nasty little secrets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be on page one of the school paper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay! If you go into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the girl's bathroom,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's in the third stall,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on top of the water tank. You got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll go and check.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait! What about my diary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone disconnects]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, you see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's good to have real friends, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about time. I thought that guy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would never get off your back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you know what's good for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shut up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[professor]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what are you doing there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing, sir. I felt sick,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm fine now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, Odd and Ulrich were right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is at it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The pulsations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are getting stronger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita, the activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the desert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[driver] What's going on now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is weird!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[people screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Get back to your seats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not allowed to get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on with this bus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That, kid, I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I know is it's out of control!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it seemed to be working okay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before you recharged the batteries, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, everything was just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But now, I can't...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what's happening, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has taken complete control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the bus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, gimme a sec.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I wonder what XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to do. Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>At the corner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Washington Street and Franklin Avenue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll call you back soon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as I can localize you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in for a rough ride.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's gonna need a hand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Lyoko. We've gotta go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then you go. I'll stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take off your backpacks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and use them as airbags.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[horn honking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, things are getting tough here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Come straight to the factory after class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now hurry up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get your seat belts fastened!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on kid, take it easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just calm down, huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Does the little girl need any help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The little girl can take care of herself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[horn honking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've just gone through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Constellation intersection. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't worry, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got you spotted now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I still don't understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA is trying to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can see it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a virtual image</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay where you are. Yumi is on her way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wheels spinning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, in the scan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The situation is getting worse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rapid beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electric zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yumi! Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[up-tempo fantasy music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, XANA is launching the bus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the petro-chemical complex!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way to stop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this infernal thing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have any other choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to jump!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now look what you have done, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[driver] By cutting the cables,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you blocked the door!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim. Jeremy thinks we're headed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>straight for the petro-chemical plant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mind telling me how he knows that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um... we'll tell you that later,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but for now you just have to trust him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] He can help us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs] Okay, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uhh... Ulrich...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm really sorry about your diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was wrong to take it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Please forgive me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I help in any way?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Here, take this. You can be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the go between for Jeremy and me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower is real close now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] No wait. This is too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Coming all this way without seeing even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one monster, there's gotta be a trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] A sandstorm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It's a tornado.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a problem here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make that two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a monster behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind blowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calling all cars. All cars I said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calling all cars.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In ten seconds, the bus should bear left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He says we're gonna turn left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everybody over here with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[people screaming, grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe we should jump off the bus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Might just be the best idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, at least we won't go crashing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the petrochemical plant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At that speed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no way we could survive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gimme that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how are things going back at Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and Yumi are almost at the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except that they're caught</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a sandstorm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll wait a little longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, be careful at the ridge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Aelita falls into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the digital sea, she'll be lost forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi, be careful in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's a mega tank!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get up! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] XANA set a trap for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vocalizing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good work, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Yumi breathing heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, hurry to the scan!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You'll be reaching the complex</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in ten minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Careful,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna turn left again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everyone to the right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hide Aelita, and don't move until Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is there with you. Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring, powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh, powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electric zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Hey, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to our world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go to work, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, we only have four minutes left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we get to the complex.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are things going on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, Aelita and Odd are handling it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Careful, there's a ridge!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I have an idea. Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Odd, you're out of your mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Aelita grunting, groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud thud in the distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistles relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up now, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you like it here, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing in distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! We're gonna crash!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's all over for us. It's too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing in distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing in the distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine slowing down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it was close, but we did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, are you ready to go back in time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping, whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water trickling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, I didn't read it. I swear, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you about it one day, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd really like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'd better go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't want to miss Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid footsteps fading]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Sissi, were you waiting for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looking for something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just passing by, so...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>