<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electronic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Now then, if you provoke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a collision between two neutrons,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what do you obtain?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who would like to answer? Anybody?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nobody?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Me, ma'am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all] Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shoes tapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Who is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you, the principal's daughter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should know the rule</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dealing with cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you remind us all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what that rule is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"All mobile phones have got to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>turned off before entering the classroom</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under penalty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of having them confiscated."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Hand it over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that goes for everyone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students protesting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] Quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Put all your cell phones</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my desk right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's sure gonna be happy about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell continues ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] [footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We had this weird problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This morning, everyone's cell phone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>started ringing...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] The teacher confiscated them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Us too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Crazy, huh? All those calls,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and no one at the other end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'll contact Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This could be XANA's doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta do something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Jeremy's is right and we can't stay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in contact, we're in a real jam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Hey you three</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm organizing a meeting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've got to give us our mobiles back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, are you with us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You bet we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you really mean it, we'll see you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the auditorium right after lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right. We've gotta see what's up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Connection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fast music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, hello Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have you noticed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything strange on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Should I have?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'd better launch a scan to check.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, and I'll see if I can pick</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up any of XANA's pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good, but be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screen beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[keys clacking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screen beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[peaceful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna take back your cell phone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's called stealing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, it's not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Taking back what belongs to you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not what I would call stealing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The students were warned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not going to return their phones</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that quickly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the school's antenna.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, even with new phones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they won't be able to use them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you handle that, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Hmm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have no choice, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Charles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Ulrich, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knob rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door squeaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] The coast is clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tinkering sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tinkering sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining hard]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Now, let's see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Oh, hello, Mr. Leever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Leever] Hello, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pen rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rattles and stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shoes scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[receding footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens and shuts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jubilantly] Mission accomplished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sonar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope that nobody finds out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we're worried over nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, the scan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hasn't found an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I haven't seen anything either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>False alarm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense, pulsating music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Why would XANA be interested</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in mobile phones, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I'm hoping to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out by checking out the school's antenna.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm off to the meeting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promised Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, who let you guys up here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trying to stop me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from disconnecting the antenna?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Us? No, we were just passing by.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim screaming loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boys straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll take him to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll try to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out what XANA's done to the antenna.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey Jim, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] He smells like roast chicken, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jim. Hey Jim. Yoo hoo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dorothy] Odd, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman] Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What happened to him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, you know how Jim is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's a regular live wire. So, I mean...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bizarre beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The main television antenna?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct conversation]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Miss Yumi is gracing us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with her presence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where were you when we wrote the petition?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just what is going on in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, Dad... I mean...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, what's going on here is this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] You see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We all signed a petition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You have to give us back our cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Oh really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, let me remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that in this establishment,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the students do not make the rules!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Secondly, Miss Hertz has just learned</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that someone forced her locker open</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get back his cell phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct mutterings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's only normal, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can anyone live</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without their cell phone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but this theft is another reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for not returning them to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] We're going to investigate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who had the nerve to steal back his own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I say that we don't set foot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the classroom without our mobiles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct conversation]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You see these waves?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's using the school antenna unit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to try to plug</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the main television dish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sonar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's why all the phones rang?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It jams the frequencies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA manages to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>take control of the dish,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll have direct access to the satellites</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that are now orbiting the Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he'll be able to guide</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a military satellite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sonar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, but for what reason?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In peace time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these satellites are used for spying,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if XANA reprograms one, who knows?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything can happen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy is right. This is serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You better believe it, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The scan has detected a tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, XANA has activated a tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the polar region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll go through the tunnel in the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, you stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[military drum beats]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"No more phones, no more school." Perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here in case XANA's got plans</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, are you with us or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs sheepishly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ever heard of solidarity?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't worry, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm with you a hundred percent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] "No more phones, no more school."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] No more phones...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slow lugging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[paws shuffling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, what are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a dog, he's stubborn as a mule!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, now that you're here, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[racy music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blades rolling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muffled sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling and swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wheels rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita's on her way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the polar region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I made it to the ice floe,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't see any activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Wait there for Ulrich and Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and watch out for XANA's monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well are you ready? Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer-Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer-Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner-Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[key clacks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring and swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Odd, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There she is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Good news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's still not in control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the TV dish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That gives us a little time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to find out which satellite</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA might want to get his hands on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it won't be easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keys clacking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students chanting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more phones, no more school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more phones, no more school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now let's try the access code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Access code accepted." Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Bingo! Let's see now...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] "U four six six."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Military satellite armed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a highly destructive laser beam."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Where can that tower be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>One thing at a time, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First of all, I figured it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I know what XANA's after.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wants to gain control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a highly accurate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destructive satellite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he does,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he can destroy whatever he wants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] The factory's safe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA wouldn't fire at himself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Right. That'll give us the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take care of things on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sounds good, but if XANA decides</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy the school...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Remember, Yumi's there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that's for sure what he's gonna do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to warn her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without a mobile?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Wiki woofs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Wiki whimpers and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students] No more phones, no more school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No more phones, no more school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students] No more phones...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I demand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you stop this absurd strike now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what is going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[stammers] Well, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is inadmissible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] To my office immediately!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to save her from the dictator!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Free Yumi! Liberty for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Free Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>According to the holomap,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower is just across the bridge,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's probably guarded by those...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] By the waspsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Thanks, we've noticed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Remember,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the poison they're carrying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will kill your life points, so watch out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are they waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They must just want to hold you there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until XANA's able to control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the satellite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to get past them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No Aelita, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, don't take any chances.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave that to Odd and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Yumi, I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A strike, a dog...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You're usually</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so sensible too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, will you listen to me?!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm sorry, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have to leave right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You too, as a matter of fact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone around here has to leave.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One of you has to make the sacrifice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I'll attract their attention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you can get through. Here I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that! [grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's nuts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between the poison and the arrows,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've already lost 70 life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] You said, no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, you horrible beast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You've only got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>20 life points left, Odd. I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no! XANA's taken over the satellite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He let you go, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I escaped when he wasn't looking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because our demands are more important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than anything for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, we should increase the strength</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of our movement and protest in town.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone into town.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to get other schools</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on our side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go. "Freedom for all our schools."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] No more phones, no more school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[satellite beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Wow, what an incredible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>technological masterpiece!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Parameters locked in place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Targets localized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The school's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the satellite's line of fire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[constant beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] High school students,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>middle school students.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All for one and one for all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, come on, faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all] No more school...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You will not leave the grounds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You have no right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was supposed to be here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ten life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heaves] Ulrich, it's game over for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! Ulrich, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the waspsters are after you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The holomap doesn't lie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's got to be somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triplicate. Go on. don't worry about me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting and straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder how accurate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this satellite really is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no, I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi is in danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The laser's aimed right at her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You're making a terrible mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I beg of you, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've all got to get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have had enough, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm suspending you for a month.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and your dog</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are to leave this campus now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for the rest of you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back to your classrooms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This strike is over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Sir, it's a question</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of life and death!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let us all leave! Please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, aren't you being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little dramatic, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To the factory! Hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's you the satellite's after!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clashes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling and fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Laser flight path locked</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Satellite ready to fire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's gonna fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Where is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! We have to reach the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the only place that's safe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What in the world is happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get out of here now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, have you found it yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time's running out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm doing my best,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but nothing yet. It's pretty well hidden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Aelita, answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm here Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Ulrich's out cold,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I still haven't found the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you found the tower yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I have.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, I found it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To the boiler room. Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's now or never. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser swishes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[joyful guitar music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Invitations to a party?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Official school policy reminder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to all students:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All mobile phones not turned off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before entering the classroom</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be immediately confiscated."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Talk about teacher's pets!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I'd like to see someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>try to confiscate my mobile!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] You're so brave, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>