<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A LACK OF GOOD WILL</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's a question of reflexes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta trust your instincts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything you can do I can do better, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wanna bet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, watch and weep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like I told you, my Odd-like sixth sense</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>defies all limitation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, show off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now admire my Aelita-like sixth sense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi wails]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who did that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You win, hands down. Even at the top</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my form, I could never match that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Haven't you heard that forks aren't meant</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to play with but to eat with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] You hear me, Dunbar?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The glass is empty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but that is the very last straw!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanna play at being an idiot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, two can play at that game!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's clone's not supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to act like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't matter if he gets punished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not even human.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's just it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a polymorphic specter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>driven by a basic non-evolutionary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>behavior program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you say that in words?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's clone shouldn't be capable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of taking any personal initiatives,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like trying to imitate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's stupid stunts, for example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then how do you explain it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't explain it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why I'm worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Unless the…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yesterday, I installed an upgrade</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for his software,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something to improve</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his artificial intelligence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, something that would</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>make him appear less stupid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. You think that imitating Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>makes him look less stupid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, we're gonna have to play it by ear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I may have to delete the upgrade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we need is for William Junior</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to start making waves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I did improve the Superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to the data you collected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during your last jaunt on the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was able to set things up so that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it can now find other Replikas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You mean you think there are more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of them out there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For sure. In fact, I've already managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to localize a second one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A second one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many Replikas do you think there are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I suppose if we destroy them all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll finally be rid of XANA for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic! I love it when you talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that. When do we start?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] I feel bad for William's clone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's my fault</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he's in trouble with GI Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No reason to feel bad, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like Odd said,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's totally artificial.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like I was not all that long ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's not the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An artificial clone has no feelings,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least… not for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An artificial clone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So William isn't really William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It means we've got a scoop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have any more paper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, that's enough for now, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've learned a lesson, today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll use your fork for eating,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not for catapulting your glass</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into your neighbor's mashed potatoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, using a glass is not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only dumb, it's dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A ball of bread is much more discreet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take it from someone who knows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A ball of bread? Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… No. Forget that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Definitely not with a ball of bread.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you do, I'll make you write</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I must never play with food."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to catapult it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into my mouth with my glass.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… I mean into my mouth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my mashed potatoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Anyway, you get the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get the picture? Where is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to go? Okay, energize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Replika, here I come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, the best, the greatest,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the mean lean XANA wrecking machine!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lean sounds right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know about the rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget who saved you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Digital Sea last time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And who took out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>those two Megatanks with talent and style?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was Odd. Odd the magnificent. Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like that, Odd the Magnificent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I got devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to Odd the Lame-o.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if it hadn't been for me, you would…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't we being sensitive today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, if you wanna be a hero,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can give you lessons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But not everyone has the right stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The main thing is staying humble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's about all boys can talk about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I'm the greatest at this,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"You can't beat me at that."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich isn't humble enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to admit that he can't even hold a candle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to me, even though he knows I'm better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ha, ha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny. Okay, Odd the Magnificent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's check out the results</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the end of the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, cut the hot air</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and let me concentrate, okay guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stabilizers…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Online and check.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Primary axis… Clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser generators… Online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holoweb system online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm sending you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Replika's coordinate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Gotcha, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>High speed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>acceleration in three seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three, two, one…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William! We're doing a story on school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>punishment for the Kadic News.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think Jim throws</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his weight around too much?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He weighs 240 pounds,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is too heavy for his height.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not what I meant. I meant that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he can be a real windbag sometimes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You get my drift now, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry but I can't even feel a breeze.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh. Are you an idiot or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a little hard to explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Replika straight ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, you found it within a micro bit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The improvements on the Superscan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seem to be effective.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Digital Key operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your localization program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>works like a charm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At this rate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll be able to wipe XANA in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, it was no big deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I had to do was reconfigure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the course of the alternate algorithm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>based on the data that you recovered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the first Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sounds simple to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's Greek to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one sector, the desert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower at eleven o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I see it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Dock the Skid while I activate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower for our own use,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-so we can carry out the teleportation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's as good as done</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Docking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not gonna get anything out of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's been like a vegetable for months now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave this to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna bluff him out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a second William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to tell you… How much you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hurt me by not answering my letter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I know that usually guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>make the first move,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and since I decided to tell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you how I felt--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wrote him a love letter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without telling me that you did?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tamiya, I told you I was gonna bluff him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] I'm really sorry, Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't me who got your letter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must've been William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad Ulrich's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>been teleported already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He won't be able to admire the exploits</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Odd the Magnificent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and weep with jealousy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm yes… Even though last time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he did save your neck, didn't he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come on. Don't you start now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Save your strength for XANA and his pals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just spotted Aelita and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're in New Mexico right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm… Looks something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a military base.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With no one here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it shouldn't be too hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You're right, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is a military base,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's obviously been abandoned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I located a plan of it on the Internet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so… I can guide you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA? Who is this XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't know. Do you know him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it was you who just told us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA had captured William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So who are you then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then I guess there must be two Williams.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! There's just one, and that's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The other one is a prisoner of XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the other William's a prisoner,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we should call the police, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Certainly not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and the Lyoko warriors are doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all they can to set him free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Loco" warriors? Who are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, if I'm gonna forgive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the other William about the letter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna need some proof</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're not making all of this up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some proof?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have any,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can ask Jeremy to show you some,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the computer lab at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I think I found it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In front of you, on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the foot of a hangar,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's an elevator that'll take you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>to the underground part of the base.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Place is really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet we're in Area 51.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The base at Roswell?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The one with all those aliens?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it wasn't the same at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a second, how do you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what Area 51 looks like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't. I was just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here comes the welcoming committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On your mark… Ready…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, he didn't say "go" yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, not very polite little beasts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They didn't even introduce themselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, we could use a couple of taxis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come I've got an activated scanner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did anyone just get devirtualized?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why leave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when it's just getting interesting?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It wasn't me either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it wasn't us, who was it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it sure isn't someone we wanna meet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-William's in the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sure looks like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll handle this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Were you expecting company?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you stock up on potato chips,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>soda, magazines for him to read?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not coming up here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's going down… To the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He must have come to destroy it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, no! Here comes trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is this place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy? Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get back to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, are you there? Can you hear us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no need to yell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's probably trying to figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to keep William busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, you and I are stuck here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tell you we've gotta go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Jeremy hasn't teleported</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Aelita yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't do it for him from here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can't join them out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to protect</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Skid at all cost. So we wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There must be something we can do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There is. Defend our position, look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good. Thanks to our friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at least we won't be bored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had no idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were into computers, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Check it out! It's like a scene</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Executioner 2</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it smells like Odd's feet in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What worries me most is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've lost contact with Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get back to the Skid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then return to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Abort the mission?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look around you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's putting something really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>serious together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like this anymore than you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Jeremy must need our help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well anyway,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we do decide to abort,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's only one way for us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get back to the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathing heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, you are going to witness the total</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>destruction of the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your gang of little friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, do you have any proof</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you could lend me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get your hands off Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi girls. What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Milly, I want to go home!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which one of them is the real William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's very simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The real one is the bad guy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Williams grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, the two of you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go back to the computer lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and tell the others</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that they gotta back here, and fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you say the others?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right. I'm out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantulas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! My overboard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another one bites the dust.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't ever do that without telling me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you didn't mess up the paint job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantulas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both keep grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Hello! Anyone out there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's with that voice of yours?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You catch cold?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Huh… It's… It's Tamiya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tamiya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantula growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Tamiya,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you doing at the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantula growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's one heck of a surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy told me to tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to come back right away, huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-W</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>hoever you are…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] We're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The fun's over. We're going home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's your lucky day, Tarantula.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hasta la vista!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you hear that? If Tamiya's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the factory, we've got a big problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-On three. One, two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich and Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>might have been teleported.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yoo-hoo, anybody home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Those Tarantulas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stick to you like glue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Williams grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] That ought to hold you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William bad guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good riddance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, not at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's going up to the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can still mess with the programming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get rid of the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The trap door. Go on, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to stop him before he starts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doing some real harm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Which one are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The good guy or the bad guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The good guy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, we're onboard the Skid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ready to take off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, make it fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shooting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Coming…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Embarking… Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, everyone's onboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next stop: Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the welcome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you're the bad guy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if you think you're gonna wreck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything, you'll have to deal with me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have to deal with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I do have to wreck everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's the Hub.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready for high speed acceleration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever you want, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're nothing. Just an insignificant</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bunch of digital dust.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me that's normal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that everything's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not normal. The cooling chamber…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's overheating and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Supercomputer is gonna reach</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a combustible critical mass!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The double failed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to stop William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you see what I see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it's too quiet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Retro brakes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… I really didn't feel like fishing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bombs away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, keep to your right, Sunday driver!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got one stuck to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's worse than forgetting a candy bar</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in your jeans during a heat wave!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just another groupie,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>crazy about Odd the Magnificent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Torpedo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, higher up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can get him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only because it's you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Over here, cutie-pie…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, that takes care of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't you tired of me saving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you all the time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everyone into the Skid ASAP.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've already lost a lot of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're starting the docking procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's still not answering.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there aren't a whole lot of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ways to devirtualize ourselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Again, oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The cavalry is finally here…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only too late, as usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? We'll see about that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful, Milly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He disintegrated the other William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just by pushing a button!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm… What did you do to my scanner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time for small talk!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're all in the scanner room now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's six against one, so just give up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Boo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The Loco Warriors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on, run away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go back where you came from!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William set up a delayed virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's going back to the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he managed to cut the cooling system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I managed to stop the process in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How long have you been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fighting against XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We began about two years ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And does this happen a lot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Are you kidding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It happens all the time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We fight XANA almost every day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This has gotta be the best scoop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've ever had!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on a sec.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me tell you one last secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great, let's hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The reason you're not gonna remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any of all this is:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I know what you're thinking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but even if it's really tempting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't do it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A wise decision, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially if William's clone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is into imitating your stunts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We sure don't want to draw</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any attention to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And in the meantime, I'll try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to create a new upgrading program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure you want to erase</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the old one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The replica did fight for you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against the real William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I know, but… Actually,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I created it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I used some pre-existing programs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that were already in the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'd been created by Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did it to speed things up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think they might have been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some of the same ones</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that developed the personality</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of huh… XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, nice one, Frankenstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better find William ASAP or we'll have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a "Xanastein" Junior on our hands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Or much worse, a human being.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That could never happen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without that upgrade, William's clone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will never be more than a program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>