<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>FALSE START</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me what the good news is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're waiting for you here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what those kids are hiding,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I intend to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me and my friends... we do have a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your paranoia is beginning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get on my nerves!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm gonna have to let you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, Jim, if you help me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll tell the principal everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Shake on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready for the big jump, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita, I'm launching the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for your materialization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Code Earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Gilles] Come on, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Relax, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just history class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd feel a lot better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if it were a class in computers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know anything about history.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're here to learn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it were a computer class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you could be the teacher.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Gilles] Take your seats so we can begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Just who does that new girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>think she is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All she cares about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is having boys around her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I think she looks worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Obviously, Nicolas, you don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the first thing about girls! Ha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Acting frail and helpless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will work every time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boys love that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the best way to attract them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have a new student in our class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll let her introduce herself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammering] My...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's her name. And she's my cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's very shy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Gilles] Well, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let me welcome you to Kadic Junior High.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We all hope that you're going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to like it here very much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Y'see, everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was no reason to worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums] I guess not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides I really like history.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you fight a lot here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are wars all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys, how's our new earthling doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'm fine. I'm trying to adapt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to so many new sensations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like the air that you breathe here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the colors and the smells...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about time we deactivated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the super computer, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't wait for XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to send us an invitation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And who feels like going back to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now that Aelita's here with us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll think this is silly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it scares me a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko, after all was my home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not really sure what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>effect destroying it might have for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd hum]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing to worry about. I'm sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hi, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Did you have a good sleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping] Oh, yeah, great! And I really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>appreciate everything you've done for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I was getting a little bored,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to admit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] How'd you like to watch us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>deactivate XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thinking] Ah, I wouldn't miss that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't forgotten</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your promise, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I haven't Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as XANA's deactivated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell everything to the principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you'll get your job back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait 'til all this is settled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I honestly never imagined</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I would miss being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your P.E. teacher so much!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eh, from now on, call me "Jimbo."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, so are you ready to go, Jimbo?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here we are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] If you wanna wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a day or two...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, the sooner the better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I think you should have the honor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'd rather you did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] XANA, you gave us a lot of grief,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but thanks to you, we met Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And good-by, and good riddance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Put the power back on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's not well! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What's wrong with her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Let's hope XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't rear his ugly head!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her pulse seems back to normal again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know... what happened, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You fainted, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a little bit like sleeping.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A really deep sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I like the way it felt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Maybe you did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you passed out, and that's not normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I modified</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the scanner's program while you slept.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you mind if I examine you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smirks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Launching program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Data recovery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Don't tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you really understand all this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's not very complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We're ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to begin the analysis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fine, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can come back, now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Let's try to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what the trouble is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's just what I was afraid of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>infected me with a virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have done it during the transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was a sudden drop in the voltage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a very short time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I remember that because I had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a strange feeling at that moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For a few seconds, I felt XANA's presence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if he was trying to hold me back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's probably the reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why you fainted a while ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA implanted a virus inside you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because he wanted you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be linked to him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if we kill XANA...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Then I get destroyed as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah... is there anything we can do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, try to find an anti-virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it could take a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up an analysis program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The computer will work autonomously on it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until tomorrow morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take you back to Yumi's.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's kinda late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smirks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What a strange sensation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You shivered, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a reaction you get on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>account of the cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like the feeling of being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little chilly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sounds and the smells</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are all different at night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah, it's quiet and peaceful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the plants breathe differently.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here... smell this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffs and hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It's wonderful to be alive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's thanks to you that I'm here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I... I... Didn't do it alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita smiles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that? A scanner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not exactly. Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[camera flash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy laughs loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, your castle awaits you princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for walking me back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In spite of the virus, I still had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the most wonderful night of my life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] See you tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[inhales and exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's... wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Do you have any idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to get rid of this miserable virus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No, not yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope the calculations my computer made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will help me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here come the girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How was your first night on earth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sleeping is really wonderful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She would've slept all day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I hadn't shaken her a little!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're just like me, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you'll see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sleeping in class isn't too bad either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat noise]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim surprised] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[math professor] Who can give us the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>definition of a pair of prime numbers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm? Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers] Well... a... a...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a pair of prime numbers is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>two numbers that are the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well... can one of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>give us a less harebrained answer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A pair of prime numbers occurs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when their highest common denominator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is one...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good, although...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] In a principal ring,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's equivalent to the fact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that their direct sum is equal to one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But of course, with a non-principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>factorial ring, that is not the case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[trombone music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is... according</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the theory of Bézout, you see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[math professor wonders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down children.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Get back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take cover!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's changed tactics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He sent one of his monsters to earth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the first time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How did he manage that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Who cares?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem is... how do you suggest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>getting rid of him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Like we always do. We fight them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You three head for Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and I will stay here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and defend the home front.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! That's crazy, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You know very well</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that if there's a victim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that going back in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't bring him back to life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi... Yes, we already know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta find weapons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll meet you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>outside of the math class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile turns off]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let's go guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Let's see how good you are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] A few more seconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the coast will be clear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What would you do without me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both pant]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Jeremy grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wow, Jim gave them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a good run for their money.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It looks like they've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>their sights set on us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electric saw]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's show 'em what we can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey, over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roachster groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah! Miserable monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll make you think twice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before you leave your world again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts] Hang on, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] I told you to call me "Jimbo,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>remember?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to transfer me to Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you forgotten XANA's virus, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA stops you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from deactivating the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or from returning to Earth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a risk we've got to take.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The priority is to stop XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know as well as I do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we have no choice, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think of all the other monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA could materialize.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, get into the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send you to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm deactivating the infected scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Nice going, kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've located the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's in the glacier region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's where I'm sending you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, where are Ulrich and Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At school, fighting monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm off. I'll be a lot more useful there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, it's like a Swiss army knife.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See ya later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's strange being virtualized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but you get used to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No air to breathe, no smells,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no warmth, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I miss the real world already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both pant]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roachster grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich, we're never gonna make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Banzai! Ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that, ya cockroach!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ya! Got one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say your prayers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something I've gotta admit, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad you caught us by surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My friends call me Jim... bo! Got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Squadron approaching</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at nine o'clock:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>three hornets.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here they come now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Watch out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They're coming back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Odd groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the tower! I'll hold them off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got 40 life points left, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is it, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you? Odd and Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We haven't finished</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the job here yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's only got forty life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Aelita's left all alone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's headed for disaster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two had better hightail it to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can handle these bugs on my own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I right to say that the sooner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you deactivate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the safer the world's gonna be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Hmm Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, what are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on now, and get the job done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It takes a lot more than a few ugly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>monsters to beat your friend, Jimbo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're losing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>too many life points, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich pant]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You gotta hang in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, it's about time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd's only got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>20 life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We're heading for the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry about Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can hold on a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twenty points is enough for him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, I'm waiting for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm out of arrows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye-bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Watch out, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[resonant voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] So, you still haven't had enough?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hey, you creeps, over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's taking cover in a cave,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can do better than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Now, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] There, that's more like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's all in the wrist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm a great Frisbee player.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] That was close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Aelita. You know we would</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>never let you go it alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, we can't let the school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go it alone either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Yeah, take that... and that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't just stand there, go on, run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave those kids alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Come on you bedbugs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>give me all you've got!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on! Is that all you've got?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What're you waiting for? C'mon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think I'm all washed up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita, we're restarting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the materialization program immediately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta wipe out XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before he launches another attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The virus is still in me. I can feel it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We've still gotta try it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you can be treated here on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No Jeremy, you know that as well as I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As long as this virus is inside of me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can't destroy XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without destroying me at the same time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We could materialize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for an hour or two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you can pay us a little visit, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the rest of the time, I'll have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stay here on Lyoko to fight XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until the day you find an anti-virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim! We forgot about him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[trombone music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So, you kids are at it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No, Jim, we were studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Studying, my eye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had enough of your lies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna stay right here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until you tell me everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, what is going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] You came by at the right time, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just about to find out exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what the children were up to again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Oh! Another one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your absurd stories</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about mysterious meetings</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and secret passages, eh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had about enough of this, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm going to have to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right, sir. We really were plotting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were! We were going to play</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little joke on Nicolas and Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas mutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, if Jim hadn't caught us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we would've been late for school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'll look the other way this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since you admitted what you'd done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, off to class, children. Go on now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you made up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one heck of a story, kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why did you get me off the hook?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's just that... you never know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe one day, you'll do the same for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we never get the time to thank you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for all you've done for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So thanks a lot, Jimbo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud kiss]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a hero,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a fantastic P.E. teacher, Jimbo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, well...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you oughta tell the principal that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now, go to class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a hero... Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>