<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>FALSE LEAD</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can't a guy sleep in peace around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry, it's Jean-Pierre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a ridiculous name for a Tamagotchi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't pay attention, little baby.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's pretty cool, uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's disappeared?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre's disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Maybe he needs someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give him a new name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stole my Jean-Pierre, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I want him back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you out of your mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want your dumb plastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if it wasn't you, it's been kidnapped.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope your piggy bank is full</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to pay the ransom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop it. Don't you understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll die of hunger without me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What're we gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I know. How about some breakfast?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Jean-Pierre,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're interested in non-enriched uranium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jean-Pierre isn't an old Tamagotchi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's only a few months old. He's fragile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you abandon a helpless baby?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he was just plastic, sure I would.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go to look for him, right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we better wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it. Wait for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For you to buy another one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get the picture now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought friends were always there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I was mistaken!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You left your little Tamasushi at home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you like soggy frozen waffles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>genetically modified?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why do you wanna know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'Cause I may stuff them down your throat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have gotten up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the long side of the bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the wrong side, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Zip it up right now, Herb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Wait! What is it you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't done anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got an affinity for bombers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially the long range kind,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a particular affection</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for anthrax and other degenerate stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I assure you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a respectable school principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-All right, we believe you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what's the meaning of this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And who are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We belong to a secret security division,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unknown even by the president.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even we have no idea who we really are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But then you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Keep still!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last night, a company's secret computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was hacked,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and sensitive and classified documents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were accessed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, unwittingly, the hacker left a trail</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>leading directly to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the trail led us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to one phone line in your school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whose phone is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opening]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] This is Jeremy Belpois' room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something I don't get.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's impossible to hack into the system</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>using this computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something that's not commonly available.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could he get his hands on it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who are his contacts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which terrorist cell is he working for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy Belpois will be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under our surveillance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Microphones, cameras. We'll watch him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll use him to break this group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But our Jeremy Belpois, a terrorist?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In any event, you have my personal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and total cooperation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I might be able to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never told you, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I worked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as a secret service agent once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, but I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Enough!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you wanna help, set up the equipment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then, we can take you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>off the suspect list.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, when do you recall seeing Jean-Pierre</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the last time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Again, he went to sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right next to the bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi would've growled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if anyone had come into the room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not if he recognized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who it was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's up guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jean-Pierre has disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The principal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, the Tamagotchi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, let's see if we can find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any clues in your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[male voice] Password?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Birdbrain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it. Come on in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim Morales reporting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Audio, video, all mics and cameras</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>discreetly hidden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get this show on the road.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lucky you weren't a TV cameraman.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I did work as a TV cameraman.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, camera three A!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What are they doing in Odds' room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at this time of day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why aren't they in the lunchroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, would you tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what a dog is doing in my school?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the first time I see him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet, you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking through machine]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where is the microphone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Under the bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice! Right next to a noisy dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're all leaving the room now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Camera two C. Dormitory hallway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought it was clever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to conceal the camera</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>behind that distinguisher, insignia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean inquisitioner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm getting more worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we don't find Jean-Pierre,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's the end of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you hear that? He said "Jean-Pierre,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as my name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes, we heard it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there anything you'd care to tell us…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But this is completely absurd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've nothing to do with this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, drop it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to turn things up a notch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, put a tracer on the suspect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, he'll never be out of our reach.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Still nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] What are you doing in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Out! On the double!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tap]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, is anything the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those darned mosquitoes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tracer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to lunch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while Jean-Pierre is dying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because he has nothing to eat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Life is tough, and he sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is blaming you for his misery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's on the attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm never gonna find Jean-Pierre!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't XANA take a lunch break?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, and we're not gonna take any either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calling Hen House.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The bird has flown the coop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I repeat: flown the coop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[agent] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What kind of gibberish is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mind talking normally?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Belpois and company are on the move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, stay on their tails.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're going into the sewers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here are your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is situated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>south southwest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Last one there is a rotten egg!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine speeding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's crazy. The tower isn't activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any explanation, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Seems like XANA's found a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to mess up the super scan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would he lure us to Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No idea, but I don't like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm bringing you back in right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[agent] Step away from that keyboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're under arrest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what have I done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you're gonna tell us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened to your pals?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Jean-Pierre?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, take him in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here with Morales</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see what I can find.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't just stand there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Find me those other kids, fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's wrong Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone else laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something's very wrong. Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire at me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you made fun of my Tamagotchi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's not enough to zap you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is no time for jokes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Anything for a good cause.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want you to explain to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what all this UFO equipment is doing here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry about this, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear to you, I've never hacked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any information in my life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a weirdo in the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, this is all XANA's doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bring everyone back home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone hang up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very interesting. Who's this XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did he recruited Jean-Pierre?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just trust me this one time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and let me go back to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta help my friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this? A video game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Morales reporting. I apprehended one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the underground room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but then he managed to escape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanna see for yourself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Seems to be real this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I don't wanna pry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'd like to know what you're doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want an answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to me! Let go of my arm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't, sparks are gonna fly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Aelita, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what's the matter? Where's Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No idea. There's a weirdo here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's possessed by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There must be an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>In which sector?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How should I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm awful at computers, remember?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to me, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to guide you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go to the mountain sector,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>25 degrees west and 72 degrees south.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry up, 'cause… Wait a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, did you hit "delete" or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but there's trouble down below.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, hit the "enter" key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The guy possessed by XANA is trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy the super computer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the scanners are off line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's plan is diabolical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the super computer is destroyed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko will vanish, along with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get the scanners on line, and bring us in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sounds good, but I'm no Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better deactivate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I deal with that creep downstairs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Roger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time for us to change sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Watch your life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the scanners off line,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be game over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Woohoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's what I call extreme!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Their disappearing act isn't very cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Have you ever heard about fair play?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I take it back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the boss now, uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Thanks, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. Seven years of bad luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Let's hope it works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have idea what this is used for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you say it was for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We didn't say anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, the super computer is badly damaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope it will work again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What will work again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Not again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lost Jean-Pierre again, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna find out who stole him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen up. Now we're gonna see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who Jean-Pierre's kidnapper was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're all a bunch of traitors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only one I can really trust is Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it was my idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! You too? But what do you all have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against my Jean-Pierre?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's for your own good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because you were almost hooked on him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Relax, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre is just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Believe me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he couldn't be in better hands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamagotchi beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>