<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA AWAKENS, PART TWO</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cutlery clattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey lovebirds, sleep well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's with the hairdo?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko style. It's pretty trendy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[imitates cat meowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting with pleasure]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurps loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You always eat that much?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I'm not that hungry today in fact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Has anyone seen Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was up all night in his room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>working on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after he put the computer back together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Man, that guy's a real Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unfortunately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're not like Odd or Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't be devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you lose all of your life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least now I know how to change sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and I also found out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what the towers are for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're portals between the real world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the virtual world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and when they're red,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means they're activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just about. And they may be the way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to materialize you on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable, huh? I can't wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell the others about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want us to go back to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get Maya into a red tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like I said, I'm sure that's the only way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring her into the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty wild, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Pretty dangerous, you mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could have all been wiped out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for good last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's right. We're better off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shutting down the super computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad for Maya, but still,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not like she's human.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But she's still</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sort of intelligent being.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's got emotions like we do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, I told you. He's madly in love</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a computer program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on guys, be cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just asking you to go there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one last time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't even make it past the monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll probably get ourselves blown away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a heartbeat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If only there were at least three of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Sissi's too scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? No, I'm not. I really do want to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with you guys to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but when cheerleading practice is over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So here's the scoop. As soon as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya is materialized into the real world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I give you my word</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'll shut down the super computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meanwhile, we got to keep this a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ditto.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I look like on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me too. With some luck, I won't be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the dumbest looking one in the group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't you coming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see my cheerleading routine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I've got something important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-to take care of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Back for another thrashing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ending on a bad note.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's good. I like a challenge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna get one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing heartbeats in distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeats]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, two, three, four.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is gonna blow their mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear me? Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true that at first,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought Sissi was a real babe,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the more that I get to know her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the more I realize she's a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can I put this tactfully?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A turkey?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] "A cheerleader cheers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so her team won't lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got short skirts and sparkly shoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're just so gorgeous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how can you choose?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no doubt, we've got clout,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>winning at Kadic is what it's all about!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bravo, well done! Encore, encore!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cheerleading is not about being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a boomerang juggling baboon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing heartbeats]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you been training for long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents think it's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, I'm Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You, you're Yuri, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] A baboon? Why not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a red tail macaque while he's at it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you two dumb dorks, were you planning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on following me around all day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're your biggest admirers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the whole school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We even started a fan club called,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Friends of Sissi."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! And about how many of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are in the club?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… two of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Then come back and talk to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when there's at least fifty of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meanwhile, if you don't stay away from me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my father's gonna find out that you two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>clowns tried to break into my room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's even more beautiful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she's angry, isn't she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A couple of days ago,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dug up a brand new program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the super computer called</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Return to the Past"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I just figured out how to activate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, Einstein, but could you give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>me a hand with my electrochemistry report?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Odd, are you planning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on calling me Einstein forever?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, what about my report?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, why don't you say that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that electrochemistry is a science</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that deals with the relationship between</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>electricity and chemistry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then, you say that electrochemistry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>involves opposing polar systems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>composed, at its two extremes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of electrically conductive material.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean all I have to do is say that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, no, of course not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to give examples.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…so Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim was taking her to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What'd she do, pull a muscle in her brain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to add two plus two?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] No man, she got electrocuted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you there? Answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Call it a tie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I got to go. My friends are gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>start wondering where I am. Same for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have any friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! What is that thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No time to explain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, we've gotta get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the one who brought Elisabeth here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She was in her room, and she was attacked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by this electricity monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-that jumped from a coat hanger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Would you try to be serious, Poliakoff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's going to get a shock in a moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was as if that electrical thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was alive. What is going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? Great, I really need you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi just got electrocuted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by some sort of giant…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Electric thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. How did you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That same electric thing attacked me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the gymnasium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is getting more and more dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and your super computer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All the more reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to materialize Maya ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and bring her to the red tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it works,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can shut the computer down tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll meet you in the sewer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Sorry Yumi, but I've gotta go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You seem to know what's going on here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What was this electrical thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that attacked us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what is this super computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I don't have time to explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have time for a third round then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're stubborn as a mule, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, and since I have no friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have lots of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, come on, I'll explain on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, who's that girl?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She was there when I was attacked,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she knows how to fight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-so I thought…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, okay, later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have to get to the factory. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't tell me you're scared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] So who's this Maya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going to be meeting her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in just a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go straight to the scanner room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get ready for the big plunge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Big plunge?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't have a bathing suit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, you won't be needing one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya? Can you hear me? Maya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm being chased by monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why did you leave the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we got there? Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I heard some strange pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to see what they were.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm sending you backup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, just try and hide somewhere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This story of yours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is pure science fiction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, except that it's for real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through headset]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't tell me you're scared?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm coming too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi. Scanner Odd. Scanner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich. Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bummer. I'm still a big purple cat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! That Japanese outfit is pretty sharp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not fair. I'm the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who looks like a nitwit on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind telling me where we are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] In a virtual world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, you'll get used to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya needs you. She's in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, my head. What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You'll be fine, my dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must have electrocuted yourself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your hairdryer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Electrocu-- Oh no, it wasn't me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was that super whatchamacallit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Jeremy's at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where is Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, try to stay calm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Ulrich is in great danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So are Odd and Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] There's an electrical monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the loose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to find him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure there is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a giant chemical teddy bear, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy, I'm not crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy Belpois found this gigantic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>computer inside the abandoned factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] They use it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go into this other world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where these monsters shoot lightning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi. Are you Maya? I'm Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to admit, you are a real cutie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's got taste.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time for flirting, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got work to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I don't have a weapon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A fan? That's all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try throwing it at them. You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow. I think I'll keep it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice work. Now bring Maya into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the red tower, so we can materialize her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come now, Sissi, this is ridiculous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We are not going down into the sewers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can tell that to the police</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you find Belpois and the others</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-burnt to a crisp!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans, grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I've got a good life size example</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for your electrochemistry report.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through headset]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah, and what's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A nice little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>electric monster. Where are you guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're coming up to the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry it up then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Things are about to start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>jumping over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it, guys, there are some more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>monsters coming your way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, crabs! Who's got the tartar sauce?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Go on, beat it crabs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tide is coming in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These guys are not only ugly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're tough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd just got devirtualized. Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wanna give it a try?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bull's eye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya, get back to the red tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Was it you who just did that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Run to the tower. Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's okay. Maya is--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What is all this about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait till I get my…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] What's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What were those flashes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You swore to us you wouldn't tell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I came here to save you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And what's this Chinese girl doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I am Japanese!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Maya? Is she here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, sorry Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it didn't work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She didn't materialize.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, that's enough, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I order you to shut this thing down now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then you can explain to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>exactly what this is about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I think we ought to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>alert the authorities right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me too, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's much too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you so, didn't I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're nothing but a rotten traitor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more than you are, Ulrich, darling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go, Belpois. Kill this thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>immediately, and follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm launching a new program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With a little luck, it'll work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What're we doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we were doing this yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't think…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Einstein, you're a genius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your return to the past… it works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that? What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't forgotten about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the super computer… and Lyoko…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my big purple cat costume, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You… you know all about Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But how come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like the return in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't quite work on him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, we're gonna fill you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would I not remember anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe because you were the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who didn't get digitalized on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, that could be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, tomorrow, I'm going to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>first thing and scan myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No Jeremy. We have to shut down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the super computer, and you know it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But Maya…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… When I went into the tower, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I remembered my name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… That's even better than Maya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what about bringing you in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promised.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me one more night to work it out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll find a way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll meet up in the computer lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tomorrow morning to see how you're doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been waiting for you for an hour!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never been stood up like this before!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's always a first time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now if you'll excuse me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm with my friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll make you pay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you hear that, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a bad feeling about this girl,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get the idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she's gonna give us a lot of grief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hi… Well, find anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes… XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA? What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A super dangerous program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a virus which can control electricity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that activates towers on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to gain access to your world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So, the red tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the electricity monster, the weird symbol</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the monsters on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of that was XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Only Aelita can counter it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by deactivating the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that it uses for attacks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what about materializing Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could do it, but I need some time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA can attack at any moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be reasonable, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better just shut the thing down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now that we know how to neutralize XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we just have to get Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can find a way to counter the attacks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while Einstein figures out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to bring Aelita back to Earth, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's risky, but I think we should.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, we are Lyoko warriors,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you really think you can do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They don't call me Einstein for nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a few weeks, I'll have it figured out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meanwhile,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's not forget about our pact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, relax,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we all know how to keep a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>