<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay. The connecting blocks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have been configured.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, we have to compile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the structural intermediate data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you scan the random</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>distortion components?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'm programming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the axonometric vectors</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to browse the dipolar coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how's the virtual submarine going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to go on a XANA hunt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't wanna wake up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our sleeping beauties.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The coordinates have been recognized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great teamwork. Huh, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't have done it without your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The programming is complete.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to launch the construction phase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a few more seconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll be all set, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay. I'm ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping louder]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music crescendos]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's that room? It's new to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's new to everyone! Aelita just</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>programmed it into the core zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll use it as a sort of hangar</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our sub.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta christen it! Give it a name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you don't christen a ship</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until the building is over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's when it gets its real name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But nothing says we can't give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it a code name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why don't we call her Melanie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Melanie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean like that redhead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're so mad about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have a crush on a girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who reminds you of a submarine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, it's pretty late. Why don't we</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>talk about it while we're walking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The rest of the calculations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should keep running by themselves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until tomorrow afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By then, the atomic layers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the virtual external structure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be complete.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At 4 p.m. sharp,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will be launching phase two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the programming operation:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the construction of the core.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we're gonna have to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on time, ‘cause if we're not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the kinetic dipolar distortion energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will enter a dangerous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destructive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>chromodynamic sinusoidal phase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind saying that in English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we're not in the factory by four,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the core will collapse into itself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kind of like a black hole.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you saying Melanie will be destroyed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it sure will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's gonna take months</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we can reprogram it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Months during which XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can continue doing his dirty work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without any interference from us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and I still have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some technical stuff to work on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we go to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty soon we'll be able to track</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA on the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We might even localize my dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That would be great,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we'd better not get our hopes up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Even if it's possible,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not going to be easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I know, but I'd completely lost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hope when XANA destroyed all of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door crashes open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelling] Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… I'm… This is my room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? I… Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I was saying…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Stones, what are you doing in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, um… Mmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the girls have to stay upstairs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is their floor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that they're not allowed downstairs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where the boys are, down here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so tomorrow, you can repeat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>word for word, what I just said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about downstairs and upstairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the principal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[playful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Now listen to me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>both of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic is a highly respectable institution.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The rule is strict.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Girls have no right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be in the boys' rooms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and vice versa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And especially after lights out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no excuse for your conduct!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… We didn't do anything bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right! We were just studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, since you like to study so much,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be glad to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that that's what you'll do in the library</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the entire afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope that's clear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, you're in charge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Delmas, you can count on me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[playful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shakespeare's work has been divided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into a number of categories:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>comedies, tragedies,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>history plays, and dark comedies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to work on his most…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a disaster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we're not back in the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by four sharp, it's so long, Melanie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, what are you gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Skip out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no matter what the consequences are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? You can't do that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you leave the library,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll throw you out of school for sure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we absolutely need the submarine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to travel through the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if you guys get expelled,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how do we fight XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have an idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[teacher] Yes, Odd? We're listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you find so much more interesting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than Shakespeare?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Melanie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, Melanie as a code name</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is pretty lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You prefer Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>C'mon, that's enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Melanie or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've still got a pretty serious problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about using lunchtime to get away?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could just tell Jim</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're in the infirmary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because something you ate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't agree with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think that might work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's on the menu for lunch?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ravioli.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh yeah, it's bound to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim laughs menacingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Belpois, Stones!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha! You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have lunch together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, I can get you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the library right on time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs] They've got company for lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We've got to find a way to get them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of there by four o'clock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that was when I had to bail out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of a big storm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the North Atlantic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I made it, but then I realized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I wasn't going to get back in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-for dinner! Hm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exasperated grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Jim Morales spe-- Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Would you repeat that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? I won the lottery?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] Hooray!!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs triumphantly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim continues laughing loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students confused]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim slowly stops laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[quietly] Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Absolutely!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, if you don't come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to claim your prize immediately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be given to the runner-up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[suspiciously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, just a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never bought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lottery ticket in my life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Really? Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't, by any chance, have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a twin brother who could've bought one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Mm-hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the one who's gonna wish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he had a twin brother</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do the detention I'm gonna give you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt with disappointment]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[playful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim sighs with relief]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah-ah! Not together. Separate desks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what they say about dividing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to… multiply… to conquer… I meant…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, Belpois, over there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Stones over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door squeaks open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog barking excitedly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, I just came to borrow something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from you, so calm down, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relieved] Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts approvingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mm-hmm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[watch ticking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs anxiously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screaming] Red alert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Red alert! Mrs. Hertz's mice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have escaped from the lab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're taking over the whole school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to catch them right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[surprised] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you really wanna know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what has be caught, Della Robbia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An idiot in a purple outfit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a dumb ridiculous haircut,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and who's gonna be in big trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if he and his toy mouse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't get outta here, pronto!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ridiculous, my haircut?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I bet your jealous, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Della Robbia…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you seen a mouse made of plastic?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Out! Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How'd it go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A fiasco!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I even got Kiwi mad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we can't use the door next time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, how about the window?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[device beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans in disbelief]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engines firing up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buttons beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Confiscated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're here to study and that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meaning that there's no gabbing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your head off on your mobile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your cell phone, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And your… thing that goes beep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shut it immediately</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or I'll throw it in the garbage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, look…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was not born yesterday,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so don't think you can fool me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever game you wanna play,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>remember I can beat you at it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any luck?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The window's locked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, then come down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not that light!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[makes impatient grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think Jeremy's trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give me a signal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean his message wasn't clear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was a little bit too clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, are your bright ideas working out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but speaking of bright ideas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy just tried to blind us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with one of his.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me have a look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, it's simple. Concentrate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Morse Code, turkey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Morse Code turkey?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sounds pretty scrumptious!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's trying to communicate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three short,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>three long, three short…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-SOS!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why'd you learn Morse Code?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki and I keep secrets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from our parents that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fac… to… ry…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] SOS Factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a word about Melanie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We gotta get to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The message ended with the word "William."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers booming against shield]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mm-hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Jim? Is it true you were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a math teacher in the tropics?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Affirmative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't figure out what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the square of the hypotenuse could be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you help me please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but… Uh… It's not all that easy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because, um… In the tropics,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>uh, the hippopotenuse is, um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's what's variable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, because of the heat?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein left us a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"XANA's attacking Melanie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, take over for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich, off to Lyoko."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, go on, Yumi. You've done it before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, but what if I make a mistake?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't afford to lose Melanie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can do it, Yumi. I have faith in you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would even say that the hypothermia</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the hippopotenuse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>depends on the hyperactivity of the noose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, who would have thought?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a walking encyclopedia, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you see, Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you're out there all alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the tropical jungle,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with nothing more than a</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cigarette lighter…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't know all you need to know…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Zap! You're dead meat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! You're incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a huge problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once the protective shields are gone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing can stop XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from totally wiping out Melanie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] And, according to Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it can't be reprogrammed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, as soon as you get to Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna have to work fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And try not to mix things up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I don't wanna find myself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my arms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where my legs should be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my nose in my navel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you imagine that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do your stuff, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Two arms, two legs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one head, one tail…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All present and accounted for!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It worked, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in the arena.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs with relief]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy level… Melanie… Window F9.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep going till you reach the access hall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then, take a platform elevator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the hangar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita did a fantastic job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roar of transporter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching to a halt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machinery whooshing and squealing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, everything's cool up to now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, we're almost at the hangar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll let Jeremy know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've been punished</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for not having obeyed the rules,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it seems you never learn!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No computer communication!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Mr. Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't know you were here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bravo for you surveillance, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I, um… was helping Aelita here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with some hippopotamus--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, that is… hippopotenuse problems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm confiscating this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the rest of the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, please, sir! You can't do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, I must have my computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's urgent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's right, Mr. Delmas. It's really--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] …vital!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Vital? Ridiculous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you like to know what's vital?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen. It's vital to be aware</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that there is no one in life</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who can go unpunished</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for being disobedient!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry about that, Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you've still</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little punishment time left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And until then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna stand between you and that door!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You grab William's attention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll handle the Kreepers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yo, big shot…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna mix it up a little?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swords whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting with effort]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd chuckles triumphantly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing and banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mantas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all we needed… XANA's air force.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer Jeremy, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what is the matter with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, if you let us go now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we promise to do double detention,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>starting tomorrow…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or… Or…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or triple!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll do triple detention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a whole week, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts "no"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers booming against shield]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser shots booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[booming explosions]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music grows louder]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, we need back up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't go it all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I… I've lost contact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The submarine shields are getting weaker!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Improvise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and Jeremy have to get here now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>regardless of Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you a favor, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, because Johnny and me are playing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Babylon Ninja Fighter Five</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on. She's so cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's give her a little help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you let me get to level five first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got it, sis,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but on one condition:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you do my homework for a month.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a real crook, Hiroki,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And make it fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget to tell her it was me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who convinced you to change your mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, sure…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I already told you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you got no chance against Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing and banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer warnings beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[watch ticking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just fifteen minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of detention to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting approval to each other]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The mouse didn't work,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so now it's a mechanical dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty good imitation, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's the real thing! A mangy mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Stay where you are! Get back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting] I got… I gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[booming from lasers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're just like sitting ducks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Sitting Kreepers that is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[booming explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing and booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna win, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better let your master know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal clanging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[airlock hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door rattling open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hey, it's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi, Aelita, head for the scanners!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only eight minutes to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get over here, sweetie!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna need you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd, backup is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things were heating up around here. Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine whirring slows down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a pleasure to see you again, ladies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's always nice to feel needed, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you realize it's five minutes to four?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, Odd, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only five minutes to run</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Melanie's core programming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But even more important,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of our protection shields</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are just about down to zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girls grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal clanging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[booming and rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors hiss open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, ladies! The sub only has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seven percent of its life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[booming and screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[booming explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts in frustration]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the sub's shield is almost totally gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more hit and it's all over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Melanie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three fifty-nine and forty-five seconds…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forty-six… Forty-seven…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The programming for phase two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is under way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our ship is finally completed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors hissing open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh wow! Close call for Melanie, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] But Melanie's a great name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we keep it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a nice name for a girl,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but not a submarine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, for a ship that's gonna hunt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>down XANA on the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we need a name that's got some punch,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like, um… Nautilus, for example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sarcastically] Hm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's pretty original.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Find a better one then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita, are you coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… I'll be right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father used to read this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>book to me when I was five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Viking Gods and Legends</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was a mythical tall ship</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that could even sail on land,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it always reached its destination,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no matter what kind of wind was blowing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"The Skidbladnir"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Skid… Skid… Blaskid… Ski… Ski…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really like that name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I like it too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, our new ship's name</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is now "Skidbladnir."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Skid… What about Skid for short?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what about Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did he react when he found out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you guys were gone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we haven't seen him since, so…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe he forgot about us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't seen him on campus at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have other things on his mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you, little doggy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you're around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uncle Jim's got a little snack for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on out now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't get away from me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you hairy hound, you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>