<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A SPACE ODDITY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is it! It's the end of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong? They run out of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>spaghetti and meatballs in the lunchroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Almost as bad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just ran into Jim and Delmas. They're</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>making a surprise inspection of the dorm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… Didn't they make one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few weeks ago?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but this time they're looking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for appliances that could be fire hazards.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] So what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing dangerous here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No appliances,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not even an electric kettle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but the problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is what do I do with Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Do we have enough time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take him to the factory before math?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In ten minutes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I wouldn't want to leave him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>alone in that cold factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He hasn't been himself lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's going to end up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the pound, or worse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in some travelling circus strapped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a rocket and shot out of a cannon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pleading voice] Yumi, you don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>class for another hour? Could you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't even think about it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, please. You're his only hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The answer is no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Good old surprise inspections!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They make even the cloudiest days sunny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at what we've already dug up…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An electric coffee maker,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an immersion heater,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a 12 person fondue set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like being a pioneer explorer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see what we can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>come up with in Sissi's room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although, I doubt if she would be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hiding anything suspicious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, being your daughter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, let's look behind this door,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just in case. You never know…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A hair dryer on the blink,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a forgotten pack of matches,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a curling iron invented</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by some crackpot scientist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would never have guessed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For a stern school principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're a million laughs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, take pity on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a poor defenseless puppy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] You will?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You know if there's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one thing my father can't stand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's pets that shed their hair</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all over the house,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>chew up furniture, do their business…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pretty, pretty please…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Odd, you win this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing can stop me from kissing you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors creak]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay, Kiwi, get in. We're off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ishiyama, Della Robbia, Stern, Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Stones…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All together in the same dorm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They sure don't look like they're in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a big hurry to get to class, do they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well, I'd better be going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't just give him any old thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to eat. Only steamed, organic vegetables.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And no potato chips. He can't digest them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And no mustard whatever you do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, he hates household appliances,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like vacuum cleaners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The noise drives him nuts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, the coast is clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If my dumb brother hears you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's bound to say something like,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"what's that ugly mutt doing here?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's that ugly mutt doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Kiwi, Odd's dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki, promise you won't say anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but, promise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll do my homework for a year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A week!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Three days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A deal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're such a little crook, but I don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have a choice. I have to go to school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look after Kiwi until I get back. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't give him any steamed vegetables.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems he only eats chips and mustard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry about a thing… Litchi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take good care of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children shouting and chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] There you are, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No sweat, Hiroki's watching him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki? Are you nuts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you forget what happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to poor Jean-Pierre?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your Tamagotchi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sad… We're still in mourning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I don't see what's so funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What are you doing now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, we've already got an encyclopedia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a second, don't hang up, Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Everything is cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your dog is in good hands. See you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[munching and barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know what you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want some more of these. Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I've got a surprise for you this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These are chips with </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>mustard</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice to know you trust me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you don't understand…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi happens to be a very sensitive dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess what, everybody!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Supercomputer has just picked up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a new Replika on the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats! Now I've got to come up with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a new excuse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get out of Chardin's class again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't be missing much,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except maybe a little nap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to stop by the library,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I won't be long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you all know where to meet up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds squawking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have to remind you that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the more Replikas we destroy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the more we weaken XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course you don't, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you don't have to remind us that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we can find the new Supercomputer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we might be able to figure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out what XANA's plotting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd get straight A's if you were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as good as that in school!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, get ready, guys! Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everybody okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for Kiwi, I'm not so sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chill out, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He couldn't be in better hands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurping and munching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scratching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, we're in the Skid garage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get on your teleport spots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Prepare for lift off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Release docking mechanism.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Immediate opening of tunnel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready to dive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holoweb system online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm entering the coordinates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the new Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Rotation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Powering turbo prop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and auxiliary generators.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer game beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little patience, Litchi! I'll play</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with you soon as I finish this game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think it's going to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this time around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It might be a Replika of the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>My guess is mountains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What do you think, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should've fed him more tofu kibbles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stay focused, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poor Litchi, those chips</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't agree with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what do you say we play ball?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Replika in sight, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll unlock the portal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as you're connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water flowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Digital code entered.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just give me a minute or two, and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll see what this Replika looks like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you the entry portal code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical grating and squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What do you</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were all wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to a Replika of Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just spotted a tower in the core zone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that can be reached from the North Pole.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll guide you in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that you can get to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Got</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're in the driver's seat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice piece of work. We're in a</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>room exactly like the ones in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower dead ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take over from here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay Aelita, do your stuff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Skid docked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect. Yumi and Odd, do you want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to volunteer for teleportation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aye aye, Captain Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you give the bad jokes a rest,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Private?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich and Aelita, you two--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We stay here and guard the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guessed it. I'm activating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower for our own use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for teleportation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just say the word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Teleportation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Yumi, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We read you loud and clear Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, which continent did you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>land on this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>None of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What? You mean you're in the ocean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh for two… But we are floating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Outer space!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys are in outer space?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's more like it, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew you'd figure it out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sooner or later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, look at this, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It's unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] It </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>is</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's beautiful, and yet, it seems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so fragile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He gets sick even though I only</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>feed him good healthy food.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm beginning to think there's something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seriously wrong with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you're looking at the most beautiful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sight you're ever going to see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all you can think about are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your stupid cans of dog food!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kibbles! I never give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi canned dog food.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-According to your coordinates,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it looks like you guys are on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the brand new international space station,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four hundred kilometers above the Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>This is great! We can meet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some astronauts and get their autographs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't bet on that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The station is uninhabited right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A new team is coming in about ten days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good. That'll give us time to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer and destroy it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Be on your guard all the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can never be sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA has up his sleeve.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Up, up and away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki] Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fetch, go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good dog! You did it again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there's a line</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of little metallic spheres here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like mini Megatanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think XANA's manufacturing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>those things?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, they look harmless enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe XANA's taken up bocce ball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It could be nothing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or something major.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're definitely not made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to serve mankind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and find that Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No Odd, don't touch them! You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's enough. Lie down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said lie down! If not, I'll lock you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my sister's room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[car door bangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] Now, what did I do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my keys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're in your attaché case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why, of course. Where is my head?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you left it with your keys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't move, and don't make a sound.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here they are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] Look at this mess!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the meaning of this, Hiroki?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't get stressed out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have all cleaned up in no time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's weird. Usually, XANA would've</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>launched an attack by now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'd be the first time that he--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts and cracks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a really huge problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see it. XANA's doing all he can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to wipe out the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If you have a solution,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm all for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the Replika is an exact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>copy of Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then it should function exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like it did on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just like before on Lyoko, you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to activate a key to stop the mechanism.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I have a volunteer to take care of it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy, I'm the fastest,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I'd better go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The key is directly across</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from where you're standing right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. I'm off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think we just found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect timing, because XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to wipe out the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better take out the Supercomputer now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful, though,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make it look like an accident.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This space station is too well known.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't want any rumors about sabotage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] An accident? How do we do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope your brother remembered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give Kiwi enough to drink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're facing disaster,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all you can think about is your dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Water, yeah, that's a good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We'll create some water damage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There has to be water flowing through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of these things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't thank </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>me</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>. Thank Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't expect me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bow down to you, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well done, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Odd, over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's water in this pipe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The water flows through there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What did you kick me for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh… Thanks, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Odd, give me a hand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[vacuum suction]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's strange. It sounds like a dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vacuum gets louder]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[vacuum stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[howling continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door squeaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Make your next left, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I transferred</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of the energy into the shields.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let's hope they hold up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They seem to be okay for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, William just showed up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Doesn't he ever give up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it! That was so dumb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] XANA's really having a ball…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And lots of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop the joking, Odd. Those things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could reverse the teleportation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we fail this mission, XANA wins.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[firing and cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Skid just lost one shield layer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm doing all I can, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It feels pretty stuffy in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's air the place out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, you can't do that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I don't do that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going to be bowling pins!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hang on tight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling and rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's better. Smells less like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an astronaut's dirty socks in here now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[monster roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time you stopped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>drooling over me, pal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Not much further, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The key's on the other side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot, Jeremy. I can see it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, when you've got to go…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing and crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's what I call</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being really "pressed" for time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope they've got insurance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[water gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's working, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>it's going</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>to</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>blow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you both in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De-energize Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De-energize Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exploding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sizzling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Leave our friend alone, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fans whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to be a pain,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if I were you, I'd get out of there…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Everyone's on board. Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exploding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That's one less Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mission accomplished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Rats! My parents are home!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah? And?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let's say that I wouldn't like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be Kiwi right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Ishiyama laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice little doggie. You love playing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your uncle Takeho, don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Ishiyama laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Back already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yes, Mr. Ishiyama,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want my dog</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be a bother to you, so I'd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to take him home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Well, if you like I could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>take care of him for… A week or so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you Sir, but I missed him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans with pleasure]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can understand that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] Just a minute, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, take some sushi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, ma'am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm not crazy about raw fish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's not for you, it's for Litchi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He loves it, especially</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when it's got lots of mustard on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>