<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ROCK BOTTOM</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A three-day weekend!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fantastic, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With a little luck,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just may have the house to myself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but knowing your parents,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not gonna be easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm betting on Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't tell you, but I've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot of homework this weekend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay home and look after things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you have nothing against it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to have a little gathering.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A gathering to do homework together...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or to wreck the living room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, answer your father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I thought I'd invite my friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over for a quiet evening at home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm... You mean those three clowns?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But daddy, you hardly even know them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They seem nice enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish you'd... trust me a little more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, they can come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is so great, you won't regret it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and kisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, mom! You're the greatest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have a nice weekend!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I've got great news, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the house all to ourselves!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'd better get organized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Anything wrong, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm trying to localize Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It shouldn't take this much time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If there's a problem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will contact you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah well, we can always hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Time for physics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Class dismissed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don't forget Monday´s quiz</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on seismic phenomena,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>better known as earthquakes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Theo and Benjamin said they would come,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but what're we gonna do about Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wouldn't break my heart</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if she didn't come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She and that horrible music</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she'd bring with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, leave the music to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait 'til you see the surprise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got in store for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have a real DJ, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No dumb music for us. We're gonna rock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great. See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go shopping after class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, in the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try and contact Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and warn her to be careful tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's time for Ulrich to get ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and enter the starting block.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Tensions are high</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ladies and gentlemen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as he zeros in on his objective.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The timekeeper's about to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sound the departure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Bang.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] And he's off and running!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What grace, what agility</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and what great speed he's got!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's ready for the sliding phase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What perfect knee coordination.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, he beat me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really, Ulrich went farther than you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, how did I make out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] A new dorm record.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] What's all this racket about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotta hang up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Secret code: "Big fat clown."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha. Okay, talk to you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Jim. We're just a little bored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing to do here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Every long weekend,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you kids stay at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never go anywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If for once you guys took a vacation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have some peace and quiet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That just goes to show you how much</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we love this place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? And I'll bet it's 'cause at home,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your parents are sick of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sympathize with them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] And now, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want all of you to go back to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your rooms, on the double!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhale disappointed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Right away, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your turn, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'd better hurry, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Bang.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells and crashes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, didn't I beat the record?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is this your surprise disc jockey, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you mean you don't recognize her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She goes to school here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her name's, Samantha. See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got some work to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna introduce us to her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That must be her. Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the fifth time I've launched</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the localization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The network must really be blocked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't get into contact with Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat and giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you have any trouble getting in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The gates were really easy to climb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When can you show me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I'm finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna add a little more stuff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I haven't found anything I like yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should try the old vinyl records.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's lots of really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>great stuff on vinyl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If you want, I'll lend you some.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can't we stop talking about music?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got better things to do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for a big thrill session?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh...yeah, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, take me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the computer room, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh. I think this time I've got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more operation and...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita... Aelita, it's Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you read me, Aelita? Hey, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello Jeremy. How are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Mmm... so-so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why, what's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I had such a tough time contacting Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's nothing new.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko is constantly changing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>its access points on the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, feel like playing some chess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Samantha]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, what kind of power's this one got?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I don't know... Two gigas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, cut that out. Put that down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you hear? What're you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I'm gonna make music,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need a powerful computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm broke, so I have no choice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but to rip this one off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your school's insured,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so everybody's happy, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Insurance or not, stealing's a crime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, nobody does that around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, you're...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would never have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>believed it of you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wasn't gonna steal it, Jim. I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh! What were you gonna do with it then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] You've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some explaining to do. Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Checkmate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I try beating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you at... like karate?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Go on, keep moving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Looks like trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well Odd, this time you are in one heck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a jam. That's for sure, kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Caught in the act, stealing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a computer that is school property</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't like not doing your homework.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Listen, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What the...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever Odd needs a computer, I lend him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mine. I've done it lots of times.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, tell him, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, although... this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I needed a really powerful laptop,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that one was just perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And why didn't you ask permission</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to borrow it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems to me that would've</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>been a lot more simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I was afraid that you say no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh... What do you think I am, an idiot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want the truth right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stole it, didn't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's the school disciplinary council,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you might just get expelled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? No, wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't do that to me, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The use of cell phones is strictly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>forbidden on school grounds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hand it over. Confiscated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just spotted an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, XANA's launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm... I gotta get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, tell us what happened. Come on, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got nothing to say. See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got things to do... alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Do you see what I see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, they're getting really deep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's gonna be swallowed up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll see you at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[trembling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hold it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Uh-uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I can't go with you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Samantha's locked in the science</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>building's computer room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go back to the beginning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause I think you lost us, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's the one who stole the computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really tried to stop her, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>well, she's already got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot of problems at her school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I didn't tell Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No matter what happened,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we gotta get her out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. I'll run over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and meet Yumi at the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, step number one: we pay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little visit to the gymnasium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Let's hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're the only ones at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It must be in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] So, which way do we go now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, oh no, I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm never gonna get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's at least a 20 meter drop down there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, make sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the rope is attached securely.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ambulance siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Connection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Connecting to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you're there at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA's activated a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's what we thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've already been affected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take your time, and concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, here we go. Yah! [grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, the stairs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you're off to the mountain region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got problems connecting to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The landing could be rough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] Hey, get me out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get me out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Let's hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we don't get there too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta get out of here! [grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Samantha! Sam! We're on our way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Sam. We're gonna get you out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay? It's over now, Sam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Samantha] Oh, Odd, I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate to bother you guys, but we've</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gotta get out of here, and fast too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasping and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yumi, your hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Give me your hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got here just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now we've got to hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's monsters aren't here yet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but they're bound to come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The tower's not far from here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well, this promises to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a charming stroll.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not as hard as all that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you jump at the right time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I see what you mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twenty-six, twenty-seven,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>twenty-eight, twenty-nine...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] We're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You were right, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It wasn't all that hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out, three hornets approaching fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay behind me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They've disappeared</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from my control screens.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did they go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know. In this territory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they have the advantage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I'm calling you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the junior high school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I work here at the school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, it's a real emergency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm stuck in a closet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with tons of mud around, so get here fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No lady, this is not a practical joke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] No, I can't wait any longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, the hornets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are coming straight at you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, I'm caught in a crossfire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold out much longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich are on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope so anyway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ae... Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try using your creativity,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita. We need a little time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Samantha] Wow, this place is wild.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you're finally here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's been devirtualized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's fighting three hornets all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I don't understand any of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, there's no time to explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You keep Jeremy company,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll see you later. What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Destination: the mountains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We made it, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The path in front of you leads</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the platform where you'll find Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Get out of here, you monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Sorry we're late, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This'll convince you to forgive us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You missed the target,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd. Ulrich, careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you wanna play? Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, what's my problem today, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They're coming back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich pants] Triplicate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich pants and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just us now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Aelita. Let Odd handle it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't wanna die! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Psst. Okay, he's gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He should be here by now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I thought you said no one else knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, they're my pals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This is Ulrich, and this is Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the genius who's gonna help you rock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have a seat, Sam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll show you what you can do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you've got great equipment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing and digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, if you don't mind, let's focus, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>