<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TIP TOP SHAPE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This new stuff will get rid of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my unsightly zits for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should have seen them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, they're back together again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Julian, you mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're studying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The eye chart!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm nearsighted, but I don't want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have to wear glasses…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'd be too lame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right… Being blind as a bat sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a lot more cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holding up the wall, huh, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! Push-ups.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why? Can't you tell?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sick of hearing Yolanda</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>telling me I'm scrawny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] But you </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>are </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>scrawny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am not scrawny! I'm svelte!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>want to look over my health record</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at my weight curve… Just right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And my growth curve…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Just right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfection is really wonderful, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You don't understand, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't have a health record,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've never even been vaccinated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if the nurse finds out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're not really human?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean you don't find me very human?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, sure I do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but that's not what I meant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, relax.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't get so carried away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alright… Jeremy Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd Della Robbia and Julien Xao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on, Rambo! Blow them away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Sissi titter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got the heart of an athlete, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, you look a little skinny to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure you're eating enough?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By "enough,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you mean more than an elephant?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elephant roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I eat a lot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yolanda] In that case, it must be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your metabolism that keeps you so scrawny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay! Your turn, Julien!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am not scrawny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm svelte!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alright, read the top line, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A, Q, T… Z.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what do you see on line one,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>H, B, P, V and L.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yolanda] Really, Julien!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not only are you nearsighted,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got a bad memory, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Jeremy laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yolanda] Jeremy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scales rattle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ma'am, is it bad if we forgot to bring</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our health record,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if we haven't had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all our vaccinations?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yes it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're completely up to date.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth Delmas and Aelita Stones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not to worry, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She thought </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>were human, didn't she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hilarious!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping coming from satchel]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy opens satchel]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-An activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the middle of a medical check-up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has no respect for anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, stay here and wait for Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bring her to the factory as soon as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she gets out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and I will head over there now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, quit dawdling!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is 100 meter sprint,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not a chorus line!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy. I'll be there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Next!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girls straining and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! There you go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone, at least,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is putting their back into it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you just broke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the school record!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scales rattle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] What!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your scale must be broken!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's five pounds over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The scale is perfectly accurate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Sissi! This is outrageous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to tell my father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yolanda] I'd run over to his office</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I were you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yolanda] It might help you lose</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few pounds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your turn, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really sorry, ma'am, but I forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring my health record.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's no big deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll just put your results</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a separate piece of paper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you can staple into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your file later on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should have left my health record</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at home too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But, why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, can't you guess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] My ultra-perfect weight curve</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has just been wrecked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by these five extra pounds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Well, you can't tell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by looking at you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[latch creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There… The nurse… She… Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, I get the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shivers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yolanda has been possessed by XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] She'll probably try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-so she can transfer Aelita to Lyoko…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doors clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…and then deliver her to the Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll try and stop her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can't deactivate the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about we block the elevator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That might buy us a little time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's only going to give us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>five or six minutes, no more!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what do you suggest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we could do battle with Yolanda</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on equal terms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I've been studying XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>specters for a while now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I could manage to pixellize you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean you're going to turn us into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>people like the ones possessed by XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Instead of being XANAfied,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going to be "Jeremified."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you get it, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Couldn't that be a bit risky?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could say no, but I'd be lying!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, Yolanda is heading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the corridor!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold it off as long as you can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How much time you need?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ideally, about three months!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'll see what I can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do to speed things up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, how do you plan on pixellizing us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Frankenstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First step… Activate a tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You know how to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, theoretically… yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It doesn't work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, it does. Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… activated a tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, thanks to this activated tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to send a digital impulse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which will travel at hyper speed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through all the networks and gather</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>huge amounts of energy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll guide it by remote control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>toward the exit I choose,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like the cables on my screen, and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the impulse will come out as a specter!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>English translation, please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… I'm going to send a specter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you'll become invincible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a little score</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to settle with Yolanda Perraudin!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Excuse me, ma'am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you forgot to give me my check up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I remembered to bring</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my health record and everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I guess my reflexes are pretty good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yolanda grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How about testing my eyesight now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door lock rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, but I can't get through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the corridor!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We're coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is going to be big time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If this ends badly, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you promise to look after Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If this ends badly, there'll be nobody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>left to look after Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd? How do you feel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fully charged!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lock rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lock rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please hurry up! Jeremy, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] She's here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, miss nurse, do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I look scrawny now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yolanda growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way, nasty nurse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Catch me if you can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me? Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita! Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] I'm alright.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What about Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I am! Am I dreaming,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or has Odd turned into a super hero?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy's managed to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Jeremify" him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah? That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah, but I don't know how long</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he can last against Yolanda,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so we have to deactivate the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's controlling her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better and better!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Overbike and the Overwing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>above the forest in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Let's move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any news from Odd and his private nurse?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last time I checked,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the atmosphere was </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>electric</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He should be hanging in there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for now, that is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you guys better be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA sent out some monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop you from reaching the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Isn't that a surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sarcastically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yolanda grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Jeremy, we're losing power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that supposed to happen?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's what I thought!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're using your "I hate to say it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you bombed the exam" voice?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, do you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yes, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's about Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a big problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well, it's not too easy at this end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>either!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[slashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen! XANA is taking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>control of the tower I activated for Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and there's nothing I can do to stop him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Whenever you and Odd start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>messing around, it means trouble for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how's that going to affect Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will XANA take control of him, too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well it looks as if he'd rather just pump</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of his energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You mean, until he…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where's the other tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>In the mountain sector!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a way tower to the west!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Got it! I'll go with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Saving Odd is top priority now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here to clean up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Aelita, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd doesn't have much time left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, ladies, the tower is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dead ahead of you. Can you see it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi stammers] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No! To tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the truth, we can't see anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has already pulled this one on us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right at the edge of the cliff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to hang on real tight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to me, okay! I'll guide you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The path leading to the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is dead ahead of you, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep walking straight ahead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I say "stop."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita strains and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next time, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>give me a little more warning, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Sorry. I can't judge distances</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>too well on my screen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, turn right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's XANA got in store</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for us next?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going to have to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around the rock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The best solution, as I see it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to go around to the left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, are we there yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After the rock, it's straight ahead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the tower. You're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] You've got company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hornets!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Duck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay! Run straight ahead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Where are they, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't see them…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I do now! They're diving down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>straight at you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, run to the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're in front of the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Spotted!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wings fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, any news from Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's coming out of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're going back to Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'll program the Overboard for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, do you read me? Aelita and Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are on their way to you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good. The three of us could use a few</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ladies around here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The girls are coming,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd better clean up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fusion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little lonely out here by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What about the monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It was pretty rude of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to interrupt me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of our conversation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nurse Yolanda!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, am I glad to see you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… I'm glad to see me too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's getting pretty hairy over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sizzling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really think XANA needs to work on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his bedside manner, don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Yolanda turned into a weird,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scary demon and jumped out of a window!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] That's what happened!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Reminds me of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I worked in a psychiatric hospital.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You worked in a psychiatric hospital?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's the truth, I tell you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Sissi, dear, stop this nonsense</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and tell me what really happened!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why don't you ask Yolanda?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Mrs. Perraudin</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wasn't feeling well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so she went out for some air!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Out the </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>window</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, of course…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> really</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> what happened, Yolanda?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yes, I mean…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't really remember.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as though I blacked out, but</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't see why Aelita would want to lie!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Nice one, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were perfect!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, anybody who lies that well</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could only be human, right Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hold it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am not crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are some super-weirdo things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that happened in that infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Relax, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We understand how it would make you crazy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be five pounds overweight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am not five pounds overweight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, now, come on! Don't worry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know… Nobody's perfect!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speak for yourself… Scrawny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am svelte!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>