<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune fades into background]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, are we rolling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Yeah, but we're upside down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Hello fellow students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Kadic Junior High.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your ace reporters, Milly and Tamiya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are here to bring you an exclusive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for today's school news,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's really big,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since as I'm pretty sure you already know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tonight is the big night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the night of our annual school prom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[camera static buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unfortunately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our cameras weren't authorized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to film the site</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where the festivities will take place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I can make out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from where I'm speaking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the girl who might be crowned</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our beauty queen tonight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just as she was last year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your principal's daughter, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see whether</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she'll answer a few questions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Sissi, how about a few words</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our TV audience before the big night?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Munchkins,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only talk to real pro reporters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] I have no time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-to waste on a couple of nerds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya sighs disappointed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's for the school news program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] What about freedom of the press?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Milly, little dipsticks your age</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't have any freedom. Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, who needs your dumb reporting?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, you've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget you have to have a date,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't know anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who'd want to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a jerk like you... even them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I'll bet if you asked them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'd run like scared rabbits.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who needs them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are lots of other boys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, Yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting for, then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try and find one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi giggles mockingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitating] Ulrich, would you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you be my date tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pauses doubtfully] I'm sorry Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wouldn't be a very good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm too old for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, well you see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I promised to go with Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] You see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs mockingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did I tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry Milly, I'm sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll find a boy for the sandbox dance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Meanwhile,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why don't you go play with your dolls?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps rushing and door creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Milly wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I hope you're proud of yourself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense strings playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[synth and drum beat playing theme tune]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, this is Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi. How are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm fine. How about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't see anything unusual</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around the towers. It all seems quiet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, for the moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I'm making progress</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my research, so...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you can come and live with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The key to materialization?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You found it at last?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy hesitating] Well no,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not yet but... I'm working on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just a matter of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then XANA won't be able to do anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to harm you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-or us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's great. Thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Milly, don't cry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go to the prom. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for the news, Jim said it was okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have until nine o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly sobbing] It's a waste of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya sighs disappointed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better face facts, Tamiya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They don't care about us or the newscast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatically] I hate them, all of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate every single one of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate everybody in the world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] You don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're saying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's just the...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly crying] Stop it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sick of you too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So just leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crying dramatically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] Hey...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich could've been a little nicer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tape ripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't look so gloomy, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it because of Milly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could have said yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know me and the prom...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even if I was your date?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Sissi really did come on strong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If meanness is one of the qualities</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a beauty queen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she'll get reelected all right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's true,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-but try to get Miss World to see that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs sarcastically] Miss World?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss "In her own world," more like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi snarls angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[piano notes playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] At least you don't care</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how old I am, do you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We understand each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not like those dumb older kids</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who always want to run things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They think that because we're young,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we don't count at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If for once, we were older,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot older than them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-they wouldn't laugh at us, would they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya knocking] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Milly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-are you in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you finished sulking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, we have work to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Okay, okay, I'm coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stay right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be back for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaking and slamming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] We have a report to finish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the prom, remember?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music build-up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[creeping slush]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I hope you two aren't gonna follow me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around all day long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As far as I know, you're not beauticians,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so stop sticking to me like glue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't need you. Understand? So scat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitating] Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, we thought...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take this advice: Don't think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't suit you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both boys] Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles to self and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heartbeat thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] A bunch of babies at our prom!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've gotta be kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat music playing on the stereo]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that other freak</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who had the nerve to invite Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If anybody's going out with Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it absolutely has to be me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am the star, the diva of the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi shrugs and giggles to self]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat thumping intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat thumping quickly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[music fades to low volume]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales and giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heartbeat thumping very quickly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bottles rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's there? Answer me! Who is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps and squeals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move along. Back to your dorms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything is just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks as if we've got ourselves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a super scoop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you say we take a look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make sure that our old friend XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't behind this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mhm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] A simple short circuit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too many appliances</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>plugged in at the same time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yeah, the hi-fi, lights,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lady shaver, curling iron all together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you expect to happen?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Not to mention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the brain stimulator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing] although she probably</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>never figured out how to use it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[camera flashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] I don't know what happened,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you ask me, Sissi had it coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] I couldn't agree with you more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! My teddy bear is gone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Aha! Caught you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's forbidden to play in the garden shed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait a minute, Jim. It was my...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't wanna know why.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've told you a hundred times</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that this place</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is much too dangerous for children.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at all these rusty tools.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think this is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a kid's playground?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] We know but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] No buts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I hope I made myself real clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Entry forbidden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Access reserved for adults.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] With you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything is off limits.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you listen here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would change the way I talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I were you, little girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angrily] Little girl! Okay, I'm young.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's only big kids</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who can say what they think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you think you're real big kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sneers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, that's fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>News report or not, the two of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are grounded for tonight in your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, Milly, really great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to you, it's goodbye prom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling] Now, beat it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly sobbing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aw, Look at the pictures we took.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're really fantastic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Something wrong, Milly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Somebody stole her teddy bear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing] And I'm sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of the big kids did for spite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Milly, you're right. Look at this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a picture of Sissi's room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] And there's my teddy bear hidden</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under her pillow. Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jokingly] Ah, who'd have believed it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon she'll be playing with dolls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, come on now. We've gotta find her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Jim catches us in the dorm,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're in big trouble, Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You go back to your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both sigh and then laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's there? Come on out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rustling noises]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nervously] You better watch out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a black belt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim shrieking loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[puzzled] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[puzzled sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You're sure, Jim</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that this is your attacker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim whimpering and babbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] And you say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's an expert in martial arts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim whimpering and babbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think it would be better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to call the police. Right, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened to Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was kinda weird, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was a short circuit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a simple short circuit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What else could it be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm not so sure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you know just what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, let's play it really cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Walls have ears, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well, I've gotta go now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get ready for the prom tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sometimes being a day student</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can really be a total drag.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Don't complain. No one wakes you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at 6 a.m. You have hot water,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you don't have to sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>near smelly Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks and shuts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Odd, are you looking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. You see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just heard about what happened to Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do they know who attacked him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, I think our gym teacher</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-could use some rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[paper wrinkling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[paper clacks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[trash rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA in a teddy bear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah, I'm pretty sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's always where you least expect him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay now guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who goes and who stays here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't have a solo mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too dangerous without Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you go alone, you never know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're gonna find over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I volunteer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What did I just say, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, have you got any other ideas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There've been two accidents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't leave the school unguarded,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and even going back in time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if there's an accident, it's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd is right. You go, and I'll stay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I find any clues,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll pass them on to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, and say hi to you know who for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Mhm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune build-up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat theme tune]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wheels rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat theme tune continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electric guitar strumming theme tune]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator door shutting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machinery rattling and clunking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gate slamming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch rattling and clunking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[seat zipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune fading to background]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, it's Jeremy! Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We think that XANA has launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you noticed anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we can take a closer look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm sending Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's coming over solo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich had to stay behind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to watch for any virus action at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through walkie-talkie]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are things with you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like we have a problem...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a big one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[capsule zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch zooming shut]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[capsule humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing and buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drum beat and synth playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's bad, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The bear got out of the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he's under XANA's control...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll only become much madder.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll go for anybody that's around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially his mortal enemies... like you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shocked] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] You see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has activated can't be too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well... not down there anyway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe on the neighboring plateaus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Mmm... Oops, uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here comes the reception committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>take good care of Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone call connecting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer, will you answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser beams blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser arrow firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd, you just lost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another ten life points!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser beams blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I'm afraid we haven't any choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser beams blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doorbell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[water dripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doorbell rings twice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slow footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, watch it, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry, are your parents home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, they went out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Come on. We can't stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, would you mind explaining?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We don't have time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd, be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You only have 50 life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser arrows firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosions]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser arrow firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rocks rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[skidding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't leave you alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for one second, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Odd, I think I found something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[man] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[woman gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roaring in the distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crushing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi is with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're coming back to the school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to evacuate everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell Odd to move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's getting rough around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer sputtering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, hurry up! Teddy's getting real angry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] The tower can't be too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Houston, we've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting intensely]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd still hasn't found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You clear the dorms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of the gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mhm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We found the tower, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! Well done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now all you have to do is deactivate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ok. Just give me a minute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to say hello to an old buddy of mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cut the courtesy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you only have 50 life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't let him hit you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muffled club music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[club music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[people chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could've made a little effort!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe how sloppy you look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Well, I'll let it go this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I'll put it down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the company you keep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to chill out, and have fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look like you're expecting a disaster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you? Hey, where did your date go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Next time, just call me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And now, the moment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've all been waiting for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The election of this year's beauty queen!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[people cheer and applaud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotta run now. It's my moment of triumph.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh in a silly manner]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both stop laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beam charging and blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rocks rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's what I call</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a really warm welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beam blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's not gonna make it on his own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yes, he will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, go on, you have to hit the target.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beam charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muffled club music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now everyone, this year, once again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time to elect the young lady,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who in your view, combines,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more than any other girl, charm,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>grace, beauty and elegance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And here is our first candidate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through microphone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[feedback]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to what I have to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have all got to get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to evacuate the gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, keep calm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm not joking...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We are about to be attacked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by a gigantic teddy bear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy] Teddy bear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aha! I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone stops laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw it too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I saw the giant teddy bear too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shut up all of you, you bunch of idiots!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you see what he's trying to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a trick, I tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A trick to keep me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from winning again this year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A gigantic teddy bear, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not King Kong while you're at it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screaming in panic]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone screaming in panic]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[quivering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roaring and smashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's now or never.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beam charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powerful beam blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistles relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go on, Aelita! It's up to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital warping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[teddy growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[teddy growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighs relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi laughs relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital sputtering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for a trip into the past, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct reversed chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, would you, would you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you be my date?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uhm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'd be glad to, Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy 2] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll see you here at eight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not too mad at me, are you Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, my secret admirer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will take me tonight. Right, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Ulrich, you're gonna go with that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that silly baby?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, I sure am. But don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When your brain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gets another neuron or two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe I'll go out with you too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You are recording, Tamiya, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] You bet I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is a scoop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] A super scoop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital warping]</c.bg_transparent>