<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>MISSING LINK</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What could Yumi be doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get some data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not like her to be late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe she's with William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I said maybe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>By the way, Jeremy, have you made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any headway on the antivirus recently?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… Actually, it's going kind of slow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm missing a lot of important codes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, with a little luck,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll find them today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then it's "Ciao, XANA."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll finally be able to shut</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>down the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We better forget about Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm transferring you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now head for the edge of the sector, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! There you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi Jeremy. Sorry, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up! I'll tell them to wait for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little longer and we would have started</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the party without you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where were you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had something to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right. Like being with William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Hey, don't you get tired</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of being jealous all the time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aha, I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were with him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can believe whatever you want!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be a jerk if you want, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must think I'm really dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful, you have visitors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey! Settle this later, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna give them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little Odd-acupuncture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, take cover!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great way to start off the morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Watch it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>More Kankrelats at five o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty interesting welcoming committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you expect?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA hates it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when we go fishing in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! The Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know. I feel kind of funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Anyway, it seems to have scared</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Kankrelats away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why would they go after you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll abort the mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Yumi! Materialization Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must have tripped on your fingers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein. Yumi isn't here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Is something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Umm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I must have made a mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll reboot the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't devirtualize you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go hide out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a tower while I figure this out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Direction south-southeast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't worry. I'll find the bug!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be safe in the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's not XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm worried about, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, no! I almost forgot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Today it's the class picture!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What class picture?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hello! The ninth-grade picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One day's suspension</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for any unjustified absence!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot, Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you just picture my parents' faces</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I get suspended?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do all I can, Yumi, I promise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey! I have an idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what a good actor I am, right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With a wig, a dress, and a little makeup,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could take your place</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the photo and bam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Signed, sealed and delivered!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Signed, sealed and suspended</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is more like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on a second, huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not a bad idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! You see, Ulrich finally admits</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm a great actor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You? You stink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I know a really great actress!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hi, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, can I talk to you for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah, of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have something really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>important to ask you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who? Me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And in exchange, I'm ready to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whatever you want!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, almost anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In my opinion,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when the Scyphozoa attacked you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he gave you some kind of bug, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Could he have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stolen some of my memory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's strange, it's my memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA seems to be after.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me, the Scyphozoa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>took something else from you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stand still, I'm launching</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the digital analysis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa has stolen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the sequence code for your human DNA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, when you're virtualized,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you keep your human DNA sequence code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't do it without it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It defines</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your molecular structure which--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, OK! Just get to the point!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No DNA, no way to get back to Earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, since Yumi can't be here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like you to stand in for her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… In the ninth-grade class photo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] You'll do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And… what do you want in exchange?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! What do you think I am?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want anything at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just call it a personal favor to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This can't be true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about my parents! And school!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And my brother…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to find a solution, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My whole life is on Earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do everything I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What if…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You have an idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think so. Send me to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you going to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just trust me this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alright, I'll bring you up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>close to the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A quarter of an hour to put on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a dress and a wig. Unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The hair looks like Yumi's.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but she doesn't dress like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She always wears black,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and her dresses are longer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and less…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Less sexy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissy] Well, why don't you bring me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of her dresses?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Good idea, we'll try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissy is being, uh, strangely helpful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I suppose. Weird, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool, it's open, I'm in. Piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Warn me if you see anyone coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I read you loud and clear, General.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, Aelita, the tower is nearby.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At ten o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] I'll have another </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Shiro-An</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did a very good job</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the white bean paste!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know Takeho, I've been feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-depressed lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] You don't pay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any attention to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's almost as if you never</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>listen to me anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] Hmm… Delicious…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sorry, what were you saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out for monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, now will you tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what your idea is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's always the same thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My mother warned me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to marry a man from Tokyo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, tell me what you're up to!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] There. Process launched!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What process?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The process of transferring my DNA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sequence code to your virtual structure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, Yumi belongs on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If anyone should stay on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until we find a solution, it's me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't agree with that! Aelita, stop--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew he was going to say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know that you're making</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a big sacrifice, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Call it whatever you want to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Do you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! I can't believe this…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't even know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how that kind of transfer works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! This is unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] I'm gonna wake Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darling? Have you seen Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] No,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she must have left for school already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She forgot her cell phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[videogame blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, is that how you stand guard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't see anyone go by.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got the dress?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't mean to hang up on you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it was either that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>or getting caught by Yumi's mum!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Listen to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is on Lyoko, transferring her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DNA sequence code over to Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… So what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean, that's not a good idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita doesn't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that when she transfers her code over,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her memory will be exposed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Are you saying say that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will just be able to steal it at will?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure that's why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Scyphozoa attacked Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is another one of XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>little evil schemes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then warn Aelita! Tell her to stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't! She's cut all communication</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to get to Lyoko fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I wouldn't exactly call glamorous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it will do. You can count on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Sissy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I owe you one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only ten more minutes before the transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything will be just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Girls!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You leave them alone for five minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's mess after mess after mess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, warm up the scanners,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi. I was looking for you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the school yard this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, wait, who are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the principal's daughter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Elisabeth. Too weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, first of all, my name is Sissy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and second of all, juts shut up, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK, Elisabeth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissy slaps him]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh, that hurt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You should</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be able to spot the tower now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There it is. We'll be there in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one more minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Stop right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the transfer takes place,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA will steal all your memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita, stop everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're so stubborn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was a silly thing to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I thought I was doing the right thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I understand and I appreciate it too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're turning into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a real human being.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're beginning to confuse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>generosity with stupidity!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, we still have no idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to save, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't bet on that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just happen to have a brilliant idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has stolen Yumi's DNA code sequence,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so it must be in his memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And how do we get access to XANA's memory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why are you dressed up to look like Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's none of your business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, that dumb haircut</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of yours is really old-fashioned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never look old-fashioned, understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything looks fashionable on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh, it's a good thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't eat breakfast this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right! Shut up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's all this noise about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Is something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi! I'm speaking to you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] I can explain everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy darling!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Daddy darling!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[principal Delmas] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's enough!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>By the way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, just a little detail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without your human DNA sequence code,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're just as vulnerable as Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If you get hit, you'll disappear forever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Come on! Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The countdown has started!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have three minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get out of the Core Zone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First we have to find the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Check at the end of the corridor!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I spotted the mechanism on the wall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the end of the room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I see it over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like a trap to me, but when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you gotta go, you gotta go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Watch out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The whole ceiling is booby trapped!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster, guys! You've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one minute left to turn the key!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Timber!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! [groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good work, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After you, ladies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Here comes our taxi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better not miss it! Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you know where to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's DNA sequence code?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really… But I'll manage somehow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] The Flying Mantas' nest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is about to hatch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have much time left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Yumi… I wanted to apologize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was none of my business</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you've been doing…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's true. But I'll tell you anyway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was buying two tickets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the Subsonics' concert</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it wasn't easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bad Internet connection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out! The nest has hatched.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Oh, that's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending it to you now, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, I've got it! OK, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll download it back to you in a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to be real happy to go ho--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Did you have time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to reinsert her code?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two, get out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The North Tunnel! It's open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi. Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's OK, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's out cold, but she's here with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about you, Odd? How are you feeling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ever been flattened by a steam roller?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's simple. Just get yourself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>devirtualized in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Your father caught you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I going to get suspended?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry! I saved your day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get punished but not you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I know how to talk to my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here! Here's your dress back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's really nice of you, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, she's right, thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you you could count on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Mmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm-hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Sissi, uh, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How would you like to go see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Subsonics with Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding? Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something's really fishy about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the way Sissi's behaving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe deep down she's a very nice person.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or she's really crazy about Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a mess!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>