<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ATTACK OF THE ZOMBIES</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[faint scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light bulb rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[kids chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, how did the Italian test go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't string two words together…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sei veramente nullo in italiano,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mio caro Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It means "You're so lame at Italian,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, old buddy!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see? I didn't even get that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Sissi! What do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your father's decision to set up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an exchange program with France?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our readers want to know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dear Milly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your paper doesn't have any readers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And anyway, I don't need the whole school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-knowing what I think… Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No danger there, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd need a brain to think!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good old Odd, unfunny as ever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shut up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I hate her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not the only one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're wrong, I tell you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I didn't say that Kiwi was stupid!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, you said he was brainless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you throw him a stick,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he won't run and fetch it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Neither would you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does that make you brainless?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franks and beans or ravioli?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's he doing there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Jim sees him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's gonna be in trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take him back to his room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll meet you in the showers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] Good doggy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shower turns on]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shower turns off]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly strains]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, you're not going to finish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your chocolate pudding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that your fourth one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd is like a cow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He has more than one stomach!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ta… Tamiya came after me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She looked so strange, and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her eyes were completely white…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They were horrible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She looked like Doctor Schrank!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's Doctor Schrank?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The psycho TV brain surgeon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Hospital of horrors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Smells like XANA, doesn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm launching a superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer bleeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down, it'll be all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must have had a bad dream.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! I didn't! It was real!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's head for the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll let Yumi know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? Uh-huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-huh, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. No problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Was that Ulrich? Your boyfriend?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki! For the 100,000th time…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He is not my boyfriend!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] ♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi's in love! </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Yumi's in love! ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi's in love! </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] Hiroki,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>leave your sister alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are such a pain! I'm going to bed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think it's serious. Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go get your father please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a problem with Milly Soloviev!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! Come back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll meet up at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Woah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies growl and moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Woah! About-face, everybody!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, nothing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're surrounded by zombies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Zom-- Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Rosa faints]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool it, maggot-faces!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan and growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thumps and whacks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relieved sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] There! You see, I wasn't dreaming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet they'll be back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with reinforcements.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] The problem with the living dead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that you can't kill them…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because they're already dead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar] No, I'm not joking! Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone key tones]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Zombies! That's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like in </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Out of the Tomb</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I hope Ulrich got away alright!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's probably at the factory by now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we've gotta join him ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where d'you think you're going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Outside?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way! It's too dangerous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's our problem, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar] Sorry, I'm the oldest one here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I'm responsible for the group,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm telling you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're staying here and waiting for help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want zombies to get you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If they attack here again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll need as many here as possible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone who tries to get out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has gotta get past me first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! William thinks he's Bruce Willis!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all we needed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do I do now? Can't get through!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Sissi, listen, we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get to a safe spot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get back to the lunchroom fast</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get some help. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[owl hoots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolf howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A supercomputer that lets you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go into a virtual universe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where you have to battle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an evil enemy called XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you put it that way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I admit it sounds a little weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you wanna stop this zombie attack, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and I have to get to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm sorry, but I don't believe you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so we're all staying together!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Plan B. I'll distract him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you take off with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Jackie Chan! So you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're the boss around here or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! And I want us all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get out of this unharmed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look! They're getting away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but it's for your own good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll thank me when you get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of this, safe and sound!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Safe and sound… Yeah, thanks a lot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator door hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Oh, fantastic. No one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[policewoman] Hello? Anybody here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh… yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[policewoman] Good evening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We got a call alerting us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about an attack… by…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, anyway… You haven't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seen anything suspicious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going on around the campus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh, zombies… Living dead?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I haven't been out of my gatehouse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As far as I know, everything's normal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you it was just another</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stupid kid's prank, right? Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you! Goodnight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distant barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy, it's me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you at the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Still not there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This joker William won't let us out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. I'll see what I can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jim! You heard this thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about some… zombies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's completely nutty!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, so much for the way out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What have you guys been up to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been waiting at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Haven't you heard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a living dead convention over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm trying to find a way to get Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the factory but it won't be easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi hangs up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] They're coming from all sides.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, there's Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He found me! See how smart he is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, my little diggity dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! That's the same dog we saw</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the hallway just before Tamiya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got zombified!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, what's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd strains]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William! Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to tie him up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got a plan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but I'm not sure you'll like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar] So you're saying Kiwi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is possessed by this XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. But now, thanks to you, Kiwi's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere ready to bite us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, we're surrounded</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by an army of the living dead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you had let us out before,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we wouldn't be in this mess!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you'd gone out you might</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be a zombie yourself! Idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm getting tired of hearing about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this factory and your supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kill the zombies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Come on, deadheads!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich imitates zombie moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Open up! It's me, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Open up, I said! I'm not one of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's lying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Prove it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a subscription to </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Pretty Girl</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I still sleep with Nin-Nin,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my stuffed moose!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That has nothing to do with it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that just proves you're a lame-o!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombie growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You open this door,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you bunch of pea-brained dorks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's Sissi, all right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas strains]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come on! It's now or never!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moaning and growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dunbar snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That one's on me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Urgh! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get back to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Get into the scanners!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start the virtualization process!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, ladies! Ready to roll!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanner humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanner buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanner whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And here's the Overwing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, you're getting better, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon, we'll be landing on top of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, on your way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and watch out for nasty surprises!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] What are they doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're preparing a final assault!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's okay…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growling and sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[manhole cover scrapes open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Overwing whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated tower in sight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Krabs also in sight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's played his cards right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wanted to bring you to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but with the fewest bodyguards possible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why Kiwi bit Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but not you or me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] But now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA doesn't need me anymore!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What do you mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta deactivate the tower fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I get zombified, I won't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be able to launch the return in time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't talk about the mess we'll be in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Krabs growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita nods in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're gonna try to push through!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's suicide!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't make it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will be alone with the Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fan swishes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fan charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, guys, this is it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Rosa gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I think I'm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Rosa gasps and passes out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're on our tail!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ladies,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you know what you're doing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, so do I, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb screams and pans clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take my fan! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Overwing powers down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miserable Kankrelat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to go on foot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Dunbar growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead! I'll take care of it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi strains]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Don't drag your feet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Jeremy! The tower's disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Maybe we went the wrong way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, wait, the tower's there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can see it on my screen!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, Jeremy! It's straight ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are we gonna get to it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can tele-transport Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're crazy! If you fail,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she'll fall right into the digital sea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] You have a better idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I trust her, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[resonance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi! Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi cries out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rushing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elevator door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fan swishes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's one of XANA's tricks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Krab growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy! A Krab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Keep going! Normally,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it wouldn't dare fire at you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! Ha-ha! Nice job! Ow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zombies moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly and Sissi whimper]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Don't you touch Milly, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zombies moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly and Sissi whimper]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd snarling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you program the return to the past?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snarls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi and Milly screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tower powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tower deactivated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Re--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You see? I didn't even get that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! What do you think about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your father's decision to start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an exchange program with France?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our readers want to know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dear Milly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your paper doesn't have any readers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And anyway, I don't need the whole school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>knowing what I think. Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I hate her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true that she's a pain, but you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>deep down I think she really likes you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I really think that she can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be very brave and a real nice person…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she wants to be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… In fact, you never can guess</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a person's true colors, can you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>