<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>CANINE CONNUNDRUM</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't shake the guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I'm coming in for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Watch out on your left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi, I'm aligned with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, tall dark and handsome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll never get anywhere with her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't back off a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take my advice, give her some room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yoo-hoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cat and mouse, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through compute]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The coast is clear, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can take off now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi's coming in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take over for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. I'll break away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, watch out! Torpedoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way, fish face!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys are way low on energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gonna have to abort the mission now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We didn't even get close to the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's my point.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You still have too far to go,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and with XANA harassing us all the time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's way too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm coming in on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, I'll lock on your Navskid, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Okay Odd, you're the target now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Olé!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's fantastic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just like in practice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our fighting techniques are improving,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it doesn't change a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're still too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta bring you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Rotation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[torpedoes blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] This one is mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He overstayed his welcome a long time ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>My pleasure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Navskids in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey! Wait for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Maximum propulsion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's another mission down the drain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't even remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what we were trying to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] "It's such a simple procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We construct</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an intermediate digital sinusitis</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with intergalactic lyrical context,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all multiplied by the virtual factors</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Thales and Pythagoras.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Piece of cake."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sniggers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect imitation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… What do you say we go to sleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, What did we agree on about your dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… There was no need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get carried away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me try and guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No seconds in the lunchroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A prank that backfired?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Girl trouble?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Worse. Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not that terrible, is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you wanna bet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi pants and barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You think I like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the idea of sleeping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in wet sheets every time you forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take him for a walk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Put yourself in his place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The poor little thing's locked up all day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The poor thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And me, how do you think I feel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, paper makes Kiwi sick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So if you didn't leave your books</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all over the place… Right, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what about my stuff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it because I leave them around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Kiwi steals them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I spend my life digging through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the campus grounds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mr. Reilly thinks I'm a nut </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>case!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm really sorry, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but something's gotta be done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He ought to be punished, and that's that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Objection, Your Honor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Before sentencing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my dog has the right to a lawyer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you're an animal lover.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta help me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>defend my little diggity dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I wouldn't mind,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but after what he did to my new shoes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just last week… No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I get the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the sentence?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To make Kiwi understand his bad behavior,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's gotta stay in the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for two weeks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Two weeks in the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how could you do that to him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] It was easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, he'll be fine there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The factory's not so horrible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so horrible?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Staying for hours in a computer lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>may be fine for Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but not for my dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I even remembered your froggy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one understands you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially not our so-called friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be brave, my little diggity dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping rapidly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music crescendoes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hello there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad to see so many of you here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at my Pentchak Silat class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pentchak Silat, as its name indicates,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a combat technique,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is half aesthetic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>half self-defense and half spirituality.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, well, um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These three halves could save your life,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially if you ever parachute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the middle of the Burmese jungle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the height of the monsoon season.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I see we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an extra student today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, this class is open to everybody,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna learn Pinching Skillets too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers] It's called Pekhach Silar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you two doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We came here to be with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I love hanging out with you, sis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough talking and let's get to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want you in groups of two for a warm-up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to begin</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with short little warm-up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly and Tamiya] Excuse us, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, just what are you two doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We wanna do a story on Paunchy Muskrat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ishiyama said you wouldn't mind at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? Did you say that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not her… It was him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Well, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matthew] …and what a fantastic pass to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the center forward who takes the ball…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Well, go on Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matthew] …sizes up the goalie,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who looks kind of lost and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matthew laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take your time, why don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's impossible to concentrate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with all that racket going on behind us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The defenseman steals the ball</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and heads down the field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He passes. Goal! That makes 13 to two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, would you guys mind making</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little bit less noise, please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're trying to concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Concentrate, that's all you bookworms do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you try something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>important like foosball?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you talking to me, Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Which sector?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-In the Desert Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cellphone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Einstein. What? Oh no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi already has a hard time whenever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I leave. Now if have to go to Lyoko…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay, I'll see you over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready? Begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi and Johnny grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, what you tried to do was a </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>langkah</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is complicated for a beginner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi, demonstrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Get the idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cellphone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a XANA alert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you watch what you're doing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you dork?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Deep breaths, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As my Burmese master said,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Serenity is vital</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in order to stay calm." Stern…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ishiyama, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, sorry, we gotta go…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little emergency to take care of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Have a good training class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's Kiwi Two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what he's doing here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he let himself out to do his business,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then Jeremy must've upgraded the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what? I think it was XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who pulled a few strings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll try to distract him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rapid beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning, shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I want a clear explanation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did all these</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mechanical dogs come from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have time to explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only chance we've got is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if Ulrich and I can get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, do you remember your dog robot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Surprise, there's a whole army of them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lined up outside the gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only built one Kiwi Two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he's just programmed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>to play basketball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, don't look now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I think XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to form a whole team.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna try and get out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the boiler room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet you at the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, don't try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to pin anything else on him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not your Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's mine, Kiwi Two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's been Xanafied and multiplied by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Yumi are stuck in the gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're gonna try and get out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't know if they will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you take me for a nitwit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Ishiyama?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Absolutely not, you've already been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the factory a few times.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course, we had to erase your memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>every time by returning to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, and once this is over,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you won't remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any of it either, as usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Craziest story I have ever heard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You watch too many</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stupid Japanese "mangos."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is to say… Can you prove</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that what you're saying is true?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, how do you explain all of those</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>robot dogs out there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think Jeremy built them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all by himself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Listen, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta trust us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we don't get to the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita won't be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll all be attacked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by those mechanical dogs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I have confidence in Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't usually trust Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But since she has confidence in Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for today, I'm gonna trust her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But just for today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me too, I trust Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I keep telling my sister</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she should go out with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tell her and tell her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she pretends she doesn't want to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… You mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how you plan on getting to this factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We obviously can't just walk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the door,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there's a chance that we might be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get from here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the sewers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through an air duct.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] But for that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll have to create a diversion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And why shouldn't I be the one who tries</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get out through the air duct,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell me that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because you're too… Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because you wouldn't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where to go afterwards.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it seems pretty clear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'm launching the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do your stuff, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Transfer Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping].</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come out XANA, and fight like a man!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is northwest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep your eyes out for uninvited visitors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here are your vehicles…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Overwing and overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] There's the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird. No one's around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go while the going is good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The faster we save the world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the sooner we can get back for lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now… Are we all set?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Let's be careful, kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that, you filthy beast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, little doggies! Come and get it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music crescendoes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on! I'll cover you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, look out. On your right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were expecting you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Manta!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better be careful Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see Tarantulas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi managed to make it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy. I'm gaining altitude again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, Aelita. I'll try to find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how Yumi and Ulrich are doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cellphone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how come you answered Ulrich's phone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because he's in no condition to talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your robot and his clones</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sic'd him in the leg,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just like they did Milly and Johnny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Now listen here, Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know whether</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you and your strange gang</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are capable of doing anything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you can, do it fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita, we've got to shift</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into high gear right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that Ulrich's hurt pretty bad,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Milly and Johnny aren't much better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not exactly in paradise either,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there, Aelita. Just a little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unfinished business to attend to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling and barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting, groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, my little buggy friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm the boss from now on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Einstein! Reload me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Coming up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A good thing that you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Einstein, where are my arrows?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, are you still there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or did you take Kiwi out for a walk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunting, gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, what do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm reloaded!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Just you and me, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good shot, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I called the police for help ages ago,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they still haven't come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the robots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They won't let anyone through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of this place, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you've already tried it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it didn't work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>From now on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm chief officer of this unit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hiroki, Tamiya, take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all these floor mats over to the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna help me pile them up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] We're gonna build us a barricade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And all I wanted to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was spend the afternoon with Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yowls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I fulfilled my mission, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Victory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dog's a genius,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I wouldn't have given him your job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita just fell into the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] They're getting in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bring them on. The more the merrier.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It takes more than some tin cans</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to scare Jim Morales.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you expect my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to show up to bail me out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He won't be coming today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Surprise. I can duplicate myself too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You mean you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>haven't launched a return to the past yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And when I saw</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how the Kiwis multiplied themselves,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I decided to do the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The rest was easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, you are really amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, she's not the only one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She managed to get away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because William was distracted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was an accident.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still, what if he hadn't been there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, who do we have to say thanks to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To you, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me? No, to Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who do you think reloaded my Laser arrows?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, so Kiwi's a hero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you trying to say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just that heroes don't sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in abandoned factories.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's your call.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, you're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who shares a room with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can come back home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You feeling okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I was… thinking of something else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see, he's a brand new dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's much more calm,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and much better behaved and more…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd, your pants, look at them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? That's just…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, for ventilation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It gets so hot here at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure it wasn't Kiwi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up to his old tricks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you it wasn't him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we go and eat now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>