<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's only got ten life points left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready, girls! I'm starting up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the devirtualization process!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated towers, Lyoko battles, danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't you guys starting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get sick of all this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, sometimes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really wish we were done with XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… You missed an episode, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, Aelita is carrying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a miserable virus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that links her to our old friend XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye bye XANA means bye bye Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I don't know how to create</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an antivirus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, not just yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I have an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we explore the new mysterious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sector we discovered?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sector Five?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we don't know what's in it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure we do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are monsters, ultra-dangerous traps</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a Scyphozoa, as you call it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that wants to steal Aelita's memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, but what if</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's something else there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like information about XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to go back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good idea. All three of us will go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You mean, all four of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna be part of this expedition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With that Scyphozoa slinking around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What if there's a tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate? Think about it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to be there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With bodyguards like us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she has nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And I promise to be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Tomorrow night… exploration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, my gosh! It's so late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents must be going bananas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye! See you tomorrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And as for us, we missed dinner again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And when I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was spaghetti and meatballs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car honking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we need to talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] You come home</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>late every single night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight is the last straw!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's past ten o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you didn't even bother</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to telephone us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you haven't eaten anything either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on, dear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you have a problem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you know you can tell us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, really, everything's fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was studying math at Maïtena's house.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maïtena Lecuyer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… That's strange. When I called her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she was studying… by herself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] You're lying to us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi. That's not like you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I worry about you, sweetheart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] Tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's bothering you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise you that everything's just fine!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You saw my last report card.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It was great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, why worry about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. and Mrs. Ishiyama sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm concerned, Takeho…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to have to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot more strict.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nice of you to come with me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm big enough to go to school alone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-really I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you were,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then you would stop lying to us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and tell us why you come home</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so late all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you gonna watch me 24 hours a day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I in prison, or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're trying to understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you and to protect you too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh wow! The entire Ishiyama family.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I bet that you'll be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>picking me up as well, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be waiting for you here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at five o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] I advise you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to be late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, isn't that adorable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all giggle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] They're not going to ease up on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what a mess!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The worst thing is, I hate lying to them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just explain to them that we're fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a virtual universe against</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a demoniac Artificial Intelligence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That ought to reassure them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dork.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to win back their trust in you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think maybe you should stay away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Lyoko for a little while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What about exploring Sector Five?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's for tonight, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Jeremy will give you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>play-by-play update.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Promise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, guys! I know you're all dying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go to Mrs. Hertz's class. Off we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Did you study</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the marine biology test?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I did. Listen. Fish are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>remarkably well adapted to water,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-what's more, they can swim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] You are so lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Off to the Forest Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Everything OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The monsters must be sleeping.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They need all the sleep they can get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to recover from all the grief</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've been giving them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to get to the other end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the sector to take the Transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna materialize your rides.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd! You promised to be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go straight ahead and hurry up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before the monsters get there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We made it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>OK. I'm layering the coast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] There's the Transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you there, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everything OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Everything OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, they're in the Transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-All is well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell them I'm thinking about them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Happy campers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm beginning to get used</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to these little trips.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh… not me. I shouldn't have had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that fifth desert at lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, the wall is about to open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, meaning the countdown</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to find a way to deactivate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That must be the answer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to exploring further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Watch it, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Everything will be fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd promised to be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's started.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what'll happen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if Aelita loses her life points, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have no intention of losing her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The last time, there was a big room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the end of this hallway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I got a feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the architecture of the Core Zone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>changes each time you go there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's a great help</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for finding our way around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we knew everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we wouldn't be exploring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got two Creepers on your tail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've only got three minutes left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop the countdown. Get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Haven't we already been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How should I know? Everything looks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same in this place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Aelita grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Forty life points in one go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those Creepers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sure are powerful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're powerful, and really ugly too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy? Any ideas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but I've got news for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're in a labyrinth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Make a left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at each fork and leave a mark there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the way is already marked,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then make a right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This is incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll never get out of this thing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You'd better!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just two minutes left to find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop the countdown!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're out, Jeremy! We made it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Nothing like having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little luck on your side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why complicate things, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, great. Now what do we do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jeremy, can you see anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from your end?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] So you need me again, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go back to where you were.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I spotted a mechanism on the wall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry! Time is running out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts] Me at it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fourteen…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirteen… Twelve… Eleven…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ten…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nine…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eight… Seven…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Six… Five…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Four…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! The countdown is over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The room is bound to change now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, no more Creepers. That's a start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I'll rematerialize Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich and I'll get you out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd and Ulrich didn't come back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, that's impossible. Are they lost?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the moment they are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, there's no rematerialization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Sector Five?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sure there is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once we find the right program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And do you think you can find it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's probably as easy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as finding your antivirus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna do the impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki, could you make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some more noise, please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The volume's as high as it goes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go into the other room, Hiroki. Go on now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[videogame noise]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I pass.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me too, I pass.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then the game is over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have five points more than you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-On the </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>goban, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget that I played the whites.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>komi</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I win by half a point.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's bedtime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good night, my dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Badly, head for the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's heading towards you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay calm. Yumi's coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Can I come in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to talk to you for a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy? I'm in the elevator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You have to get to Aelita in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa is there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What about Odd and Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] You want the best-case scenario?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'd rather.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I've got about a one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a million chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of finding the right code</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring them back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So sorry to bother you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at such a late hour, Headmaster Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we're so worried!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, yes, I understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's quite possible that Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is somewhere on the campus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why, sure! She's probably hanging around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with her little gang of friends! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You're on the edge</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the territory, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is gonna do all he can to keep you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from taking the Transporter!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Enter the code!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Huh? No one is here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one in Stern's room either!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Looking for someone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Hmm… Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you know where your friends Stern,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois and Della Robbia might be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Probably up to no good, as usual,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't know where, although…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] their little mascot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can find them for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Mascot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What mascot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ta-dah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A filth-ridden mangy mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh! Excuse me, Mister Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, little puppy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's your master, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go get him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's follow him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there, Aelita! Yumi's on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes. I'm in the Arena!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Transporter got to me just in time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Horrible Kankrelat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Listen up now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to get to the corridor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and trigger the mechanism</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-before the countdown runs out! OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I'm right about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how the core zone functions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my plan should work!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[owl hooting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with that hound?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Oh! I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] This reminds me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of when I used to work in the sewers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You… huh… used to work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the sewers, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Only two minutes left, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Down to ten points, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't not the time to mess up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, we're wasting time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Give me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you let go of that slippery flip?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Let go of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, this is no time to drag your feet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let's look at the mechanism!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's on your right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have ten seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Two seconds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It works, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The whole zone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is being reconfigured.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> We did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, take the access behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! It's some kind of elevator!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what we do with elevators, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We ride them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Try to grab Aelita as you go by!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you taking me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] There's an interface.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I can get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This interface gives access…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to XANA's own data!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sector Five… is where XANA lives!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] XANA is not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a very good housekeeper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are some weird things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hanging around this place!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I've got access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to all kinds of data! It's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Look for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the specific devirtualization code</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you find it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can save Odd and Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[manta rays growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to need the Overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, oh, bad news!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When Aelita is working on that interface,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do anything from my end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I found it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm transmitting it to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK! I'm taking over again now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] What would a nice girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like Yumi be doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Where are we anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, the Overwing now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do we get out of here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] There are some tunnels.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] They're closed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let's see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tunnels… What if…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if they corresponded to those</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that open into the Arena?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yippee! It works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got out through a Way Tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>OK, now get to a neutral tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I'm ready, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It's OK, Jeremy! I'm here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what about the others?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the new code!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now all we can do is hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! We did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, how do you feel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Say something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"Something"…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I believe you </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have some explaining to do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Hey! Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Ha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trying to outsmart me, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What the… Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is this place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Nothing rings a bell, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Funny 'cause you've been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here before!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't remember this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, yes and no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So then… you still refuse to give us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an explanation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Alright, I'll tell you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in love!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi! I knew there was a reason.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And will you tell us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your boyfriend's name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, sorry, I won't, mom!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that sure seemed to satisfy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your parents! What did you tell them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The truth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>