<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>NOBODY IN PARTICULAR</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Quiet down, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The results of the class test</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were far from brilliant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your grades were almost all C's and D's.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Obviously, there are exceptions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois, I gave you an A-minus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The minus was a reminder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there is no such thing as perfection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, you are clearly pushing the limits</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your "I don't care" attitude.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A nucleus is not made up of croutons,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but protons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>D-minus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If memory serves,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and mine is more reliable than yours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you promised to put in an honest effort,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's clear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you didn't even look at your notes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This won't help</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the Academic Review tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Poliakoff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A kilogram of mercury doesn't weigh a ton.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, if I were you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd stop snickering like an idiot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Don't worry. It'll work out fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I doubt it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hertz will do all she can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to transfer me to ninth grade remedial.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They wouldn't do that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of the year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With my grades, don't bet on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents will kill me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finding time to fight XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be a real nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on. Nothing's been decided yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. A teacher may defend you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of transfers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have some good news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found a way to virtualize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly into Sector Five. Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without the Transporter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, that's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By interpolating the source codes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Planck's quantum space,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can get around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Heisenberg uncertainty theory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only risk is coming up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a mathematical singularity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm, it can work, but it's dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters] Before I am sure, I'll need a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A guinea pig?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right. Any volunteers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The shortest string bean is it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thumps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess today is not my day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll run the test tonight at eight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here. I'm leaving you my cherry soda</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in case I don't make it back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding! Thanks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I couldn't possibly accept.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, Yumi. You're the most worthy heir</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the great Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The first man to set foot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Sector Five without passing Go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you all get to the Arena?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! Last stop, everybody out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're good, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're standing by to welcome Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Loud and clear, Yumi. Ulrich? Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Logically, you should arrive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly into Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right between Odd and Yumi</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure you know what you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, well about 98 percent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich will be with you soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where is he? Did he take the local</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>instead of the express?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The virtualization did take place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He should have appeared next to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Maybe he was transferred</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the wrong place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll do a search, but I can't see how.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no! Impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy stutters] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He doesn't show up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the screens anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want us to sweep Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see if we can spot him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And have XANA take advantage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and pull a dirty one on us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, thanks. I'll run a search from here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better come back in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll re-materialize you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Nothing in the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing in the Arena.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing in the Celestial Dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing in the Core of Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not a trace in Sector Five, either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich has… disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't get this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Despite my research,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't managed to localize him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll keep searching from my room computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must be somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Go on, keep trying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you messed up big time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich may be lost forever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get off of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Kiwi, buddy, I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice! Thanks for such a warm welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's happening to me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can hear me, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well? Anything new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still no sign of Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He couldn't disappear into thin air.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do I make you see me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must have made a mistake somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't know where I messed up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yoo-hoo, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finally, someone who can see me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, will you cut that out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, you're a good dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any ideas to make them realize I'm here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe an emergent property</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>appeared in the algorithms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and altered the normal functioning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the virtualizations. It's possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Looks like a system bug to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] I'm down here, lower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through Kiwi] Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My training methods have finally paid off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi's talking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's me talking, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from inside Kiwi's body.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what are you doing inside my dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I entered Kiwi's body by accident.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's thanks to him that I can talk to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Otherwise, I was just like some kind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of completely disembodied ghost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What an adorable little diggity dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Knock it off or I'll bite you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mangy mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snaps fingers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I know what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>During the virtualization,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's body and mind separated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that why you couldn't localize him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, Ulrich is not there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's his inanimate body,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his corporal envelope,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which doesn't give the same signal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you put me back together?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since we have no classes today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go to the computer lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Aelita and run another search.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once we locate your body,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure I'll find a way to put you back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, and how long will that take you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope I have it all worked out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Cool! That'll give me time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see about my future.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? You still there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks and growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alive? That's great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did you find him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's that handsome looking guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Jim Morales.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clearing voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through Jim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's that handsome guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's that handsome looking guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you for finding it for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been looking for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans] Oh, my back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Mrs. Hertz? Just the person I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, I was hoping to talk to you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the Academic Review and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really, Jim. Call me Suzanne!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a favor to ask you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet me in the gym in five minutes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's very important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll be there, Mrs.-- Suzanne!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where can he be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Jim, darling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You told me you used to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a professional ballroom dancer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Buenos Aires, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, that's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good, I'll need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since you mentioned that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been dying to learn how to tango.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a minute, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to discuss</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the case of Ulrich Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, please, Jim, not now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Academic Review</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the time to deal with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll be too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need to discuss this now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, don't be like that, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a date with Pedro</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the Sunday dance and brunch,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I've got to dance the tango by then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I don't,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he won't pay any attention to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but first, let's talk about Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he had a second chance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he could get better, I think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must have given that boy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a thousand chances!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Honestly, I'm sick and tired</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of that lazy good for nothing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on now, Jim. Let's tango.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No second chance for Ulrich Stern,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no Australian tango lessons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Argentinian tango!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sounds like a zoo around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, cut it out, it's me, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What are you doing inside Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to smooth things with Mrs. Hertz,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-but up to now, no luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Yes, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We located Ulrich's body.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It turned up in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, great. I'll tell him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to get to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like Jeremy solved your problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, after the Academic Review.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after what happened with Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be there as soon as I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Odd Della Robbia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time for the Academic Review.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are the Class Representative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, something's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's body seems to move on its own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But isn't that normal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Of course not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Ulrich's brain,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it shouldn't do anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better get over here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as you can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now, I'm by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich are at the Academic Review.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats! Aelita, can you send a text message</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and tell them we've got an emergency?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, how should we begin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shall we treat the student case files</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-in ascending or descending order?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish you would show a little courtesy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cell phones are forbidden here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Turn yours off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, whom should we begin with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Abulabbas or Zlikaric?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Zlikaric!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Abulabbas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lady's choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We begin then with the case file</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Miss Sorya Abulabbas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We're okay. We reached the edge</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm sending you the Transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Holosphere system, connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The key is over there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-just on the other side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Right, and now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's look at the file of Jeremy Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All is well. Nothing to add.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I think that everyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would agree with me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he is an exemplary student.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In short, he never makes a mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never makes a mistake,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you must be kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Morales,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sports aren't everything, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, next student.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At your service!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, take the next passage on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both pant]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And now, go right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does everyone agree</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Della Robbia has remarkable potential</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he is lazy as the day is long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But wait, I think he's made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot of progress, especially in gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that so, Mr. Morales?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, a lot of progress.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others aren't afraid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when it's his turn at the javelin,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he stopped dropping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the shot put on his toes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll make a note of that in his file.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[distorted] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's closing in on the Great Hall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the Core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try not to lose him, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's easy for you to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He changed direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see another way out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, just a shaft.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's it! Go ahead, jump!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] So, now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we come to the case of Ulrich Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone care for some turnip soup?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Afraid that's all there is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we have a serious problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, this is scandalous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They could have left some variety</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like tomato or vegetable, or just coffee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I was referring to Ulrich Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He has stopped working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He does nothing at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] His grades are terrible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As far as I'm concerned,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I recommend he be transferred</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to ninth grade remedial,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where he has a vague chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of catching up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, is everyone in agreement?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I do not agree at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Neither do I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, you have the floor, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't make a decision</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>based only on my… his grades.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're far from excellent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not denying that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but from there to saying that I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he doesn't lift a finger</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is an awful lot to assume.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And don't forget that you were--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We were what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were once adolescents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He reached the Great Hall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the Core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, ladies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can you see a way in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No, it's a dead end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, what luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA must have opened up a passage for him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>leading directly into the Core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you? Can you do the same?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I wish I could, but you'll have to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by way of the Celestial Dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll take the elevator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember how much your emotions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>affected your work at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who in this room can say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they've never felt lost?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never had problems with their parents,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>never had girl or boy problems?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern will straighten out. He promised me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, seriously, don't you all think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he deserves a second chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if you look at it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from that point of view,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we might want to reconsider his case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I disagree completely!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And as the senior teacher,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel bound to impose my veto.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern should be transferred</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to ninth grade remedial, and that's all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heartbeats]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hurry! The shield layer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the sphere took a 30 point energy hit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you program our vehicles?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Come now, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were a teenager once, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I was,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I stand by my decision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suzanne, can I have a word with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Suzanne,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you give Stern a second chance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have my word</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'll teach you the tango,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the rumba, the cha-cha-cha,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and any other stupid…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ballroom dance you want. I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since everyone is against me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll leave that thumb twiddling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Stern in his current class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if he doesn't shape up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll ship him out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can I please go to the bathroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me too, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The emotion, you know what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About time. Ulrich, first of all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you must leave Jim's body now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I hope he doesn't flip out on us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I bet he'd rather not talk about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you over right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you wait in one of the cabins.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The minute your body devirtualizes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll re-fusion it with your mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just be patient, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't mess up this time, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who left our gym teacher</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the floor asleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, move it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one shield layer left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>protecting the Core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Move it? Easy for you to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only have two legs, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, perfect timing, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, one more blow with his saber,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the second shield layer's destroyed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted] Triplicate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, it's time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up your fusion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's a great feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have my body back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop! There, under your foot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Stern. Saved me on that one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why did you do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's just say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I've been in your shoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, my boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see that something positive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has gotten into that head of yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, I'm ready to dance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What should we start with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tango, paso doble, rumba?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting with a hot cup of coffee</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and six doughnuts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got jogging with the eighth graders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what about my ballroom</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dance lessons? You promised me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Suzanne! I think you had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one too many herbal teas last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They do weird things to your head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>