<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>GHOST CHANNEL</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Odd, take Aelita to the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's in trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on, Yumi, you can do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, princess, the home stretch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>two Bloks are coming at you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat. Be back in a second, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He is amazing! How does he do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The crowd is going wild.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Odd, cut it out, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] There's a third Blok!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A third one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[charged laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fiery whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, you've lost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>too many life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Take cover.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's too risky!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, one impact,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's game over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You've got ten life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ten is more than enough. Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see? What did I tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Great, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Congratulations!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>next time just enjoy the show,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and let the real pros get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the job done. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughing] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grumble]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go take care of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, take it easy. I was just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't mean it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Einstein, you hear me? It was a joke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Valerie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Valerie] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Benjamin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Benjamin] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Present, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Nicolas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Present. Hey, great work, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were better than ever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No hard feelings, Odd. It was...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Odd?... Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's absent? Well, and so is Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Present, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nicolas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Dylan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Dylan] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that was great work, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were never better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No hard feelings, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Sabrina?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Caroline?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Caroline] Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After what you said to him before,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's no wonder he's sulking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Odd, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Ulrich] Here, ma'am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I know that you're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I do not know is what you have to say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to each other that's so interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'd asked me if I'd noticed that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with all due respect, ma'am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Brower equation you wrote on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the blackboard is wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's not wrong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a mathematical point of view;</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it fails to take into account</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bronsky's theories</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the phenomenon of compared masses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should treat</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the second unknown element</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as a squared mass, not a factorial.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why yes, you're...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're absolutely right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you know where Ulrich and Odd are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[running footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door swings shut]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[running footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is weird. I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's gone too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[running footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Nobody here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Ulrich, Odd and Yumi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me they're with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? Didn't they come back from Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita, I've lost them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Something must've gone wrong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the return trip!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Calm down, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they couldn't have just vanished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and check the scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I look around Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Good idea. I'll go and see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You guys okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As okay as two guys can be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with two hours of bio ahead of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Anyone know why he's sulking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's angry at Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, something really strange</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>happened in English class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Kensington] "All the world's a stage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all the men and women merely players.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They have their entrances, and..."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"And all men and women merely players.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They have their entrances and..."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like a broken record.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it only lasted a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're thinking it could be XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't know, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it sure wouldn't hurt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep an eye on things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Nobody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pulsations?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Jeremy, this is serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone is very concerned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, for the last time, do you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where Yumi, Odd and Ulrich are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No, sir, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I'm sure you can imagine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>their parents are worried sick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] But I told you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know where they are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Think about it, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any clue could prove to be of great help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You four are always together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, sir. I'll think about it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I need to be alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have an awful lot of nerve, young man!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>However, if it's the only way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring you to your senses,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll give you three minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Thank you, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I felt your message. What's new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but they're not on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's an activated tower though,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only I can't seem to locate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm stuck in the Mr. Delmas's office.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are? Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll help you out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes Jeremy, just like XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can operate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the school's network as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen closely now...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I'm sure Jeremy knows more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than he's saying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Should we call the police?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've thought it over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you where they are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Pass the peas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] No, you can reach 'em yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] D'you hear Rockout's new single?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Didn't I tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, I needed new wheels</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I broke them on a ramp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So I call over the guy selling them...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Hey Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you use canary feathers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the washing machine instead of soap?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is so dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have you know that yellow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the "in" color this year!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What a dope!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Pass the peas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] No, you can reach 'em yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] D'you hear Rockout's new single?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, did you hear that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I sure did!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissy] That is so dumb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have you know that yellow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the "in" color this year!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't say anything that time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] We've got a problem, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] But there's nobody here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to wait a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll be here any minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pipes hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[watch ticking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[pipes rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, where are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pipe bursts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[steam hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim and Mr. Delmas coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's gone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He couldn't have just disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>for giving me a hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you realize that if...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't detect anything alive on the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scanners, it'll mean that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I know. We'll find out soon enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Empty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[disappointed sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] They aren't there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it, if they're not here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're not on Lyoko either,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, just before you got here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I captured this sound byte...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sort of radio</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or TV station transmission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But be careful, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was really bizarre. Let me show you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>All right, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We'll start with some stretching.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And one and two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and one and two...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And one and two...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] That's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Hey, watch what you're doing, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] You did that on purpose. I saw you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] And one...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] And two...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Hey watch what you're doing, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] You did that on purpose!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It happened again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll show you what it feels like!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] And two, and one...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's happening all the time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Keep going on your own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What am I looking at?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They didn't come back to Earth, did they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if what we're seeing is a recording?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how can that be, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm in the picture!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are weird things happening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any news from Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm having difficulty contacting her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if there's an activated tower or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but at the slightest alert,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll have to move in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, how come you're not doing phys ed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim agreed to excuse me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He did?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not exactly his star athlete.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta know how to handle him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Twenty-six, 27! Keep going! 28!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not like them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure isn't a tape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's happening somewhere, right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're neither in Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nor in the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're somewhere else!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've checked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the transfer protocol data,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and unless a sort of parallel world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>exists somewhere,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no such thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as an intermediate space.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless XANA has manufactured one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it! A world parallel to Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he modelled it after the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He couldn't have made a better trap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi and the others</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>think they're in reality,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's only an illusion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're living under XANA's control,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>completely at his mercy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We've gotta rescue them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Find out where the signal is coming from.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've been trying to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's been masked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The signal is scrambled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we have is a sound wave,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not the signal itself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what we'll have to use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta program it to guide</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the scanner and dive towards the source,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-using trial and error.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But that's crazy, and you know it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, who could do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're all alone, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gotta be me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you take over the controls,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be able to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we can't leave Ulrich and Odd and Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the mercy of XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I'm here in front of you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's the other Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's something I want to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather be entering a virtual world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find you waiting there for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So would I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've prepared the transfer procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can get into the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? Woah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, of course not. That would be too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA as Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ugh. There he is at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA as Jeremy] We've got a visitor, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's got to be it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better go now and have a closer look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's what you might call intuitive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she can be wrong sometimes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And let's face it Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any girl with a crush on you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't be absolutely normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Jeremy? Don't tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't find him strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well yeah, he's been acting weird lately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but to think he's hiding a huge secret...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, hello... Yumi, is that you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It started again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but this time it's worse than ever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time it's at my home!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What's going on, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're acting so, I dunno, so strangely.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They keep making the same gestures,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they act as if I'm not even there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as if they were phony imitations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my real mom and dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta do something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better not stay there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you in the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go to the factory. I'll warn Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] No, not Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just Odd, you and me, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's leave Jeremy out this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I... I have my doubts. See ya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope they're in their room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim snarling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[XANA as Jeremy] I've got you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA as Jeremy] Soon I won't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any more obstacles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I only hope it's not too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[running footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What about Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We didn't tell him, but you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once we're at the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-we can't get to Lyoko without him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll see when we get there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm afraid he can't be trusted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[leaves rustle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Must have been a squirrel or something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] C'mon, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb and Nicolas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb and Nicolas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Outta my way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim, Herb and Nicolas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For a program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're a pretty good imitation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolf howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no link.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like Lyoko didn't exist anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA as Jeremy] And that might be exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, but what are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got a message from Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that a tower's just been activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She said something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about a program to erase Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't heard from her since.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we've gotta check this out, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, wait a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the link has been cut,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how will you send us there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've created a new access protocol.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we need now are the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what are we waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold it, Odd. I'm not too sure of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, it's Jeremy, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta get moving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if Lyoko does get erased, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you thought about Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, you've gotta believe me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you have any doubt,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let Ulrich and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be transferred before you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elevator door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's a trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA as Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA, is that the best you can do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A cheap imitation to delay us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's lying! The phony is there. It's him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything here is phony.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never came back from your last trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're in a virtual world created by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That would explain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the inconsistencies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course it would.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA can make mistakes too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He only has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>theoretical knowledge of reality.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What he wants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to get you into the scanner,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get rid of you once and for all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's absurd, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true, we have no proof that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's not the one who's lying to us, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He could have created</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the inconsistencies too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly, to hold us up while Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Lyoko are being erased forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only proof is the fact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm here with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to decide</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which one of us is lying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's not me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Assuming as you claim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that this world is virtual,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you mind telling us how you got here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're listening, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got in here via the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm here in virtual form.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gave yourself away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone knows the real Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wouldn't step foot in the scanner;</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'd be much too frightened!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm sure he would go into the scanner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if his friends were in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No doubt about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Absolutely none.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's not logical, don't you see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's too scared to even try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm much too scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, then why haven't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I already done it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you why.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because he's not infallible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's knowledge of people</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is only approximative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and as far as friendship goes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not approximative; it's double zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good to see you again, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's not logical!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[XANA as Jeremy shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA in distorted voice] Not logical!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[minions growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are going to die!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat accelerating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[minions growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fast heartbeat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Jeremy! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanner powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, here I am. Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, fine. Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relieved sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got them back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of them, safe and sound.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The parallel world bubble has disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't remember anything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I feel just great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened to us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA created a replica of where you live</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you'd think it was reality.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He locked us up in a virtual prison.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] But Jeremy and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did all we could to set you free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Jeremy came to Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Join the daredevil heroes' club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks, Odd. No hard feelings, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Look, it's XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>welcoming committee!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're used to this. It's a piece o' cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>