<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>LOST AT SEA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey there, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein isn't with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't seen him yet today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speak of the devil, look who is here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting, sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me guess. You fell asleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of your computer again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Yeah, how'd you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have the imprint of your keyboard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on your forehead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Aelita laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was up all night working on a program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I came up with an idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for bringing William back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, could I talk to you for a sec?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, well, if you really have to, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead. I'll meet you inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, uh… Everybody says that girls</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really like you a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That depends on the girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, like my sister, for example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Beep, wrong. Try again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and I are good friends, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe that's just what she told you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But anyway, uh, I didn't want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk about Yumi, but about… Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Milly who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Milly Solovieff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that tall redheaded girl in seventh grade?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, little Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, of course I know her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] So?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, actually, I… I kind of like her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but when I try to talk to her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't think of anything to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just talk to her about the things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she likes… Her interests.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's got a passion for journalism.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great idea! Wouldn't it be great</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I could find her a scoop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She'd be crazy about me if I did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Yeah, a scoop for the paper, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just what kind of scoop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you can leave that to me, Ulrich. Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mid-tempo music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cutlery clinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did Hiroki wanna talk to you about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aw, he wanted my advice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's crazy about Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now isn't that cute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But isn't the guy a little young for her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No he's not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's just a little small for his age.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he skipped a grade in school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he acts even younger than his age.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurps loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Jeremy, tell us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about this new idea of yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever a human being is virtualized,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he or she emits a binary residue,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which we can say manifests itself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as an emanation of his physical person,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>resequenced in a sort of digital format.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-In English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you go to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you leave a kind of digital trace,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something like a scent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Couldn't you have said that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the first place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mm… No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I came up with a program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>based on William's DNA sequence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I recorded when he went to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the first time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I can upload this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto the Skid's sonar,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can hunt for him on the network</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>every time we go there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and finally find out where</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William really is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what you're saying is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Skid will become a sniffer sub.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, Odd, and since</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we don't have class this afternoon,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was going to suggest that we try it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mid-tempo music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki, what do you think you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Give me that back right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure look far away, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nothing. Just thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about something Hiroki said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Uh… Nothing, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oops, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong? Does Sissi wanna go out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with him or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! Yumi, hold on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Whoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is this yours, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? You kidding me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A notebook with a dark cover</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a flower is not my style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give it back right this second, you brat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aw, come on sis, I was just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, here it is. Huh? Well, it was here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna laugh,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I dropped it, I think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You better be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's a pretty good shot of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's your secret admirer? Let me see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Yumi's, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's her diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why she was running after Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is a great chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see what she thinks of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no. What's written inside here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not my business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't forget that Yumi and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are just good friends, that's all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I'm not sure at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey Yumi, what is it? You look angry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, my stupid brother. He stole a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something important to me, and he lost it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Look, Yumi, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I upgraded the Skid's sonar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All set for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh right, you don't know yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might have found a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring back William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow, cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Uh, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been looking for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I wanted to apologize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had no right to take your diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you find it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, but I… I looked everywhere, I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, until you find it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can consider yourself an only child!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh nothing, some "diary straits."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll tell you about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, can I see you for a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, so what do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We go to lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what's the deal? I thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were going to return the diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you saw how crushed Hiroki was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I'm the one who gives the diary back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi'll still be angry with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what if we fix it up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that Hiroki finds the diary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and gives it to Yumi himself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's two birds with one stone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She gets her diary back, and he gets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his sister back. Pretty good idea, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, great, but how do you plan to do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hide the diary under a pile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of leaves in the park,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>near the gardener's shed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but give me a few minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I've got to get Kiwi first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot to walk him this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I totally messed that up, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi will calm down and forgive you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially when she gets her diary back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but I've looked everywhere for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I even retraced my steps back to here…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing. I dunno what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, by the way, this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought I saw Mr. Riley</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>raking up some dead leaves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the park grounds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what? He's the groundskeeper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's his job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if he raked up the diary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the same time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's dumb. Why would he do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. He might have raked it up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by accident.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! The diary could be under</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a bunch of leaves! Let's go check!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Wait up, Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lighthearted music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Well, find anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Keep looking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[leaves rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which one did you put it in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki will find it soon enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, there you are. Where were you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my little diggity dog? Get in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] I got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[suspenseful music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never forgive you for this, Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't look at me like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was all there when I hid it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Get to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start up the virtualization process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All set? I'll launch the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>For once,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it won't be ladies first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[up-tempo music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi's in a foul mood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better tell her the truth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And how do you think she'll react</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she finds out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you were the one who hid it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, this was your idea, Casanova.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[low-tempo music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ladies and gentlemen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your elevator's waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[low-tempo music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everyone, get on a teleport spot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing vibrations]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone ready? Stand by for liftoff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Releasing supports now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Vertical propulsion operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Lift off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready to dive into the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holoweb system connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[futuristic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We've left Lyoko, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Rotation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Turbo propeller launched.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[program beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm running the program. Stand by</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to receive the initial coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A problem, princess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We've got a system error.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think the Skid has a malfunction</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in part of its sensory capacity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I see it, Aelita. It's my program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that bugged up the Skid's sonar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The mission's too dangerous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without sonar. Gotta end it now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger. Returning to drydock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, next mission, diving into my pillow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and burying myself under the covers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Objective: a good night's sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to clear my head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but you're gonna have to postpone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your nap, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got three Kongers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>heading straight for the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Navskids away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Take this, fish face!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's pretty effective when she's mad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got one on my tail!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's sticking to me like glue!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, bull's eye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice one, good buddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wanna team up for the last one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, let's do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Nice job, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to come home now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Navskids in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, where's Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have any trace of her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've lost her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She must have gotten hit by a Konger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, you think she might have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>been virtualized for good?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping, scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I… I don't think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The data recording from the fight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't show any sign</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of her having been eliminated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That means she's still somewhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on board her Navskid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere in the middle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, but the Skid is in no condition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys have to come back in for me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to run a repair program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't just leave her behind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, no one's leaving anyone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but all of us run the risk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of being virtualized forever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Skid's systems down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you're right. We'd better go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How long will it take you to fix it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Reprogramming the sonar is linked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to balancing the bipolarity of flux</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the one hand, on the other--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just tell us when we can go back, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon, as long as you let me concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Ulrich. I'll help him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call you as soon as we know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can anybody hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know where I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ow… I'm in trouble. Almost out of power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can you hear me? Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Somebody please answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a nightmare!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax. You heard Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She isn't gone from the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll bring Yumi back. Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growling, barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what have you got there, Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-this is Yumi's diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi saw me bury it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he thought it was a game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So I guess he dug it up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and buried it here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right where we're sitting now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great. We found her diary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but now we lost Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost out of power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's cold here, and I feel all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi, you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only one torpedo left, so don't waste it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, not enough power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm not done yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If I reduce power in my shield,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should have enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, you and me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-An explosion. A Navskid torpedo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're on our way. They found Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna go home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who am I gonna play with if you go away?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Hiroki, "foot" becomes "feet"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the plural.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] How do you know all that, sis?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what are you children up to this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Hiroki laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, how long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, at least ten minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had no right to take your diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Until you find it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can consider yourself an only child!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aw…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never forgive you, Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi sent us a message, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, we'll go and get her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to finish the calculations first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've isolated the area,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it'll be impossible to find her exact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>location before I fix the Skid's sonar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if she fired a torpedo,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that means she's in a jam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've transposed the data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the explosion into the Holoweb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get her position via triangulation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There she is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She must have gotten sucked into a hub.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why we lost all trace of her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[serious music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the sonar is still down, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So going under right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna be a big risk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. I'll go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Count me in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we all waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's a hub dead ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I read you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the coordinates from where</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi fired her torpedo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aspiration into hyperfluid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in three seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang on tight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What's he waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William distorted] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So, Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thought you'd wander off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without telling us where you were?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It took you long enough to get here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I wouldn't mind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little fish soup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess I better cook it though first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I cannot leave you alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a minute, huh, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay. He's behind Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Big mistake, William. Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mission accomplished, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, great job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now anchor yourself to the Skid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and head back in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, they're all coming home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But one day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll bring you back, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sonar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mid-tempo music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted you to know just how sorry I am</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for what I did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Thanks for bringing it back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I understand now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that what we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is more important than some old diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgive you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you in love or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get out of here…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>