<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>CRASH COURSE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd oughta be here already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were supposed to play foosball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know Odd, something probably</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>came up at the last second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet he's afraid to show up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I know Odd, he's hiding somewhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause he knows I'll beat him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it just might be that redhead with braids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our ladies' man is at it again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter and indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know life isn't bad at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't know you split up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Melanie, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah… Melanie, right. Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She wasn't very…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She was a little too…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, actually a lot more… Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see what I mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I see Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that you collect girlfriends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the way other people collect stamps!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I tell you it's for real this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Believe me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Camille, she's it, she's the one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's so funny, sensitive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and really cool too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just like all the girls you fall for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich slurps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe, but Camille has something special</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the others don't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… She's crazy about dogs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What's so funny?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that makes all the difference</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! And this afternoon, we're going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the movies together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To see what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wheelchair Zombie Four</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Snorkeling Combat Two</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way! Those days are over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to see something real</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>romantic and intellectual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The picture is called </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Petals of Desire</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem with you, is that you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no sense of romance and no intellect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of intellect…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone seen Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He went back to his room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think he's got a few big problems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only problem I have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is our friend XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You remember the last few times</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he attacked?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which time? The one with the trees</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or at the swimming pool?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! We agreed not to bring up that day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the pool, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened at the swimming pool, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh… Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts] Nothing at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever! I meant all of the attacks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA has launched recently, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Haven't you noticed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what the target has been?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah, us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but especially Aelita and me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it just so happens</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we're the only ones who can use</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, we've all done it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Following our instructions on the phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, what would happen if Aelita and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>weren't around to give you guys any help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA wins hands down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Which is why I'm giving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of you a crash course on using</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? No way. Count me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to the movies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I've got a test to study for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I've got Pentchak Silat practice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you guys think you have better things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do, I can't force you to come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But then don't expect us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to gain ground on XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, but you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some days it isn't easy being heroes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then listen. We'll meet up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the computer lab after lunch,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if you pick it up quickly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be over in a couple of hours. OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I can't make it this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got my audition with the Subdigitals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, for the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Today is the final round of tryouts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, that's impossible! What if something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>happens to me while you're gone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>While you're teaching everyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to run the Supercomputer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll keep my phone on. If XANA attacks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be back in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK. Maybe you're right. I worry too much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead, I can manage without you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So much for my training session. Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to flunk another exam for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think you've got it bad, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How am I gonna tell Camille</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Petals of Desire </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>is out for today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think about it, Odd. You're better off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't have to pay all that money</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to sleep through two hours of a film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's a lot better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than sleeping through a class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>given by our friend, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, to start off, we're going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go through a little bit of theory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've printed you up a small list</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of basic functions to prepare you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, wait a minute, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wouldn't it be easier if we just went</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>straight to the practical side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You tell us what button to push</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>basta</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, working the Supercomputer isn't like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fooling around on a game console.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Before I can trust you with the controls,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to be sure you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this thing inside out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you all relax?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see, guys, the theoretical stuff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is actually a lot of fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. It's gonna be a million laughs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Eyes on the prize, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, hello!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad that you could make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me introduce everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You already know Nick and Benoit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my partners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sophie, who holds the purse strings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris] And that big bear in his cage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is Simon, our sound engineer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this is Mehdi and Lise,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who are the other contestants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this final audition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so, if we export the virtual memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the B block into the inertial matrix,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-you can reconfigure the transfer files.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This will let you delay the alignment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the quantum two beats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure you see where I'm going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with this? Any questions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I've got one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you expect us to remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of this blah blah junk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you guys were a little more attentive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd have been able to understand it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's right, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop trying to teach us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just show us how to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some practical stuff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like materializing us on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or programming up the vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, fine. I guess we may as well get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the practical end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are we there yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, Mehdi, nice one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make sure you hit the right button.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't want to end up there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with four arms and three legs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay… Tran… Transfer Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You turned me into a garden gnome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's cool here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so bad for a beginner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were confused there for a second</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and almost hit the wrong button,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mr. I-don't-need-any-theory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs] You're never satisfied.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did get him on to Lyoko, yes or no?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, because I was here with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you weren't even under the stress</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a XANA attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Give me my seat back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated tower, Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanners. Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Leave him to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] He disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, take our breath away, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music starts playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's still breathing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he took a lot of volts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>remember me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I think we're in a big jam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA sicced a polymorphic spectre on us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Einstein's out cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's a good thing he just showed us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to work the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah, you're right… It's up to us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone have any idea what to do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, call Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electronic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No answer. I'll send her a text message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll just</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have to improvise. What do I do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… For openers Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>try and get to the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, shouldn't we bring Odd back to Earth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while we try to get into contact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. You know how to rematerialize him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No, do you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sense arguing, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather stay here and fight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just tell me where I can find a Way Tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see… A Way Tower… Oh, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To find a Way Tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to bring up a radar window</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with these two keys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you doing? Get it right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Stop it! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks. Well then, Plan B.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to bring up my overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I can find that stupid Way Tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my own from the air.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Overboard… Overboard, darn it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein's notes are all over the place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I think it's this one here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, take your time, OK,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause I've got nothing better to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Speaking of which,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any sign of 'Spectre Gadget?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, how come he disappeared like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Guess he had another date.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The spectre must have gone after her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to warn her right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on. You're not going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to leave me alone like this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're doing great Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just keep it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where is this Way Tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I don't know, but Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got some "thingamajigss"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>heading your way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? You're making progress Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but those "thingamajigss" are Bloks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they don't look too friendly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it. I missed them all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay you monsters, cool it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engines running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess that's it then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris] Okay, thanks a lot to all three</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of you for that great stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just give us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few seconds to talk it over,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll let you know our decision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita has got to be our choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah, no doubt about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all nod in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, where's my ride?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sending it over or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm working on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see… I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, there it is. I got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Try to work faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Materialization overboard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you just sent me the overbike.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] Sorry, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't send you anything else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's better than nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there's another problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were supposed to send it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not to them! Dummy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess it's up to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to "unblock" the situation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to saddle up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yee-hah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well Mehdi, Lise,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really sorry guys, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where's Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[spectre grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car honks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi panting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Let's move it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing broken?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything cool?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[driver grunts] Hey, that's not cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] Hey, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching tires]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, where is this Way Tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Odd. I'm afraid to push</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some of these buttons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, you'd better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting to rust over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that number doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Great, Yumi, just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through the phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've got some sort</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of countdown window up here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on. I've got the expert with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, it's Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there anything written</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>above the window?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it says "big fat cheese head."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does that mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've started a delayed virtualization,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly into the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, has Odd found the Way Tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but I just got a mega idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Big fat cheese head?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spluttering] It's a… It's a private joke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between Jeremy and me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching tires]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car speeding up and braking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching tires]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[car brakes abruptly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This ice floe sure is deserted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's try that tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching tire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm still stuck in the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich just virtualized himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the Mountain Sector!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That Way Tower is just a little further,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bearing northwest from your position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll meet you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Mountain Sector. Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, better late than never.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine powers up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your turn now, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Virtualize me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yoo hoo, guess who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams] What's on the menu?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Usual stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A whole seafood platter over there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and William's the lemon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure took your time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah, but at least I got here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and no thanks to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you knew how many towers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been through,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before hitting the right one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We're going to need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more vehicles, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you read me, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, answer us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Transmission problems?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think it's worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm pretty sure that the spectre's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the computer lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll go. Shoot me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I should be the one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've already lost a lot of life points,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you've still got all of yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd be more useful here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, that's exactly what we did</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the swimming pool attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't ever want to hear about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the swimming pool again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] That will teach, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Saddle up, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] This is gonna be a close one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blade whizzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[spectre screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swords whiz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I didn't realize you were back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Neither did he, but he sure knows now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got no time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He could re-form again any second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Ok, don't move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think you can virtualize me, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax. I'm a computer whiz. You know that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Super smoke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energy buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps] Super sprint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's this, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another girl catch your eye?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Nice one, Odd. Just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was just a taste of my talent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Einstein would be so--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's funny,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have sworn you were taller.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Later 'gator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groaning in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look up there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It works most of the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're finished, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We'll see about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… The spectre…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spluttering] Tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you… Did you do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't do anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I have to say that you guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>held your own in the end,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you have to admit that I was right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA attacks Aelita or me now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that you'll be able to take over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that means you trust us, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… A bit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's good news,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because the day after tomorrow,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be gone all day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got my dress rehearsal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Subdigitals chose me to be the opening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>act for their concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even though I walked out on them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's fabulous, Aelita. Well done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yeah, that's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way Odd, how was </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Petals of Desire</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it was lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, I even broke up with Camille.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm all over that romantic stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I'm more into action,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like the day of the swimming pool attack,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for instance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi clears her throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, don't talk about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the swimming pool, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, don't tell me you're never gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell us what happened at the pool, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, it's simple really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see now… Do you remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the attack in the gymnasium?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, we told you never to bring up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the attack in the gym, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? What happened in the gym?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, nothing really…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nothing at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>