<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>HOT SHOWER</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, I'm uploading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the program over to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, the Skid's sonar should be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to differentiate bio-signals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the rest of the computer code</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>program received and activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you think that with this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll be able to find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where XANA is keeping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the spiritual essence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of William prisoner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let's hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the best chance we have to bring</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>him back to the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The return of our tall, handsome hero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure Ulrich's gonna be thrilled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have his old rival back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sometimes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're really a bit too much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only sometimes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, I guess I must be slipping.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't mind being in her shoes today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Helping run the outdoor science lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with fifth graders</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't exactly her idea of fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet she's loving it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>To mark the exceptional event</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the comet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>VG-seven hundred twenty four's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>passage near Earth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we are going to build a giant mockup</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the solar system to plot its path</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>its periodic extra solar orbit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beside me is a scale model of our sun,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as you can see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What you're going to do now is create</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the eight planets which orbit around it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, we'll break off into different teams,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with each team responsible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for one planet and its orbit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fifth grade students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will make their planets to scale,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whereas ninth graders will have…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd really like to be on your team.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Johnny, that's up to Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are there any questions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could I be on Yumi's team, ma'am?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right Johnny, but don't let me catch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you clowning around with Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is gonna be a lot of fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The mass and velocity of the comet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>VG seven twenty four, are so great</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that striking the Earth would provoke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an explosion equivalent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a thousand times the strength</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the atomic bomb dropped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Hiroshima in 1945.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Subsequently earthquakes and tsunamis</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would destroy the world's major cities;</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Atmospheric debris would blot out the sun</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a long night lasting two centuries.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Consequently, this would spell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mass extinction for flora and fauna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the entire human race.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no risk of this happening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since the comet will pass</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no closer than um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, two million</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>kilometers from our beautiful planet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have also been informed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by highly confidential sources</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the government operates a military</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>satellite armed with laser cannons,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sufficiently powerful to alter the course</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of any interstellar threats such as this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The detection spectrum is honing in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sonar is picking up a faint residual</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trace of digital DNA in the area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might be William or maybe…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Your father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] This is for you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Too cool. Guess what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We get to do planet Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great. This is my lucky day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Earth and the moon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yippee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And to think that Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wanted to take my place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget, the sun should be the center</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your calculated orbits, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And fifth graders, note your planetary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scale in relation to the sun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This exercise will be graded.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now get to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a second, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have an important announcement to make.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, about the poles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to call your attention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to an important technical aspect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They have two ends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One is pointy and sharp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the one you put into the ground.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you try to do it the other way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you might hurt yourselves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pushing on the pointy end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students mutter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Come on, you'd have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be an idiot not to figure that out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim wonders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[trombone music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Why now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why can't we just go on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an exploratory mission in peace?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA, what do you have in store</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for us this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you're needed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back on Lyoko on the double.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Got it, Jeremy. I'm turning around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] Okay, I'm done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think of my planet Earth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the moon is yours for the asking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah right. Hiroki,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't the Earth have another name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"The blue planet," yeah, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was using a little imagination,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like if there was a Mars attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Johnny, do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything can grow on the moon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well no, but I thought it would</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be more poetic with plants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Both of you, start over and fix it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagination and poetry are wasted on her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, send me a miracle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get me out of this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Yes Jeremy. An activated tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, thank you XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wonders] What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, nothing. I'm on my way right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kid 1] What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kid 2] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some breaking news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It appears the comet VG seven hundred</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and twenty four has broken apart…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…following a shot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a satellite… Um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…For reasons yet unknown.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Correction…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV woman] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>International observatories</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have now confirmed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that all's well with the comet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it will simply crash on…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… N</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>owhere…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It will pass very far from Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, we could obliterate it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with military satellites.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which of course, don't exist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is just a little April Fool joke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from our producer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, that's it, farewell…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean more news later</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uno</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, it's not April, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>dos</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something is going haywire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see, "Orbital Observation Program"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>comet VG 724.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just figured out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA used a satellite</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to change the course of a comet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gonna create a meteor shower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that will pour down on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What? Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well actually,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to my calculations,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>most of the meteorites should burn</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up completely in the atmosphere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On the other hand, there's a chunk coming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>behind it that will crash dive into…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no… Into the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you have to get out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the computer lab right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I can't do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the computer lab gets destroyed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you guys will be stuck in the Digital Sea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at XANA's mercy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, we've got to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Jeremy. We'll do it in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's not gonna stop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the meteorite from falling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's true, and that's why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm staying at the control center,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to launch a return to the past</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we're hit by it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, full speed ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You've got a hub,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bearing northwest of your position</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under the databank shelf.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hub dead ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy. I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, a meteorite,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and considering its mass,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll obliterate not only the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but also the entire area,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>including the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others are on their way back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll meet up with you on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hiroki…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, I'll be right there, but I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got something important to do first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, this is not the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>immediately!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[terminate call beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holy cow! What is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A firewall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's got to be a present from XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get us out of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's not working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see it, Aelita. I'm already on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, where'd you go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I painted over it with blue,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and now look at this awful color.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki, I want you to go home right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take Johnny with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll meet you there later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? But what about Mrs. Hertz's class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki, you heard me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You get into a fight with Ulrich again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Suzanne,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how's it going with Pedro?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, really Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not around the students! Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have to evacuate the Academy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's… I know this may sound crazy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but a meteorite is going to hit right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here where we're standing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on now, Ishiyama. I told you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that raw fish was no good for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I swear it's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just found out from… a friend</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who works at the national observatory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey look, did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Check it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, great fireworks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, we have to evacuate the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wonders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The firewall's energy is set up along</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a fairly basic algorithm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we have to do is crack it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to slip through a breach in security.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I think I finally understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA's really up to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Bravo Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You finally realized that he wants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep us from coming in and pulling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the virtual carpet from under him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, obviously,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he picked the most perfect moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By destroying the Supercomputer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA will not only destroy Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but more importantly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our only way back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would he want to trap us here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] To get a hold of you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the one XANA has wanted to capture</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since we re-created Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's called "killing two birds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with one stone."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come now Suzanne, this is ridiculous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you absolutely sure it couldn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have been from something else?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fireworks, for example?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[differs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] That's what I keep telling her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think she overdid it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the mint tea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what I saw, Jean-Pierre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was a meteor shower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get the students to safety now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jean-Pierre] Fine. As a precaution,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm willing to go ahead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and evacuate the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I don't want any panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim sniggers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found the weak link</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the algorithm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as plain as day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The system overcompensates pressure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but takes three milliseconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to inverse its polarity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By synchronizing the initial pressure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can neutralize the sinusoidal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>distortion, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Translation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rubber band system. Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stand by for stopping turbo prop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready? Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now hurry and get over to the hub.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need you back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Lyoko ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] My breakfast wants to come back up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to say hello, but otherwise, all's well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're never gonna get there in time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unless I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, if I could manage to regain control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of that satellite, even for a minute,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just might get the meteorite</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to change its course again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, let's see…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Defense Department… Top Secret Data."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Password… Piece o' cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, fire drill, everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want all of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make your way calmly to the main gate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] No, not again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh man, another drill?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hub in sight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirty seconds to dive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, now I'm just gonna need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a transmission relay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to link up the satellite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I'm still at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really sorry, but I had to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Yumi. Plan B time. In fact,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad that you haven't left school yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Your lap top?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll go to your room and get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's your sister going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only one way to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You read me, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the coordinates for Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stand by for broadband</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>acceleration in three… Two… One… Zero…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Take cover!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 1] No, thunder…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 2] I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 3] It's a meteor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Calm down right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just picked up your laptop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the roof of the science building,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and hook it to the antenna.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy, we're back on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's the activated tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Desert Sector… Quadrant 57-42.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[efforts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] Security door versus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's ankle. I'd bet on the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you two think you're doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Teleport!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower is only fifty meters away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How much time do we have, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Enough, if you can rid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your welcoming committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He ran away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So why waste a Laser arrow on a coward.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, buddy, he's all yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Uh-oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of a sudden</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that tower seems a lot further away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you should tell us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you think you're doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't time for you brats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go back outside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We know how to open it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shut up, Hiroki.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sick of hearing your lies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's true. We can open any door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if you think you're so good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then be my guest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but first you gotta tell us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're up to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[annoyed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what have I got to lose?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A meteorite</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is going to crash on the school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if I don't connect this computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the roof antenna now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't be able to access the satellite</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that might change its course, understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A meteorite? Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now tell us what's really going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tremble noise]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] Okay, okay, let's go Johnny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's hot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, well this is the desert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It doesn't look good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll never get through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should never say never.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy, I'm on the roof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now what do I do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, try to find the antenna cable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now cut as cleanly as you can,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stick it in the blue plug</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the back of my laptop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Push hard. We can't strip the wire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's not enough time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It should work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! What am I gonna do without a knife?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wonders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Coward and cheater? Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've gotta change tactics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy, it's in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, let the duel begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[short circuit noises]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did that rat XANA get onto me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going over there, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Not so good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Stay behind us, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you get devirtualized, we'll never</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be able to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] How can anyone be such a bad shot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[surprised]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The Tarantulas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>haven't fired at me even once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's because you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>great bodyguards.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get going you two. Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't let go of the cable. Beat it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is a flawless program and I'm human.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] This time it's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm forcing XANA to make a choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry Odd, devirtualize me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Do what I say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's our only hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What was that all about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] No idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To win,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sometimes you have to know how to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think XANA understands that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] Hey, what's… Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki] We're saved!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Johnny] We're saved!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great shot, Jeremy, a real bullseye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like he gave up on his plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA wanted to capture me more than</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he wanted to destroy the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With me back on Earth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he couldn't do either of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well Yumi, don't the "brats"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get a thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, brats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[surprised]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mwah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yuck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grinning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys really helped me a lot this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not gonna let you forget that either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, give me a little break?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] So how was your day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't believe it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we got the highest grade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so I promised Johnny</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would keep his moon as a present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I owe him that at least,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even if he doesn't remember anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See? Your brother's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not that bad after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, he can be pretty handy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he wants to. That's why I'm worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah? How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because now I know it's useless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>locking the door to my room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>