<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TIDAL WAVE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] All I have to do now is analyze</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the data you gathered from Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think we can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>learn anything from it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea, but if there's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a possibility of finding a clue</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for fighting XANA on the Internet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's worth a try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know about you guys, but something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to eat would really hit the spot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better forget about it, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't be late for gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we haven't had breakfast yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stomach growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could you cool it for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right. Your stomach is almost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as talkative as you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now listen, if I don't get something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to eat right away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no telling what I might do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, did you forget you just had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a chocolate bar five minutes ago?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's nothing. That was just a warm up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need some real food to get me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going in the morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like some beans or potatoes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a banana or two for dessert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I know you kids are going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be disappointed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it looks like I'm going to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to cancel today's shot put competition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone cheers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone] Way to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, since today is Nutrition Day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our school nurse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yolanda Perraudin is going to speak</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you and tell you what you should eat…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in order to have a great shape…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… to keep in shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yolanda clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So those of you who can't wait until</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you wolf down your next junk food meal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>had better think twice before you do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because junk food is your worst enemy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless your name is Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His worst enemy is whoever gets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between him and his food.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nurse] …and so for example, if for lunch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have mashed potatoes and lamb,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for steak and fries at night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is she talking about anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I eat mashed potatoes and lamb,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no reason to wait for dinner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can have steak and fries for dessert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better hope we don't get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a test on what she said,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because you'd get a zero for sure, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, don't forget that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a head of lettuce can save your life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And remember, the better you eat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the better you live!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at me! I'm an example of what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>good food can do. I am in perfect shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[body cracks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just pulled something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yolanda, help! I can't move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yolanda gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Odd, it's finally time for lunch--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] So Rosa, what have we got today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shepherd's pie, sausages and fries,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>beef stew?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I didn't want to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but they said I had to cook healthy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and well-balanced meals from now on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Grated carrots and cucumbers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>steamed vegetables</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and… fish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not even fried or breaded!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Great! I love broccoli.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say that again, and you're dead fish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry I can't go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got Italian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No big deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're just going to analyze all that data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you brought back from Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And how about you guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you want to come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! Ulrich, you stay here! I need you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You do? What for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think the Internet looks like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, but I guess</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An alert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking Italian]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Italian is such a beautiful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and romantic language,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi's phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, William's not feeling well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to take him to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What seems to be the trouble, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, to tell you the truth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't really know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess, you wanted us to be alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why you said I was sick?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me too. Whenever I see you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I mean I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe I ought to tell you this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Italian…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking Italian]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Where'd she go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a soul out here. The coast is clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to eat up a storm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich's phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Head for the factory on the double.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA's activated a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Be right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you think. I refuse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be virtualized on an empty stomach!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Eating healthy is okay, but I'm starved.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern and Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you two doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you? I thought you were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a nut about staying in shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I asked you first. Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[window pane shatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That was fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where are Odd and Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're on their way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What is it, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a bit of a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We might be a little late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Is it XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It kind of looks like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're not hurt?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurt? No, I don't think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Anyway, you were right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about one thing…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>food </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>can</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> be your worst enemy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a little further north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out, XANA's sent some Krabs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we read you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Krab scuttling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, no more Mr. Nice Guy. It's time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to teach this pile of junk a lesson!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay here! This won't take more than</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>two seconds. Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing and thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was right. It didn't take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more than two seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to be eaten by a mountain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of food, and I'm starving to death.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some guys were born to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Yumi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I can see the tower, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, ladies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wait a second, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something feels weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Digital Sea seems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have risen all of a sudden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's going on over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you're right, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Digital Sea's really going way up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Another one of XANA's tricks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mean</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Lyoko's going to be submerged</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and disappear forever?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, it won't disappear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko's sectors aren't affected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it will get submerged unless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can find a way to lower the sea level.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Monsters are heading for the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>chamber at the core of Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's trying to stop you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from deactivating the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and from accessing Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by raising the level of the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's precisely how</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he plans to quietly wipe out Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to get to Sector Five before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the sea swallows up the mountain sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But first, take care of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late. It's not accessible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] How are you guys doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let's just say we've got indigestion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>big time without having eaten anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's grim here, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible to deactivate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Yumi and Aelita are going to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be needing backup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love it when you talk to me like that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, we'll figure something out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Want the latest news, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is it good?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Then, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the sea's getting higher and higher.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know if we're going to make it all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the way to the edge of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to make it there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich should be there soon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give you guys some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, head for the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I try stalling this junk heap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll let you have all the food,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but only because it's you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling and thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, don't tell me that XANA…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…is sending hornets after you? He is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Things were getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little boring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>S.O.S. Service here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the trouble, sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, get into the scanner room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry! Where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got some game</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going on in the sewer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Out of commission, great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you back in, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were much faster than I was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on now until Odd comes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I materialized your Overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and Aelita have got to get into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sector Five no matter what, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last I heard he was down in the sewers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fighting one of XANA's monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His mobile isn't answering.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll go find him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must need help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can relax now, princess,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your knight in shining armor is here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Odd, play the hero later,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but for now, get into position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm typing in the code, "Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumble]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're inside, Jeremy. What's the latest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The latest is that all of Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has been submerged in the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You think we can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bring the level down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I hope so,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to the information</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're going to find for me…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we won't be able to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to reach the chamber</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the core of Lyoko fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or it's bye-bye to our beautiful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>virtual world forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't forget to stop the countdown!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No sweat, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no? Then how come I'm sweating?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there! I'm coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You actually conquered the junk pile!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't bet on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an unconditional surrender.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's okay Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We passed the core zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're in the elevator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry. The monsters have started</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We made it, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We're coming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the Celestial Dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, head for the interface.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to get me the data I need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to lower the level of the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you head for the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks for saving my life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What wouldn't I do for you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, have you found anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about you, Odd? What's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in the chamber at the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know I said everything's cool,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm still dying of hunger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can stuff yourself later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, don't let them hit the core.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> If the sphere goes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko goes too, forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Jeremy, nothing like a little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>encouragement.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bad news, guys. The first</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>protective shield layer just blew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The second protective shield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't hold out much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I might have found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what we need to debug the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I might have a little problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>getting through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This thing won't quit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I found the high diving board.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scratch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I made it, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, but the core can't hold out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>much longer! Okay, move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm going to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rematerialize you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Odd doesn't make it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you could disappear along with Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, don't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just about to get hold of the data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It'll just take a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just at the wrong time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks as if the monster's gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think maybe you spoke too soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll distract it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you head back to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not distracted too easily, is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how much time do I have left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a few seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, the faster I finish up here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the faster I get to eat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That makes two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found it, Jeremy. Are you ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to download the data?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I sure am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll launch the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for debugging the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just hope this is going to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and Odd, you've got to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the activated tower ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I'll get Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Yumi and Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still nothing. Not a word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling and banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, Aelita! The data that you found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was exactly what we needed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko's not the only thing to resurface.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to jump?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this! Pick up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! I guess I'm all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bon appétit, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crunch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, now we've got to launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a return to the past, because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no way that Jim is going to forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the monster he saw in the lunchroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go. Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm so hungry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>