<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>LAB RAT</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping and children chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the big news?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't wait to hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found it at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? How to build up your muscles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without any exercising?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Funny… No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I figured out how to materialize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto Earth from the Network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, it was much easier</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than I thought it would be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I applied the "synchronicity" principle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Supercomputer's apparatus,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then I used it to develop a kind of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>energizing projection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In other words…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In English then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that means you now know how to send us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere directly on Earth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from inside the Network, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You understood Einstein's babbling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all this time, I'm finally starting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get the hang of swampum physics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quantum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well it's still muddy though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold it, that means that now you can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bring us up anywhere from the Skid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not anywhere at all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can do it in the vicinity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a Supercomputer generating a copy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's what I call teleportation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi guys, what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and blow up a Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can get us to the real world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Network?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. We're all meeting at the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tonight to try it out, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? I wanted to ask you something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that was about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as cold as the North Pole!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you do to deserve that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The cold shoulder started</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>day before yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird. Her birthday was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the day before yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was? I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I hope you wished her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a happy birthday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how important things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that are to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, I totally forgot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Man, I bet now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's going to hate me for weeks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Probably… Unless you go and buy her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a nice present to make up for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go now… Well, I would if I could.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Stern!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] How many times do I have to tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that a flounder is not a </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>flying </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>fish?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So there's no reason to throw it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the window,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially when the window is open,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and when I happen to be there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So I've got one word for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's two hours of study hall!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're making a mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear to you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well Stern, you're right this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did make a mistake. It's not two hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>four </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>hours of study hall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you keep baiting me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll make sure that you don't get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>off the hook for </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>eight </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>hours!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got four hours of detention!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then, we have Chardin's class, and--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to go get a few things for Kiwi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and while I'm out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll pick up a little present for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? You'd do that for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah sure. Besides, I owe you one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In case you didn't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the flying fish thing was me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was? And you let me take the blame?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was laughing too hard to tell Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you know I ought to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, would you stop hating me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a minute, Ulrich? Here…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This should get you on the good side</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your "platonic friend."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, thanks Odd. What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's really going to go for it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey, you guys, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>hello</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't mind keeping up with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the rest of us, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I have to remind you that we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a really important mission?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, hey, we're not factory workers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, technically, we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thudding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How did your classes go today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not bad. How about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You guys ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Energize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling and whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Standing by for liftoff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Standing by.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Supports aweigh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ignition. Powering vertical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Liftoff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shields activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sonar activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stabilizers on line and checked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Primary axis clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser generators online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to dive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the coordinates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holoweb system online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you're looking for a hub</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at zero four five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Got</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Course heading set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm powering up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the turbo props and auxiliary engines.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Replika, here we go again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't somebody shut him up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? He's nice at least.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible! They're talking to each other!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Shut up, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relaxing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get ready. Broadband acceleration</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in three, two, one… Zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Reverse thrust.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're clear, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know. You guys ought to be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see the Replika now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, it's right in front of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're heading for the entry portal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Digital Key activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm sending</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>the signal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Roger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm about to open it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] There's an activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tower on the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means that XANA is up to no good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere on Earth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not far from the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're looking for. But what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If we want to know, we've got to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what if we gave your teleportation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thing a try?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just to be sure once and for all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I was thinking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But first, you're going to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to moor the Skid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's one nearby, at three o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I see it, Jeremy. It looks</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should be able to secure the Skid to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gently though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little to the left… Be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Back seat driving again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better cut it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you can do it without me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Ready to moor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Skid secured.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice one,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>princess!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good job. Now just give me a minute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to activate the tower for our own use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, we're all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, guys, it's time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for teleportation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to go, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Teleportation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It didn't work, Jeremy, I'm still here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot to tell you, that this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I decided to energize only Aelita and Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather you stayed with Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to protect the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it's anything like our last experiment,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA will be sending you a welcoming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>committee in no time flat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you'd have told us before,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we could've chosen sides ourselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! You really sound happy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be with me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That wasn't what I meant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you guys know the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll put you ashore</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I get a little work done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew what was happening!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cool Einstein! It works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Glad to hear it, but that's no reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to blow out my eardrum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're not going</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>to</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>believe this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we're in the jungle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And it's daytime here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're in a different time zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're in the Amazon region, it seems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] That's exciting!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we're dressed like on Lyoko. How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Because the teleportation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't a real devirtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those aren't your real human forms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-that I materialized onto Earth, but--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Slow down, "Frankeinstein."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you trying to tell us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we're not really us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, you're you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but those aren't your real bodies,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more like some kind of spectres</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>image</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>of your virtual manifestations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita and I have become spectres?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, you're like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>polymorphic spectres that--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty impressive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you say so. It doesn't matter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hurry up and find the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The teleportation won't last forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How long have we got?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fifty two… No, twenty six…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, thirteen minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The guy's a comedian!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And just where does he expect us to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a Supercomputer, behind a tree?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good guess, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yumi, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't we make up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, if someone forgot my birthday,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't make a big thing out of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's because I never, ever, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, not </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I mean </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>somebody, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, quit while you're ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're just making things worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Aelita have found a laboratory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My theory was right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're trying to locate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything okay on your side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little chilly, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, XANA's on the move again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Two vehicles coming right up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll take care of Handsome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the Skid gets disconnected from tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's "mission over" for Aelita and Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll try to make life miserable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the enemy. Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fighting William should put me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a better mood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster explodes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's open.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right or left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Through there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How can you be so sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-My sense of direction is infallible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster explodes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Hurry up! This way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What's this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A supermarket display</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for office plants? Guess not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scuttling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up and find the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Ulrich are busy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fighting off a bunch of Tarantulas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Funny, their cousins are right here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what do you make of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these souped up spiders?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd say that XANA wants to transform</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these tropical tarantulas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But for what? Spiders don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>attack unless you sit on them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't look at me in that tone of voice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I'm sure nobody heard anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Odd groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone ever teach you to play fair?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you know that thing really stings!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You've lost, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing menacingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so fast, pretty boy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's over, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Mayday, SOS!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need two more fans, like, right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Right now" is a pretty tall order,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, but okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me see what I can come up with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here we go! Back in your cage now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Hey, you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a great spectre!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, no medals just yet, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We still have to find the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's okay, I'm nearly there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't have a rabbit's foot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a four leaf clover,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or a horseshoe on you, would you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it as bad as all that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Infallible sense of direction,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was positive that we should've</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gone in the other direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on a minute!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we found the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! You'd better destroy it right away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because Yumi can't hold on much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[warning alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! An entry code!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not a couple of guard dogs too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me handle it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, we've got to get rid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of this thing for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me handle this one. Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Supercomputer has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an energy field around it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to find out where the shield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is getting its energy from.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do anything from here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do whatever you have to, but hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's now or never!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm really sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There. That must be the lens</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's projecting the energy field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we destroy it, there's a good chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll deactivate the shield.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could have found me a</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>little bigger target.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one could possibly hit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from this distance. That is… Except me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead! I'll take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Adios, amigos!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arr--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Come</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>in please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this? What's going on now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has taken over control of the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your teleportation has stopped.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to abort the mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You might as well come back home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wake up,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Spiderman and company have just arrived!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] There's no sense</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dissing ourselves. We did our best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe, but we've still got to find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA's planning to do with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-those cybernetic spiders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to go back onto the Replika,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>teleport you back in,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destroy that Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fine, but until then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anyone mind if I sleep for a few years?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we get the message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could all use a little sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps on bridge]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, a little birthday gift.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[romantic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Ulrich, that's very sweet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smooching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't you going to open it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In Japan, you never open a present in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>front of the person who gave it to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fine with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you're thinking about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your own birthday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's one of those things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still don't remember.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't any idea when I was born.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem. All you have to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is make up a date, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why don't </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> choose one for me, then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm not telling. It'll be a surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, are you guys coming or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before I fall asleep on this bridge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we're coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No need to wake the whole town up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who is the pretty present for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's it for, my little diggedy dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Odd, thanks again for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really saved me this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No sweat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[paper rustles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty classy collar. But don't you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's a bit too much for a dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[toy bone squeaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>