<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>COUSINS ONCE REMOVED</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it now, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess what? Yumi and Aelita just bet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they can wipe us out in foosball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Ulrich and I are gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>teach 'em a lesson. Wanna watch?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How many times</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do I have to tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm working on the Navskid program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and can't get away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We thought you like a front row seat</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see the girls get thrashed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We weren't gonna make you play.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen. Reinforcing the Skid is "slightly"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more important than foosball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't want your next expedition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to end up being your last, do you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Always the optimist, huh Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on over, you could take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little break from the computer…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If that guy calls again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna break his neck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where was I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… If I compress the executable files,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to free up enough memory to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knock at the door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now who's gonna waste my time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for your warm welcome, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, hi… I mean… Hello, Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope at least that you'll be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little happier to see your cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Patrick, what are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm surprised your parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your cousin has enrolled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on their recommendation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And until we can get him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a room of his own,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we thought we would put him with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… A camping bed should do the trick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Sir, it's just that I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, young man, welcome to Kadic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois, I'll leave you to look after,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>uh… Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might be a good idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to show him around the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How you doing, cuz?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I caught you by surprise, didn't I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Glad to see me, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I'm overjoyed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I have to do work now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so don't you have to go get your stuff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or fill out a form or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh yeah… I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy, anyone tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's bad manners to hang up on people?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein's made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a handsomer clone of himself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is my cousin, Patrick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gonna be a student here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi, my name's Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another Belpois, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you also a nut about square roots</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all that stuff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. I'm not as bright as Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think he's bright, do you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me, he wears kinda drab colors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well I guess that compared</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the way you dress,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-anything'd seem kinda dull.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! This is a classy outfit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's based on </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Kung-Fu Commando</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a great game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you're stuck at level seven,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because at level eight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the clothes get a lot more tame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shocked moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two should get along…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A couple of joystick junkies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we had someone new for football.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't just play video games.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm into Aikido, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's cool,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>although I prefer doing Pentchak Silat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, we could train together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, but right now, everybody out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got work to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My, uh, report on the Vikings</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and their legendary </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>drakkar</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ship…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the "Skidbladnir"…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's important, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Roger. Time to ship out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a date with a foosball game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, why don't you come with us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'd be great, thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your friends seem really nice, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can see exactly what you're after.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So just leave my friends alone, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make your own friends in the rec room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Was that family reunion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>typical of the Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll meet you over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot my mobile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts to herself]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why did you act like that with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's because I know him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He tries to act super cool</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make me look bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was like that at summer camp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Patrick would steal all my friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and act as if I didn't exist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe he didn't do it on purpose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He seems pretty nice to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you blind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you see that he's doing the same</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thing he used to do at camp right now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't make excuses</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for being such a sore loser</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and for behaving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a three-year-old baby.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So chill out and stop feeling sorry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for yourself, 'cause you're not like him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because I've already wasted enough time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[frustrated sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme song]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's taking Aelita so long anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to teach you two ladies a lesson.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like the one we're giving you now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you don't deserve the credit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was Patrick's pass!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Jeremy wasn't stuck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to his computer all day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he might be able to play like you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I wouldn't be too hard on him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, it's harder to be a whiz</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in math than playing foosball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's incredible! Einstein treats you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like dirt and yet, you try to defend him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he was my cousin,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd ask for a divorce!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we change the channel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the third episode</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Love, Glory and Paella </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>in a row.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just shut up! I decide and you obey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Me, a three year old baby?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bit of a sore loser, but not a baby.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knock at door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who's there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Got a bit of family company?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[disgusted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh. Looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Happens to me sometimes, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should do more exercise…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Takes your mind off other things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping and chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, some good news. About time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Is that you, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Aelita. I have to tell you something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm warning you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you're going to be as rude as--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The Superscan's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>picked up a Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll meet you at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Call the others…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Ah, Aelita, finally!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, little change of program…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mm-hm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispering] Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but we have to go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little problem to take care of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who are XANA and Replika?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A couple of Greek friends?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And they make a wicked moussaka,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you gotta eat it while it's hot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nervous laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Tell me how it ends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I can't keep it from you anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not Ramon's brother.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Change the channel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What're you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible save by the goalie,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the pressure's on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still no score. Muller gets ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and kicks the ball out of danger…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme song]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Already here, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you reinforce the Navskid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The program's running.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I left my computer working</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I'm gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The update will install itself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly on the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, but won't Patrick see it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I locked my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can't get in until I get back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess Jeremy locked his room up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good thing the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gave me a copy of the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, my name is Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really glad to meet you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors hissing closed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and I don't hate each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no need to lie to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm on the side of the good guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like you, Patrick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and his gang are up to no good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but together, we can catch them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? He wouldn't dare steal a lollipop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's always in front of his computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if the answer was in his computer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's the kickoff to start…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Sissi… Well, uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miguel and Teresa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were just about to kiss each other,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-when all of a sudden--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't care, you little dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You don't?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just go over to Jeremy's room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and step on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[low roar of engines]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I'm steady</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the right direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hub 110 in sight, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stabilize the Navskid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the hyperfluid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I enter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Replika's coordinates and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darn it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-More like three problems…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A trio of sharks at eleven o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll stabilize the Navskid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just one for each of us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Piece o' cake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm an expert at desserts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would the captain mind releasing us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Battle stations, sailors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Navskids away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sharks roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Keep 'em off the Skid!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The deflector shield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hasn't finished uploading yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you hurry?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I though you said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were a computer whiz!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's some kind of program running,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's blocking my access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Jeremy's personal files.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what you're doing is way outta line!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Jeremy has nothing to hide,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we won't find anything, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That doesn't matter. It's still wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miserable program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't ask me how I did,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I think I did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[device powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, my protective shield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just dropped all of a sudden!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, I'll check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer binging and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's going on now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You won't get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>away from me that easily!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take this, you overgrown sardine!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gun fire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Factory to Navskids:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head back to the Skid!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong, princess? Feeling lonesome?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No time for jokes, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have a shield anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computers beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've lost power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no control at all! Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Navskids,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've lost contact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Catch up to her fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's being swept away in a digital tide!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm breaking off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ship whooshing by]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's impossible to debug it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's coming from the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I left running in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[frantic typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see her date of birth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her social security number,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of her school records…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is weird. It looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's forged all of Aelita's ID papers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was sure if we looked hard enough,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd find something interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait! I'm sure that's Aelita's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>real ID file.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have scanned them for the photo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got a crush on her, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and her health records.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did he scan those to get her eye color?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh-oh! Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone's trying to access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the system from a distance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's tango.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"Access denied." Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could that happen?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy to Navskids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only way to deal with this bug</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to go back to my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot for leaving us alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to protect Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sharks roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[missile fire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a whole aquarium</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that won't let us get through!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but as soon the bug is fixed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can bring the Skids in, so hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping quickly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated tower in the Desert Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Navskids, we're changing our plans.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta bring Aelita back to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You want us to turn a squadron</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of deadly sharks into fish sticks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>find the Skid and then haul it back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with our tiny little reactors?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That pretty much sums it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay! We're on it, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm activating a firewall in the system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you won't have any trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I'm gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors hissing shut]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jean-Pierre Delmas speaking…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Mr. Dunbar here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm calling to tell you that my son,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, still has the flu,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that the doctor advises</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more bed rest before returning to school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Thank you for calling in, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tapping phones is a serious offense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're through, Jeremy Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here's another call.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hi there, Julian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Sissi, the love of your life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… But I never said that to him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Julian, you wouldn't believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how mad about you I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's… It's that idiot Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>imitating my voice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that's why that dork,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Julian Xiao, wouldn't stop following me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>At this hour,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you should be in your room studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've no excuse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's all! I burned a CD</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with all this on it for your father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! We've got enough on them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get them all thrown outta school!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure Jeremy has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a perfectly good explanation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father will be glad to hear it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Outta my way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over my dead body.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop playing the hero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can get you kicked out of school, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William's maniacal laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Navskids! Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William's voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ah-ha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Torpedoes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We've got to dive down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and find Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Patrick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Patrick, what's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This guy, Herb,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was snooping around on your computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the principal's daughter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tried to stop them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but they went totally mental</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and kicked me out the room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like I was a rag doll.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're gonna show the ID</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you made for Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the principal and get you all expelled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry. This is my fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You didn't like me much</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to start with, and now--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm the one who's sorry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for acting like a total idiot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ever since you got here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No hard feelings?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat, cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I don't have time to explain now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if we let Herb and Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>play around with my computer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>getting expelled from school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be the least of our problems!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Will you help me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can count on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[satisfied grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Skid here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Navskids, come in please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitors beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical droning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[droning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Over there. I can see the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What have we got now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It looks like a monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The Dentist Drill Massacre</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Except this one looks worse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Patrick groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling with William's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Patrick yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I cracked the firewall!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The mad dentist is a saint</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>compared to this monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>In formation, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Navskids, stand by to fire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sputtering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more power! What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No idea. Something's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>New horror film:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Return of the Sardines!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sharks roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi growling in William's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've both blown a fuse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now there's an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I cut the electricity,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my computer will switch off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so will the access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You stay here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shark roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My deflector shield is almost gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>One more hit and it's all over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To think that I'll never get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to level eight of </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Kung-Fu Commando</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Patrick's such a lucky guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["William" panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[maniacal laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-["William" roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps and moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[maniacal laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Must be one of these buttons…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering crowd on TV]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Vukovic is ready for the penalty kick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He runs up and--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[TV turns off]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, this is impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come back on, this is impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer booting up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The shield is back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you did it, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice to hear your voice again, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein strikes again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad for you, fish face.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm off the hook, but not you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[missile fire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope the others get a move on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more sharks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not as easy as it was, is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hate to bother you, princess,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but do you mind stepping aside?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Reverse propulsion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Well done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can bring you in now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Next stop, Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Navskids in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maximum propulsion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sweet talk won't get you anywhere, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines roaring and powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Disembarkment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, that's much better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had virtual pins and needles in my legs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A good, old-fashioned land duel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser fire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, don't be a party pooper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're spoiling all the fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Enough complaining. Jeremy's in trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser fire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, handsome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you forgot to look up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, it's your move, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's invited some friends over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[booming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs to himself]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Let me go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams then groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pa… Patrick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors hiss open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you seen Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, and he's not answering his cell phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Patrick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you at the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Launch a return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Patrick's in pretty bad shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You… did it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, you're gonna be okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I'm glad we settled things…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Patrick… Patrick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[air lock hissing open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[device beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor chirping and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we can finally play foosball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a hurry to get crushed, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… Odd's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's all go to the rec room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You too? What about your program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, your report on the Vikings?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not every day you can hang</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Should we give them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a three-point handicap?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It depends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Patrick plays on their team,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we get stuck with Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll be the ones needing a handicap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your friends really seem nice, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, they are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait till you get to know them better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Patrick] You think we could be friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, you and I have never</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really gotten along that well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just kid's jealousy and stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all over now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've only been here an hour,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I feel like we're friends already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois, I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but parents have decided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to enroll you after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>From what I understand, they'd rather you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>attended a school closer to your home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sincerely sorry, my boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what a bummer that is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's really a shame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess that means we'll only get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to hang out at family reunions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you around then, cuz?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, you still got time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a game of foosball, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Will you be on my team?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've always been dying to whip Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Works for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>