<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>COLD SWEAT</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] If you had the choice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you rather be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a screwdriver or a monkey wrench?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] Hey, you dreaming or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you were a tool,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which one would you choose?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you think of anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>less dumb to ask?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure. Are you still in love with Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or aren't ya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! I'll never be a tool,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you'll always be a fool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Get your Kadic news</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hot off the presses!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rosa and the tuna salad caper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim Morales,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the former professional athlete,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tells how to throw the shot put</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without breaking a toe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz reveals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to make a voltmeter out of your MP3</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with just a few simple operations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Plus an exclusive picture</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the secret past of Yumi Ishiyama.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where did you get that picture?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but we never reveal our sources.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's an absolutely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fundamental rule of journalism.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we can tell you is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's one of your very best friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that at this very minute,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's in the rec room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Wait until I get my hands on him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could you do something so lame?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's wrong? I didn't say his name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's the Champion's Cup final.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The favorites, Brazilian Coffee Beans,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lead six to five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against the German Liverwursts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tension is high.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can hardly hear a pin drop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-as Walter Brem--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another one of your girlfriends, I'll bet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, hi, Milly. Yeah, what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? But why did she have to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the last time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll ever give you a scoop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we play now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah sure, right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I've got a little problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you really have to bail me out this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you do know, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little practical joke. Nothing at all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you gotta say it was you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I asked you what you did, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, in the name of our friendship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna regret this. I know it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll do it? Lyoko warrior's honor?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you the one who gave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this photo to Tamiya and Milly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why are you angry? You look adorable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] For once in his life,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd the dope is right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pink does wonders for you, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I think of all the times</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you made fun of my look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You must feel like an idiot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Black is my color!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Black like your eye'll be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't back off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Huh! Come on, boys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me beat you at ping pong again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time Odd, you're gonna be sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I'm gonna give Delmas a list</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of all the pranks you've pulled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the past two years.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure he'll be happy to have it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're wrong, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I gave the picture to Milly and Tamiya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was you? But why'd you do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I, um, haven't the slightest idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dumb dork.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Don't ever speak to me again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really are a good buddy. Thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't bet on that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, lend me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your pink princess costume for Halloween.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I use your wig?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you shut up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Are you okay, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look upset. Is anything wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just located a new Replika</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna destroy it tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you at the factory later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be there. I've got history now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's face it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she does look awful in pink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although the color</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really looks great on you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The Skid is docked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll activate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, who's gonna get teleported tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I vote for Yumi and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're good together on a mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way! I'd rather go out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my own than go with him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa, chill out, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you and Odd go this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And why not with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wasn't dumb enough to make me look bad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of the whole school!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, we've gotta talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just changed my mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh too busy for that. Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Teleportation time Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, will you? Wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Patience, okay, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why is everyone so wound up tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energize Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Energize Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the middle of a snowstorm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's like any one of a thousand areas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I can see some kind of a base.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Gotcha. Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me, Ulrich, what did you do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Yumi to make her angry with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that I gave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that picture of her to the Kadic News.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That sounds more like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the kind of idiotic stunt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Odd would pull.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Funny you should say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi must really hate you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got any ideas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of how to get back on her good side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only way is to tell her the truth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, I think I found a clue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It says "Union Base."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Position 63 degrees,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>16 minutes North,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>143 degrees, 15 minutes East.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're in Siberia, at a scientific base</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA's taken control of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see if I can download a floor plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on inside in the meantime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have ever done such a thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never been this mad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at anybody in my life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even the day when I threw</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your math homework in the incinerator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was a great gag though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you trying to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my hit list or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, come on. Relax, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, you've gotta admit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the photo thing was funny, wasn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha ha ha. No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, yeah, sure it was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] You don't think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It was mean and nasty!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't even know if I can call Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a friend after what he did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, nothing. Why don't we just concentrate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the mission?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Jeremy, how's the floor plan coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now I've got you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the staircase</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the end of the corridor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll take you right down to the basement.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're on our way, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats! An activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, XANA's counter attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What kind of attack?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Search me. Surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lightning cracks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both exclaim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Did you get that, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's managed to teleport William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is a pretty awful surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sure is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This might be a good time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two head for the door</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the other side of the room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, activated tower east</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're on our way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Disembarking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here come your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Thanks, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Come on, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I'm coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William has blocked the door!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of it in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I just have to crack the code</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the electromagnetic lock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you hold out that long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We'll try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cries out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you go. Open sesame, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring and clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Nice going, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, which way do we go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take the second hallway on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Aelita, how's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can see the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good. From this end,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything's cool for the moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's what I call coordination!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're gonna need it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two Tarantulas at eleven o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Strategic retreat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Ulrich yell]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Yumi. William is on your tail!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hide somewhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until Aelita has deactivated the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll hide in the room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just in front of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wow! This looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dr. Shrank's laboratory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[machine hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What's this stuff, I wonder?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Beats me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like some kind of soup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's beginning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to look like brain soup!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Ulrich, Odd and Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have William to deal with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope Aelita's already in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nearly there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We'll have to force</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our way through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you got a better idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think it might work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll wait here for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] He never gives up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, William is here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't sweat it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's already in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This tower commands</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's teleportation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so the interface must contain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the protocols and programs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA uses to control him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So, if we hack into the data,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe we find a way to free William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right. Aelita, you're a genius!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send you the programs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yoo-hoo! William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'm out of ammunition!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's no picnic around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is Aelita gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>deactivate the tower or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yeah. Right. Yeah. Hang on a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Aelita, I've got what I need.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can enter the code Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nap time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go back into the hallway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Supercomputer is not too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nap time is over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That takes care of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now we can go home and get some sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What do you mean "not yet"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William is back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he's heading straight for the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He can still wreck our mission</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if he enters the code "XANA" in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can always count on William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to mess everything up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any vehicles left for us in your garage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd hates lending out his equipment,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but anyway, here's the overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of it. I promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that I know how to use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stop! It's to the right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's locked, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll hack the lock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just give me a couple of seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you know Ulrich pretty well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why'd he do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, are you still hung up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on that dumb photograph?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna know why! That's all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno why. Maybe he…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, maybe it's because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he wanted you to notice him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Weird way to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, he's not always that bright.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, they say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that love can make you a little crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you just say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That Ulrich isn't always that bright?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh uh, after that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's open. Get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, no time to chat, Yumi. Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Odd's precious overboard! Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what do we do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Should we bust everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or should we finesse it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I think finessing it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would be a safer bet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Describe the thing to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there are a lot of wires</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a ton of electronic thingamajigs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thanks! That's a big help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna have to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little more specific.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All clear, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We took care of William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect! It's smooth sailing from now on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think the Supercomputer is based</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a Russian M13 machine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Da! </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If you say so, Comrade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Give me a couple of minutes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll tell you how to destroy it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's consolidating the energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from all of the Replikas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] And I'm not talking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about just two or three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why's he doing it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both exclaim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What's that noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's coming from behind us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, that's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, whoa! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich, I'm getting something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my screen. What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We've got a new monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deal with, Jeremy, and he's gigantic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any idea how to get rid of it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry guys, but I don't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one solution.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both exclaim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, XANA's created</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a new kind of monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he's gigantic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He could destroy the Skid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a fraction of a second!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, you got any info?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not that we're bored</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or anything but, uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna bring you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But we're so close now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you could stay virtualized forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So let's not waste any time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energize Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energize Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Whoa,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's this chunky hunk doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's probably as mean as he is ugly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, major trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get us out of here now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You got it. Docking release!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Close one. Good work, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a mountain, not a monster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't to see what Odd's gonna call him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… The Kolossus,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a "K" like in KO!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno who's gonna get KO'd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the name sure suits him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll never make it now. As soon as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we try to set foot on a Replika,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll be there to devirtualize us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we can say Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One thing is sure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've gotta change our strategy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because right now, XANA controls hundreds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Supercomputers all over the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll never be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy all of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got anything in mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I'm working on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stick with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm ready to stick</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to my pillow right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, I'll sleep through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my math test tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm warning you, Odd, if you don't tell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi the truth about the picture,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then I will, you understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to, but I can't. I'm too chicken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do it, if you don't wanna get plucked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But let me think it over a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, how long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… A hundred years?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Can I talk to you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, well, I'm off to bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you, guys. See ya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had a talk with Odd about the photo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I think I understand why you did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there's something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you ought to know. I--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no, let me talk, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanted to get my attention,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you thought that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we had a fight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I would start thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about you all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[inhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't need that to get my attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kisses Ulrich's forehead]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next time try talking to me instead of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doing something so dumb. Good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, good… Good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Odd, what's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't go on being such a coward.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to tell you the truth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The photo prank was me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich took the blame</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to cover for me, but he's innocent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not still mad, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's forget about it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and start from square one tomorrow, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gate crashes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What a pair of dorks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You still there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. And you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 1] …party on Friday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 2] Whatever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Get your Kadic News here. Extra!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the Kadic News, how to be first</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in line for your medical checkup,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another easy quick recipe,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>liverwurst pancakes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and an exclusive picture</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Odd and Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're definitely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not gonna wanna miss!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you Photoshop this thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way. I took it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when they were coming out of the shower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You told me to tell her, didn't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm gonna kill you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>