<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where are we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In my laboratory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To a world where you and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be safe… forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you in a minute, honey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Alright, dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy? Daddy, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here I am, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I can’t materialize myself into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>human form yet, as you can, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still have more work to do on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This world needs to develop more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy, there are some</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>strange looking creatures over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Run, Aelita, run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Fumet] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know young lady,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>most of us go to sleep at night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everybody laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I’m sorry, Mr. Fumet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumet] Scandinavian mythology,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a natural disaster brings about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the end of the Norse gods’ world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scorching the Earth, before a new,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>peaceful world can arise from the ashes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>called Ragnarok!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And roll!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ragnarok… and roll.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was just a joke, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, would you kindly leave this room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that a joke?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, it’s an order!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess as jokes go, it wasn’t very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, how was history class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Who cares? It’s history now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Well, Miss Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>better get a good night’s sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A super brain like yours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>needs a little shuteye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And most of us you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go to sleep at night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course, you don’t have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that problem, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause your brains are in your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn’t Odd a riot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look who’s got the nerve</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk about my feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially after what Heidi Klinger</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>told me about yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did she mean by that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What’s wrong with my feet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, to put it tactfully,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you take your shoes off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it’s a little bit like… uhm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like a pile of very fresh manure that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we just can’t seem to get away from.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That’s it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, come on, you’re nuts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There’s Heidi. Now we’ll find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey Heidi, is it true my feet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>smell a little?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just make sure you and your sneakers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don’t come within fifty feet of me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a disaster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My reputation as a super stud is at stake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No girl is gonna want to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go out with a… a--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A walking pool of toxic waste?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some friend you are, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could’ve said something, you know…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>given me a little hint at least.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It’s hard to talk when you’re holding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your nose, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were trying to be funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Don’t worry, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Modern medicine must have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some kind of cure for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, there’s amputation, for example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everybody laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Start without me. Be right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emily, can I ask you something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When we went out together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you notice that--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That your feet smelled? Better believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why do you think I kept dousing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>myself with perfume?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yolanda, I got a real problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It’s awful, I--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, yes, yes, yes, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You suffer from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>severe plantar perspiration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Say what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your feet smell badly, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mean to say that everyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at school knows?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, there’s… uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well yes, everyone does know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don’t worry?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’ve seen cases that were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot worse than yours, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What’s more, I know just what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I have to make contact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with XANA and persuade him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-that we can live in peace with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who’s XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A multi-agent computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>program I created.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It has achieved self-awareness</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and autonomy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and it’s trying to eliminate us now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But why, Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Whatever you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don’t leave this tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy? Daddy! Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hum?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what’s the matter? Is anything wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No I… I was…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was daydreaming I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys, no more feet nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Call me “Odorless Odd”!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How’d you manage that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You’ll find that out tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It’s a surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swallows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I’ll let you kick your foot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>problem around a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’ve got a math test.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Jeremy, do you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you think my father’s still alive?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father, Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think it's possible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to rematerialize him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I mean is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there’s no way to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he managed to survive when XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>captured him the first time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not a second time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your father sacrificed himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he had to have used whatever little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>strength he had left in him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring you back to life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but… but I thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there might be a hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that maybe we could find a way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I checked every inch of Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and there isn’t the slightest sign of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I’ve been working really hard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a way of getting into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the World Wide Web</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that we can fight XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you should think the way I think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, think about the future.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And just forget about my past, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think it’s easy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You didn’t spend ten years of your life</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as some sort of computer software.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I’d never recovered my memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’m coming, daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get back to safety… in the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You possess</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the keys to Lyoko, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA must never get his hands</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on them. Do you understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It’s over, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is too powerful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's become a threat to all mankind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to shut down the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>But does that mean we’ll die?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Waldo] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, but you mustn’t forget me…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never forget, Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I knew I’d find you here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, our good buddy Einstein</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>may be a computer whiz,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but diplomatically, he’s… he’s a… a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A total lame-o.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But he really likes you. You know that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I really like him too. I just</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wish he would understand that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my father is all that I have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>left of my past life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have to go to Lyoko. To Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to try and find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some trace of my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that may not be too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard what Jeremy said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He’s not very anxious to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So? We don’t need Jeremy, do we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm… We?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just us. You and me, okay, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, do you think I was a bit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hard on Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn’t easy for her to learn</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she was human.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Better talk to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You shouldn’t talk to anybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There is no talk permitted in a library.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anybody I find talking from now on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little conversation with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you haven’t enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after our little chat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can just walk down the hall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and have a talk with the principal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] No talking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita must really hate me, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No she doesn’t.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I’ll bet that she’s running around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>looking for you to make up right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey William, did you study hard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just ask me anything you want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about American history.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… That’s great,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the test is in math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh-oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I’ll launch the procedure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which’ll automatically virtualize us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the desert sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as we materialize, we’ll have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one minute to get in sync</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-with the transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how to do all that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure. Piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, an activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the mountain sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we’re out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can beat XANA if we act fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Talk plan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm telling you the recipe calls for eggs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>vinegar, whipped cream,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little wheat germ, and peanuts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I’m saying you’ve gotta</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>use hazel nuts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You don’t!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, we’re not, by any chance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>speaking too loud, are we Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want you out of here immediately!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now go on, get out of my sight, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That was easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what was that recipe for anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sounds totally gross.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It’s one of Odd’s concoctions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you finished already? Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi’s on her way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can’t seem to reach Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think she’s still mad at me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I hope we didn’t miss our bus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do you smell that? It’s weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It smells as if Odd has been here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Forget it Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd hasn’t been here since yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His feet smell, but not 24 hours later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still, it’s bizarre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still nothing from Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Or Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It looks as if Odd is angry as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-'Cause of his smelly feet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That’s dumb. Odd is losing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his sense of humor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I hope this isn’t a false alarm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I raced through my exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It’s real all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’m sending you and Ulrich in right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others will join you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just as soon as I can hold of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Nice one, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You materialized us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of an air show!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry you guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but more surprises are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's called up his heavy artillery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’ll materialize your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Better hurry. Ah…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, tarantulas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Supersprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Huh! It's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dialing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you’ve moped long enough. Now pick up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, the key! It's up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is almost too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[animal roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[animal roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy-field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bizarre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd think they were surprised to see us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, we're not disturbing you, are we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I see the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] So do I,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I also see a welcoming committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you get hold of Odd and Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, not a word. I’ll try again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Stay in position for now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don’t get devirtualized!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We’ll try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Aelita, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What is going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holosphere system on line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They’re already there the traitors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd, I know you’re there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For your information,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while you’re out there having a ball,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA happens to be attacking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Yumi are already on the spot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What now, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let’s go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as you get to the Dome,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’ll program a vehicle,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then I’ll open a tunnel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is in the mountain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sector, okay? Now get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They’re not attacking. It must be a game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we’ve just spotted some flying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mantas in the south pole of the Dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They seem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be guarding the entrance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that is not a good sign.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on, I’ll check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like you were right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attacking the core of Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower in the mountain sector</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was just a diversion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, we’re on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your telekinesis thing is really cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi, change of plans. Listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Aelita are in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You’ve gotta get over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What? What’s going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’ll tell you all about it later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, it’s suicide.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You’re kidding. This is a snap, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's really outsmarted us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>While he kept us busy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the mountain sector,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he was free to attack the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but he didn’t count on two scanner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stowaways already</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fortunately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So then, you’re not mad at them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, soon as they get here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they’re each gonna get a big kiss.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you at the extreme edge of the sector?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sir, yes sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, then I’ll enter the code, "Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… These guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are tough to get a handle on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, you might try throwing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of your shoes at them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can do better than that. Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, Aelita’s all alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the first shield layer of the core</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Lyoko has just given away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on! Yumi and Ulrich are on their way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mantas squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Supersprint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, did we miss much of the show?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, just the opening act.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] My sabre!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you know that you still</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have a tower to deactivate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you wanna stop at a terminal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to collect some new data on Franz Hopper…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… if you want to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Yes, why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so what’s the miracle cure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Yolanda gave you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on. I did tell you it was a surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now close your eyes, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I’d rather close my nose, I think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What’s that foul odor?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a cream. Pretty effective, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now my feet don’t smell at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That’s because the stench of that cream</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is so horribly strong!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help! Open a window or I’ll die!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some guys are never satisfied.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any luck?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on a second. What’s that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What have you found?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A fragment of a DNA code sequence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that belongs to… Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father might still be alive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>