<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA AWAKENS, PART ONE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Diary of Jeremy Belpois, Kadic Academy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>eighth grade student, October ninth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A few weeks ago, I was hunting for parts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to finish building my miniature robots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't find anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around here I could use,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I decided to rummage for scrap</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the abandoned factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not far from the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I figured that I could find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>plenty of cool old mechanical stuff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>left inside there that would be useful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I wasn't disappointed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was unbelievable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I stumbled into some sort of complex</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with an entire computer lab, with scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and especially</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this totally intense mainframe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the moment, I haven't told anyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's my little secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the coolest thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's ever happened to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that wasn't all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even though I was scared stiff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I decided to start up the computer."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope I'm not gonna regret</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, let's see what you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under the hood, my friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! What's all this? A video game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who… who are you? Where… where am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans] Are you Ulrich Stern?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That depends. Who wants to know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-His brand new roommate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm new at the Academy, and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the principal told me to move in with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm… Latch onto me, sounds more like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax! I'm totally cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trust me, you'll see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you won't even know I'm there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, we don't exactly go way back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So just for now, let's take things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nice and slow. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Nice and slow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi there, Ulrich sweetheart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>very important to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Important like… hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I lost my mascara"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or "my pink tee-shirt ran"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing as serious as that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's something about you and me, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you wanna know more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>come by my dorm tonight at eight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm counting on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich… sweetheart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the good looking babe?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's the principal's daughter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guys flip over her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she's only flipped over me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's pretty cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Cool?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's totally brain dead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a leech as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In that case, it's pretty lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the waiter says, I don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>frogs' legs. That's just the way I walk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You get it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but what I am beginning to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're determined</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to give me a break.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have to get to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>each other, and you'll see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the end of the day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you won't be able to do without me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Artificial intelligence, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but would you mind calling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something else, please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. How do you like the name… Maya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but what I'd really like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is for you to tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I'm doing in this virtual universe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not so easy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've already got a couple of answers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're part of a virtual environment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>called Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you've gotta try to get out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look around for a door</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or something like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I can't find anything. I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is weird. You have to see this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you think you can give me a visual?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya, there isn't just a forest out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's an entire world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I count four sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Each one is different.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Jeremy, I'm not all alone out here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are some animals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This virtual world has an entire</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ecosystem, with virtual living creatures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can you get closer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're attacking me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Run away Maya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get back to the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants and whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Phew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your… your life points are regenerating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what I was thinking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know your girlfriend there… Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's not my girlfriend!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So that means she's available.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm telling you, she's lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Plus, no offence, but you're not her type.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh, yeah, I hear that a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey, Belpois, you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take him to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell the teacher, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nurse] Nothing too serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a minor electrical shock</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and some superficial burns.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanted some juice. Well, you got some.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny, Stern,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but thanks all the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't mention it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll come by to check on you tonight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after my martial arts class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you all? I'm happy to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so many of you here tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kalaripayat. Kogusoku. Jutsu.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, these are not dishes served</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the Golden Dragon Chinese restaurant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No offence, Miss Ishiyama.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>None taken, sir. I'm Japanese.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well, whatever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, these are combat techniques</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that can save your life,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as they did for me when I was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a forest ranger in Quebec.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Really? What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That night, well, I was quietly enjoying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a waffle with maple syrup by my campfire,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I was attacked by a vicious beaver.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Its razor sharp teeth were going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for my jugular,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I was able to save myself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to my perfect mastery</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of "the raging hand of Li Fou Chang."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What? What's so funny about that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Excuse us, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Honestly, I think you would have been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>better off not talking about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Okay then, enough laughing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get into groups of two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Pretty good for a beginner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Not bad,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you could both use a lot more work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That will do for tonight, kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bow to each other,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and go and get some beauty sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice to meet you too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? What is with this mess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where did that mutt come from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's Kiwi, my dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He just had a little fit, that's all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The poor thing's not used to being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cooped up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean look at this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My CDs, my clothes…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's trashed everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you see what he did in my bed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but I couldn't take him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out with everyone around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There are no dogs allowed at Kadic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think the principal's gonna be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>interested in hearing about this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's okay, Kiwi, my little diggity dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I've seen that logo before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay. Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your little friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are kind of aggressive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you should check their settings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had nothing to do with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They just attacked me all of a sudden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You lost me. Do you mind explaining?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, tell me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I could be of some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if you suddenly get attacked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by a hair dryer, and I'm not around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha! Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not leaving this room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I know what's up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. What have I got to lose?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm already in over my head,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I might as well tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is so crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, tell me if you can keep a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That tunnel in the gym is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a great way to beat curfew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yep, and there's another one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the campus as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter? Scared of heights?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, so that's the mega computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you started up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's actually a super computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's ultra powerful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And while I was examining it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found out that it runs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a virtual universe called, Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what, Belpois? This morning's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>electric shock fried your brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This thing is just the control center</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the factory, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah? And what would you call this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A program for spray painting doors?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the girl with the pink hair?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's Maya, a form of artificial</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>intelligence who lives on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what she's there for yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't mess with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You programmed her, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I woke up the moment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Jeremy restarted the supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know who I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My memory has been erased.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maya has to hide in some kind of a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as she leaves it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she gets attacked by monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta believe me, Stern!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is an incredible discovery!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Let's say it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if… What if it's just some</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>kind of giant video game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then it's a very dangerous game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My robots are programmed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just to go and fetch a ball,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they just tried to kill me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't forget. You saw them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, the moment they attacked,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a kind of logo appeared</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my computer screen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The same one that the monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>had on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better and better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mean then that… that the virtual</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thing that attacked Maya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>also wants to kill you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what it looks like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If that's true, Belpois…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it's that dangerous, I think you should</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shut it down, and call the police.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but first,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to help Maya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>understand what she's doing on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really do, and if I'm right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can materialize her here on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that's too much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What makes you think you can?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see, Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This one is absolutely perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight my dear Ulrich, you are all mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What's all this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still haven't found the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that can bring Maya back to Earth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I dug up the one which allows someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be scanned and sent to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, the super computer analyzes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your molecular structure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through these cabins,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then breaks down your atoms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before digitalizing them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and recreating a digital incarnation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the virtual world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You go inside the cabin,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're teleported to the virtual world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, these things don't exist yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You still don't want to believe me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would love to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but virtualization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is straight out of science fiction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we try it out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, you can see for yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we're gonna need a guinea pig.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A guinea pig? No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, got a surprise for you, doggy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're gonna be virtualized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog whines]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream and groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Ulrich, come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where is he going? I'm sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's another girl behind all this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, look, It's not a girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Kiwi, my dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why is he taking Kiwi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into this factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who knows?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe he wants to use him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for some horrible science experiment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You watch too many horror movies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you're right. That was pretty dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's probably more like some sort of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ritual sacrifice or a voodoo thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Nice puppy. Don't move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's cool, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The mutt is in the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, let's see how it goes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not gonna be a piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Those things look like coffins.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe it's the tomb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of an Egyptian pharaoh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right. We're all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, are you okay, boy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, you're going to be mummified!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer guinea pig.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner guinea pig?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's a weird looking dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's no dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's Odd Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to stop the procedure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, man…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Where am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And why am I dressed up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a giant purple cat?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd Della Robbia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's calling me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me, Jeremy Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is this a joke or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, it's OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd is safe and sound on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I in a video game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like the set for Babylon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ninja Fighter Three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I don't really know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a virtual world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That much I'm sure of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… That's a lot less cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these giant cockroaches attacking me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Is that normal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, nothing to worry about then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not what I meant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta get out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Della Robbia's in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I need time to devirtualize him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He needs help. Do you think you can send</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi and me to Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, I can always try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Send us where, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To a virtual world where</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>weird monsters wanna massacre you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanted to go out with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now is your chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I prefer real worlds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not into the other kind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Plus, I couldn't possibly miss cheerleader</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>practice tomorrow morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you, chicken. Jeremy, I'm ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm starting the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich. Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, hang in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich Stern is on his way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give you a hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! I was starting to get bored</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! This sword rocks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey that's not fair!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come he gets to be a samurai?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's much cooler.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea why.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Maybe the computer just reads</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into your subconscious desires</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and projects them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto your digital incarnations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't dream about giant purple cats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather have a weapon like Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not these great big useless paws!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, watch out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… These arrows are pretty cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I take back what I said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to hook up with Maya in her tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on, I'll give you the coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Who is this Maya,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and what is that thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's… it's the mainframe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a super computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Who is this Maya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A virtual girl who lives on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you mean there are babes here too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, but I get the impression</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Belpois' flipped for her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-For a virtual chick? Is he nuts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kind of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, are you going to give us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>those coordinates or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, are you asleep or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sic them, I said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sic them, you dumb mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I see a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could be that one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Is there a door?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold on for much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're too heavy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Drop your saber.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice try, but forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, right. Where are we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where did the forest go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How should I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you see the tower over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Weird how it's not the same color.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And those creatures…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're kind of weird too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Might be a good idea to beat it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich keeps grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So how do you kill these things?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew. Hey, you wouldn't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how many life points we have?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes! Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! At least we're alive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alive? Well, if you say so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'm about to throw up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hang in there, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It works the second time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you that by the end of the day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you wouldn't be able to do without me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Maya, are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is everything okay on your side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we're a little shaken up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it could have been worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>