<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE CHIPS ARE DOWN</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey everybody!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow, that's a tough break!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unfortunately, I'm not!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I could do something, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] That's really nice of you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would somebody tell me what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, we'll talk more about it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after class, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Don't mind me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep making like I don't exist, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teacher] Remember…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say that again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's father lost his job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're thinking of going back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Japan so they can find work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You've gotta be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not for sure yet, so don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Yumi's leaving?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We may never see her again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I shouldn't panic?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There is an easy solution.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you see, if you marry Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then she can get a green card.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Just trying to lighten things up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Italian teacher] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Vuoi qualcosa?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you want something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Per favore, signore </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Caggia…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sì</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Could I please go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not feeling very well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[English teacher] In Moby Dick, Melbourne</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>uses the literary technique…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-…of a character in the novel speaking--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Excuse me ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[English teacher] Yes, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Could I please go to the Infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why can't you stay at the school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as a border?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you could go to Japan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during summer vacation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents would never go for that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's more, they need me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't it supposed to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the other way around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What if--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's nice of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to try to find a solution,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but nothing has been settled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There might not be anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know. Why don't we write</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to our congressman to ask for help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, why not the President</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while you're at it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radio on]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you ready for dinner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You go on, I'll see you there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dear Mr. President, I'm writing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you about a young girl named Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi is an amazing person.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She is originally from Japan,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she really likes our country.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radio on]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What a load of garbage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dear Mister President…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you be quiet? Can't you see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm trying to concentrate?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[announcer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Remember, folks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this week's super jackpot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-is 30 million big ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now that big bonus number…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fourteen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two times lucky seven, fourteen. Anyway--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[announcer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Remember, folks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this week's super jackpot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is 30 million big ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I couldn't do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wouldn't be right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you go back to see the temp agencies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't had time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They might have had something for you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean to tide us over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until we return to Kyoto.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing out there for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are too many people in my field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know that very well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, if you don't look,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll certainly won't find anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you stop it now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you go to the temp agencies today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Ishiyama gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls and barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He isn't in our room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know where he is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get the feeling that Ulrich is taking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this situation even harder than we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can say that again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For Ulrich, losing Yumi is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine how you'd feel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if Jeremy had to leave!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm… Why do you say that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-'Cause I love making you blush!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait… what just happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why did we return to the past?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Could XANA have taken control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the back-in-time function?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's done it before!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I made a special program so he couldn't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The Superscan doesn't show</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any active towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after class and check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Here you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm… You do know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're not really old enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to play, young man?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, It's for my mom!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She asked me to buy it for her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] Oh, well, in that case…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich, we're gonna check out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>things at the factory after class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About the jump back in time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are you coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to… study for chemistry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, mind if I study with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mendeleev's periodic table at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'd rather study by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Well… I know you're going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to think this is ridiculous…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I heard you had some problems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with work and everything and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I thought… Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I bought you a lottery ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never know… Maybe you'll be lucky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then you could stay here with Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you have to admit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that it is very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know the odds of winning the lotto?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least you made me laugh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's something I need right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, it was very nice of you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're really touched.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget to listen for the numbers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And please don't tell Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I gave it to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She might take it the wrong way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radio on]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That Ulrich is such a sweetheart!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. Only he doesn't realize that we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one chance in 14 million of ever winning!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[announcer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, once again, today's lotto results.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The winning numbers for today's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>super jackpot draw are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>six… twenty-two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[announcer] …</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>ten… forty-seven…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thirteen… thirty-seven…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the bonus number is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[announcer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fourteen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Ishiyama] I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hey, there. What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the winning ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The jackpot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki] What's a jackpot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's incredible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You played lotto?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I thought you hated gambling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Ishiyama clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Actually…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was your friend Ulrich who played!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he gave us the ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He didn't want you to know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA had nothing to do with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as if someone had set off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the return to the past from here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Except that I'm the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who knows how to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless… someone read your manual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why do you say that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I'm really impressed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your computer skills!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who, me? You are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you did enter the code for returning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the past into the computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without making a single mistake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't waste your breath!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We know it was you who set off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the return to the past!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You broke rule number one, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only did it for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you can stay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't ask for your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you realize what you've done, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know that going back in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>makes XANA stronger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why didn't you talk to us first, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why did you have to go sneaking around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's too late for sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You betrayed our trust!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here. You can keep your dumb ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you should keep the money.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-As of now and until you hear otherwise,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're out of the group, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope this will all work out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Hey, what's up, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You don't look too good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And when I see you, it just gets worse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'll teach me to be nice to people.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, wait…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I apologize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just a little edgy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what she sees in him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You said it. He's sure no match</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for my looks or my brains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… You think you're handsome, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more than you think you're smart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dare you to say that again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[punch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumey] Africa is the continent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that suffers most</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from problems related</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a shortage of water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And rural areas of Africa are affected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to an even greater extent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Less than half of all rural zones</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have any access to water…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! When I think how much</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we complain all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumey]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…has access to sanitary systems…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA has launched and attacked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have less than a minute left of class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as the belt rings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Without Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Without Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you next week then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Hey, Nicolas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And don't forget your project reports</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on your own ideas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for helping African communities.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita. Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Here come your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Madame</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, would you do me the honor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of climbing aboard my humble board?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tower is located two plateaus North.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No monsters on the horizon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the time-being!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not monsters I'm worried about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's XANA attacking on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We still don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what he's got in store for us this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well, I'd rather we deactivated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower before we find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's your orders, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look! Over there, a crab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are my eyes playing tricks on me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or are there at least 20 of them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, there aren't any mirages on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I was afraid of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, thanks for warning us, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now your wounds will become fatal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas laughing through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, was that you? Answer me, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That wasn't Jeremy. I'd recognize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that laugh anywhere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's Nicolas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nicolas? Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nobody else has a laugh that dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one in the whole universe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out! The crabs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better get out of here fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting and screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why does it hurt so much?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shouldn't I just lose some life points?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Something's wrong at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, the crabs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have to take cover.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You're even more handsome</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you train.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, I think I'd rather be alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you crazy? That's the last thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you need when you're feeling down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just the opposite,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you need your friends to be there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have friends anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What does that make me then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, Sissi, there you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been looking all over for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah? Well, pretend I'm not here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and keep on looking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why don't you go out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and play with your friend Nicolas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would but I can't find Nicolas either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He ran off like a madman after class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to follow Jeremy, Odd and the new girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He was really spaced out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] His voice sounded weird</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and there was something strange</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about his eyes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why are you telling me all this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't care.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can you see I'm with Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, not anymore, you're not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'll go and check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better move, otherwise…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! That really does hurt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It won't take them long</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find a way around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I'm the one you're looking for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, since when have you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>become an athlete? I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Come on, Spiderman!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on, I'm not out yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, wake up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Hi, Ulrich. How are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Pull yourself together!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because I'm not feeling so great…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd… Yumi… Aelita… Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer me, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, is that you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, great, you're alive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but not in great shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's also in pretty bad shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's nothing on the screens.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That must be why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the fire from XANA's monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hurts us for real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That's just what I was afraid of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The crabs have broken</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the sand wall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really sorry about this, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's for a good cause.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sweet! What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, this is no time to drag your feet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas has deactivated the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should be able to fix it pretty fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, I wanted to tell you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Head for the scanner and get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah! We're invincible again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hold on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't miss me too much, did you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a little, yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! But those guys aren't gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>keep missing us if we stick around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Your vehicles are on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They could come in handy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, great. Now, all we have to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is cross the line of monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and Yumi may as well go over the top.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do what I do best…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chef's surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Aelita. We haven't much time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They've really lost it this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more than you have.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engines revive]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're never gonna make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another row of those guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines revive]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop moving around so much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you expect me to help you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut me some slack, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just trying to avoid getting hit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think we've done it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you're the greatest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, what about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't I get any credit?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy chokes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You say this is how he was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you found him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, in the middle of the campus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's very strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have fainted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing serious in any case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you did it for me, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I should have asked you first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So are you back in the group?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm… Looks like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you going to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with that lottery ticket?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought about it and I decided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give it to an association</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that builds wells in Africa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really? That's a great idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes? Yes, Mom, I'm listening…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-huh. Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right. See you tonight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father's found work with Takahashi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Takahashi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean, in Japan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No silly, right here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>