<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>COMMON INTEREST</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[police radio]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>HQ transfer, calling Car Alpha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Car Alpha, go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In three miles,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll meet up with escort two as planned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles and tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Copy that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You happy to be going home, huh, Duncan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't talk to cops, so save your breath.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Typical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you get trying to be nice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Duncan screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Duncan, hey! What's going on? What's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pull over. He's had some kind of attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breaks screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[policewoman] Car Alpha to HQ Transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[police radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go ahead, car Alpha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Duncan! Hey, you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Following procedure three:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>momentary stop to assess the situation…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[policeman screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[police radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger, Car Alpha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Standing by for information.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[policewoman gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[police radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Car Alpha what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Duncan laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[police radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Come in please. Car Alpha?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Peter Duncan escaped from a police</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>transport van without any outside help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's what they said on the radio.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, ever since David Copperfield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>made the Statue of Liberty disappear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing surprises me anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What bothers me is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the two police officers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who were guarding him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>talked about a supernatural force.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think XANA is involved?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Not a chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Superscan doesn't show</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any activated tower, I just checked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine, public enemy number one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under XANA's control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Talk about double trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A public enemy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did this Duncan guy do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, nothing much: fine art theft,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>safe cracking, kidnapping,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bank robberies…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes… I just…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't sleep very well last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't forget, we have a math test.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You gonna be all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As you all know, the exam covers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the principles of division.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you've studied hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich. What's the last digit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a number divisible by two, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah, that's the answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, ma'am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that's the grade you're going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get if you keep trying to cheat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Jeremy. Is there a problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I finished, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see… Good work!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excellent in fact, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[classmates murmur]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students gasp and murmur]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, what have we got?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Adolescent, 12 years old, unconscious,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-very weak pulse, irregular heartbeat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Put her in Bay one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gone into fibrillation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ten milliliters of adraxine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doctor one] Heart's failing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's holding down. Cardiac unit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Clear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flatlining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Clear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flatlining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[steady beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That kid's got a real guardian angel,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, how is she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's fine, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She'll be all right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's an extraordinary case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we see her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't see why not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but not too much noise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She needs to rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry doctor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone knows that I'm quiet and calm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are your test results?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Completely normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe it's got something to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the fact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're not really human.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could be the virus that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA implanted in me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you find anything, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dead calm, as far as XANA's concerned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No activated towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although, the Superscan seems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have reset itself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not giving the right results.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kind of like me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess it didn't study either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No class this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to pay a visit to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can have a girl to girl talk for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! What the…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This guy's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs sinisterly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't move… Put your hands in the air!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles sinisterly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hands up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's exactly what I was afraid of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The Superscan bugged up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll find out why in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The real question is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you fix it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, normally… yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the debugging phase takes time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know if it's a minor bug</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or something more serious which might--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay! If XANA's activated a tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll find it much faster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by going directly to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You coming, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Ulrich! Scanner, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All clear here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have to search</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm calling up your vehicles, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going with th</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>e S</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>uperscan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not too great…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well anyway, you might as well forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No wait, we found it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated tower, dead ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, I've got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twenty-five degrees north-northeast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice job, you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now all we gotta do is bring Aelita here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm bringing you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sarcastically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great! Now what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you hear me? Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, not that we're in a rush, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Taking your time, there…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Must have forgotten to pay his phone bill.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, the funniest part is:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki says to my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Papa, when I grow up, I'm gonna look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like you, but with muscles!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[flatlining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get a doctor, quickly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with this darn Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, are you gonna bring us in or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll manage without him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We… can't be devirtualized!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The scanners must be offline.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is going on around here, anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we've got a real problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the understatement of the year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is really bad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about… a gigantic, invisible eraser?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Let's get outta here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, do something fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before it's too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, start up will you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have a big bug here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flatline]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finally!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like Lyoko's recharged</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>its batteries.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flatline]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[steady beeping resumes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In all of my years as a doctor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've ever seen that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, we're doing okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, the nuclear battery is going dead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The uranium in the nuclear battery</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is almost all used up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so the Supercomputer keeps failing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and pretty soon,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll turn off altogether!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh… Is that all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then we just have to change the battery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A Supercomputer is not the same</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as a Game Boy, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't just pick up a bar of uranium</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the corner store.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But isn't there a kind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of emergency backup battery?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I checked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] XANA is dying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] And so is Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And all on account</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of that miserable virus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Odd sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna get something to drink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is this the best TV set they could find?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't bother trying to cheer me up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I heard what they said in the hallway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he can't have left just like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[flatline]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, it's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's just had another attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That figures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just turned off the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Peter Duncan is under XANA's control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He kidnapped me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make me replace the battery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means that Aelita is safe too, then!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except that once the new battery is in…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Duncan's gonna try to kill me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's room 117.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Little Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only way to get rid of Duncan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is for you to go to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get Aelita out of the hospital,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get here ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's heart can't take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an awful lot more of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I know, so hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This oughta do the trick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Easy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please let Aelita still be alive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[battery powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Duncan] You won't get away from me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich, Odd, are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me you're there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Is Aelita okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Couldn't be better!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Launch the procedure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Aelita, Yumi and me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna deactivate that darn tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You didn't think we'd let </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the fun with Peter Duncan, did you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Odd! Transfer, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should see the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kankrelats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We haven't seen you guys for a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I missed you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One down…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're gonna need our vehicles!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your rides are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you're down to ten life points!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The vehicles are materializing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're doing our best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's no picnic out here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no time, Odd, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Must be your lucky day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you little Kanker creeps!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower dead ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you handle him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love entertaining guests.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two monsters in view.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, jump!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run to the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now it's your turn!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, time to pull out all the stops!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Duncan groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] "Peter Duncan was found unconscious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of police headquarters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The police are investigating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but for the moment don't have any leads</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as to how the escaped prisoner ended up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>outside the police station."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even if we did tell them the truth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'd never believe us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, that's how it is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for unsung heroes like ourselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We gotta act and win,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and remain in the shadows</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess that's what being a true hero</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is all about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But someday, everyone is gonna know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just how brave we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we'll reap the real benefits</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and rewards true heroes deserve.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, speaking of rewards,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just saw Mrs. Meyer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She gave me the results of the math test.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And great, what did I get?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eight thousand six hundred and fifty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>plus 51 minus 10,000 plus 1,299.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean I got… Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got 100?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… Zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One day, everyone's gonna know how brave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you are by not studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you'll reap the rewards</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that an unsung hero like you deserves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't hold your breath!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh except Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>