<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A BAD TURN</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just a few more missions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that on Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll have all the elements I need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Aelita's antivirus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] See you tomorrow, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… Later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello! Anyone home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you waiting for anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You know they're right, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really ought to go for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>now</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, wait until she starts going out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with another guy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because she's sick of waiting for you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make a move, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what if Jim notices that I'm missing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll cover for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William! What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. I told you I was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I go totally crazy when I like a girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running away]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. I'm a little… confused.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Ulrich, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Goodnight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So then I told her I was going to order</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a T-shirt on the internet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she asked if it was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going to come out of the printer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here's our hero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, champ! How'd it go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, then. I think I'm going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go to bed. I'm tired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, me too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well! What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Leave me alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Some of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are already riding scooters,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and at this stage, I don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it would be a waste of your time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go over the rules of the road.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] This training day will…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] …with the correct way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to drive a vehicle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Assistant Warrant Officer Garrigue, here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has agreed to take you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under his responsibility today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as part of the exchange program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between the Police Force</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Board of Education.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our Physical Education teacher, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will assist you as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Corporal Jim Morales,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seventh Engineering Battalion,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>serial number: nine, two, twelve, one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[military drumming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At ease. You were in the army?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Captain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>only </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>a Warrant Officer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excuse me, Lieutenant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, well, I'll turn operations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over to you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I count on you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting] Affirmative, Mr. Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Officer] Driving any vehicle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is serious business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Caution, concentration, and safety are…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich. What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sulking, or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it with him? Last night when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we said goodbye, he was in a great mood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] But, what about after? What happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after he followed you back to your place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>followed </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, I'm going to call you one by one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take a drive around the circuit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The rest of you can go back to your seats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Delmas, Elisabeth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I prefer Sissi to Elisabeth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you? Do you have a nickname?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[officer groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[officer] Della Robbia, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[officer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ishiyama, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[officer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Pichon, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[officer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stones, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[brakes screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! You're not any better than I am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a morale booster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, will you just shut up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's not Odd's fault if you drive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a dork.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[punching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Stern and Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where do you think you are? Get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Straight to the principal's office!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Your behavior</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is unspeakable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Violence is no way to sort out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your differences!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next time, I'll suspend you both…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Understood?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim! Take them to the library.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, General!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, right away, Mr. Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Don't worry, Aelita. It'll work out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not the first guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who ever fought over a girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you fight over me, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I fight for you every day, Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pretends to cry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's so beautiful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speak of the devil…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I've got an activated tower here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Let's head for the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sooner we deactivate it, the better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We'll manage without him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer game beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Ishiyama] You're home early, dear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] The meeting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Morimoto San was moved up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's your dictionary coming along?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Ishiyama] Well, my editor called--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who could that be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There! Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, now we know what XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has in store for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello, Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's a big monster outside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I swear! And the monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>looks like the one in "Ultimate Blaster."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy's outside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] XANA has virtualized another Krab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's at my house!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents are in danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go help them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and I will manage on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Take care of yourselves!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] You too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're going to need some back up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… That might be important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] There we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? You think I confiscated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your telephone so I could use it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got his voice mail… What bad luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to do without Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, I've got a plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This, is the gallery</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which I'm going to call "G."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is where we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the elevator landing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which I am going to call "E."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to get to point "E"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without being spotted by the Krab "K."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You get it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No. But I've got another plan…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouting] Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting for? An invitation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get into the elevator! I'm coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical scuttling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator door creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get to the scanner room! I'll start up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the virtualization process!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[police officer] You can't come through,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a dangerous animal on the loose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] But, I live right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to get to my parents!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, miss. We have our orders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you there, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah, but we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little problem here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our friend, Mr. Krab has busted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the scanners!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not all of them… This one still works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm going to virtualize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the Mountain Sector…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thirty-five degrees north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've programmed the Overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your turn, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got another problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, it's a big banquet. XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has sent us an entire seafood platter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students screaming outside]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What's all that ruckus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two stay put, if you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's good for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is that thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A Krab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The very last scanner getting destroyed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by a Krab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita is on her own now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, there's not time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zoom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You've got to believe me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the one that the creature is after!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I already told you, miss.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Orders are orders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[voice on police radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Calling all cars,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the animal has just been spotted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the vicinity of Kadic Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I repeat:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the vicinity of Kadic Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[police officer 2] Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sirens blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is 15 degrees more to the west.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be very careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Jeremy. I learn fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You better!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Not a moment too soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has materialized three Krabs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One of them is at Yumi's,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Odd's playing upstairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the second,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that it won't do any more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>damage outside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] The third one is here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the Academy. I'll deal with it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming outside]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Looking for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Anybody home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy? Mum?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! I'm at the groundkeeper's shed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[skidding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're lucky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wasn't going to save you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you? Crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay away from our group!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, man, you're the one who</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't get it. In the race for Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not in first place,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or didn't you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Ishiyama laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These Krabs are just as bad as on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Squadron of four hornets coming in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hornets buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> They'll do everything they can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to slow you down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's for sure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll want to give the Krabs time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take care of Yumi and the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, we took out one of the Krabs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finally, some good news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's doing everything she can to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the tower and deactivate it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but nothing had better happen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Yumi and Odd in the meantime!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'll take care of it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> We'll</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> take care of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wings fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well done, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd would be proud of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> They're catching up with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got an idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It isn't dangerous, is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… No! Odd showed it to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that supposed to make me feel better?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Ishiyama grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're about to arrive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at a hollow mountain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Could you dematerialize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Overboard when I give you the signal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah, sure, but why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Make my day, shrimp!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Too cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you the Overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glass shatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got a slightly crazy idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not much further. Dead north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William! Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good job, man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many times have I told you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is the guy you should go out with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki] Ulrich, you're the greatest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, get out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zoom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Decoy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope it's not too late…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were great, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you won't remember any of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Hey, you really do know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're doing, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want to come with me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to my go-cart club?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd have a great time together!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Sure! Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>