<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>FIGHT TO THE FINISH</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy, no! Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door knocks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come you're not asleep at this hour?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'Cause it's time to get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh wow, time sure does fly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you've hardly slept all week long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to get some rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't got time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've almost finished</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my multi-agent program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll be able to attack Replikas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>simultaneously.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And soon we'll be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to wipe out XANA for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're ready to die of exhaustion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If that's what it takes, I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Breakfast time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Dunbar, good to see you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your head screwed back on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta pace yourself, kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just because you're half as bright</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't mean you'll go twice as far,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-something like that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what they put into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these croissants today? Yuck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take them off your hands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How can you eat those things, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just watch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you worried about Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, but… That's not all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I've got a premonition that all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of this stuff is gonna have a bad ending.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna get rid of XANA, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's no match for the one and only</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd the Magnificent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you're gonna scare him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with those crumbs on your teeth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you mind answering a few questions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the Kadic News?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a rumor going around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you've got a twin brother.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you confirm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I can confirm is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to breakfast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey William, that was a great gag.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You had us all fooled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We really thought you'd lost it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then Sissi asked me if spaghetti grew</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on trees or in the ground.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Hello. Can I sit down here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot. I get the message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, William. Don't go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks but no thanks, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know when I'm not wanted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not fair of us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to treat him like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not our enemy now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe not now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he was XANA's trusty ally!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not of his own free will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it was his fault too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he hadn't tried playing the hero,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Scyphozoa wouldn't have caught him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa caught me too,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lots of times.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it could have happened to you as well!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, we'll try to be nice to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But he can't ever go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it was a message from Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wants us to meet him at the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in 15 minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… How do you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not a fake message?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sounds like a XANA tactic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but it came,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just when I finished the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's no coincidence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It could be my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father just sent Jeremy a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sounds important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's head for the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you want, I'd sure like to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no, no, everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No attack in sight, so…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't really need you, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's a shame 'cause I've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a score to settle with XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well, some other time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, see you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music playing on player]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, well, well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where could he have gone? He couldn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have just disappeared like that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looking for your friend,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sourpuss, I guess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The park is still open to everybody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>last time I heard, but what about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You four look like you're in a hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've got water polo practice, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right now too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah… and we're late too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got practice in the gym with… Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm not as stupid as you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing at all. Hey,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you would look really great as a blond.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suits your personality.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bummer! Look, the door's locked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the first time ever. Bad sign.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can get in if we go outside the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] That's a long way to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're sorry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll be there as fast as we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have no choice. Let's move it, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You run out of water in the gym?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi, why do you always have to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you are, my lovely princess,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my beautiful flower…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you out of your mind, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you gone bananas again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, don't go, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I missed you so much, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I haven't gone anywhere lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hands off or I'll tell my father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you guys tell him to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where'd they go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if you're gonna reject me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess I'll have to try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my luck elsewhere. See you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you, dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I was beginning to wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you'd ever get here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It took a little while to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi Super Glue off our tails!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, what's all this about my father?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper sent me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some interesting data and coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's preparing something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the Ice Sector,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something really critical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Critical in what way?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if he's suddenly decided to reappear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think it's only to say hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gonna need an escort to protect him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from XANA's monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. That's why all four of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-are going in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Yeah, like all five of us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what do you think you're doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I thought that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after I got rid of Sissi for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you might let me go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better have another think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way William goes back to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So that's it, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't trust me anymore?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I was XANA's prisoner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>totally against my will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] XANA captured you once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can do it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're not like us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not…. strong enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we have no time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William stays here in the factory with me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you guys need some backup,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send him to you. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I guess so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Count me in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You four get down to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start up the virtualization process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gonna be okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you might even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get to see your father today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Ulrich can ask him for some tips</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on how to get better grades</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in computer class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Everybody in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ice floe, here you come!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The meeting point</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the south of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The ladies are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita. Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita. Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>According to this message,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your meeting point should correspond</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to an iceberg dead ahead of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] How come you're always right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, if only XANA's taken a day off…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We're here, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm picking up intense activity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the other side of the waterfall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we waiting for? Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I'd like to have a minute alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I understand, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, you won't be far away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if something goes wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy, are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An activated tower! I wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA has up his sleeve this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what? I think it's time that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts, groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think that my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is going to send you some more data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps, groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Daddy! We can't stay here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Kolossus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and he looks ready for action too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna need our vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Jeremy, what's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy should have warned us that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Kolossus was on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something must have happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to play for time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yumi, use the monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get you back to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'll keep him busy. Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] For once,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to bow down to you, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder why I'm not surprised.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That Manta just won't give up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And he's making me dizzy too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bull's eye, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts, sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, do you read me, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about time, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You almost missed a wild party,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a Kolossus and a bunch of Mantas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever you do, protect Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> He's sending me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some data right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what happened to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He knocked me out and Xanafied William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We should've brought him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Lyoko with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and tell that to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How's that for teamwork?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs] Good work, you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holoweb system online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Be careful. XANA's drawing energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from all the Replikas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to strengthen the Kolossus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you've gotta find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to slow up the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I've just about reached his head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm gonna try something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting, grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well done, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You immobilized the Kolossus,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a while at least.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How is the data transfer going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nearly there… But you have to protect</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopper from the Kolossus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot. Did you happen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to notice the size of that guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, Odd… but I absolutely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have to get that data, 'cause…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it can't be possible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my father's heading for the Digital Sea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] He… he disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he sent me the data I needed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to complete my… my anti-XANA program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Would you say that again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You heard right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to this program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can destroy XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Well, better hurry up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and run the thing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause the Kolossus seems to be getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his strength back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For it to work,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've all got to be in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do it alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way with the Kolossus around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as he shows up, he'll be playing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ping pong with the transporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich is on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] He's on it all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Let's hope he doesn't fall off it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, wouldn't it be better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower first?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know but it's our only chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of finally getting rid of XANA for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi'll be saved no matter what.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least I hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the code, "Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] There it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And there he is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] So long, Volcano Brain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say hello to XANA for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping, shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good job, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you can celebrate another time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's not having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what'd you call a great day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, William but let's face it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were never meant for each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd, how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're in the Celestial Dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you the anti-XANA program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh. Looks like we're in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a flying fish show.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You there, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run the program right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well, is it working?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, we haven't got enough power</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to run the program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we're only a step away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from beating XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't wanna see you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hanging around Yumi ever again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you okay, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've wanted to do that for a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is he trying to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The power!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, try running the program right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But my father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Your father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is supplying the energy that we need.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to run the program again, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no… No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, if you don't launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the program now, then your father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will have sacrificed himself for nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The program is destroying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the Replikas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA is dying!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yowling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can't be, but it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, we've done it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's been destroyed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you home now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sobbing softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>