<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>VERTIGO</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holosphere system connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Welcome to Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] The wall's gonna open</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any second now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three minutes to find the key! Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Uh oh! The doors are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the wrong place!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Oh, here come our friends!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Creepers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They just can't stay away from us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, guys, the clock is running!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Let's see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found the key,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at two o'clock directly above Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a job for a cat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[odd exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Not so fast, dummy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd! You're running</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of life points!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Uh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm connected, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Aelita! We've gotta gather</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the data before the Flying Mantas come!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> The Mantas are about to hatch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Five…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy, I don't see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any Flying Mantas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Strange! I can see them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my screen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay on your guard! They may come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the other end of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi cries out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Done, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can take over again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've programmed the overbike!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hang on, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. The passage is open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, we've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We just found the Flying Mantas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You should be able to lose them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>…what is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Mines, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're hatching flying mines.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, these are codes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for XANA's subsystems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I cracked them three weeks ago!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This one looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the source code to a virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might be able to use it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the virus inside you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is anything like this one,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might be able to free you from XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You mean, like soon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a big climbing competition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tonight. Gotta practice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I already told you. I'm not doing it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Because.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least come and watch me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Ulrich. For once, Odd's found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sport where being scrawny is a plus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I am not scrawny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am svelte. It's not the same!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Come on! Keep it steady.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should have left your zits down there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>huh, Herb! They're too heavy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia! I'm gonna--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the king of the world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Stern. The wall!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, Jim…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First one to the top!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. I don't climb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you scared?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm not scared--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Stern. Show us what you've got.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get up that wall! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, man,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>humiliate this guy and let's go eat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! The test worked! It's unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We did it! We've got the antivirus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Mmhmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! What if…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if you injected me right now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could surprise the others!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that a little risky?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It will be just as risky in two hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or in two days!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay! Go to the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William and Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is he doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Come on, Ulrich! Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You can beat him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go for it, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, huh, Spiderman?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You spinning a web or did you fall asleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Stern!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little nap before lunch, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got vertigo! Is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let him chill out awhile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give him time to get over it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! Do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! How do you feel? Say something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you can make jokes as bad as Odd's,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then you must be okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe he went to the factory to mope?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Hey! We've got great news!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've found the antivirus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I've already given it to Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's so great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we have to do now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is shut down the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>adiós </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>to XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but not without Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to find him first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why? Where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Off somewhere hiding. I mean, sulking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah. In that case, he's in the forest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He always goes there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he feels like moping!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[branch cracks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[leaves rustle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, back to your usual cool self yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a hundred percent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, this might help you to quit sulking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got some incredible news!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm actually writing the final entry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Lyoko travel log book!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you imagine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think it's the antivirus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. It's just an energy slump.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go and lie down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my room for a minute or two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Aelita! I didn't even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>see you standing there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's hardly surprising!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're such a wall flower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can you expect a guy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to notice you some day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not talking about Jeremy, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's already married to a computer chip!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean a real guy, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Look at me, for instance…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…I'm really pretty and attractive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but that's not all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm also funny, intelligent, sweet and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…very attentive to others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Just what I was saying!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's so unremarkable you don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even realize that she's gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is awful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure is! XANA is attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] I'm here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] You are? But where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Right in front of you. But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm… I'm invisible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oops! Sorry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Could this be XANA's attack?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick! To the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[leaves rustle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Uh oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A nice little doggy, I hope!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. A big bad wolf, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolves growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, when you're faced</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a pack of wolves, what do you do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi's recorded voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Konnichiwa</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've reached Yumi's mobile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave me a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Meet us at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a bug!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Let's go! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolf whines]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't look down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves howl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Concentrate on your handgrips!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't think about anything else!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah! That's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep climbing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Just a little further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] I've got you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd exhale]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm here, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It isn't XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a bug in the antivirus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to deactivate it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's going to take a little while!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What about the activated tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the attack?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We've got a big problem, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in the forest with a pack of wolves,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>possessed by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Aelita can't go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and deactivate the tower by herself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We'll do our best!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll keep you posted!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hangs up the call]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualize me on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I can deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way! We have to wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wait for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For them to be devoured?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have no choice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Your foot okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good thing you weren't wearing sandals!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves howl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh, great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A flying wolf!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! I'm here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's good to be visible again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've programmed the Overwing for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you. The activated tower shouldn't be far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is where the kind hunters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>usually come to the rescue, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a decoy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They… They're just images!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That XANA's even slyer than I thought!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No Scyphozoa in sight, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Anyway, be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh oh! This one's real!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So are these two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure is no picnic over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is almost at the activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The antivirus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I injected into Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has modified her virtual signature.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The towers doesn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>recognize her any longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You mean she can't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>deactivate them any more?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Exactly! That is until I manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to extract that dumb bugged virus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But she is all alone on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I can't devirtualize her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay! We'll be right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hangs up phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita needs our help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Glad to hear it, but how do you plan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on getting out of this jam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We split up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, I said! Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I may have vertigo but I can handle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few flea-bitten mongrels!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On three, get going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean one, two and go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or do mean one, two, three and go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cavalry's on the way, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful! Behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You can start the process, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You know what you have to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your vehicles are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Follow the trail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is inside the cavern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] No news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolves barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car horn honks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Odd! Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well done, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you're the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who can do anything now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A complete mess! And you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Ditto.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves howl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! They've got guard dogs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shivers and takes a deep breath]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how's it going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the antivirus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm working on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to help him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Wait! The antivirus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you can get into the tower now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope this works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales] It's okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Launch a return to the past!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First one to the top!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You chicken! You got vertigo or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. What about it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No worse than being afraid of spiders!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! How did you know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have my spies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you around, Spiderman!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Aelita, what's it like,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being invisible?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I always wanted to be like, you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sue in </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The Fantastic Four</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>