<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a bad feeling about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you almost done, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes. Almost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Watch out! Another squadron</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Mantas is headed your way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Done! The controls are all yours, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! Here come your vehicles!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, guys, the passage is open.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] So? Anything good?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No. I wouldn't call it good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-More like amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With this, I bet I can crack the code</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Franz Hopper's diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Way cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only problem is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna need a supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to process such a large amount of data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to activate a tower or two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, that didn't go very well last time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA hates it when we play with his toys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but we don't have a choice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, can we go eat now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's mashed potatoes today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can have mine! I'd better stay here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to prepare the mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, you can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>set off right after lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… Jeremy's not coming. He said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could have his portion too, Rosa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Rosa] With everything you put away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just don't understand how you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can still be so scrawny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not scrawny. I'm svelte!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, come on, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stop holding out on us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your overall average?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Seventy three for the term.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, me, I got seventy five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I beat you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only because you made up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some points in art class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your grade point average?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ninety five point two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, but it's only because of math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but still. You must have gotten</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>good grades in all your classes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, especially</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since you're not really…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, I mean…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I know very well</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not really human.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still, sometimes I get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a strange feeling as if…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As if I'd already lived here! Weird, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that's just the magical "Odd" effect!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, you see me once,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you feel you've known me forever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Magic "Odd Effect"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some mashed potatoes right on your face!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone vibrating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really. Some girl wants me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to meet her in the woods!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding! Who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The number's masked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No doubt about it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's another girl who's too shy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to admit she's crazy about me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, Odd, your love life is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like something out of a soap opera!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah, and yours is real simple, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An activated tower. Oh, boy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all I needed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah, Jeremy? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're on our way. Activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You call Yumi. I'll tell Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me. Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean, "SOS XANA"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way, not now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[leaves rustle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, who's there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screaming] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sent him a text message,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he was supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be meeting some sort of mystery girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A girl? What girl?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mystery girls don't leave their names.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I hope he won't be much longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not only do we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to decode Franz Hopper's notes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but now we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate a tower as well!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone dialing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Odd! Pick up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not answering. Forget him for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll meet you later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here I am, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. Not a moment too soon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been trying to call you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Well, get ready!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll launch the process!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Everything's okay. I'm on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was a bug during the transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? The tower has deactivated itself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. The superscan shows "all clear"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As if XANA had called off his attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well that's one less thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for us to worry about, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's up with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is he sulking or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe his rendezvous</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>didn't go well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here are your rides. Please remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we have a diary to decode.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've chosen the tower at 72 degrees</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>South and 55 degrees West!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as I activate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>start the decoding process!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'm activating the tower…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! It's working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The decoding of the data is underway,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, but it might take some time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever XANA's leaves us in peace,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I spoke too soon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out! XANA's creatures</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>heading your way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where from? We can't see anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! XANA's pulled out the big guns!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh! Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! XANA's taken over Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. I'm sure of it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and thumps fists]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I don't know how XANA did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I do. It's not the real Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's one of XANA's creatures!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A polymorphing spectre!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where's the real Odd, then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Is anybody there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yoohoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantulas whine]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantulas howl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Talk about a tailgater! Worse than Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, it's a trap! He's trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to lead you away from the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there a problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, man!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to gain control of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Abort the mission! Stop decoding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and come back to Earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the woods. but it's like trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find a needle in a haystack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait! While I was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hacking into the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I managed to locate the emergency</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>telephone closest to Odd's phone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You can do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Odd still has his cell on him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then he's in the North-East</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>corner of the woods!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's near the Hermitage. I'm off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hangs up phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't stop the decoding program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's taking up too many resources.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's out of my control now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bad news! If XANA manages</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get control of the tower now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll be able to get into the restricted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>access part of the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could lose all the data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Franz Hopper's diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Not to mention everything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've programmed in yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our combat gear, the vehicles,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the transfer codes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my materialization program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is about to take control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the tower! You have to stop it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich exclaiming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, right. Okay. But how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to isolate the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try and cut the cables! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantula moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're wasting your time, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd has never beaten me yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yeah. Well, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That changes things!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both exclaiming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantulas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's is going to do it, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there anything new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way to stop the process!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's buggy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both exclaiming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! You're not so bad there, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Full of surprises, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[XANA yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, no fair!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It figures. At least</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have to climb anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess you can say that I'm really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up to my neck in trouble this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is about to take over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've just got one last little thing to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…take care of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[XANA yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All done, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Make it back, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantula growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! I'm here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yoohoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi straining] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is about to steal all my data!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're done for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Hey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't get it! It looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has lost control of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper's helping us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on on your side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The decoding program is going full speed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No girl's ever kept me waiting that long!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got Odd. How about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're decoding Franz Hopper's diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper was the creator of XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In his diary, he wrote down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything that happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the creation of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means that you'll</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be able to find the antivirus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, it does.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there's something more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Spit it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before Franz Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>virtualized himself on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and being taken prisoner by XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he lived on Earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We already knew that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but what we didn't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was that he had a child.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? What became of her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He virtualized her on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the same time as himself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And? Did she fall victim to XANA, too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She stayed on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Hopper's daughter were on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would have definitely known.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm… not…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>