<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA'S KISS</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Jean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Azra? Claire?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lola?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… Double yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you've dated every</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>girl in the eighth grade?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone except Heidi Klinger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you a trying to set a record</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way! I'm searching for true love!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, look who's here. Hi, dear Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna see a movie with me this afternoon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Depends on what's playing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Adventure in the Tropics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no… What a bummer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've already seen it! Shame…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll see it with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] The film…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! Let's go, then!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do you mean that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb sneers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You actually went to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Adventure in the Tropics</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather study for a math quiz</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than go to the movies with Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] You make me sick, Stern!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really think you're hot stuff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna knock that smile off your face!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, go on! What are you waiting for!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and grunts clumsily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch… Now that has gotta hurt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd mumbles unintelligibly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd spits]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I said: jealousy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>makes people go bananas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] And love</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>plays tricks with your mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I gotta go and get Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promised to give her my croissants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She likes them with her hot chocolate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What were you saying about love?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does it do to people's minds?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like there are no exceptions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the rule!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Speaking of hot chocolate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I gotta get moving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I finally got a date with Heidi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're going to give her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your croissants?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You must be joking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A guy's gotta eat, doesn't he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't seen Odd, have you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He promised to have breakfast with me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Heidi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Heidi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Ulrich gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Heidi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey there, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't have the answers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the math quiz, would you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mathias groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow… I sure am glad I brushed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my teeth this morning!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Would you mind telling me why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you kissed me in front of Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you out of your mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Heidi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Heidi shrugs angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey everyone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Slide over and make me some room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you wanna sit with Heidi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's all by herself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen! I don't know what all this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is about, but I swear to you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure threw me a real</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>curve-ball there, Mr. Romantic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Guess you won't need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this croissant!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Ulrich! Glad I ran into you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In case you haven't heard,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's going out with Mathias Durrell!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Morning everyone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, you like Durrell, do you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a nice guy, why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How does he kiss, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiss? How should I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Cut out the acting, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William saw you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? What--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rumor has it, I'm dating Mathias Durrell!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No kidding! Well, rumor has it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I kissed Heidi Klinger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Croissant?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm not hungry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sneers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich will never go out with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He said so! I heard him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speak of the devil, there he is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you ask him yourself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What were you saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] How does he do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does he have that I don't?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything! Except for your gross pimples.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dare you to say that again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey Yumi! Everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumet] Yes, right…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last time we were discussing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the causes of World War I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Aelita, can we talk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're in class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumet] …the assassination</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the archduke Francis Ferdinand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-the heir to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why did you kiss Heidi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>not </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>kiss Heidi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't a very nice thing to do to Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kissing Sissi to get back at Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You call that nice?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What! I didn't kiss Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>saw </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumet] And now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my first question is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"when did Gallieni die?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, class? I'm waiting!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When did Gallieni die?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dithering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the end of his life?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whole class laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern! What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should be in class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, is that you, Yolanda?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy 1] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy 2] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanted to talk to me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's talk about you and Nicolas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita puzzled] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope he's better at kissing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than he is at math!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never kissed Nicolas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, you kiss the biggest loser</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then you lie about it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trust me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You make a fool of me in public,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then you lie to me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and now you ask me to trust you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could you do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really let me down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have no idea how much, either…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs and huffs frustratedly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dialing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm telling you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never kissed Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings] Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy on the phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich on the phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's meet in the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dialing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita's voicemail] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hello!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Aelita! Leave me a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, I can explain everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All this kissing is another</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of XANA's schemes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That doesn't make any sense!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can't control us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that, but I also know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I did not kiss Heidi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so there must be a Jeremy clone somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And a Yumi clone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And an Ulrich clone, also.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. And I bet they're all just</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one big polymorphic clone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A poly-what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A polymorphic clone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can change its appearance at will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA must have sent a kind of ghost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that can look like anyone it wants!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To make trouble in our group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Divide and conquer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's really smart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not like us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess Odd was right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jealousy makes people crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, we've gotta go to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to solve this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gone. And all because of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sarcastic tone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, bravo! Where did she go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I might know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really sorry, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're… not angry with me anymore?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No! I figured it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, XANA was using a polymorph</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that can change its appearance at will!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, you didn't really kiss Heidi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! Let's go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get to the factory fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not too upset with me, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! But--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's XANA! He made a clone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of me to trick you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't listen to him, Aelita! He's XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I've got this straight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of these two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the poly-talking clone, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The polymorphic clone, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… Trust me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't listen to him! I'm the real Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know I am! I kissed you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That's right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The real Jeremy would not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have kissed me like that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Keep your hands off her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Jeremy's distorted groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick! To the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys go on, I'll take care of him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy stomp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Not the big tough guy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Jim's distorted grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch mechanism whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanners!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm launching the virtualization process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming and buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The tower isn't far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Direction: north, north-east.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Across the bridge!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, XANA… If you're gonna keep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>changing appearances like that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do me a favor, turn into a wimp next time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, not him! I know his kind:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>small, but tough as nails!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Odd's distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming and whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Head for the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did I tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Odd's distorted panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[weapon zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's sending a monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're almost there, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Super-speed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Odd's distorted yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blade swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Let's swap monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator mechanism whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gate closing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Careful, Yumi! At ten o'clock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll materialize the Overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts and howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator mechanism whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans] Thanks, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts, groans and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Careful! Behind you, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hornets!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thump]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosions]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clink]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[squawks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm nearly there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm trapped!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why isn't this elevator working?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa's attacking Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about the monster for now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's no picnic out here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You okay, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted nod in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm gonna need the Overbike!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got it, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Yumi! We'll manage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, poly-whatever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna transform you now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical stomping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>De-virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy thump]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you do to him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Yumi in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! Help me, it's XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this polymorph, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! No, cut it out, pea-brain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the real Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right! You expect me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to fall for that old one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On three, we pulverize you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One… Two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Three…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both yelp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, you've gotta wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's hardly got any memory left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Drop her, fish-face!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shudders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm… I'm okay…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm not feeling so great…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing ceases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's very sweet of you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But as I already told you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm engaged to be married.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if that's true, Yolanda,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why'd you kiss me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I… kissed you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should get some rest, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now be a good boy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and let me take your temperature.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How did you guess</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was the real Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Because you called me pea-brain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA would never call me that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got too much… respect for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, XANA just doesn't know you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as well as Yumi does!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with me for a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to check something, do you mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, go ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Check what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smooch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, come back down to earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope XANA leaves us alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a little while!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think Jeremy's gonna need some time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get over that one. Right, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd, Ulrich and Yumi laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>