<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[eerie music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who is that screaming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… You are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know what time it is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts] Five o'clock in the morning…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, that's right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this is the third night in a row</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've woken me up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have had it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping, screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Out of our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't go in there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a huge wolf inside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[comedic horn]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A four-eyed wolf.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a shame you didn't dream about me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because you know me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a real dream come true!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>More like a nightmare</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell the truth, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These visions of yours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are becoming a real problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It all started at the Hermitage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you should go back there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What? Back to that old house?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure you remember, but last time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we were attacked by a cupboard,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lamp and a gang of forks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like that place. It scares me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have any choice, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we don't do something,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your hallucinations could get worse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't worry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this time we'll be with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] My legs are shaking…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's happening to me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nothing to worry about!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It happens to Jeremy all the time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come on, we'll see who's scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[foreboding music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There… there… Stay down, boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See. Everything is just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[foreboding music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes… I mean, I think so!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you have another vision?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but it was different this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as if something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or someone was leading me to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was something in a tree</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Mr. Pück…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mysterious music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] So to make a long story short,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's never seen this toy gnome,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she's been dreaming about it for days</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she knows it's called Mister Pück!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not a gnome, it's an elf.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, whatever it is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this whole story is definitely paranormal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So Aelita? Still playing with dolls?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! Give that back right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go fetch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! A bit of advice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>give me that toy right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What toy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Herb, I dare you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take your glasses off, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer] What is all this noise about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. You can have it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but only because it's you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at this triangle marked A,B,C…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer] The point "I"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the middle of the segment AB…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What's this key doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What do you think it opens?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure wish I knew</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have no idea at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a property that can be proven.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Meyer] Do I have a volunteer…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A locker!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the key to a train station locker!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy. I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A complex number is called transcendent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only if the rational coefficient's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>polynomial root is a polynomial zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, indeed. That is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Sierpiński-Mazurkiewicz paradox.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it is not the answer to our problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[announcer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Train 6537 leaving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on track five, all aboard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This is it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you like to do the honors?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] FH, what does that stand for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fuzzy hands, fifty-cent hot dog,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fried "hegg."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Egg" doesn't start with an H.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just testing to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you were on your toes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh wow! Music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Certainly not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see what we can come up with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Franz Hopper's diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe we'll be able to find out more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the Hermitage's mysterious owner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] For sure! But not right away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything is encrypted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] We'll have to decode it first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] How much time do you need?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] One, maybe two hours?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-More like one or two years.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rock music playing on alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Come on, time to get up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans] Just a little bit longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna take a shower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lamp rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking, growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning, screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you can't…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps, grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's ghosts attacked us! Me and Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. No harm done. They ran away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Superscan didn't detect any</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>activated towers. XANA'S attack failed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird. XANA can possess humans…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But not you two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must have something to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with sex appeal…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right. I'm sure of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Running is the noblest event</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in athletics,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except maybe for the long jump,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or the shot put, javelin, high jump,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pole vault…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some of you may associate running</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with cowardice, as in running away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing could be further from the truth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as he who runs well goes far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Now let's see how powerful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your strides are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For those of you with short memories,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let me remind you that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was I gonna say? Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May I remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we start when I say "go"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not on "get set" and not on "ready".</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, well, after "ready, get set,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is when I say, "go!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Okay. On your marks…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get set, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] What now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I twisted my ankle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Yeah, of course you did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't get strong muscles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sitting in front of a computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb, take him to the infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, would you mind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if Aelita came with me instead?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, whatever. Go on, then!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take him far away from me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! You're not limping anymore!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Has your ankle stopped hurting?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone vibrating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers] Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's been possessed by XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This morning, Odd and I were almost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>possessed by a couple of ghosts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But they didn't succeed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why would it have worked on Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No idea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I saw him heading for the parklands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's in his arms. She was unconscious!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll check the super scan!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's meet at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pitiful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A slug could've made it around faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm counting on you to raise the level!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've got to go to the restroom first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, and I gotta go too, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make it snappy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right! Which one of you wimps is next?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Sector One, the ice territory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>south, southeast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yeah, XANA's attacked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to stop Jeremy and fast too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, no! Listen to me, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So are you going down, too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, it's totally weird</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be fighting against Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, I don't want to hurt him, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick! We've got to get to Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here. These are the coordinates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay. Over here, twinkle fingers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a good feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're really going to hit it off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How are you doing, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think you can handle it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not as good as Jeremy at it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The virtualization countdown</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has been launched.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Look, there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He who runs well, goes far!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is Odd the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who teaches you nonsense like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, as a matter of fact, it's Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm sure glad that post was there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not my face.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Got any other tricks up your sleeve?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Uh oh,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that wasn't very smart, was it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially since you're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's got to fix it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep your eyes open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have Jeremy to warn us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about monsters this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh oh! I don't like the sound of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can you have a decent discussion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with someone who has no sense of humor?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Easy does it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] Not so clever now, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Blocks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Take this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, protect Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of the Blocks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Triplicate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fusion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, sparky! Scared of heights, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, so you're not scared of heights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans, screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna knock your block off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you dumb blockhead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sounds like you miss Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your jokes are worse than his.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I call a job…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Materialization Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triangulate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not nice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to devirtualize your best friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd coughing, gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No sweat. Head for the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of this overgrown bug.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never trust a guy with glasses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning louder]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well? How are you feeling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I remember talking to Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich and then after that, nothing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just a black hole.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA took control of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He destroyed all of Franz Hopper's CDs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Apparently,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he had a problem with his notes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean "whew"? It's a disaster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it isn't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last night when I got back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the train station, I stopped in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] And I copied the CDs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto a highly-restricted access part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the super computer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the only one who can access them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a genius, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still, there's something I don't get.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why couldn't XANA's ghosts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>take control of Odd and me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then have no trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>controlling Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] I might have an explanation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Apart from you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're all used to fighting on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe that gives us more resistance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] But then how can we protect me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just might have the answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the last time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I ever set foot on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just because of a couple of Megatanks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's really just not my thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'll never be able to hack it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I think I'd rather be possessed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by XANA than go back there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll just keep on the lookout for ghosts,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well? What did he look like on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He looked… How…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can I say this tactfully?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ridiculous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[orchestral music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita's voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Come on, Mister Pück!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go for a walk in the garden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>