<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>IMAGE PROBLEM</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thirty degrees north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both keep panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should be able to see it by now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sticks out like a sore thumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing happening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's awfully calm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, be careful. You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yoohoo. Hi Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't see anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of the ordinary in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure it's the right one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was what the scan picked up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at least for a few seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] And you said you felt pulsations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a while ago, didn't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did. Well, let's say yes and no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure I did anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought I did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then, I'll go and try to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Jeremy gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sounds like Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you hear me, Yumi? Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, Yumi's disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, she couldn't have just vanished!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, hold on. I'll get back to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's wrong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the hot chocolate today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It tastes like sweat socks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and an old pair of sneakers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, the gourmet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Yoo hoo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, yoo hoo, yoo hoo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, well, what do you know, your fan club!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it. Your darling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's deserted you for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like your brain, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It deserted you a long time ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hello? Oh, it's you Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I recommend the hot chocolate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Take my word for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hm. What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, easy does it. That's it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, well then, what happened to her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, she started feeling sick...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during recess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's ‘cause she's been studying real hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our teachers give us too much homework.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, I'll take care of her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now back to class, all of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard what I said. Now go! Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, feeling better? Mmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, no, come on, lie down now, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Please, you need to rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure she wasn't hit by a laser?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe there was a megatank</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hiding somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no, I would've seen it on the screen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She still had all her life points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she was devirtualized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, in any case,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something abnormal happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The proof is she passed out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Normally, the return trip's pretty easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah! That's what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to try it one of these days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You'll love it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Guess you're feeling better, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You had us scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell us what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure you're okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah. I'm just tired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, tell us what happened on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's go over to the factory now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In your condition?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a pretty crazy idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey listen, we have much more important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>things to do... like eating,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about Aelita? Is she safe?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, I hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told her to stay in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to go and check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you really can't remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think it could come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the scanners?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A bug or something like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless it's XANA trying out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a new way of attacking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't the slightest idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm wondering if all these transfers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't becoming a health problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do I smell fish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or just cheap perfume?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're such a riot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Ulrich, what do you say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we get together after school, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get together with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very tempting, but... </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>not</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're showing off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because Yumi is here, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mademoiselle </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>likes to keep the competition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as far away as she can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you go out with her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's really pretty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you wouldn't be trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make fun of me, would you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] Great, thanks a lot Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be waiting for you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the park after school. </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ciao</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to pull anyway, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing. Go on, go out with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's been waiting for this for ages.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Ishiyama,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>come to my office right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that thing wasn't there before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like a guardian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energy buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's going on with Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is she mad at me or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen her like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She must've had a really serious shock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the big idea of having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a date with Sissi, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't the time for that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you hear, Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you want an explanation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go and ask Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll leave you to your love stories.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a super psychopathic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>computer to feed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Yumi, this is unspeakable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our poor nurse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dorothy is still very upset.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could you have done such a thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm giving you two hours of detention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the library to teach you a lesson.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something troubling you, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Care to tell me about it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I'm here to help you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's part of my job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep this up, and I'll have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to inform your parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the way you're behaving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's enough now Miss Ishiyama!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get your hand off the phone right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not my parents!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't warn you again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, if you keep this up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll suspend you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[telephone line beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hello there, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts puzzled]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as I got close to the monsters,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they started to shoot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You shouldn't have left the tower, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're not mad at me, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mad? No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you made an important discovery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This could have something to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with what happened to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Should I go back there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send Ulrich and Odd as backup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what happened to Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>might happen to one of your friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or both of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If they come to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it could be very dangerous for them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you're right. Go on then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but promise me you'll be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You know me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's you. What did the principal want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to go the factory now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First of all, there's no reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go and second, you have to rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to go to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nobody's going back to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I give the order.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got some tests I have to run first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's important, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to go back to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers] Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you trying to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I... I'm not sure it's a good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should go home and get some rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, take me to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers] But, but, but, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should go home and take a bath.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, a cold shower... very cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very, very, very, very cold</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to calm you down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta get going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, no, wait. It's not what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I swear, Ulrich, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bravo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, time to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teacher] And we can also observe cases</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of parthenogenesis among certain insects.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This phenomenon is relatively common,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>comparable to a sort of natural cloning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is to say the animal gives</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>birth to a replica of itself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an exact replica with no differences</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scientists have succeeded in employing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this process with rabbits.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll continue with this subject tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you have to listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't wanna listen to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something's not right with Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's not in her normal state.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what she's been through,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she's traumatized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this phenomenon is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I could tell you, but I have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no idea. Aelita's checking it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could be XANA's doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no, I forgot to lock the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] All my equipment!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think Sissi's behind all this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would she want to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, maybe it's Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He sure was mad when we saw him today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, who was the last one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to leave this room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that's impossible. Not Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh, you gotta admit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's been acting weird lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi hasn't been herself lately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But still, the enemy is XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's launched an attack,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm sure all this other stuff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to distract us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while he's calmly and quietly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>getting rid of Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's all alone on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we can't get to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are we going to the scanner room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Go on, do your stuff, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready? Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich. Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd. Scanner Ulrich. Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? She's not with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, she wasn't transferred.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, we've got to go and free Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Yumi's not...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The real Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The one who's here in Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The other one was created by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, whatever you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't go anywhere near Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you hear me, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi continues grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a guardian...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A sort of digital jail adapted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the body imprisoned in it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't destroy it with my weapons!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can create a clone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a false image of Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can try to convince the guardian</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he's mistaken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles] Wow, piece of cake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants] What... What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, no time to explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's not responding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have the feeling that something's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's all alone with the other one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If she destroys the scanner,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The other? The other what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who wants to wreck the scanner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The other... you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if something has happened to Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and what if we don't manage to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower in time? This is serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, one of us has to go back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to reality and right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We don't have much time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right. I'll go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's better if I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know how many life points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have left, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if I only have five or ten,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't be of much use to you here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I also have a little matter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deal with, that only I can settle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's between me and myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then you go, but first you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to devirtualize yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The question is how.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're armed, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look just like me when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm having a bad day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh. [grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, watch out... on your right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many life points do I have left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's gotta be less than ten by now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[real Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] I'm still here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess I messed up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my calculations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You always were a washout in math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, but thanks to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can count to three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triplicate! [panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all three screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Fusion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you're up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fake Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fake Yumi laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming fades away]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energy buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The fact that XANA was able to materialize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another Yumi proves one thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It proves that materialization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is really possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] That's crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's helping us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with our materialization research.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Back to work then, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start programming again right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why bother?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I were you, I'd go and see XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got the answer. So ask him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't trust him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at the Yumi he sent us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes, she wasn't that different</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the original.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She sure was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She didn't fool me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw the difference,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as she started to flirt with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you have any proof</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that it's the real me you're looking at?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[stammers] What're you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no. Cut it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had enough of that for one day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not jealous, are you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sure looks like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>