<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ZERO GRAVITY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy 1] Okay, pass it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy 2] There you go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Come on, guys, you haven't even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>worked up a sweat. Let's go, go, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy 3] One, two, one, two...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ball whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[goalie grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ball whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[goalie growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clank]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone clapping and cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, guys. Good warm-up session.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Play like that and you'll whip</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lincoln Junior High</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with no problem in this afternoon's final.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you all at the stadium</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after lunch for a final briefing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and always remember:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a soccer team is like an army.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It needs a good general</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who can lead it, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, break ranks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Working out to stay in shape?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen kid, I'm gonna be honest with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're my key to winning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this afternoon's game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know we've got a good team,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Lincoln's got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this striker whose name is Matt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's nasty, I know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but don't worry, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't disappoint you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm counting on you, kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna pulverize them! Massacre 'em!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make mincemeat outta them and gobble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'em up and spit 'em out, baby!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey there, champion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Lincoln never gets the ball,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-we'll be bored out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nice of you to come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were here this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll be here this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not for you, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't wait to see Sissi cheerleading.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why we're coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[marching band music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-One, two, three, four!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on team, give us more!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Five, six, seven, eight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lincoln, we're gonna seal your fate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi whoops] Ta-da!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[baton whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lights crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lights crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, it disappeared, I tell you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It never came down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It just... just flew away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, sure, it's up in the sky</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or maybe it came down and landed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on someone's head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl 1] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ciao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] But it's true! I tell you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear, my baton disappeared</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into thin air!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We believe you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even if, scientifically,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's impossible... [groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, if I say that a supernatural thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>happened to me, it's because it's true!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You hear me, knucklehead?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A baton that flies up has to come down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if it doesn't there's something wrong!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something seriously wrong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I wanna know exactly what it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl 2] Look,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's the mysterious baton twirler!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Sissi, eat your steak and French fries</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fast before they fly away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girls laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both in unison] We've gotta talk,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy, I've spotted an activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tower in the mountain region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? Have you noticed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything strange going on in your world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just the usual things...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Batons that fly into the air</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don't come back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and Yumi who's suddenly airborne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It was weird!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lights started to blink,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a second later, I was floating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I couldn't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A break in gravity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>causing spontaneous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and localized weightlessness.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the connection between electricity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and weightlessness?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The magnetic field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could be the effect of a powerful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>electromagnet XANA's using to offset</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the magnetic attraction of Earth. You see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How dangerous is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not, if it's within</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the limits of space and time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But on a larger scale,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>look what happened to Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her baton never came back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We can't afford to take the risk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to go to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Well, count me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? You gotta be kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I said count me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go after the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna abandon the ship...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a soccer game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wake up Ulrich. This is about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>saving the world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to mention Aelita who's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>surely in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd rather kick a ball around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard what I said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't go and that's that. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Somebody say something, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's dropping us like a smelly sock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm really sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all you can say? "You're sorry"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd rather please the crowd, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All those admiring fans</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are more important than your friends!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave him alone. He's got his reasons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His parents are coming to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the game this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you ever met Ulrich's dad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not first in everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're nothing in his book.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And since Ulrich's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>report cards</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are kind of disastrous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the only way to make his dad happy is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When he plays soccer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why he's been training</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so hard for weeks now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gonna play today's game</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if his life depended on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why couldn't he have just told us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the reason?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, give away a secret?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, why worry?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich is gonna win the game,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and in the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're gonna save the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just have to do without him this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, you've got me, don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both chuckle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clock ticking loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] All right guys, the big day is here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Testing, one, two. Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello everyone. This is Milly and Tamiya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>reporting to you live from the stadium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a big day today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The ninth grade interschool final</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is about to begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although our school is favored to win,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot will depend on Kadic's striker,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our own Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're really counting on him today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now everybody, it's soccer time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[player 1 grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[player 2 pants and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me? Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm here, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, it's XANA, he's attacking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's trying to take over the city's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>electrical network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm gonna try to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get the spy program started.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With a data flow so dense,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there ought to be traces on the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Bingo! That's XANA all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heavy and predictable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[player 4 grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matt grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We knew Ulrich was in great form,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but what he's showing us today is beyond</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even our wildest dreams!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting and howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[goalie groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] A fantastic goal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Kadic team makes it one to nothing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after only three minutes of play.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lincoln's going to have to find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop Ulrich if they're going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to win this game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heavy, but very fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have much time. Ready to go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No problemo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta hurry up because if we don't,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA will be able to create</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>much more powerful magnetic fields.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Scanner Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The tower is at 30 degrees west.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[goalie groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy in crowd] Kadic! Kadic! Kadic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no stopping Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's amazing to watch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's two nothing, and the score may</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get out of hand if Ulrich keeps this up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's so handsome when he runs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, thanks Tamiya for that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>expert commentary on the game!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's ready to attack the school!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Fill us in, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not for today with Yumi and Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd have all gone to the game,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's where XANA wanted to trap us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it was his plan,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to concentrate all of the energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the science lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if we don't make it fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a good chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's gonna finish the game</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>outside of the stratosphere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No monsters for the time being,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we're still far from the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] This is awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta find a way to gain some time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing and crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You asked for it, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can hack a network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not the only one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on now! Stop Matt! He's getting away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matt panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Matt grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Matt gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Fantastic! Ulrich's as good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on defense as he is on the attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go Ulrich, go, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This program will help me counter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attacks on the science lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps] Ulrich, do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] That's the end of the first half.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic has a commanding two nothing lead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see if we can get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some comments first hand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I imagine you're confident after</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dominating Lincoln the past 45 minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh, Lincoln's in the finals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means they're a good team.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the words of our coach, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's our motivation that'll make us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>winners, and I honestly think...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Talk to you after the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better relax a bit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before the second half</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see what Jim has to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Answer your phone Ulrich, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What do you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich, I've been trying to reach you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a quarter of an hour.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't play with a cell phone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my hand, sorry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Listen, I know about...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Odd told me why this match</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is so important to you, but there's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an enormous and serious problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't go into all the details,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's not enough time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but XANA's gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>put the school into orbit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's true, I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He doesn't have enough power yet...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He'll get it from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the science lab's generator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta make sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nobody is in the building.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Ulrich! Second half's starting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No problem. Everyone's at the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mrs. Hertz isn't here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's probably in the chemistry lab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta go get her out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fluid trickling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't ask me to do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, anything, but not that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! What's wrong? What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm sorry, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta leave the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the only one who can do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta save her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Oh, everyone is numb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The crowd including yours truly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>simply doesn't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why has Ulrich just stopped?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] It must be the pressure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Stern moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Stern] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's a matter of life and death,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[player 2 grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Matt grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd gasps disappointed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Lincoln team has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just cut our lead in half.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Matt can't believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Ulrich let him score!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Please shut up, Jeremy. Just shut up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Matt panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] I'm gonna stop you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matt] We'll see about that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What awful luck for the Kadic team!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich looks hurt after that violent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tackle by Matt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come on! I didn't even touch him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, it's true!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Ulrich! Oh, no,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it. You can't do this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave me alone, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Oh wow, absolutely incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our superstar striker is leaving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the field with a knee injury.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our one irreplaceable player</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is out of the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi thinking]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I don't believe it for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a minute, and I'm gonna check this out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm leaving as well. Tell me everything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that happened while I'm gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, you're a cheerleader.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's not gonna be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot of cheering without Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if we do score a goal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can replace me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The crowd will love it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just dance your head off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs frustrated]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, objective in sight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The welcome committee looks manageable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of them in no time at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I should be able to neutralize XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but only for a few minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you've gotta work fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ten seconds to attack time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, Yumi, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hornets buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hornets buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Yumi panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hornet buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Yumi groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty sharp mosquitos.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since when did they grow brains?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants] But there's only one left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Negative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A new swarm of hornets is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, change of tactics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time we'll try diversion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, I've reloaded 20 arrows</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you, but that may not be enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Your turn, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] They just keep coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no end to them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? I just left the stadium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] Thanks, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What you're doing is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on my way to the chemistry lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] The best defense</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is an offense, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, but it depends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the number of enemies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's okay, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I made my own electric field</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to create a short circuit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But XANA is bound</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get ahead of me soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So be very careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno how long it's gonna last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just walked in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing happening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like I spoke too soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass shatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to hang on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for just a few seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as you've secured Mrs. Hertz,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can move into action.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta hang on now so</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita can get through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yumi, Odd, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, yeah, we're cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's okay. I've got Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, do your stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The reverse circuit is working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry to be so familiar with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yoo-hoo, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I dunno.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>impossible to control. Be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screaming in the distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts] I've got you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what's happening? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's too complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, where are you at now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, I'm back in control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's gonna rock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass shatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi and Ulrich yell]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do me a favor, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me it's gonna calm down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not for the time being.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It may get worse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so hang on tight any way you can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Yumi, what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It's horrible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost out of arrows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The telekinesis has exhausted Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the more hornets I kill,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the more there are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich, do you mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I do mind, so keep quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey Jeremy, what's that sound?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I... I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! XANA has managed to take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over 50 power stations!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, whatever you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't leave the building!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You understand? Stay inside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Hang in there, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not now! Concentrate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give us just a few more seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do it, Odd. I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, it's too soon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Well, Matt has a chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tie the score with this penalty shot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Matt grunts] Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[goalie groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The stadium!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey Aelita, you're crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hornets buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass shatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, no, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita utters soft sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. and Ms. Stern groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Stern groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] As soon as you're done crying,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just let me know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps] You were just luring them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you are the greatest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glass shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Stern groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Stern grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Stern] Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good-bye Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm proud of you. Really, I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. and Ms. Stern screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past. Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] It's a big day today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The ninth grade interschool final</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is about to begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although our school is favored to win,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot will depend on Kadic's striker,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our own Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're counting on him today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's rock, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, world champion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well yeah, but which world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why both of them, Jeremy, both of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[players grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>