<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko be, there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[game guns firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ha, ha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that, fireball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you, you slimy Vortex. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think you're so smart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait till I discombobulate you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the black hole!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, you mind cooling it a little?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, thanks a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just made me miss the bonus ball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm dying from sleep deprivation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and now you're making me start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-all over again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-At four a.m.?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Odd, wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to rise and shine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you guys dressed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll come to you. Think it over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, phys ed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about it, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Galactic Battle </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>totally wiped me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think an excuse like that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna sit well with Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do me a big favor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think of a nice legitimate excuse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I can stay here and sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? What am I supposed to tell him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks a lot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Della Robbia? Della Robbia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to have to repeat that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd felt sick, so he went</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the infirmary this morning, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Absent, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess when you're not feeling well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the only thing to do is head</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-De Vasseur.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ducros.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ducros] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] You say, present or here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>none of this "yeah" stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ducros] Yeah, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello, Naomi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How would you feel about having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a fantastic and breathtaking experience</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>together with me in the moonlight tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta be kidding, you dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Right. Today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going to work on the high jump.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't go to great lengths</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell you how this kind of sport</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can take you to great heights,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so just watch. Demonstration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gain momentum…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Release and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've told you over and over again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you insist on doing this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is where you'll end up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it's an occupational hazard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see you've already sent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd? But he hasn't been here at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, what kind of lame-o speech</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did G.I. Jim bore you with today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the only part I'm sorry I missed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Every time he opens his mouth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he cracks me up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, why don't we share</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little laughter in my office now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please tell me that I'm still sleeping,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and this is a nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-uh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're wide awake, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right about one thing:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is your nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Disappointed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that is the only word for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Stones, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am deeply disappointed in both of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I agree with that, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those two took me for some sort of idiot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You shamelessly acted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with total indifference</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the ethical values</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that this institution</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was designed to teach you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You lied, both of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Therefore, four hours of detention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Aelita groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Only four, sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and that's because I consider myself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be too--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Too weak?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls] Magnanimous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the lame excuse, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd, how could I know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Jim would pull his back out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you'd taken the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to think of a better excuse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't have had four hours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of detention!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you were just a bit less selfish,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd realize that I got stuck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with four hours of detention too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For what? Because you needed your sleep,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you lazy loser!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How would you feel about having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a fantastic and breathtaking experience</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>together in the moonlight tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita would rather have detention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than to go out with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How nice of you to ask, Nicolas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks! I'd really like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm hallucinating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna go out with that nerd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather hang out with a nerd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than a selfish potato head like you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These fries are tasty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I say something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it looks as if we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a bit of a cold war on our hands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, you two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why don't you kiss and make up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got more important things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Like exploring</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the network with the Skid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Especially to check out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that sphere you came across</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-on your last first trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great. When do we go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The longer we wait,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the stronger XANA gets,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I say we try tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's if our friends are ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bury the hatchet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As long as I don't have to talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to that dummy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suits me. What would I have to say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a lazy, selfish brat anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's progress, sort of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Aelita, are we still on for tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry. I mean, really I am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but something just came up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A… A big test I have to study for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well I guess that figures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was too true to be good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what I mean, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Herb. How would you feel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about having a fantastic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and breathtaking experience</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the moonlight tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[reel unwinding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is your fantastic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and breathtaking experience,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a dumb fishing trip?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't believe how fantastic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and breathtaking it can be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to catch a big fat pike.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a clown fish,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you know that, Nicolas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll scare the fish away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you talk too loud.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Take your time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Give it a rest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is Odd doing out at this hour?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought Aelita had a huge test</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to study for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, aren't you overdoing it a little?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's obvious whose side you're on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible! You'd think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they were back in kindergarten!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlocks seal]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right now, cool it, guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's concentrate on our mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hydraulics engaging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry over to your transporter spots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Doesn't it freak you out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have a real loser at the controls?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, energize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[power charging up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, do you mind asking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that dorky friend of yours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if he still remembers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to use the Skid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut it out, Aelita. Just ask him yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good answer, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you're starting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get on my nerves, both of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we've had enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you guys are all finished,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what do you say we take off?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Supports away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Vertical propulsion operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Ready to dive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in the network, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holoweb system connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, set course for bearing 170</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and look out for a hub.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll enter the coordinates of the sphere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you guys saw</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during your last mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hub in sight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hyper-fluid aspiration in three seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] This place is weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It gives me the creeps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I'm here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks. Glad to hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] What are you doing up there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm scared of heights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get really dizzy when I'm high up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, you're only fifteen meters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>above the ground.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas, would you shut up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay where you are. I'll come and get you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, this is horrible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't wanna die now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never even got to tell Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm crazy about her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Retro-brakes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lights operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sonar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're coming to the sphere now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Check the South Pole</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for an entry portal, like on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a visual on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's shut. What do I do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why don't you knock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe they'll open up for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Rotation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Shut up, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Key activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] There's an access code to crack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll take a couple of minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can let go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember what I said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a minute ago about Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I didn't really say it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you didn't really say you loved her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't tell Sissi what I didn't say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This looks really ancient.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think about it. What if the cable snaps,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or the floorboards give way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under our feet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or the rusty motor quits with us inside,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we're left here to rot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-with rats eating away at our insides--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, I get the idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll look for a staircase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I cracked the code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Way to go, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guy are on an exact copy of Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except that there's only one sector:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Forest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA created another Lyoko on the network?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you can bet it's not to save humanity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Knowing our friend XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure he's made lots</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of other copies exactly like this one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So do we check it out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You bet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want as much data as possible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on this new virtual world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, energize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All this for a forest territory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess we're not out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the woods yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we don't want him freaking out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or crying,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess someone should laugh at his joke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Odd were doing here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, they're not here now, so let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on. Check out that light.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, what you're gonna do now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is work in groups of two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One groups goes out exploring</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while the other watches the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll work with Ulrich, or Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For once, he's got a good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I've had it with you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and I are out of here right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We could use a vacation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you two can fight all you want to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as long as we're not around to hear it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here come your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Thanks, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] See ya! Have fun, you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicles zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[container clanks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers] Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] False alarm, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could've thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a different excuse, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you could stop thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about yourself for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, Megatank at three o'clock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Aelita, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi, XANA's attacking the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need you back there now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Got it Jeremy. We're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicles zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita, listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Skid's shield can't hold out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And without the Skid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't guarantee you a return ticket</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you generate more power</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the shields?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think so, but I'll need time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To reinforce the Skid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to re-route a chunk of energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Supercomputer itself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't taking energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Supercomputer kind of risky?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> We have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the only solution I can think of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] When you put your mind to it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can come up with good ideas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We won't have enough power</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to launch a return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But because XANA hasn't attacked anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the real world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it shouldn't be necessary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] What if it's not their voices</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're hearing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whose voices do you think they are then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ghosts, werewolves, bloodthirsty Draculas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't laugh at things like that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially not at night time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's ridiculous. Now let's climb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Odd and Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I want to catch them red handed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet they came here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do some industrial espionage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Aelita, industrial spies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In an abandoned factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe they're into witchcraft.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got a huge problem at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb and Nicolas are on the verge</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of discovering the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's impossible to launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a return</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't let those nerds get near</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take care of them, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can manage without you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] I'm not going any further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm stopping.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're stopping halfway up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You better believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Hear that? They're behind us now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] Then we'll just head back down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I saw you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Uh-oh! The Skid's done for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if handsome gets his hands on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope Jeremy had time to reinforce it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, pal, you came a little too late</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to wreck everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, reload me, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, bummer, I forgot he's not there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword slices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] You go that way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll go this way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah-ha! I got you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me, will you, you idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicle zooms]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone's knows that speeding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is really dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elevator brakes squealing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks as if the elevator works fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, you're back--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta shut the elevator down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No big deal. We'll just wait them out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll have to come back this way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Herb and Nicolas must've seen you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>come into the factory with Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and now they're looking for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it's Aelita and me that they're after,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then I've got an idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that should get rid of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'll need for Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get back here ASAP</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and for you to have a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can I say this… An open mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you mean by an open mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Better face facts, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna win.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, we've got an emergency here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to devirtualize Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? But if he does that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then who'll pilot the Skid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you can do it. I'll guide you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If you say so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat. I'll devirtualize you on three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-One… Two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword slices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be patient, like when you're fishing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you want me to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unless you've got a better idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] You'll see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the early worm catches the bird…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, the fish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal door squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kissing sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you guys enjoying the show?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] So that's why they were hiding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] They like each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look awfully serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did I scratch the paint</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the Skid or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just worried about this Lyoko copy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If there's one out there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means that there's also</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>infected with XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere else on Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To destroy this new Supercomputer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna have to figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some sort of way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to materialize you into the real world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the copy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll handle that when the time comes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure that's your only worry?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-uh. You see guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein just found out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what it means to have an open mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] So now you've got eyewitness proof</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Aelita's going out with Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the dumbest story I ever heard,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since the one about Mr. Chardin's toupee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I tell you I saw them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not a story, it's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact look, Sissi, here they come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You dumbbell!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look who's talking, you selfish loser!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slap]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That should put an end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to any ridiculous gossip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think you had your heart was in it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you called me a selfish loser.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What? Now listen, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Chill out, I'm just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, it doesn't take much to wind you up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] I'm gonna get you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>