<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] So this thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can destroy someone under XANA's control?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It isn't a thing, it's an EMP bomb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It makes an electromagnetic blast</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that affects anything electronic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And because the pixelated body</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of someone under XANA's control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is held together by a force field,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>well--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we have a class soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you give us the cliffnotes version?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bomb explodes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guy under XANA's control, obliterated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Except for one little thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We haven't come up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a mini version yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi isn't here with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course! I just saw her with William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How stupid of me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got that right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why is it whenever you see Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you feel like being nasty?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe being with someone nasty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rubs off on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] An activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's on the move again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad for a music class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where do you think you're going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the way to your classroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I have to go to music class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lucky you, we've got chemistry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Visual on the Principal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Good morning, Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were on our way to class…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! That hurts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] What's the matter, sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't treat us that way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Wait! What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans] Let go of me, sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're hurting me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Yumi groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The principal has gone crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's kidnapped Yumi and Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flute playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Mirti shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Delmas has kidnapped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ishiyama and Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Mirti] What kind of nonsense is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's true, sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] He beat up William Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't move. I'll be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] It's incredible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi isn't answering and Odd isn't either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] A message from XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita at two o'clock in the Ice Sector</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give herself up to the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, Odd and Yumi will be liquidated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We don't have time to lose! Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] OK!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want everybody in their seats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do people expect us to save the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if they don't leave us alone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shivers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teeth chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Given the temperature, I'd say Siberia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-My cellphone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He must have taken them from us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We have to get out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we freeze to death.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mr. Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, sure I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he's not cooperating with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Everybody here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Classes are canceled for the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can go home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi and William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The detective</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will ask you a few questions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! What about those guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should question them, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're always scheming with Odd and Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Stern, Belpois and Stones!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Definitely not our day…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't be surprised</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if they knew something about my father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, you three. Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Hey, come on! Get back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim groans] Back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[policeman] We got them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy and Aelita shout]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scrapes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shivers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd stutters] My friend is really cold!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Apparently, you plan on keeping us alive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or you would have already blown us away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shivers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In case you didn't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cold can kill us, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, If I were you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd do something about it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shivers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shivers and hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Nice going, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really messed up this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're the only ones</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who can help your father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters] Your father is possessed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes, right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like in </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hospital of Horrors</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's controlled by a demonic entity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who'll make him do unspeakable things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, basically, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Are you okay? Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're at the refrigerated warehouses,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-on the wharf… Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, in order to help my father,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to go deactivate a tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a virtual universe?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs] My last question.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why should I help a couple</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of completely wacko pathological liars?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep it down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not us you'll be helping,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's your father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to trust us! I'm begging you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[detective] Thank you. You can go home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth Delmas, it's your turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, next time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>leave me an instruction manual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true that my father's been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>acting weird for a while now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He locks himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the basement to tinker around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he says strange things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The other day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he told me he was fed up with life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I told him it was natural</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a Principal with a heavy load</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to feel that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he started laughing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a really crazy way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and said that he hadn't decided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where to set it off yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then I also heard him on the phone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>saying he'd gotten some material.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't really get what he said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sounded like…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-…"decorators" or "destinators" or--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Detonators?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! That was it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Evacuate the school!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for trusting us, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't mention it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if your story about a virtual world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-turns out to be phony, you'll regret it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] On my way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the refrigerated warehouses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to set Yumi and Odd free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's ultimatum expires in 15 minutes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go as fast as I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet you at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I'm coming with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, my father's involved in this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I want to check out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this virtual world business</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-you've been blabbering about!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I feel like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in a James Bond movie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA doesn't waste time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa is waiting for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How much time before the ultimatum is up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Two minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry! One minute to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there are dozens of cold rooms here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should hand myself over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Ulrich will make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The ultimatum is up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] No, Mr. Delmas, stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, the bomb you made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't blow away the Principal, will it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, theoretically speaking, no…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scrapes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You said that bomb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fried anything electronic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that would mean cellphones, too. Right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm such a dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I hadn't thought of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can we find out if it worked?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father might be dead by now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or in great shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Giving Odd and Yumi a piece of his mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] It worked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But it wrecked my mobile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! What rotten luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[punches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did you learn to punch like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I took Pencak Silat classes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To impress Ulrich, but it didn't work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-By the way, why'd you ask me to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to help Ulrich, Odd and Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only I can deactivate the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he would've never let me do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Sissi. Do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get to the factory. I'll take care of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? I think there's a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My head!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Aelita is there in the video game,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with some kind of giant squid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To Lyoko! Fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about my father? Is he all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could be better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's outside playing with Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's on the plateau</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ahead of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take the tunnel, I'll go straight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Read you loud and clear, chief!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you be all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, saddle up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should be ahead of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it, now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich must be taking a beating up there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there's no activated tower here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The scan picked it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It has to be somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Tarantulas are there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the tip!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like the entrance to an ice cave.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi shouts] Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave him alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Odd, get one of those Tarantulas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle the other one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, jump at the right moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry! Ulrich is being mastered.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so is Sissi now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Change of plan. You take the controls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans] Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums] Here's the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich, are you all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, thanks to you. Thanks a lot, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Is he--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just knocked out. Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going to happen to him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, with the kidnapping and all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It will be all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one will remember.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Neither will you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For me, it's not the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, then, you'll remember this kiss.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can go ahead, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I wonder which is worse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being blind or seeing this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi isn't here with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course! I just saw her with William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How stupid of me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ciao!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, hello!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're still thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about what happened on the bridge?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What happened on the bridge?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, what did happen on the bridge?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's true. Nothing happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, it's time for class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something smells really fishy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What are they hiding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure it's just a boy thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>