<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>COLD WAR</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Something is not right here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What do you mean, "quack"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An alarm signal and no activated tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] And you're sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the alarm last night?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Not a hundred percent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was pretty groggy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! Could you make less noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! If I don't find the DVD of my short</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>film in the next three seconds,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll turn into a pumpkin!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which short film?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Natural Grandeur 2</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or "</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I Guess our Guest is a Ghost</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I Guess our Guest is a Ghost</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] If you want me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to become rich and famous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I absolutely have to give it to TV!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TV? Who's TV?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His real name is Thomas Vincent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but everybody calls him TV,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because he's the famous news reporter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on TV… TV, get it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TV's gonna be here in five minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My career is nipped in the bud!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fame, fortune and glory are mine!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dear TV!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On behalf of the students and faculty,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're very honored that you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay! No big deal, time is money.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Edna, my camera… woman,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>person, whatever… Never on time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Show up late one more time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you're finished!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got 150 cameramen who'd kill</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a chance to work with TV.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You, sweatshirt,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>park my car out of sight from the kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want them scratching it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Now, let's continue</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with our study of plant life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After our field trip last week,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I asked you to calculate the yield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the field of corn that we visited.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, who can give me the answer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Poliakoff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Yeah… 1,527 tons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really, Nicolas… Well done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've solved the problem of world hunger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Give me a panoramic shot of the kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can I help you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. Get out of the shot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do our schools still provide a future</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our youth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faced with the teacher's lax attitudes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have reason to doubt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To see how bad it's become,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all you need to do is pick out a student</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at random and ask him his</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>grade point average. You, for instance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ninety-nine point 87 out of 100.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, cut!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's too high!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who here has a below 60 average?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you're flunking out of school, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me, not exactly. On the other hand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have this great DVD to show you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[TV] This cannot be happening!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[TV] What's with this bunch of…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm so disgusted!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TV didn't even want to see my masterpiece!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that what it means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be a starving artist?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The alarm, XANA's gone on the attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'll warn Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, I sure hope this goes quickly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I don't want to miss</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>today's meatballs and gravy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I haven't had it for ages.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Watch it! You've got company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, stay behind me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone bring their insecticide?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Supersprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser Arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bunch of chickens!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess XANA's not up to snuff today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, weird or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's better for us because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have something waiting for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meatballs and gravy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, my lady, your tower is served.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, wait! Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] The tower is deactivating itself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does that mean, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! Another tower activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The tower just deactivated by itself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't get this at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think it's a bug</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or a new plot by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Go to lunch. I'll stay here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and try to work all this out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If anything happens,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give you a shout.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'll stay with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With two of us, it'll go faster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] What's with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these little mini-servings?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] Come on, cookie, don't be shy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Load up the meatballs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] Let me tell you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sure is no picnic being a field reporter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wait, what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are all the meatballs?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On TV's tray.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans in disgust]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, this is awful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any guy who had wheels like this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd go out with in a heartbeat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm outta of here! I'm starving!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's starting up again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Should I tell the others?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might deactivate by itself again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thunder rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look! It's snowing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down, everyone. Stay in your seats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sub-systems seems okay, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! The tower is still activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe this time, XANA really is attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing, indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's enough, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA's attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Inside, on the double!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, I got you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you're right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I bet the weather's better there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're stuck at school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because of the blizzard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A nightmare! XANA's back to his old self.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb grunts] Closed. Now what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Follow me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teeth chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine starting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool! The Subsonics!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[up-tempo rock music</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>playing over car speakers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV shivering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Here, Mr. TV!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This will keep your hair in place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good, Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did well to take the children safely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the basement of the Science Building.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Look, Mr. Delmas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found the weather station. I got this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>free with my </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sumo Mag</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> subscription.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Up there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it shows the temperature outside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's four degrees below zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And down here, it shows…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the temperature in here, 37.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirty-seven degrees!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Let's go down to the boiler room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a scientific fact that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we huddle together, we'll keep warmer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smack]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] It's a scientific fact that a good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>slap will keep your cheek warm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Delmas] I'm setting it on maximum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That should warm us up a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Edna! Stop wasting film!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An unbelievable deep freeze</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has taken hold of the city</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and what are you shooting?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three brats in a basement!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] It's not even PG-13!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Edna sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-People expect spectacular TV from TV!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] So let's get out of this rat hole and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go where the action is, the city!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not with me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine! You're fired!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't have cold feet on this job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teeth chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't go outside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's 40 below out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[TV] My car keys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think I left them in the ignition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Did you hear that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forty below.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And there's no reason for XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] The only solution</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to deactivate the tower on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] But if we go out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll end up as ice sculptures!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to try. We'll sneak out of here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and search the rooms for warmer gear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and then we'll run over to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbling steadily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm warning you, Herb. If you fall asleep,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll slap you again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think you're doing in my car?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! You're not gonna leave us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this blizzard, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine. I'll drop you off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get in the back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don't get my soft leather seats dirty,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans, grunts] Stupid power steering!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We gotta go and help them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Michael?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How cold is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fifty-eight degrees below zero outside,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twenty-three degrees in here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A deadly cold snap has hit the city</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which was buried under ice and snow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a matter of minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The authorities have put the emergency</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cold weather plan into action</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but chaos has broken out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nonetheless. Telephone lines--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shivering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't my fault!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was the power steering!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yeah, right. Why don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you make yourself useful in the meantime?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get Sissi and Herb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the boiler room, fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Now that's authority.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich! Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps] That was close!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] This is why…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like bonsais better!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We'll get you out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] One, two, three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Forget it. It's much too heavy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go to the computer factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's more important!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just can't leave her here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She won't last long in this cold!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay. You get to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll stay here with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there. I'm gonna go and look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for something to get you out of there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have no choice, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA is waiting for, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For you to go to Lyoko alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so he can steal your memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If someone doesn't go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and deactivate that tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi and Odd will die of cold,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the entire city with them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I guess you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll launch the virtualization process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let… me… sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. You can sleep later! Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning in frustration]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out, Aelita! Hornets on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't see anything for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not Hornets!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're Flying Mantas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… they never leave Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We have to face facts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is getting more and more powerful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About face, Aelita! Fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Well, that's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Think about hot things, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Tahiti… Sauna…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heat wave… Fireplace…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Flying mines!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi… Stay with me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shivering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, no sleeping.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone, listen up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna tell you a little story.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's from when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was a volunteer research subject</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the space exploration program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going straight to the Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Palm Springs…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Blast furnace…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And believe it or not… Major Satanox</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really had hippopotamus blood</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in his veins…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sleeping!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shivering loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] …if you see what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Please, hang on…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure Odd's already on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Magma…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! More ice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't get rid of me that easily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser Arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I drop you off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the next activated tower, perhaps?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't say no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…and so, there I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another field of flying mines!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Please, Yumi! Don't give up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need you to fight against XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! The Flying Mantas are behind us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right where I want them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! There's an open passage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hurry, I'll cover you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shivering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I need you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi… Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Launch a return to the past,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's in trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's with these little mini-servings?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV] Come on, cookie, don't be shy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Load up the meatballs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you really want it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah. What, are you deaf, too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[splat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[TV groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What the…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you're still hungry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's seconds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>