<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give, all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>LAUGHING FIT</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen her laugh so much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're telling me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen her laugh at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The gas I've just inhaled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a small quantity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is called nitrogen protoxide, N2O.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing] For those of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>interested in chemistry, of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>although it's better known</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as laughing gas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] You can see why this gas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is sometimes used in hospitals to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>relax patients</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who are going to be operated on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a bad idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing like a laughing attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after an appendix attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But let's try to stay serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In strong doses,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this gas can be highly toxic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>provoking very serious modifications</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in perception</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and even lesions in the nervous system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sometimes even fatal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So one can, as the saying goes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>literally die laughing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only one thing can neutralize the gas:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All you need is one drop to volatilize it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Enough of that! Get out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sheet of paper for a surprise quiz!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] She's been sulking for two days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing seems to cheer her up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can try some of my jokes on her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That might do the trick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not saying you don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a good sense of humor, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'd rather go and talk to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think Ulrich will manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get her to smile?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, sure as Julia Roberts is gonna call</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and invite me out to dinner!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I think you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's really down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Please, Ulrich, leave me alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't feel like talking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I feel like talking... and with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you like talking so much,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>talk to yourself. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sniffles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Don't worry, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not all girls are like Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[making coy noises]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's a shame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Hey wait, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you coming tomorrow,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the rehearsal? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I'll be there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but not for you. It's for Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For your information, it's thanks to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Odd's playing the music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm-hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you want to be part of the group,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the role of Romeo is just ideal for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I suppose that you, of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are Juliet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, that's perfect casting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's a perfect reason for me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to play Romeo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slithering and spluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[steam hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman] It's you, darling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said to myself we couldn't stay angry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with each other for...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, hello, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good evening, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to talk to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What about your dad? Where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um... staying with a friend from work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what was it your parents argued about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My mother tried to tell me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but... I didn't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] And I'm not sure she did either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, those arguments are the worst.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really glad that you came.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how to cheer someone up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's strange</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that they're mad at each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Ulrich always get along so well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, Aelita, very often people</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who get along well have fights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, really? What about you and I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why don't we ever fight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You and I? I don't know really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, XANA's been quiet lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too quiet, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I worry most about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are the risks you all take.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA would really love to get rid of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, the only one of us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's in any real danger today is Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's rehearsing with Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that's what I call a risk!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft guitar music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know if she'll appear tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But uh... [mutters indistinctly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know she loves me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's awful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about as flat as a pancake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not me, it's the lines.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with the lines? Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] I can't even say them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing wrong with them. It's you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how long I spent on the text?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, my guess would be about 30 seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dare you to repeat that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I'd rather you repeated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your lines, Herb, and with feeling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas, there's no reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you to be on stage,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Odd, you're playing much too fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure. If I play slower, it'll give me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough time to take a little nap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, keep all your bad jokes for yourself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now let's take it again</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the top, and try to concentrate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slow guitar playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if she'll appear tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I know... but I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if she loves me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Oh, a guard en garde...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what is it now, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughing uncontrollably]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] Come on, it wasn't that bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna wanna laugh</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I get through with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Forget him, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gulps and coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't bother coming tomorrow, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're performing a tragedy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not a musical comedy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Huh? Hey wait...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good evening, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would like to see my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a second. I'll get him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you know why your mother and father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't talking to each other?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was afraid of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, how nice to see you. Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy... I want you to come home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is between your mother and me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she and I have got to work it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah, and how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not even willing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk to each other! [sniffles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I've got an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really didn't feel like laughing at all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it was impossible to stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as Sissi poured water on me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that was it. I stopped immediately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>N2O, laughing gas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ms. Hertz said the only thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that could volatilize it was water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think this could be a XANA thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, keep looking around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but no pulsations for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see if the bottle of laughing gas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is still in the science room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Kiwi, you stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woofing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] If you've come to apologize, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't bother!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I was wondering, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if there was a part,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even a little one, that Yumi could play.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And why would I want to give Yumi a part?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget that I even asked. Good-bye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Ulrich, wait, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There just might be a solution.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and I, we never fight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think that's normal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Yeah... No... How do I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think we'd fight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if she lived here in our world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I do think is that we're gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get caught if you don't hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knob rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's empty!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess we ran out of gas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you pardon the expression.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tomorrow, we'll go to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>instead of the play and check things out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[seagulls cawing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? Hey, Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrill rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer's voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Communication refused.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, Jeremy, I'm ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm-hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank heavens, a tower just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll transfer you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the mountain region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've spotted some monsters there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower can't be far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Data transfer problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathing heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel very weak, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did anything happen during the transfer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Can you hear me, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouting] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've put cue lines up everywhere, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll make a perfect Romeo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, I'm doing it for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's right, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You do make a perfect Romeo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi, now come with me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I can show you your costume.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe you stole my part!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It isn't my fault, Herb, I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder why I don't just slug you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fear, maybe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Please tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't look too dumb, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be silly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look really stunning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope we're not doing this for nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you talk to your folks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, they're gonna come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Both of them? How'd you do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I lied.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told each one of them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the other wasn't gonna come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling] Adults can be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such children sometimes, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is not a good time to desert me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The welcoming committee looks really mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm not feeling too good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtual envelope damaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrill rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things don't look so good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[water splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water spluttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] Good evening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's my mother.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good evening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I suppose your husband</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is meeting you here tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. My husband isn't able to come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's... not feeling well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Mr. Ishiyama, I'm delighted to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're feeling better already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Feeling better?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your wife has just arrived.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My wife... is here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're not out of the woods yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wheels approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm too weak to fight them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to trick them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shooting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Aelita, are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heaves]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA might send us more monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better not stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich stammers] I... Um...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know if she will appear tonight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at her balcony.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[audience murmuring indistinctly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers] What does it say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't read it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does she... What does it say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh right! Does she love me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I think she does.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[audience murmuring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Enter guard? En garde, guard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hide, hide!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[audience laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, it's Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, they're tough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, where are my next lines?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke swooshes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] There must've been a problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel weaker and weaker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathing heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, I'll be just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to hang on, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see the pulsations?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower that XANA activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't be too far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all we needed... A labyrinth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ah, at last you're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, who is so fair and fair...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've been here before, I'm sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathing heavily and moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're lost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Jeremy's help, it's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Jeremy, how do you wanna die,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>freezing or laughing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta do something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hang on any longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing ominously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You who lights up my days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You who is the sunshine of my nights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] This is awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's massacring my text.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even you were better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, my Romeo, you are my beau.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh Romeo, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>caro mio, amore mio...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[audience laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did I say? What's so funny?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone is laughing at me now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Yumi laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not normal. They're going to choke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to find a way to help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened? [gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was like I was being controlled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's he talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This thing's afraid of water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi, give me that fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You could say "please."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, give me that bottle, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi breathes heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi, you're okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Ishiyama]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darling, we were so frightened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathing heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're almost there, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've just had a psychic vision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to go left, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't wait for me. I'm too weak to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Odd, I'll get there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'm not worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[choking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Water and call for help, please hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You gotta be kidding. I won't ever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be part of that dumb play again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] At least now we know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to get your folks together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm never gonna wear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that stupid costume again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I agree.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a better idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for Ulrich, I'm really sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you've to sacrifice yourself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one more time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least, that way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can finally see you as Romeo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's face it, a nice laughing fit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is good for you from time to time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know if she'll appear tonight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on her balcony,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm certain...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... I'm certain she... she loves me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I know I love her very much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, a guard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[audience laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't she supposed to be in the play?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[strains]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[audience laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It worked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter now? What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why are you all laughing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't understand drama!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is not a comedy! It's a tragedy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[applauding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>