<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TRIPLE TROUBLE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, missed again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the Scyphozoa pulls</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita into the way tower, it's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can say goodbye to the Mountain Sector,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then, bye-bye Lyoko too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We get the picture, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triplicate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you go, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what am I here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A groupie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That makes twelve for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone top that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] I got ten. Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Not many, only fifteen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, how many of XANA's monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you wipe out this week?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know darn well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You all got super powers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Telekinesis, super sprint, triplicate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can all make stuff appear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me, I've got zilch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd over headset] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The only power</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I ever had was future flash,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it got wiped out when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy was updating the supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he never reprogrammed it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it was, I quote, "useless."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So just knock it off with your high scores</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and low scores, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter, laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's still sulking, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is the whole world trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring me down or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey. Look, I'm on your side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I put a little something together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's bound to cheer you up, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope it's nothing to eat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause you're an awful cook.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's a special power just for you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and nobody else: teleportation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the best, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I were a girl,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd propose to you immediately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ambient music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm standing by, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This new power will allow you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to travel instantly over short distances.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd over headset]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool. How does it work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, you have to visualize the place</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you want to go to. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like that big mountain, for instance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy over headset] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sure, why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next, you activate the program by saying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the word, "teleportation."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Teleportation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not fantastic at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like something's bugged up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll try again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Teleportation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yoo hoo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't you happy to see me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but honestly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of you would have been enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I take back my marriage proposal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nobody panic. It's only a minor bug.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'll rematerialize you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fooled you that time, didn't I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable. What a total meathead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We know, "Fooled us that time."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How'd you know what I was gonna say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Look on the bright side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you've got two more great buddies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's three times as many bad jokes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And two too many Odd Della Robbias</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't the two Odds lay low here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop anyone from getting suspicious,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the other Odd can go to school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as usual, and everything will be cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good idea. I'll stay here and try to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>find out what went wrong. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way, José. It's lunch time and we're</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>starved. It's meatballs and gravy time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if we hid in my room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and went to the lunchroom one at a time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both Odds] Great idea. Nice one, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought of it, so me first. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, me! I'm too hungry to wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it. Me first. I'm starved!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop. Leave this to me, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eeny meeny miney mo, catch a Della Robbia</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the toe, you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yo, Jimbo. How's it goin'?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine. Thank you, Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but watch your tone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't get too familiar. The name's Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yo Jimbo, how's it goin'?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine. Thank you, Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but watch your tone. Don't…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Jimbo, how's it goin'?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm… not that great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I think I might even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go lie down for a little while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rosa, you look beautiful today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Have you ever thought of becoming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a model or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Because you're--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Save it, will you, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Rosa] I'll give you an extra helping,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just spare me the baloney.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting with pleasure]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning in disgust]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what? I can't keep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my two best friends waiting now, can I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next. Bon appétit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rosa, you look beautiful today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't push it, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You already got a huge plate of meatballs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give you some more potatoes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but that's it. Move on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's your turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rosa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, not another word. That's it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the other kids</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ate as much as you do, the lunchroom</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would have gone under a long time ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, gym class starts in five minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the lucky winner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Count me out. It's not good exercising</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a full stomach. I don't wanna be sick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You took so many helpings</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we had to go hungry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's right, you selfish hog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What? Me, selfish?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After I wolfed down my lunch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as fast as I could?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If that's how you feel, I'm outta here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm going to the movies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that I have clones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can skip class and get away with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No you don't. Not so fast, pal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't eaten anything, so I'm going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for takeout, and you're going to class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, that's my money!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No way, it's mine!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, go then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I hope you choke on your burger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must have seen you everywhere today…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Except in gym class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] So listen up now, young man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get to the gym now and work up a sweat</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or you're gonna have something else</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to sweat about!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[comedic horn]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Contrary to what some of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>smart alecks might believe,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>throwing a discus has nothing to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with throwing out a CD</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're tired of listening to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it is an Olympic dynamic discipline</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that requires strength, skill, muscular</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>coordination and above all, a discus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, what do you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in cheap movie guide magazines?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, the cheapest one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a buck and a half.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got one left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing for 75 cents?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wheelchair Zombie Four</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>beginning at 2:30… Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] This isn't a public library!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone continues ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This had better be important, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found out how to solve</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this teleportation bug problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The three of you each have to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get into a scanner together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in order to fuse you back into one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For once, it sounds really easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish it was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there's a little problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your three entities are unstable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At a certain point,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all three of you could disappear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into thin air, understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's horrible. What do we have to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get back here to the computer lab right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now, you and the terrible twins.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If any of you is missing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the fusion is impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, don't worry. I'll go find them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A circuit in series</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>differs from a circuit in parallel,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that any single bulb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that is missing from the circuit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will cut the flow of electricity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch this demonstration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's put this into practice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>actions speak louder than words.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so, here's a demonstration for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh great, that's all we need!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy. I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you bend your knees like this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] into a position which keeps</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your shifting weight in balance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your arm holding the discus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>outstretched like this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Behind you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something weird right behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen up, Herb, I was not born yesterday!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you trying to pull?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that is what I call having a hard day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is XANA's doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to get him out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. You wouldn't happen to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a pair of wings on you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What we've got to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we stay here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll all end up as statues.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The north entrance is still</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a no-smoke zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell Jeremy about Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Ulrich? Petrified? Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means a change in plans.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's we need. And what's more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the other me isn't in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you'd better find him and then go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get number three who's petrified on campus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or else you'll never be able to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>reunited and become one and the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Great idea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but how should I know where he went?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Figure it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What would you do with your day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you were you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? Well, I'd either go to the movies</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or to Presto Burger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There you go. Now you know where to look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through headset]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll start up the virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita. Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through headset] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi. Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Movie or Presto Burger… Movie or</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Presto Burger… Movie or Presto Burger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not you again! Get over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna give you a piece of my mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean I've been here already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and if you're planning to read</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another movie magazine for free,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you better think again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean like this magazine here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. You better cough up the money,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because you're not gonna scam me again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wheelchair Zombie Four</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at 2:30 at the Majestic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, where you going? Get back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't I have two minutes on my own?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, because we need each other's company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, they say smoking is dangerous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for your health.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better not hang around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Odd number three?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On the other side of the science building,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I guess the best way to go is up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is crazy. We can't move. We're stuck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, watch out behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] He's right down there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, we've gotta bring him back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if Tarzan can do it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so can we, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just what I was thinking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're good. Pull us up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pleasure is all mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, what do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the smoke free section down there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think I just read your mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead. The coast is clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] One, two, and three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, your turn!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, it works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sure it did. What did you expect?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better than Tarzan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't enough that they shoot at us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now they're trying to run us over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's really not fair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oops, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are times when it pays</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have a head as hard a rock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's between the two of you now, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I know, and he's pretty tough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To think that I do everything I can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get out of gym!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any longer, and I'd have gone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the missing person's bureau.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi over headset] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Della Robbia family has been reunited</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd. Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd. Scanner Odd. Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I suddenly feel a little lonely,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but that's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the best, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I am. Did you have any doubts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Step aside, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let an expert do the job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My lady's tower is straight ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through headset]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything okay, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just have to launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I finally understood what went</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wrong with the teleportation process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you want, I can reboot the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with no bugs this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I sure am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You saw that last battle of mine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am a top gun, a real fighting machine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a guy like me doesn't need special powers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you're strong,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>very funny and handsome,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but most of all, you're modest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. You hit the nail right on the head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, you might say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm… one of a kind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>