<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE PRETENDER</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crow croaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your saber may have some class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but compared to my laser arrows,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your monster count is way behind mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah? I bet you forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that my saber saved you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a quick game over last time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what? I made up a little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>statistics program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm using to record your performances</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Lyoko over the last few weeks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So tonight if you want, we can compare,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see who's best. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great. I really love stats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll finally have proof</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my superiority.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But in any event, I've got something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you'll never have, good buddy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Style, my friend,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't impress a Megatank.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's all this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about a Megatank, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You talking about a video game?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Teddy Bear Heaven."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Way too complicated for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Very funny, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh, Ulrich, have you got a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I talk to you in private?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm… Well, you're… Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's best friend, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I guess you might say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… What I wanna say… hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that when I see Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… I mean, well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to… Do you remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the episode of </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hospital Horrors</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that was on last week?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? You'd like to give Yumi a transfusion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a French poodle's blood?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no. No, I mean at the end,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happens between Stacy and Dr. Shrank.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I don't remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happened at the end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're talking about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And they've got pancakes for breakfast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so hurry up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] You look happy for a change.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on? What did Johnny want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just to talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's totally flipped out over Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's adorable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what did you tell him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did let him down gently</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without laughing at him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wasn't gonna pass this up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told him to follow her, 24 hours a day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>every day, non-stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That wasn't very cool, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi hates to be followed around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She'll probably tell him to get lost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, what if she does?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can be a real jerk sometimes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's just a little bit of hazing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got hazed when I was in seventh grade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hazing, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sounds more like jealousy to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You flip out even when Kiwi looks at Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, don't forget, Yumi and I are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just friends, and that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crow croaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Johnny] Hi Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mind if I sit down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>next to you for a second, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's really nice to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, but I happen to be reading.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I love to read too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I real all kinds of stuff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>books and magazines and comics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you like comics?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Johnny] I like mangas best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you know some great ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can you recommend any to me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you. I'm going to lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like the idea of self-service,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you're having salad? Great idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Vegetables are good for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lots of vitamins.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna have the…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, wait for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe that you like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>brussels sprouts too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have so much in common.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't forget that in Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I took out at least three Flying Mantas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a matter of seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't trust your count.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stink in math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I prefer Jeremy's stats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's your table?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd really like to sit with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And I'd like to get some water!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going, Johnny?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure, but I have the feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm getting on her nerves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by following her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. You know what girls are like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, don't let it get you down, buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, when you guys get to the gym,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ask her for all kinds of advice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great idea! Could I have some water?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I think I got question two right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said that China stretched over the large</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>river valleys of eastern Asia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like the Hoang-Ho,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Yang-Tseu and the Si-Kiang.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How did you do on question three?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said China was the most populated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>country in the world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a billion people per square meter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean I got it wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess I was right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to trust your stats, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crow croaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crows croak]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys, have you noticed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all those birds. It's kind of bizarre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It reminds me of a film. A dumb flick</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where the birds attack the heroes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It wasn't even scary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Johnny, you wouldn't be planning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on following me all over, all the time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crow croaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw the sign!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was in their eyes. It's XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[croaking in a robotic way]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, they'll peck away at us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until there's nothing left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crows croak]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I take it all back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't a dumb film after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the passage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to lure them over to my side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on little birdies, over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, come on, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me a second to finish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my acupuncture session.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forget to check the Superscan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a few hours, and bang, a XANA attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Everything will be just fine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once we get the tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Go on, your turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Johnny gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Johnny grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd? What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A big flock of birds?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crows croak]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, okay? I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi, wait up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, don't follow me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Johnny, get going! It's me they're after!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Johnny grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass breaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've been through worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, it's not every day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have such a big audience.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic croaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[robotic growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll delay them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the elevator. See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over here… we're waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I took out five of them. How about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you're trying to cheat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't forget that birds aren't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>part of the stats,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only monsters sent by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's all on her own. I hope she's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crows croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll virtualize you in the vicinity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and then I'll call Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi keeps grunting and screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting and screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita. Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tower is south-southwest, in a crater.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Start up the stats program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna cry when you see the results.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I doubt it, buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't cry when I get bad grades, do I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] If you did,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd have drowned in your tears ages ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You can start earning points now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's sent you a big welcoming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>party of crabs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll leave you the claws.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We'll see about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May the best man win,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's me. Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Cheater.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are they? I don't see anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that what you mean by… style?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on then, see if you can do any better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is all this about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>crows with red eyes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's true, I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They flew into the gym and attacked Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at the windows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, you see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is that you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[through mobile] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, it's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know where Yumi is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, she's here in the tool shed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she's been hurt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have to get her to the hospital.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm too busy to talk to you at this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to call an ambulance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So hang up, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd, Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's been hurt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to launch a return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, you've got to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower. Fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave him to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bull's eye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not fair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crab growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crabs roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you mind concentrating?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I have to remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a tower to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you want to save Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's one less monster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd the great, the brave, the magnificent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has finally overcome his handicap</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and has now caught up with his opponent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Temporarily of course, because Odd is--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So long, Odd the Mega.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That wasn't fair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're losing too many life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Aelita, you're cheating!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know but you guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are just too clumsy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crows croak]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[croaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can launch a return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy? Do you read us, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you make anything out of this attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by birds with electric beaks, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… Hmm… Never seen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything like it, sir… uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except when I investigated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>paranormal phenomena</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a highly special</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>secret service section.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You did? I didn't know that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I did, but I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a classified defense secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy is out cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The birds have attacked him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's captured Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got hornets on my tail</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my saber's gone. Do something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to, but the supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>programs aren't exactly my thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can try to get your saber back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No! [grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it! Supersprint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ambulance sirens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, you're still here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure I am. I wouldn't leave you, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did you get this stupid idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to follow me from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>From Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He said it was the best way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get your attention,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so that's what I've been doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should've guessed it was him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not only jealous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich is jealous?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But of what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have my saber, but I can run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>¡Olé!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, we can't take the chance of Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going into the way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta try to launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a return in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought we were never to do that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she's under XANA's control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>¡Olé!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least try to program me a saber.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there. And here we… go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Okay, I take that back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how are we gonna get out of this one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time for some strong arm tactics!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beginning to get on my nerves!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you missed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Missed again. Tough break.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is the tenth slap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't tell me you need a real smash!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you crazy or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna let you through, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, and two, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I'm ready for action again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you need help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is no time to drag your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… What do we have here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] Adolescent girl, about fourteen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>multiple injuries, unconscious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] For the Desert Sector, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For Yumi, I hope not, so move it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] It's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi's gonna be fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Phew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but she knows about what you told</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Johnny to do, and she's furious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't say we didn't warn you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have you got a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I talk to you… in private?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, well, well, you see…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… When I see Yumi, I well huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You like her, and you don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to get her to notice you, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's it, but how did you guess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Instinct.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's one thing that can't fail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's gonna love it. Trust me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, you've gotta go find her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and tell her this…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, right, huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Ulrich is a really dumb jerk,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he wants to apologize for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pulling such a stupid stunt."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, well, why don't you sit down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can study together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To… Together? Like us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like you and me? Together?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! That Ulrich really rocks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey guys, I've got the latest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stats on the Lyoko battles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to eat your hat, good buddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the one who's not gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be able to digest this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Lyoko warrior who has outclassed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the others is… Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe in statistics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They don't mean a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not the way to determine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a real Lyoko hero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. For once I agree</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy laughs] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>