<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>MAIDEN VOYAGE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] For those unfamiliar with the sport,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rock climbing is a noble discipline,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which can carry you to great heights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A good climber commands</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>both mind and body.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This was well understood</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the famous Sherpa, Jensing Long,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who scaled Mount Everest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>using only his bare hands,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to the ancestral techniques</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>still taught by the Buddhist monks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the order of Ki Shi Tsou.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so, don't forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that only by challenging yourselves,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can you move mountains</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and, might I add, climb them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois, get up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] See if you're up to the challenge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This'll be the practical part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of today's lesson.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pull up with your arms,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and push off with your legs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you got chewing gum for muscles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] If the only exercise you get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is clicking your computer mouse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're not gonna conquer any peaks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>show your buddy here how it's done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It's no big deal, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Sourpuss, having a hard time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lifting your brain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with those stringbean arms?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, do you mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I hate to talk with my mouth full.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you mind taking over?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, your head is so full of helium,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can float to the top.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Sometimes I wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't ask for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shut up, you dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He'd to scale the rock wall in gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK, enough said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't be that bad in every sport!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you really are lame at anything athletic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, who cares?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't be a champion at everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Einstein, stop sulking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you want,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can try scaling the wall together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think I have time for that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got too much work to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and Aelita are all the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shut up in the computer lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you working on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're ironing out the kinks on the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You still on that? I thought it was done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Traveling for the network is not like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>taking a stroll</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's in the Digital Sea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is still a mystery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] For all we know, the Skid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could disintegrate on its first dive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's reassuring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You gonna eat that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have to test it out one day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we want to take on XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hushing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet, I said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Delmas said quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] That means now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's all right. Always glad to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In case you've forgotten,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let me remind you today is FSRP Day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which stands for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire Safety Risk and Prevention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so all afternoon classes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have been canceled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts of joy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I was saying, children,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your classes are canceled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But this free time will be devoted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a building evacuation exercise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This drill is designed to make certain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're familiar</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with our security procedures,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>procedures you'll need to know by heart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It goes without saying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that access to the building</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be prohibited during the exercise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I advise you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi is right, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better make a trial run in the Skid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just to see how it works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't know if we're ready yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to try it out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before XANA gets even more powerful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Thank you for your attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK. We'll take advantage of the safety</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>drill to get to the computer lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Way to go, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But listen up. This is a trial run</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to work out the launch procedures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, we'll just dive in,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>test it and come back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] As we know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko is made up of five sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These sectors are located in the center</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a giant hollow sphere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine a kind of enormous virtual bubble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>suspended in a liquid element.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This liquid element</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the world information network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the Digital Sea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is part of the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's an overflow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>accessible through a floodgate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA goes through there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack us on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Skid'll use the same gate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get us out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once we're off Lyoko, what then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I imagine you'll be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in an immense network of tunnels,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't have enough data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell you what you'll find.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll be a surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fabulous! I love surprises.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what are we waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't explained about configuring</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the parameters of the engines</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or the procedures</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for transferring virtual mass or…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Don't bother!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll work it out as we go along.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hands-on experience.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] But--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I'll be there with them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ladies first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Aelita. Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] It's OK. It's all quiet here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your elevator's waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clanking and rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] It's beautiful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Einstein, we made it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Skid hangar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Now what do we do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Each of you get on a transporter spot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, who's driving?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I am, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys ready? Energize!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! It's working, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Everything's in place,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Opening interface.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through intercom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cockpit to Navskid. Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through intercom] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich through intercom] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd through intercom]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Me too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like being in a spaceship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Galactic Invaders</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're jealous 'cause I wiped out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more aliens than you did</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> 'Cause you cheated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, if you guys are done blabbering,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can get on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Standing by.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK. Now, get ready for lift off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Releasing supports.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have ignition powering vertical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For you, daddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Lift off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] All indicators are go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are good for leaving Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Tunnel open in two seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's working, Jeremy! Our Skid is working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Nice work, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great job, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good. The test was a success.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you all set to turn it around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and go back into drydock?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What? No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I thought we'd test this thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what we did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just finished a dry run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A test in the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Otherwise, what's the point?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we stay here in the sky on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it isn't much of a trial run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't you wanna see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what the network looks like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I feel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like I'm gonna regret this, but OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready to dive into the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Five minutes maximum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] OK, shields activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sonar activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stabilizers on line and checked out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Primary axis clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser generators on line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cockpit to Navskids. Ready for a dive?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anytime Princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Base lab to Skid. Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lab calling Skid. Aelita, come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Answer, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Skid to base lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're in the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I wanted to hear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I nearly had a heart attack waiting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm okay now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[burbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holoweb system on line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What does the network look like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's… beautiful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you a visual, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you said it, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rotation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, engage turbo prop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and auxiliary engines</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to break clear of Lyoko's gravity field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Whatever you say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Turbo propeller engaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[waltz music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it, guys. Now, head for home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can't we stay a little longer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said five minutes, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger, turning around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Starboard propulsion engaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Bearing 160.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[waltz music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I don't know why,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I just lost you on my radar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might be a transmission problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can you check it out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The navigation system doesn't respond!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a bug in it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without a navigation system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll never find your way back to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be stuck, floating on the network</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'till you use up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of the Skid's power reserves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Then what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Once the energy is exhausted,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Skid'll break up and you'll end up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Digital Sea for good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Eternal virtualization… Like my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's just great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you've got a solution</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I didn't bring my bathing suit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>To get you out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to debug the system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except there are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>several million codes to crack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By then, you'll be in the drink… Unless…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Unless what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got subprograms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that might debug and repair the system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have to get them from my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to leave you for a moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You couldn't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>brought it with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I wasn't the one who insisted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on doing this trial run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So cool it, if you don't mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It won't help to get worked up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry and get your CD Rom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll wait here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like an upside down city.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] All these buildings</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are the network's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>interconnected data bases.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, why don't we turn on some light?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why aren't you in the schoolyard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darn it, Fire Safety Day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot all about it. Just my luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the principal sees you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's gonna ring my bell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I need to get something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from my room. It'll just take a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, you don't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were all warned this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and warning in hand is worth two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the bush league. Beat it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Did I tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about when I fought forest fires?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think we'll live</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see the light of day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Jeremy will find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to fix it, I'm sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Has anyone noticed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a change in the light?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're right. That's strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another teacher standing guard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this, Fort Knox?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teacher humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there isn't any other way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you guys see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that dark thing up there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I'll shut the lights</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get a better view.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you think that's Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, but whatever it is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>its gravity is pulling us towards it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind blowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This is not gonna be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a piece o' cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, let's do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wind blowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy breathing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs and shudders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'd love to see Einstein's face</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he figures out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we didn't need his help to come back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it's nice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be back on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But it's not Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's not Lyoko. Hang on now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Retro brakes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who said climbing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can take you to great heights?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should monkey around more often.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's something ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Look, it's Ugly and Uglier!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They look like some sort of eels.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I never met an eel I didn't like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heads up. I'm breaking off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've seen spiked heels,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but spiked eels, never!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got a fire to put out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[eels roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holy cow, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful or you'll get us killed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who taught you to pilot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, we won't make it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against these monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're almost out of energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Skid could disintegrate at any moment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if Jeremy doesn't get back soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door whirring and clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm in the computer lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you holding up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through intercom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in big trouble. XANA's attacking us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a kind of fish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Some kind of giant moray</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or conger eels.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you started up the debugging program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but you're burning too much power,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if this continues,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you guys'll be gone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before the debugging's done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to buy some time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, but how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get those congers off your tail,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then launch the Navskids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? We're gonna fight them one on one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just like in </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Galactic Invaders</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, bring ‘em on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you all set? Navskids aweigh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These are more maneuverable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than the overboards. Gangway!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful. If you get hit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means you'll be lost at sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire torpedoes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable! It's up to you, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're tough customers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You said it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through intercom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] OK, come and get me. Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Got him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Yumi. You get better and better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe, but not good enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful. Don't forget that the Navskid's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>autonomy is limited.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We'll do what we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These monsters are hard to hit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't try to work any miracles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just keep them away from the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, fish freak,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>looking for some more bait?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>This time, I lost him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The program is debugged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you your coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get out of there, and fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Navskids in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maximum propulsion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting and swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trial run's over, back to drydock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'd never have thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the world information network</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was a real live ocean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With fish and everything. Big ones too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To think that my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the network somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and so is William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That huge sphere we saw, what was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another virtual world like Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A replica that XANA must have created</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the data he stole from Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what he's thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of doing with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll go and explore it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Right, but not tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only feel like exploring my bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm wiped out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wiped out from sitting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in your cushy chair?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you think we feel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I told you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I was doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while you were on the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd never believe me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me take a wild guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did a little rock scaling on the roof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how'd you know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[silly trumpet]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, you can be really hilarious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you wanna be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even when you don't wanna be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>