<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>GUIDED MISSILE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Roman Le Goff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Roman] Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yannick Piranet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yannick] Here I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the second letter for you today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's not fair. I haven't gotten any.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Be patient, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mail call's not over. There's still hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I haven't gotten anything either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but you don't know anyone else</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>besides us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Aelita, I didn't mean it that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Aelita Stones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a postcard for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell us who it's from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet it's from XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must be on vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've had no sign of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] "Hi, Aelita. Thinking of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Montreal. Warmest regards."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no signature.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't mind getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something signed or not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Finally,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is for Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last, of course, like he is in everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's about time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was wondering how long my parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would forget their favorite son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet it's packed with lots of goodies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry, as you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm very generous by nature. Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what's inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that all there is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dog food and nothing else at all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Makes you wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who their real son is, you or Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Check this out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won first prize in a contest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cosmos, Future and Formula Magazine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah, what's your prize?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An aerial invitation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a jet fighter with a live,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fixed target air-to-ground strike</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>missile exercise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's for today too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The problem is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't remember entering the contest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think this could be XANA's doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] XANA's got nothing to do with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was yours truly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, to increase my chances</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of winning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sent in entry forms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in all of your names.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it looked like it worked,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because Jeremy's name was drawn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fine, except that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the prize can't be transferred.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who has the right to go on that flight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[[Odd] No! You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do ya know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never have thought of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I can't possibly go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta stay near the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, listen, you've got to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the chance of a lifetime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like you said, XANA has been quiet lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There isn't much risk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can keep an eye</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the Superscan for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Admit it. You're freaking out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're totally scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, you're wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For your information, I'd love to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Anyway, we've gotta go to class now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really envy you, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll get the ride of your life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I'm gonna have one heck of a time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Mayer] All right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's concentrate on this exercise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In normal orthogonal figure, O-I-J,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on given points A-B-C,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we first set up the points on a diagram.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then we calculate the lengths AB,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>AC and BC.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then, on the diagram, we place point D</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-so that the vector AB equals vector DC.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I missed the beginning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay if I look at your paper?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But why? It's all on the blackboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It makes my eyes tired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What are you up to, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to know who wrote the card.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think it was us who sent it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Aelita, wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, at the postmark.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Canada, not Kadic Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a real mystery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't see anything mysterious about it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Stones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You simply have to concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] After your flight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll have a quick photo session</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of you in the plane for our next issue</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cosmos, Future and Formula.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'd like you to meet Greg,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your pilot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey there, kid. Ready to get your thrills?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[camera flashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well now, our flight will begin</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a low altitude takeoff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after which we'll gain altitude</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with some vertical and oblique climbs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then I'll do some barrel rolls,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>banking, diving and loops</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before the live fire-strike exercise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a fixed ground target.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In brief,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're gonna really rock and roll.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's that for a flight plan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad, but there's just one little thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather you left out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The flight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to me. I'm really scared of planes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I didn't wanna chicken out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of my friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So all you have to do is shoot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few pictures of me in the cockpit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, your readers will be happy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your magazine will save some money,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my friends will be convinced</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I actually flew in the jet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[puppy barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That stinks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No normal dog would ever eat this stuff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who ever said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that your dog was normal, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[puppy barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's going on in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did I hear a dog barking in this room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, kind of. It was me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I said I heard a dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was me, Jim, I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You trying to make fun of me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it really was me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever I eat this home-made pâté</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my mother makes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's what happens. Woof-woof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One thing's for sure, it smells good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, take it as a present, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't do that, Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your mom made it for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My mom always taught me to share.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Besides, there's plenty where that--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pâté's my pet… My favorite food.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess I lucked out on that one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs and chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[photographer] That's perfect! Don't move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gimme a smile now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[camera shutter clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[camera shutter clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! Activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[camera shutter clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, thanks a lot. It's a wrap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank heavens I'm not going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the heavens!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jet engines roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's gotten into him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you trying to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you we're not supposed to take off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm not the one in control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[keypad beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Odd. We've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you say the Ice Sector?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll go tell Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens and closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jet engines roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower, this is Charlie Foxtrot 41.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[control] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot. What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My on board computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is no longer responding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gone to automatic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The plane is controlling itself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if some kind of virus has taken over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Greg]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I'm trying to activate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the software, but nothing's working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must be a bug.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna try launching the procedure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for rebooting the system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no! Don't do that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing to worry about, son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll be landing soon,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and everything'll be back to normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA will never let you manipulate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the on-board computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA? What's that, a name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, kid, this isn't some kind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of science fiction show.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the real thing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Which is going…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lieutenant? Are you all right, sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[control] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Charley Foxtrot 41,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is control. Come in please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[control] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is control. Come in please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I repeat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Control to Charlie Foxtrot 41. Over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Control,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is Charlie whatever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pilot's unconscious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry about a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I can handle the situation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you kindly identify yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>eighth grader at Kadic Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but I've gotta sign off now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I repeat, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I got here as soon as I could.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great, you're right on time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now Aelita can send</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the three of us to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should've brought a sweater along,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>‘cause we're headed straight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello, can anybody hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can't be. If he's in that plane,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then so is his voice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jet engines roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I read you loud</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and clear. We're at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you guys have all met over there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that means there's an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Relax, Jeremy, we're on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just one detail,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's taken control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the fighter jet that I'm in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you going to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unfortunately, the plane is armed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA must have a target in mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, give us your bearing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and your position, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll check out your trajectory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good idea, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here are my GPS coordinates: N 47-43-13,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>E 01-34-45.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we're heading north-northeast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bearing 042.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nothing in sight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The fighter jet is headed for the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then that means that XANA's target</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The factory will be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in firing range in fifteen minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That's all the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry down to the scanner room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I start up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the virtualization process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator engine whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you guys ready? Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[low humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one here to greet us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bummer. I was hoping for a little warm up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should have listened to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right about XANA attacking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't really think XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would attack either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was just an excuse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The truth is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you wouldn't believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just how afraid I am of flying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The delayed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>self-transfer process is running.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going down to the scanner room now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good luck everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jet engines roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, the tower should be that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta walk there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but I didn't have time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to call up the vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You wanted a warm up, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you've got one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Greg moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What… What's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were out cold for a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[control] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>come in please. Do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I repeat, do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Charlie Foxtrot 41.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I blacked out, but I'm okay now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen. We have now gone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into Red Alert phase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've no choice but to execute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tango contingency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Control, are you aware</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we have a civilian on board?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[control] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41, do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Affirmative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for Tango contingency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the Tango contingency?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In order to avoid a total disaster,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're gonna shoot us out of the air.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] There's the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks quiet to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A bit too quiet even.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Einstein and his radar,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-it's not gonna be as easy as usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't take a rocket scientist</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to know that bad guys are lurking around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see? What did I tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's up, Krabcakes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yee-ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You get rid of one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and there are three to take its place!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's trying to delay us, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd, all three at once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to force our way through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good idea, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure know how to talk to men!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Yee-ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been expecting you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Tell me it's not true, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They can't just shoot us down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the safety procedure, kid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but don't worry about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll eject first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What makes you think I was worried,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lieutenant?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No reason to be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything will go just fine as long as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you do exactly what I tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First of all, put your oxygen mask on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In front of you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a dark red handle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you see it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yeah, I got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start counting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and on three we'll hit it together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our seats will be expelled,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll eject.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once we're clear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the parachutes will open automatically.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Greg] One, two, three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41 to control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unable to eject.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] XANA is holding us prisoner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, enough fooling around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the lady wants to dance with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got a bang out of that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yee-ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to the club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swords slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jet engines roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please Lieutenant,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell them to wait just a little bit longer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before they shoot us down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, kid, but five minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not gonna make a big difference.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It will. I can't tell you how or why,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but please believe me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got friends who can turn</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this whole situation around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Control?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[control]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> We read you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Charlie Foxtrot 41.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget that we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a civilian on board,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a child.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only, I repeat, only execute procedure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as a last resort.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over and out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay. He's leaving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. He's pulling behind us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get a better line of fire</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to shoot us down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is going on now? Another problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! The missile's just armed itself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all set to be launched.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Delta Bravo 89, this is control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Target will be entering a populated zone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in less than thirty seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your orders</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are to shoot it down immediately!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pilot] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our missile is going to fire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[missile roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no, the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Delta Bravo 89.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget the aircraft</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and direct your fire at the missile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pilot] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swords slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's my remedy for a swelled head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, the tower. Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pilot] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Control tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is Delta Bravo 89.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The missile's going too fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't lock it in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Greg] No response at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA wants to get rid of me too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines die]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[missile roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy and Greg straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, so you're</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the mysterious postcard writer, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The hardest part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was changing my handwriting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-but it was worth it, wasn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It sure was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It reminded me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm not alone in the world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that someone cares about me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois! I've been looking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Della Robbia for hours now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you seen him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. What has he done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing, at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just wondering if he had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any more of that home-made pâté left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was really delicious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Sorry about that, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Odd took off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He had to catch a plane.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is your lucky day, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy. Jeremy Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're really gonna love this, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's an incredible experience. Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll go nice and easy, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not scared or anything only…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[jet engines roar]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>