<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>FINAL MIX</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't remember the equation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The square root of a quotient equals…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Zero? No, ten. No, wait. I give up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Wait! Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To study for the exam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's tomorrow and you can't help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding? We'll miss our snack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about the exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a little something in mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does it start with "cheat" and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>end in "sheet" by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just read my mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Forget about your dumb plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot for being so supportive…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa! I am so knocked out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you can't guess what!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The members of Love Potion split up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's old news, dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Brian fell in love with Crystal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Geoffrey fired him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now listen to this. The news is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father said it was OK</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to use the gymnasium!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] He said yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! I've got to find William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's going to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the dance party of the century!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whistle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hurry it up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two! Take those mats</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the storage room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Push that pommel horse against the wall!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Come on! Move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! I don't believe this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So it's true? The principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will allow the techno party?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like it, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Smoking, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The best DJs from schools will be there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gonna be a blast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not. The mixing board is hammered!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know how to fix it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, no problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll ask Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's Mr. Fix-it! He can fix anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have better things to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than fixing a mixing board!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I can help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Would you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And our research on your antivirus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm just watching you at this stage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about the science exam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you study?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It's in the bag!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So this is the thing that makes the music?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yup! You play the records</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the turntables and it mixes the songs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The trick is to synchronize the sound!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Interesting!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems you don't know about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will it take much longer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nope. I'm done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind if I give it a try?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[techno music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, it's working! Aelita, fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You wanna try?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[techno music stops playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[techno music playing again]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! I've never managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get that kind of mix</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, goof-offs! Don't mind me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know what time it is by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're sorry, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just rehearsing for tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you like techno?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Forget about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Electronic music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I prefer the twist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you really mix like a pro!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did you learn?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's our family!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're all creative artists.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll make you a selection of LPs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can be our DJ tomorrow night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… OK!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're wasting your time with this party.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I am not!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm trying to live. Like you guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And have some fun, a good time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's human too, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you like researching</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the antivirus with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're as stubborn as a fool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Stubborn as a mule!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you didn't study at all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… but like I told Jeremy:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"it's in the bag!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What's going on? Can't we go in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Inspection by G.I. Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[military drum beats]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One pen. That's all you can take in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch… That's an unexpected development.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Two hours for Physics</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and two hours for Chemistry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My colleagues and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will correct the exams.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After that, the principal himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will announce the results.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Test is over! Put your pens down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stay where you are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I will collect your papers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay in your seats</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I have all of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's one of your best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Mrs. Hertz…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hertz… Hertz…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope she'll let me keep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's paper swan for my collection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I never felt better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was talking about your exam, stupid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I may be left back this year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't exaggerate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you just have to study a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut it out. This is not the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! We're gonna see Aelita, the DJ!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That will cheer us up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where is she, by the way?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Already in the gym!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The DJs get VIP treatment!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's sulking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You're not going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the happening of the century!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should have studied for your exam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He sure picks his moments!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Desert Sector! Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, a question for the Kadic paper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As a DJ, how do you define your style?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hardcore, Deep-House</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or downright New Beat?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's too nervous to answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd say it is Hardcore,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's more of her own!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Totally rad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ta-dah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You snuck out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] No, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father said, "You'll repeat the year,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's no big deal, sweetie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't mean you can't have fun."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're such an idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I snuck out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, Aelita, a brand new DJ.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And as you're going to see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she totally rips!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's great! You coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your cousin's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, boy! Come on, good boy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi! Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come here, you mangy dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah… Nice doggy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on! Chew through the ropes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That mutt is as brainless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as his owner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi! This is no time for games!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and get Odd and the others</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the gymnasium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now go! Get Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! That's a good dog! Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With my luck,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll bring me the Principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's up? Not dancing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not my thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me see how you move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! You're right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not your thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice dog sounds…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which album did Aelita get that from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here, buddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim will catch you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, hold on, I'm coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ask him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could use some fresh air.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have something important to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to… polish my flip-flops.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was Jim! XANA's possessed him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where is Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the dance. She's finishing her mix.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With Jim around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's all right. She just fainted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take her to the infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on with your party.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure that Jim</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can virtualize Aelita to Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Under XANA's control, he can do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita doesn't stand a chance alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against the Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And she can say bye to her memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not here! Let's run to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>As you order, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Yumi! Take the corridor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll take care of Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] OK!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's more likely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's going to take care of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's brought a friend along, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Go! Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Help is on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't take a nap now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got someone to wipe out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you suggest, then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The bumper thing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as we handle the Kankrelats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little tap like that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could not knock me out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On our way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get to the scanners now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang on, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa isn't here yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The crater isn't far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run South-Southeast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you programmed the vehicles?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Of course! I think of everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA too, it would appear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You've got company!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the monster gets there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's done for!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead! Leave the hornets to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts] Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats! I missed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! You're down to ten life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] They're heading for the crater.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Careful! The Hornets are behind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you're not far!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You are there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it, Yumi! Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams] Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Taxi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! Jeremy, it's here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not so fast, globber face!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yumi! Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Scyphozoa shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> The Schyphozoa's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stealing her memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Ulrich, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! What the.. Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. I'm taking over from here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on tight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! What level is Aelita's memory at?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? You there? Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get back to the computer. I'll handle Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Jeremy, you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm back, Ulrich. It's up to you. Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get to the activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twenty-five degrees East!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why am I here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You'll never know, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewinding sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] So Jeremy, you're gonna help me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Physics</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Aelita with Chemistry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're gonna help me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I get it, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Promise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I am so knocked out! You know why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your father said OK for the gymnasium?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? How do you know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've already lived this day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I just traveled back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a real loony. I feel sorry for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you study with us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and Aelita will help us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Study? Me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like you've lost the only brain cell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you had left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] If she knew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] What a pity!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After the exams, teach me about techno!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love it! It's my new earthly passion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you come listen to my mix?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>