<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A GREAT DAY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What about the Mantas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are we doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like they're going to hatch soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And judging by the size of the nest,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going to have some bouncing babies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, that's it for now, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a little longer, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've never been able to access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this much data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let me take over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, listen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to rush you, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, they're here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I've got things under control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three vehicles coming right up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still just babies and check them out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think they are,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>male or female?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Considering their tempers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they must be girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Just watch, I'll show them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what it means to be a guy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, tell me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do I really need to hear this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't always choose your friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, the tunnel will be open soon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revs and roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[manta groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>OK, the tunnels are open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Mantas shouldn't follow you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The data analysis program is running.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What does that mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With all the data we've recovered,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a good chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of finding the antivirus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean soon we'll be able to shut down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Super-calculator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly. And if it works,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will no longer be tied</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to XANA by that horrible virus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Shoot! What are we going to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with our free time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we can't save the world anymore?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You might study a little more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And learn something for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three a.m. Wow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better head for our rooms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we don't want to get caught.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What's left of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, do you really think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that your calculations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will lead to something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We can never be 100% sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe that soon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be really real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To me, you already are very real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And to everyone else,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you are Aelita Stones, Odd's cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know very well that isn't true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A lie that everybody believes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't really a lie anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, don't worry, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tomorrow will be a great day, believe me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Good night, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time, I've got them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man over radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's Tuesday already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, you're not dreaming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or rather, you're not dreaming anymore!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's already seven o'clock</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the morning on Skyradio.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out your window!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sun is shining, the birds are singing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and me, I'm talking, talking, talking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep you from falling back to sleep,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you bunch of lazybones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a great day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's going to start off great</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to Skyradio</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi, Daddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] I can't help but wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what a girl your age</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could be doing out at such a late hour.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a boy behind this, isn't there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't tell him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there were three friends involved,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all of them boys, could I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That would have freaked him out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why didn't you just make up a story?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I do it all the time with my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sick of lying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to be able to tell them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything, like I used to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon, you won't have to lie anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, cheer up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's going to be a great day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They said so on the radio!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you think Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>looks happy this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not for long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you listen to something for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's not a lot of music,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the words are really interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] She taped the whole conversation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, what does she want exactly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She wants to be part of our group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that we explain everything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to her from A to Z.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, she'll tell her father everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's worse than I thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Excuse me, you three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't mind if I teach a class here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not at all, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, it is your job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My job is also to ask questions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you be kind enough to tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the mass in moles of two oxygen atoms?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirty two grams per mole.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the principal of photosynthesis?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You mean…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The synthesis of oxygen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from plants possessing chlorophyll</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>placed in light.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, here's an easy one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which student in this graduating class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the biggest failure in science</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who, nevertheless, takes the liberty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of not listening to my lessons?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, me, Mrs. Hertz?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bravo! Well done, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see what you can do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you apply yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever happens,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can't let Sissi tell her father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm so happy that you finally decided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give me a lesson in Penchar Kilat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Penchak Silat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well I wondered what could have made you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>change your mind all of a sudden!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Is it this one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe this is what you're looking for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is basic Langkah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to be able to manage it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi straining and shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-As usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They were after the MiniDisc.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, gentlemen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you think you were smarter than me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't know me very well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, now it's time to spill the beans.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me everything you've been up to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the big conspiracy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't tell me a thing, is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You asked for it. I am going to play</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this recording for my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man over radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's Tuesday already!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, you're not dreaming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or rather, you're not dreaming anymore!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's already seven o'clock in the morning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Skyradio. Look out your window!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sun is shining, the birds are singing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the Skyradio…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hey, Dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I have to talk to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what you are going to tell me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're totally right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I'm sorry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't program going back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do explain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the fact Tuesday's starting again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go over to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after science class to check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least we've got a second chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get Sissi off our backs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi, I'm so glad to see you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, you see, I wanted to talk to Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That can wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something I've been wanting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to ask you for a long time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can't bring myself to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You? You can't?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you like to learn Penchak Silat</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you tell me the mass in moles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of two oxygen atoms?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirty two grams per mole, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, that's right. Very well, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you explain to me the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of photosynthesis?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That would be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the synthesis of oxygen from plants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>possessing chlorophyll placed in light.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd? Is that you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't been replaced by a clone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, ma'am. Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No. Let's go on with our lesson.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Being a good student is so cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You learn really fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think so? That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, could I talk to you as a friend?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry? As a what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As a friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, I'm worried about Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you'll laugh, but--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laugh? But, why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Well, you see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've kind of lost it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for some strange reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they think they're virtual people.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Do you think we're going to live</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same day over again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] First I have to isolate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the program that jumps back in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To see what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe it's XANA's doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We'll know in a moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what are you doing over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm studying. That's what you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wanted me to do, wasn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Look at that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA managed to take control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of going back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In my opinion, by using</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the data we recovered from Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Booby-trapped data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would he do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He must have a good reason.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In any event, it's starting up again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to go straight back in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a few minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm launching a scan to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if a tower has been activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita in recording]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe soon I'll be real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's even worse than I thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've gone right off the deep end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's much worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're totally out of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Tower activated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But, what kind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know yet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we can expect the worst.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He hasn't taken control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of jumping back in time just for fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready. It's starting again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man over radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's Tuesd--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the Subsonics latest hit--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi, Dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What's fascinating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that plants use the sun's energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to change water</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and carbon dioxide into glucose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And in exchange give off oxygen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, if you keep this up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be teaching instead of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I certainly don't know as much as you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] I'm beginning to wonder.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I'll have to start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all over again with Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't even bother, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need you too much on Lyoko to help</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the others deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But. What about Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll find another way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fair enough, I really don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could be as clever as yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not like Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Welcome to Lyoko, ladies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The active tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is on the second plateau to the North.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but you will have to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have enough machine resources</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring them up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No sweat,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be just like the good old days!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to try and take back control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of jumping back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's kind of quiet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too quiet if you ask me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can never really enjoy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the present moment, can you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yes, I can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, XANA is sending us monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see. Separate their flight pattern,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you will weaken them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, take Aelita to the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and I will take care</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Guys, on your right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It should be a path</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that leads to the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] With a platform to land on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Logically, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's encouraging.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts] Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] They're here. Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blades slice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yee-ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita on recording]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know very well that isn't true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These little machines work well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy, that's not the point.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard what they said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, it's strange indeed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call Della Robbia's parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get to the bottom of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Aelita screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice jump,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it just cost you each 20 life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It was worth it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can see the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosions]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, the hornets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are attacking Aelita and Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, get ready for guests.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three hornets are heading for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You hide. I'll take care of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, time's running out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has started another jump</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, give Odd a hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, yours!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If only I had more time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find a solution.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cheer up, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're about to get another day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Madam, you have never heard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of this young girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who is supposedly your son's cousin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Della Robbia] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, I assure you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry to have disturbed you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man over radio] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's Tuesday--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TUESDAY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're not dreaming,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or you're not dreaming anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's already seven o'clock…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, no. I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is still on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to get back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the factory, pronto.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead, I'll meet you there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I already know what you're going to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't have time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing, I need you over here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We're waiting for Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without him, we can't do anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy's voicemail] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Leave a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still no answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, we'll find him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, you aren't yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has possessed you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must not obey him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never felt so good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy shouts] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ah, there you are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me transport this simpleton</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a safer place!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, they saw me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll never look for him here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, Sissi, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, be quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Ulrich, look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi is possessed by XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Can you see anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] Absolutely nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think we'd better get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, I'll handle her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get going, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] How did XANA learn</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to possess people?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's increased his powers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Brilliant, Einstein. But how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the jumps back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] You think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I sure do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Super-calculator is a quantum computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which uses the proprieties of q-bits!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Every time you add a q-bit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>its power theoretically doubles!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think the--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, can you say that in English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Super-calculator is so powerful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that it can undoubtedly do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Oh, no. The Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] There you are at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is in trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Scyphozoa squishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] XANA has started another jump</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We might have to start all over again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I'd really rather not, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Aelita, are you all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just have to make it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to that darn tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We're not there yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This may be the code that I need.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We won't get a second chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat, I'll cover you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Let's go, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it! I actually did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've stopped the jump back in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What am I doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My Walkman!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My MiniDisc!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi doesn't remember a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's as if nothing ever happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Lucky for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz already gave each of us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>four hours of detention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for skipping her class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if the homework is on photosynthesis,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just might get the only good marks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my entire career as a failure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, now we know that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can control people.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We also know that jumping back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in time strengthens his power!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to have to be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The next round is going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be tougher than ever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>