<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>WRECK ROOM</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not sick, are you, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Usually, you start the day singing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something from </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Paco, the King of Disco</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dreamt about a deadly epidemic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that was transmitted by potatoes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>meaning there was no more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>French fries or mashed potatoes for lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you believe in nightmares like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Absolutely, but don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask Einstein nicely,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll program you some virtual fries.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Food is sacred, Ulrich, so no jokes, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder where he is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy, forget you had a bed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I spent the night on the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>recovery program to bring back William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's the time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ten to. Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We wouldn't want to miss the blockbuster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>math class on Thales' theorem, would we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stretches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, see you there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I finished the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon as classes are over,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can launch it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't have seconds today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I haven't even had firsts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You did, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd Della Robbia said you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gave him your portion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done! No sleep, no meal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing like leading a healthy life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong? Ulrich told me that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were skipping breakfast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It would've been a pity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to waste a good meal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You want half of my banana?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No thanks. I lost my appetite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better not deny that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you pig out all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not exactly pigging out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's more like a survival instinct.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? Survival?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I've got to store food reserves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in case potatoes get contaminated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-like in the nightmare I had last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Your attention please,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>boys and girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have an important announcement to make.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it! My nightmare's come true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Goodbye potatoes forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This afternoon, after class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we will have the grand opening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the recreation room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've all been waiting for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? There's no epidemic?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Long live French fries!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This recreation room for boarding students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was designed for relaxation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You will have at your disposal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a fusball table in addition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a table for ping pong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a television set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[applause]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, quiet down please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with privileges come responsibilities,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>meaning taking care of your wreck room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that responsibility begins today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the election a of a monitor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to supervise its use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi everybody. What's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to elect a monitor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the new wreck room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I left my computer upstairs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems to me that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as the principal's daughter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the most obvious choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] No way. Forget about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Sissi's elected monitor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'd rather go to the study hall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We want a wreck room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where we can have a little fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then who would you pick, huh? Yourself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, I was already elected class rep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students] Yeah, that's right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one would know that you're our rep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never seem to have enough time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's right. XANA's not gonna give you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>time to supervise anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's none of your business, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a day student.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course, if Odd's elected, you and your</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>little gang will take over the wreck room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students cheer in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Okay, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to go to class. Go on now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we're trying to elect</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the wreck room monitor, Jim, and we--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You call this screaming an election?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to do this demographical…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Democrackingly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to vote, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, you… Over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, let's see…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fiquet, LeDuc and Dunbar… Over here too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Huh? Is that me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Come on, we haven't got all day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, whoever wants to vote</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Anaïs Fiquet, hands up now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With two votes more than Elisabeth Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-the winner is Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girls] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does anyone know what I won?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now everyone, break ranks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who won the election.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how about a word for the Kadic News?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some of the kids think you were elected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because you're not part of a group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Do you think it's a victory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a democracy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Democracies? Who's he anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought it was me who won this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hey, what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A disaster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[math teacher] Now then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to sum up Thales's theorem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a triangle ABC,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if "I" is a point on AB…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> is</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> a disaster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's copy doesn't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same personality as the original.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He can blend in with a crowd, but alone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he stands out like a sore thumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, at least for now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nobody thinks what he says is stupid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They think he's a comedian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but they're bound to get on to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After school, I'd better launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the recovery program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for getting back the </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>real</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope it works, Jeremy, because the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have now is about as brilliant as Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my dog is very very intelligent, so there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, do you want to add a corollary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Thales's theorem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What collar ma'am?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, my dog doesn't have any fleas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[teacher] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… mean I don't have a dog,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or fleas either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students shouting and laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'll run over to the factory now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and start the recovery program, and then--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go with you. That way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can both welcome William home. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go to the wreck room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so there'll be three of us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stop his double</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from doing anything dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, the lock is broken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're turning the key the wrong way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you chowderhead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and cheers of approval]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, I want you all to behave like adults.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't forget, this recreation room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is under </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>your</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> responsibility.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Ping pong, my favorite game!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, William's coming back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just can't wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, me neither.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen you kids!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to break in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this table right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Della Robbia, over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Best of three sets. Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no. How am I going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep an eye on William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, we'll handle him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, could you open the fridge for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, don't waste his time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The monitor should…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>step back from things like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Step back?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I do, I'll bang into the wall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you going to use</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower of William's clone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, because the original William's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>digital DNA is stored in that tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Ha! Ha! Twenty to five. Match point.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Twenty-one, you lose!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was interstate champion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I was young.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't I tell you why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I used to be called the "Killer Racket"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, thanks Jim. Maybe some other time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For once, I'd rather have talked about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dunbar, don't just stand there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a statue! Come on, it's your turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh Jim, he can't play</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and be monitor at the same time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll play against you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, I need someone of my caliber.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's see how you play, Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here goes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Argh! Dunbar, don't you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what ping pong is all about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[worried sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[announcer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just for you, ladies,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this fabulous hair remover for only…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-TV shopping… What a drag!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got the remote, and so I decide.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you switch over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to one of the science channels, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really? Do you mean that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think, nerd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[warning alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no, there's a bug in the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope it doesn't put</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower off line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's already match point, Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to score one point at least.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[struggling sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's impossible! Beginner's luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Killer Racket," was that it, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, before I'm finished with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're going to call you "Clumsy Racket."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we'll just see about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you that Einstein</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just tweaked the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, we've got to come up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with something, and right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have an idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Your serve, Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Achoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nah! Della Robbia, you trying to distract</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>me or what, you little cheater?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, out of the way, loser!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's up with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's worse than ever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The program has bugged some files</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the tower, but I don't know which ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's impossible to deactivate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I can begin all over again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We'll have to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the program manually. I'm going to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] All alone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Superscan doesn't show</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any XANA attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, do we have a choice?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Okay, but be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim and William grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! Aelita, your identification file</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is all bugged up as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The tower doesn't recognize you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too risky. I've got to get you back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then I wouldn't be able to get back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>quickly if XANA attacks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to debug the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here and wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not convinced, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! Aelita, I told you it was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dangerous. You've got visitors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm programming you an overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better take shelter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in another tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping and scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Catch me if you can, ladies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bad news. XANA is trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take over the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle the Tarantulas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zoom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's match point again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not such a big shot now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't even got a way to transfer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>energy from Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to protect the tower. It's also bugged up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finito</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, out, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>basta</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yours truly, Big Jim</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"the Killer Racket" strikes again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whew! Einstein saved us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the nick of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not quite. To the factory. Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dunbar, what's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim and William scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students] Let's get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Let's split up! That way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one or two of us will get to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's got into William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why did he turn into Dr. Schrank?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm the one he wants. You're okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, don't leave me here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I beg you, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all I needed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One down. How's it going, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower won't recognize your ID, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At three hundred meters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>south from where you are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh… But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William! Yeah, it's him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[epic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic! The program worked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll go help him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could be a trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what if the program really worked?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is our only chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring back William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, go on then. But be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'll hold him for a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you see Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, he had the copy on his tail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's shut.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's all over for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me your hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Need a little help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stabs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're back at last! That's great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good to see you again, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's not with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's playing the clown with the clone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry guys, get into the scanner room now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Aelita. Get a move on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he leads you to the Digital Sea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be virtualized for good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same as your father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Oh no, why me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping and scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hop on, princess, and stand clear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the closing doors! All aboard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You sure are a tough customer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Faster, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can't… I just can't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go away, you monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll hold him here while you escape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Identification Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[warning alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm never going to get there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you're going to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to wait before you can enter the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, one for each of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and me, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hands off, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you touch my Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry to say this, Sissi, but</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're not as light as you say you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fan whooshes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's heading straight for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Great! It was already hard enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This way, sweetie pie!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do better than that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I'll bet you can't climb either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't tell me you're not even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going to try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you're going to fall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't let me go. Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be silly, Sissi. We're both</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going to get out of this. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, will you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Bravo, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One last thing to take care of,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[epic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh sorry, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot to hit the brakes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, we're safe!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure of that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Sissi scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems to me that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as the principal's daughter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the obvious choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's true. Now that's a great idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we need somebody who's unselfish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and never thinks about herself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And Sissi really fits that description.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you five up to anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's unanimous then, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students] Yeah, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's going on, It's time to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back to class now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We know, Jim. We just elected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi monitor of the wreck room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did? Well, I thought you'd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>choose somebody like… Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right, I can see </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>him</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how could you not see me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That William is such a comedian!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He knocks me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must be the funniest kid at Kadic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah? Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's go to history class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, the copy's all we've got.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] For now anyway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's back to square one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] But I'll bring William back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one day. I swear I will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>