<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>WRONG EXPOSURE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Are you sure we'll find something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>useful in my father's house?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've already got everything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that seemed important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We left everything behind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we thought was useless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that was our mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We did find Franz Hopper's notes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to your little Mr. Pück.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just as I thought,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're really desperate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's just that I don't want to leave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything to chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when it comes to fighting XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, where do we start?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Try the living room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll look in the study.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, have you found anything yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, my former life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing, just a picture of…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of me and my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and your father?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's so cool, that you found it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I see it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] You look so happy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must have been one of the last pictures</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>taken with daddy just before…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… You know… Before…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>behind your father? Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo! Those formulas…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can read some of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a rough draft of a programming code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to blow up this photo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a one in a billion chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>those formulas have something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do with the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, I love challenging</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the law of probability.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, you said yourself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I was desperate, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what have we got to lose?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was right! It is a program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you only took two rounds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of seconds. Are you sick?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is this about Anaïs Fiquet by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Incredible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't get her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to notice me whatever I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could try growing a few inches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You wanna try wearing today's lunch?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ah, here comes Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So, is Jeremy still at the Hermitage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's in his room. He's not hungry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess that means you struck pay dirt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while you were there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He thinks there may be something useful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in an old picture we found.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A picture! Now why didn't I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of that before?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just have to send Anaïs my best photo,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the one with my killer smile,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she'll be eating out of my hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me, you'd be better off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sending a picture of Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She loves little dogs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How do you know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Einstein, I need your computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, what for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To send an important message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just need to log into my e-mail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I finished anyway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna go and eat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me know when you're done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't touch anything else!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No problem. You know me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I do. That's the problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't fall head over heels</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for me this time, Anaïs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then my name is not Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm… A new message?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>From Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what that dork wants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let's have look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A picture of Mrs. Einstein…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that's a pretty dumb thing to send.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That guy… I'm sure I've seen him before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that's what I call a job well done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight I'll be out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the prettiest girl at Kadic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the name of…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did I just do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could I have done that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, and I even sent the wrong photograph!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, I can't believe I'm such</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a computer lame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Einstein is gonna kill me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I cannot believe this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had no idea that Franz Hopper had family</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>connections with Aelita Stones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And who is this, uh, Franz Hopper guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A former teacher here at Kadic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who disappeared one day without a trace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suzanne Hertz took his place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were much too young at the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have known anything about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really. Otherwise,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't have brought you the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And where did this photo come from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was in an e-mail that I just got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>today from Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia? Isn't he Aelita's cousin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So then he's related to Franz Hopper too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I had better call the two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of them in here for an explanation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good idea. Make them tell the truth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and give you a clear explanation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if they don't, make sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they get a really hard punishment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm… Shouldn't you be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in class now, Elisabeth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I didn't find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything useful in the photo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a setup program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to reboot the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing to write home about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>although it could come in handy one day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So then, I guess</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the picture's not so top secret after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but we'd better keep it a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't want a picture of Aelita with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her father to fall into the wrong hands.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean like Sissi's hands?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no, Odd, you couldn't have!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes I could.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Stones and Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the principal wants to see you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in his office on the double!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, uh, while we're at it, Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern and Ishiyama, you go with them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure that Mr. Delmas has a bunch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of questions for you too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, huh… We've got a class right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard me, get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hmm… I can't believe that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everybody mumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] You heard the principal, young lady.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more funny games.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had a whole lot of tougher</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nuts to crack than you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, last name, first name, occupation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, hmm… Stones… Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Girl?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hmm. You think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm an idiot, don't you, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no need for the third degree.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just have a few questions to ask,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What intrigues me about this photograph</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the presence of both Franz Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Aelita Stone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And they seem to be very close too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so, the obvious question is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whether your name is really Aelita Stones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Sir, Aelita Stones is my real name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the daughter of huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz and, huh, Anthea Stones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And are you really Canadian?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And are you really an orphan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And is Odd Della Robbia</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really your cousin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With your permission, Mr. Delmas…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On the photo,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita looks about twelve or thirteen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and what of it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you said that Franz Hopper taught</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here at Kadic about nine years ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, if that's really Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the picture,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she would be twenty-two years old now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not thirteen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But as you can see, Aelita is thirteen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>years old and not twenty two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that can't be Aelita in the photo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can thus conclude that Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not related to Franz Hopper,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she's telling the truth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about being Canadian,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an orphan and the fact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she's really Odd's cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very interesting. So then, while</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm checking out this identity business,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you are all confined to the library</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the rest of the day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-under Jim's supervision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wonderful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So then, the Canadian Consulate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has no record whatsoever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of an Aelita Stones in its birth records.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I'll definitely keep you informed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you. Good-bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Oh, no, an activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything wrong, Mr. Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Miss Aelita Stones… I'd like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have a word with you, alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, make certain nobody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>leaves this library.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Aelita… No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where do you think you're going, Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Delmas. He's been Xanafied.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita mustn't go with him, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I don't know if I'd go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as far as "sanctifying" him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And by the way, it's not Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mister </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Delmas to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't we going to your office, Sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'd rather stay on the campus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'd rather we went to your office!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get back to your seats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one's going anywhere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Jim, Aelita's in danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, you wanna play hardball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you wanna get through,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll have to use what I taught you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-at my commando camp!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If you say so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all] Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Touchdown!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry guys, tie him up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just think what'll happen if the return</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the past doesn't work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim will kill us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a bigger</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>problem to deal with first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Compared to that, Jim's a piece o' cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He looks like he just had a fight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with his daughter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Go and find Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Okay, good luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Two-point conversion!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[principal Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] He's virtualized Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's in the Forest Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm sending you two in right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy… Are you there, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm with you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Yumi are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? The Scyphozoa?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, you slimy ugly jellyfish…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa going after Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Transfer Ulrich. Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh! I forgot how ugly it was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you liked seafood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not the nasty type. Ready to go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's sent us some visitors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But they're not gonna stop us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like jellyfish or shellfish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, all of a sudden</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our principal's a Ninja.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty good there, Jackie Chan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see how good you are at baseball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[principal Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoops uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we talk this over, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I guess that's a no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This can't be happening!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That awful monster is implanting data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Aelita's brain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa's caught Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's not too far from you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why can't you get to her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're taking a nap, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're up to our ears in shellfish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that, you clammy monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Krab growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Crabs might just become my favorite dish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, you really ought to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Dance Fever</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I hate to fight and run, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That guy is a tough cookie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gotta be out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita! Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita in robotic voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantulas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Where's she going? She's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA used the Scyphozoa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to brainwash Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's heading for the Digital Sea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to throw herself in. Make her stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and how do you expect us to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can devirtualize her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you bring her in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think I've been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to do? But I can't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa must have implanted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some sort of inhibitor in her brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to attack her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] You've gotta be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You heard me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm telling you to devirtualize Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, okay…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>things are getting complicated over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's Odd doing with Delmas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could use a little backup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, stop everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and whatever you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't devirtualize Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I wasn't even close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's getting walloped by Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, why don't you just ask her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure she'll be happy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-to accommodate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know what to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Either we lose Aelita, or we lose Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This guy's out of his mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not getting any better either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I'm the one who taught you that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it. If only I could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>erase everything and start over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… Why not? I can do that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich, get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to reboot the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my new program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? But couldn't that bug up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the whole system?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah maybe,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it just might give us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the kind of electroshock we need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to free Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Scyphozoa's control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You sure you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we don't have much</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a choice, do we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer glitching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[trembling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like it might have worked, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think Aelita's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>almost out of life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> She'll regenerate herself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as she's in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, it didn't put the Tarantula</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a better mood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you can rest later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a tower to deactivate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd is in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm sending you the overbike.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is no time to go to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal Delmas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jean-Pierre, you win. I give up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you just give me detention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Saturday instead of--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about if I do your dishes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you and all the cleaning up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you disappoint me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you know. Mr. Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were stronger than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Whew! Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Delmas couldn't possibly know me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father may have been a teacher here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I studied at home,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so I never attended Kadic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So no chance of finding any trace</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Aelita Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, none.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially since my real name</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Schaefer's my real name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When we moved into the Hermitage,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my father wanted to make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a brand new start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz was his middle name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopper's my mother's maiden name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita Schaefer? That is really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>incredible you knew that, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but it makes no difference.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As far as everyone's concerned,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's name now and forever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is Aelita Stones!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Time for class Lyoko warriors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>