<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>CODE EARTH</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure it's gonna work this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time for Plan Alpha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Yumi, it's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I just launched Plan Alpha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My five dry runs have all worked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay, tomorrow,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll talk to my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great. I'll tell Odd and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] See you tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy hums to himself]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dreamy music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita echoing] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you hear me, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita echoing] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Uh... Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mom and Dad,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can I talk to you for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about my pen pal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't changed your mind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about her living here for a while?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but tell us a little about her, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't even know her name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's Aelita... [dithers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is she Japanese?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well... [dithers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, she is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do her parents do, dear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dithers] They...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They work with computers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Ishiyama nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, all right then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's welcome to stay with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fantastic! I adore you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi rejoices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't regret it. She's really so nice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye now. See you tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. and Ms. Ishiyama chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very well then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is your cousin's name, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, where does she come from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's from Holland.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, her papers are in order</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and your parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have recommended her highly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, I see no reason why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she can't attend school here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me know when she arrives.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs] Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, what are you two up to, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd titters nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know this building</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is off limits to students,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially at eight in the morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We had an appointment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the principal, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about Odd's cousin attending school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what a lame excuse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think I am, huh, an idiot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and I'll bet you think I'm not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto your pranks with Jeremy and Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You disappear in the park</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like some sort of magic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You plot in your rooms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, it's not a crime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One of these days I'm gonna find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what the four of you are hiding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, to the cafeteria. Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You know what I think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better be careful about Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he keeps playing detective,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's gonna find our secret passage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys. Great news!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents said okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So did the principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, that was a pretty good letter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you faked from your parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't say I'm proud of what I did,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it was for a good cause.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! Jeremy, what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it. We've got it this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can hardly believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] It's fantastic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can find any kind of music you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student 2] I can't wait for a vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 3] You're not the only one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi, have you seen Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and his gang this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where? In the cafeteria?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I saw them going to their rooms, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah? Thanks for the tip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is pretty strange</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go their rooms at this hour.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said to myself, "why would they be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in their rooms now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with someone who isn't even a boarder?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean Yumi Ishiyama is with them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're meaner than I thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, tell me what the good news is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I don't know how to tell you this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but believe it or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're waiting for you here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all] Really!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The materialization's gonna work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all in here, and I can tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was really complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Defragmenting the inertial matrix</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wasn't enough,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so I had to start to recompile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of the DNA correlations...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Time out, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To make a long story short, it works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh Jeremy, that's so great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it's true!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better get used to it fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it's time to take the big jump.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then, it's bye-bye, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's not that simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, I've got to set up the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the super calculator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then Aelita will have to get to the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>passage tower in Lyoko's forest region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's where she's gonna get devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before she appears</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the flesh for the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>inside one of the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In that case,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm off to the forest right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we'll go to class in the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and afterwards, the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you later, my friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We'll be five for dinner tonight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy and Yumi grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all yelp and grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Up to no good again, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, we were just studying together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, geez. My foot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had enough of your lies, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna stay right here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until you guys tell me the truth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad you're here, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno what's going on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but these little devils are up to no good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I intend to find out what it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jim, another one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your absurd stories</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about secret plots and passages.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean, absurd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard what I said, absurd, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbling] But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now listen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your paranoid behavior</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and your one track mind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>concerning these children</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are getting on my nerves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are a physical education teacher,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not a detective, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have class now, so get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Animals live in all land,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>air and sea regions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to their</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>varied respiratory organs...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It won't be long now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Klotz] And so, in Italian,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the noun, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>"città"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which of course means "city,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is invariable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who can give me another example?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm gonna need help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] When animals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and plants breathe, they take in oxygen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and emit carbon dioxide.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Living beings with aquatic...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Aelita. She's in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Obviously, this phenomenon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>depends on certain factors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who can tell us which ones?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead. We're listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The frog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[class laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excuse me. Sorry. Excuse me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Klotz] Who would like to answer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Anybody?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Ulrich. What's new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, come to the park. It's urgent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispering] Okay, be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, can I please go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm hmm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Mind telling me what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] XANA's at it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He knows the end is near,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he's not going down without a fight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[leaves rustle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where'd they go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Jeremy grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich howls and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gate whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It took you such a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm at the passage tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but three Bloks won't even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let me get close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I've got you localized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Better hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Once the coast is clear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go to the center of the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll launch the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm transferring you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the forest region,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little south of where Aelita is now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm counting on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch clanks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay Jeremy, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready, guys. I'm launching</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the materialization program immediately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd singing on recording]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Break, breakdance </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd singing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Break, break, breakdance </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Break, break, breakdance </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Break, break, breakdance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! What've I done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Problem Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I inserted the wrong CD.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd's recording continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One of Odd's dumb videos</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>instead of the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Break, break, breakdance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Break, break, breakdance </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Break, break, breakdance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[music stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta go back to the dorm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy huffs and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You made a video?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well yeah. It's pretty good too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's the title?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪ Break, break, breakdance ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, that's enough fooling around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've got some cleaning up to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Ulrich] Sir, yes, sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Okay, let's get started.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[breathes in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] This time, I've got him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clank]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Ulrich grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, the passage is clear. You can go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, just think,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this could be the last tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Playing hooky, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dithers] No, I left something in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Uh huh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I, uh... I gotta go...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back to class now, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not until you tell me what you've been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>plotting since the beginning of the year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this time, the principal's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not here to come to your rescue!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! You miserable little brat! [grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Get back here! Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait until I get my hands on you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy stop! That's an order!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Oh! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells and groans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, my ankle!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl 1] Are you crazy, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl 2] Hey, this is your fault!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] My ankle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Where can he be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] 45 minutes is a long time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go pick up a CD.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I sure hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing happened to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come on! Stop being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so gloom and doom. Don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dorothy] And now, does it still hurt?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's okay now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can walk fine, Dorothy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If there's one thing you'd better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not do yet, it's walk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to wait a week</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before putting that foot on the ground.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A week?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you complain, I won't give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you crutches to get around with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Jim...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Dorothy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] This time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've gone too far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't say I didn't warn you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time your paranoia has</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>caused an accident.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I... I'm sorry, sir. I really am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] So am I, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm going to have to let you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lightning cracks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas' voice echoes] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas' voice echoes] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all yelling in confusion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I go to the bathroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, the doctor insists</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you stay off your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go and get you a basin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, listen, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to say I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was so sure that you guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were up to something...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[inspired] Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>...that I guess I got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>carried away a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I deserve to get fired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I went a little crazy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause I thought you and your friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were hiding a lot of secrets.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna miss you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on a second, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're, um, not as crazy as you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[puzzled] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My friends and I, we do have a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that means I was right after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look Jim, if you help me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell the principal everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be off the hook, and he's bound</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give you your job back, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great. Shake on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clink]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got your basin. [gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Over there, behind the oak tree.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-In front of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Oh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was right! I was right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic scraping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was right! I was right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this super powerful virtual thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>called XANA wants to destroy us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only Aelita can deactivate the towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And our job is to help her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as much as we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And she's on this place called... "Loco"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's "Lyoko."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The only way to destroy XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to unplug him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But first, we have to materialize Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's what we're gonna do today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanisms whirring and clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Woah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who'd have believed it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Is everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's a long story, too long,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've got the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, let's cross our fingers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and hope it works okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm launching it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Ulrich, it's up to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you piece of junk!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nobody messes with my friends!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triangulate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on Ulrich, get him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Show this XANA thing who's the boss!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Jeremy, Ulrich is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it's Jim. Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's one of the gang now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans and howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, watch out behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You've gotta protect the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] The tower's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not gonna hold much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Leave it to Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hold on, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just a few more seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm almost ready, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get into position on the platform.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Well, ready to take the big jump?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Code Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's here at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to Earth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>