<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give, all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>KILLER MUSIC</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pop music playing through headphones]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'm so glad when you're so bad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, oh </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd, if you don't mind,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm trying to study.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd humming badly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[singing badly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut that out! Maybe you forgot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we've got a test tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What did you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hear a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said I want to study, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the sense of you studying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna get a zero in physics,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so why not listen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to what I downloaded from the Web.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, listen to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure beats studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's like pure music,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and nobody knows who wrote it either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's an MP3 file, and it's free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's a pop rock revolution!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You want a revolution?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll give you one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't think of anyone but yourself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm fed up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! Where ya going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To Jeremy's room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least he knows you need peace</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and quiet when you're studying!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not like you. Selfish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[music continues through headphones]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't worry, Kiwi. He'll get over it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ah, so glad when you're bad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, Oh </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy humming softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich! Uh, what's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and his music are driving me nuts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not into heavy metal? Pop? Funk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not when I have to study for an exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is it okay if I study in your room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can give you some help if you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could sure use some.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pop music plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So, so glad when you're really bad </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh-oh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[music skips and distorts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music continues through headphones]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Time to get up, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles] Too tired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I have to remind you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have a test this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't get a lot of sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'll tell you how come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mimicking Jeremy] Oh, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Aelita, you're in my dreams!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can't wait until...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes] She'll hear you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Between you and Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't study or sleep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not gonna tell anybody, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Promise, Romeo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's get some breakfast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, but not with Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He made me so mad last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles] Whatever you say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you finished the layout?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chomps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy chomps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sips]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How come Odd's still not here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I couldn't care less.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the song's name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The title is "Glad When You're Bad."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I honestly can't believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how unhip you guys are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a couple of losers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to go out once in a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, then, fill us in, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What kind of music is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] Is it R&amp;B?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] R&amp;B! Why not waltz music?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd ought to be here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe he didn't wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about it. It's his problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, chill out. You're making</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a big deal over loud music, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't let him miss his exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yes, we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd isn't here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, and I'm beginning to worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you check in his room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna do that right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, we'll be late for the exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not if we hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Keep me posted, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He sang that dumb song over and over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And look, now he's fast asleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Let's wake him up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-["Glad When You're Bad"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hey, Odd, get up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] If this is a joke,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's a bad one, and we're gonna be late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts] Hey, something's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd? Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't a joke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd? Odd! Can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[the principal clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Call the hospital.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And tell them it's very, very urgent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the junior high school here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need an ambulance immediately!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His blood pressure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and his heartbeat are slow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we add up the resistances</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a continuous circuit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the intensity of the current diminishes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a derivative circuit however,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the current</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-produced by the generator is equal...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>...to the sum of the intensities</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the derivative circuit branches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] ...the following equation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"Y equals..."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Sorry, Ms. Hertz. It's Odd, he...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[class bustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] All right, settle down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it serious? Well, is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His heart's beating very slowly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's not capable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of attacking human beings directly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If only I had stayed with him last night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this wouldn't have happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We had a big fight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I slept in Jeremy's room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could you have known that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm staying with him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, Ulrich, but I can't permit you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to leave the school grounds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm staying with Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, get away from that ambulance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is not the right way to help him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't care.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't let him be taken away like this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] All right, you can go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna go with him, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA launches an attack?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll stay in contact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Call me if there's the slightest problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ambulance siren]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nurse] We can't handle more emergencies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich, stop. You're not to blame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's all my fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's not. Even if you'd been there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you couldn't have changed anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go get us a soda.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll do us both good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna go see Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you in his room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nurse] Doctor, two new cases</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have just arrived.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forty heartbeats a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you take them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Doctor] Send them to the Johnson clinic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[over P.A.] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Doctor Miller</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is wanted in cardiology.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Doctor Miller is wanted in cardiology.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how's everything going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not good. Odd's in a coma.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His heart has almost stopped beating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one knows what to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the weirdest thing of all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that Odd may not be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the only one hit by the illness.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bizarre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think that XANA's capable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of creating a disease?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe he was actually able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack humans directly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like he might've found a way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I'd better warn Ulrich and Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meanwhile, see if you feel any pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bleeping and powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[steady beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Glad When You're Bad"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>playing on Sissi's headphones]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-["Glad When You're Bad" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning faintly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I just spoke to Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna try and see if XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the cause of our problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he did this, I can't figure out how.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I do know is that going to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the only way to save him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll get you out of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear we will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. XANA's activated a tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy. How's Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His heart's getting weaker and weaker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi's got the same symptoms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's spreading.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it could be an epidemic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>started by XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you reach Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get over to the factory, fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, set her down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gently.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft piano music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Glad When You're Bad"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>abruptly breaks through]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! My head! That horrible song!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dorothy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The music! It's definitely the music!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Connecting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, we're in the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pulsations are getting stronger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower can't be too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any monsters around?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not yet. No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's coming soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay where you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll wait here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's the song that's causing it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean "the song?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is. It's the song.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Glad When You're Bad!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! I think that's the song</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd downloaded from the Web yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's using the media</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for maximum coverage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's formatted the song</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and now he's spreading all over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A deadly melody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Considering what it's done to Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd better deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Send Yumi soon as she gets here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'll send you north,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the mountains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the activated tower fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, it's there. You see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nurse over P.A.] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Attention please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All available cardiologists</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are urgently requested</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to report to the Fleming wing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're at the tower. There it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[newscaster] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Since this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've been swamped with calls</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>warning us of a mysterious epidemic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For an update, let's go to our reporter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bill Amster who's on the scene.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bill?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thank you, Olivia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as news</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the first cases were announced,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I went to the neighborhood,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and things here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-are dramatic to say the least.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[police siren]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that the authorities</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't quote a figure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the number of people</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who have actually been stricken</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the illness.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The victims seem to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under the spell of a disease,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whose origins are unknown</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and whose outcome</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>could be fatal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Bill] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Public health officials</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are presently on the scene.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No monsters anywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's suspicious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ah, there you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blade hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar beeping and locks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita, take cover somewhere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you're out of bounds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for three minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything okay on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich's frozen solid and Aelita's alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>To the mountains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch whirring and clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, 30 seconds to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay behind me, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] How much longer, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He's coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Glad to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Better stay alert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two Bloks are on their way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That one's yours, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Bill]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> According</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the public health department,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the very first cases were discovered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at Kadic Junior High School.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Glad When You're Bad" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-["Glad When You're Bad" starts again]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and Aelita, run to the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll never make it all alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who said I would be alone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triangulate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Position! Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Glad When You're Bad" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar locks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Glad When You're Bad" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[steady beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to enter the coordinates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the return trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Launching.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants] I did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did it! [grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts and moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita, don't worry about me. Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>["Glad When You're Bad" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping and whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-["Glad When You're Bad" playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[machine beeping slowly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pop music playing through headphones]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vocalizing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming and vocalizing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd, come on. I'm trying to study.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the sense in studying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna get a zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] I've heard that twice already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, listen to what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I downloaded from the Web.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's outta sight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Under my cover," by R.U. Phlegmatic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Later. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-For the time being, I'd like to study.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And as for you, I wouldn't say no</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to your helping me a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're so good in physics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, and if you want help,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the reincarnation of Einstein</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is willing to give a lesson</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a sawdust-filled head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'll listen to your song afterwards.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't really have to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, it's pretty mainstream.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's something that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I mean is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the kind of song</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a machine might have written?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, you know a lot about music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So, you gonna help me or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, just a second!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me finish the song.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll see about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>