<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A FINE MESS</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[air whizzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] OK.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heads, it's Odd first,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and tails, it's Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heads! Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi! I lose…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi? Are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What am I doing over here, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we've got a little problem here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Odd] Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess it's a little bug in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the rematerialization program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You call this a little bug?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't stay this way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Odd] What if we went back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Lyoko and devirtualized all over again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe everything would go back to normal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what if the program messes up again</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any bodies at all this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Odd] OK. Bad idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers] So what do we do, then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got to fix the program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How long will it take you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A couple of hours at the most?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I work through the night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it might be ready tomorrow morning!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[speaking as Yumi] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean I'm going to have to sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a guy's body?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm not getting any sleep at all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you haven't noticed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a dynamite body.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better than yours! There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For example,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something's itching me in my back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think it's the strap to your…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you dare take it off! You hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you guys worry about it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be helping Jeremy tonight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything will be fine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by tomorrow morning…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi speaking as Odd] I hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not as much as I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, so what's my schedule</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this evening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… try the three "B's":</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bacon, bath, bedtime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Same here… but Japanese style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just try not to say anything stupid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of my parents!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can you eat with chopsticks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As long as they look like forks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs ironically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't do anything stupid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my body either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mine is still under warranty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you'd better brush your teeth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and go to bed early tonight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't tonight the night you were supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to break up with Magali?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right. And with Claire too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going steady</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with two girls at the same time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't know that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Neither do Magali and Claire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Up to now, that is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I've got a great idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are always too shy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to ask Yumi out, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you can practice on me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not a great idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a stupid idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And anyway, I'm not that crazy about Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right… Tell me about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you to give it a shot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without really sticking your neck out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In this way, I can give you pointers, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pointers? You?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ask me out. I'm waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, look who is here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Romeo and Juliette!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, I can't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a lamebrain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dear Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When will you understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I am the girl for you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this string bean, anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least I don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the mind of a vegetable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Give it a rest, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and I were made for one another!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's… That's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's disgusting!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[camera clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, wow! The scoop of the year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I see why Sissi is so crazy about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do that one more time and you're dead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You try to do a friend a favor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's the thanks you get.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that's not it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut it out, Kiwi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no reason to growl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This should be it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to go. See you later Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling and barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be a good dog, now! Good bye, Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Magali] Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know all about Claire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are so despicable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know about Magali!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sneaky rat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can tell Ulrich he'll have to beg</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a date with a real flower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when his stringy veggie drops him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing? Did you find it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes, here it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi just told me to tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something… Something about veggies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't get it. What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing. Are you coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Let's go to the cafeteria.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, do you mind answering</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few questions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our "Academy Gossip Column"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I do mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What has gotten into you, now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ask that imbecile Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, did you find it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had it since I was really little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Ishiyama] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only in case of emergency, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gloating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I'm… not very hungry, so…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna go to bed…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mingtian Jiàn!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why is she speaking to us in Chinese, now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's "wuv"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh… Ulrich… I "wuv" you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll get used to me in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice puppy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought my hand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was disappearing for a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must have imagined it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. You can tell Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about it tomorrow morning!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I guess it can wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch yourself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gross!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Phew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I warned you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's more powerful that a laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was right, Aelita! It's definitely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a bug in the rematerialization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[slurping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, please, Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope that Jeremy found the bug…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you give me a hand with breakfast?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If… If… If I had a hand to give you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It only lasted a few seconds…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but my hands completely disappeared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Strange. I'll be a lot happier when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>both of you are back in your own bodies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I fixed the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just need to restart it from Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll go to the factory at lunchtime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See! Everything's fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's very bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ni hao!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-First of all, that's Chinese.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And second of all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what is with that outfit?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… They're your clothes! Cool, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks really good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are so lucky that you're in my body</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right now or I would beat you to a pulp!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go home, you hear, and change before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the entire school sees you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi Ishiyama… transformed by love!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool headline, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll double our circulation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are they talking about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with this love thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time to explain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to be late for math class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sayonara!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teacher] Take out your pens, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pop quiz on linear functions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh man… Bad break.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's gonna kill me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you always have conversations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with yourself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… Yes. Call it a split personality.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that why you're dressed like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… Kind of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ma'am, I have a sore throat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could I go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, of course, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No one noticed anything in class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They were all concentrating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the math quiz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was a math quiz this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you manage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well… If you mean sharpening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my pencils and all that… Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you think the problem is, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Yumi have been rematerialized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in bodies that aren't their own,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and so, they aren't stable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And…?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we don't take care of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the problem immediately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>their atoms might split.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean our "atoms might split"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Complete disintegration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you down to the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to get to a way tower due</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>north from where you arrive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will reboot the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from that tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the nightmare should be over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and Ulrich, you go in first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[energy buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Aelita grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… I mean, that is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi… No, wait…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh… Whatever. Transfer! Scanner!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[air whizzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, let's hear it for cat woman!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA might wanna send a welcome committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I hope Aelita makes it fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is turning into an emergency here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kankrelats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's all we need…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeez, thanks for the heads-up, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. But watch it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever happens, Odd or Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't be devirtualized!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If they go, it's bye-bye for good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi speaking as Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, I forgot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Supersprint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, how do the arrows work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… You imagine you're firing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you concentrate a little,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and bingo it fires.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oops, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh! Jeremy? We've got a big problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do anything from here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The program is being run by inhibitors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to deactivate them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I'll try to find them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thank you for caring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're doing all we can, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry, we have to get to Sector five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] But, what for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And bring up your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you absolutely sure that we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go into Sector Five?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have time for me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to try and crack the millions of codes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find those inhibitors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, if you don't get back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into your own bodies quickly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means disintegration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seeing how you handle those arrows</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you might accidentally kill Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the code "Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] A Megatank.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe I can possibly be so dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[air whizzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hollister system connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi] [groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'm going to be sick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes, the transporter does make me feel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like throwing up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tough break for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out! The wall is about to open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all pant]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The countdown has started so hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And watch out for the scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Problem here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is a pretty lame architect!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He forgot to put the stairs in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] There's the key!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! Anyone know how to fly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd as Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great shot! You missed a Creeper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at ten yards in a hallway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd as Yumi chuckles and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow! Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's modified the gravity in this room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both chuckle and gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're coming to the end of the countdown.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Darn!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't get enough momentum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm swimming through guacamole!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shields!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many life points do you have left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi speaking as Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lots! Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi speaking as Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bull's eye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out! Creeper is behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd speaking as Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd speaking as Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, the scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no! Not now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You OK, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi grunts and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi as Odd grunts and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd as Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd speaking as Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! Every time we dematerialize,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it lasts longer and longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita better find the code,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd as Yumi] Careful a Creeper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the inhibitors as fast as you can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't hang around there too long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things are gonna get messy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi as Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're at the final stage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of disintegration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd as Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That's it! Done, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can take over again now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, I got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll transfer back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the rematerialization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi speaking as Odd] Yumi, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi as Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope the tweak</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the materialization program worked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to the scanner room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that… Is that you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course. What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you recognize your own friends?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dork.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through speaker]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's OK, Jeremy, we've got full recovery!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heads, it's Yumi who shows up first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tails, it's Odd… Tails!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tails it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi wasn't too mad at me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the end… I mean, about her parents,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or for the math quiz,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or for the clothes, or for…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>taking a couple of slaps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She is really cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to go out with her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of… Did you tell her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happened between us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I plan on staying alive, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? What did happen between you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Oh, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, speaking of Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, she's over there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the school paper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I warned you. Sorry I can't give you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any pointers, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>