<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OPENING ACT</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's happening, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean to tell me there's actually</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little news in the Kadic News this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't tell me you haven't heard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Scoop of the year"… Blah, blah, blah…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris coming to Kadic…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Blah, blah, blah… "Too amazing!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris? Chris who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Haven't you ever heard of the Subdigitals?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris is their drummer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he'll be at Kadic today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you guys, cool it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It sounds like a phony scoop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, it sure does.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just another one of Milly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Tamiya's dumb stories.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it could be for real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that Chris is coming here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to visit his uncle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean that Chris has an uncle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who works here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wonder who that can be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You too, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can you believe that stuff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] If it's true,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who do you think his uncle really is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fumey, Chardin, Mr. Delmas…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi could never be Chris' cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If she was, she'd be shouting it out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to anyone willing to listen to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Reilly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Michael Reilly, the custodian? Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well in that case, why not Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just as clumsy as ever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, what a coincidence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were just talking about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. It seems that the Subdigitals'</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>drummer is coming to Kadic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to visit his uncle, and we thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd be the first to know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? No, what gave you an idea like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I almost forgot, how stupid of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not your style of music at all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is it Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're more into like oldies, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but wait a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I also happen to like rock music</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I love the Subdigitals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those guys are very talented artists,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially my nephew. He's really great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I was right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're Chris' uncle!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't say that, did I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure did, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what he said, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay, little Chris is my nephew,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, now that's what I call</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sensational scoop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm counting on you all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to tell anybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially you, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want this getting around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise not to tell a living soul, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Jim, tell Chris I love him…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wrote a song for him…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you've got the wrong guy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know any Chris!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never heard of the guy, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go away, away I say!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dear Chris,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on behalf of the entire staff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and student body of Kadic Academy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would like to wish you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a very warm welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd] Chris! Chris! Chris!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[principal] Chris, they're all yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd clamoring] Chris! Chris!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good morning, everyone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and thank you all for this enthusiasm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I guess all of you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I came here to visit my uncle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there's another reason as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris] The Subdigitals have decided to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a school tour to discover new talent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and to develop that talent by giving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you guys a chance to be the opening act</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at our next concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And thanks to the kind authorization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've organized an audition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this afternoon in your gymnasium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Now where did it go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm positive I put it here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Since when do you actually</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>put any of your things away, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs mockingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, you guys could give me a hand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you tell us what you're looking for,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe we could help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] My CD demo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I absolutely have to play it for Chris!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you did put it away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Kiwi's drawer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Let's see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, my adorable diggity dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Glory and fame are just around the corner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope not too many kids show up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You were saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smooches, giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. I was thinking, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that since Delmas cancelled classes today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we could make some headway on the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our new virtual ship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'd like to, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, come on! Don't tell me you're gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>waste your time going to that audition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine what XANA might be plotting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the network even while we're talking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to find a way to travel there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I was counting on you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right. I won't go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris has got to choose my demo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got a good ear for talent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then I'll be the greatest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DJ star of all time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The biggest DJ of all time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does DJ stand for, "dumb jerk"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just cool it, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll eat those words when you see me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a stretch limo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, don't worry. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your mix will blow everyone away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as long as you don't bust our eardrums.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, man! With friends like you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who needs enemies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for your support, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mid-tempo electronic music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Matthias, is that right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris] Next!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, I'm Sissi Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the daughter of Jean-Pierre Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the school principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[comedic horn blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Chris groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna play my best track for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's called, "I'm Headed for the Stars"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope it really takes off for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't believe your ears, Chris.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[harsh music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[discordant music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your stretch limo have a flat tire?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, hello, my name is Odd Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I think I'd better explain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that my music is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little experimental, actually,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>uh, well, pretty different.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, anyway, you're gonna love it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is where I'm stumped.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still don't understand the real nature</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the transitional interface</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between Lyoko and the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even though I've gone over and over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the flux and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hey, Aelita, are you listening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you say that again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never mind. There might be a way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I discovered that we could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>reconfigure the navigation parameters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in relative function</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the frequency of the flux…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music volume lowers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And there you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates] Well… I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd. Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what you just heard is just</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little taste of what I can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear, I've got lots of other tracks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanna hear them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some other time maybe. Thanks a lot, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[pensive piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I was good, wasn't I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well, you gave it your best shot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the main thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One thing's for sure. You said it was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>different, and you weren't lying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well now, kid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have you found a future star?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'd rather not talk about it, Uncle Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you mean, "system error"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, don't blow your cool, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll just shift the polarity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the contact flux and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hand me those figures… Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, I can finish up on my own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you want to go, you can go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you… Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. I think I know what's holding us up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm off then. See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not that simple. It's all part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of this promotional operation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we don't bring the record company</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some new talent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll be down on me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a ton of bricks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They've already made us change our name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't worry, my boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's gotta be a youngster around here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a ton of talent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A few words for the Kadic News, Chris?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one or two questions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I have an autograph, Chris?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When's your next concert?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you working on a new album?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sign my notebook, please…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Calm down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] He can't answer your questions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you all talk at once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now let's try it one at a time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on, quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's what I've been looking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for all day today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no. I'm too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you figure that compared</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the rest of the candidates,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a pretty good chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of getting picked?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just thinking about being the opening act</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the Subdigitals gives me the chills!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, it's not in the bag just yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys want a scoop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris finally found the opening act</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he was looking for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fame, fortune and glory are all mine now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one knows who it is, not even Chris.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? But how can that be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't stop repeating my name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it happened after the auditions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All he did was hear the music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He didn't see the DJ.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He went to see the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see if he could find this Cinderella,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whoever he or she is. Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Well, when you gotta go,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you gotta go, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no, a XANA attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Superscan has just picked up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to get to the factory, fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>took off and no one knows where she went.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait for me under the arches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stop by her room first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in a few minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] Chris!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was looking for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to give you this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams, groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris… I'll bet you've found out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who the mystery DJ is. Is it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita on voicemail]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi, leave me a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's not picking up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] She's not in her room either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were working together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she wasn't concentrating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She was more interested in showing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her demo to Chris at the audition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, now I understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why she took off like a rocket.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you think Aelita's the mystery DJ?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kinda looks like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Would you mind filling me in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't worry, we'll tell you on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two go and find her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] She must have gone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the principal's office to see Chris.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Meet us at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look like you're in shock. Did Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>say something intelligent for once?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris just kidnapped Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we saw him pass by</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Aelita on his shoulder.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was totally weird,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like the mad killer in </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Executioner Two</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shouldn't we call the police?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wouldn't do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was just for the… the video.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, the new Subdigitals' video.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're doing this science fiction thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with robots invading the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. We've gotta go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got parts in the next scene</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're shooting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yes, Jeremy? Chris? Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This has to be Aelita's demo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, look. Chris and Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Outside?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] She walked right into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the lion's den.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita isn't there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris must've locked her up somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He doesn't look Xanafied, does he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only one way to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look kid, there's nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna find your DJ.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris, check out this CD.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just what you're looking for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Stern, Della Robbia, cut that out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's important, look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We've got the demo</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chris has been looking for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want an autograph or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Chris, but I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beat it, you two! Scram!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I suggest you watch your step.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got my eye on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll discuss this later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he didn't kidnap Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then it must have been…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] A polymorphic spectre!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what's going on? Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What am I doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Jeremy, I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can stop looking for Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We know. There's a polymorphic spectre</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the loose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're at the secret passage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys are as easy to track</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>down as a caribou in the Great North.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay where you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have a few questions to ask you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Jim, but we don't have time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, we happen to be in a hurry too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris] Are you the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who put this together?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah… No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a friend of mine… Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's her last name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the difference? She's in danger</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's why we're in such a big hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean in danger?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's this all about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take us to her immediately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unless you'd rather settle this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the principal's office.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then, come with us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but let me warn you about two things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to avoid asking any questions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get ready for a workout.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Works for me, Stern. There's no work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I like better than working out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may be possessed by XANA, but</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're still a rookie on Lyoko, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, where are Odd and Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna need some backup over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're on their way. Meanwhile,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>try to get to the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's bearing south of your position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bring you up a vehicle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong, ladies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Having a bad leg day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music intensifies]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Chris grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, where's that vehicle?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The old William was hard to get rid of,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but this one is a lot worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans, grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A mad scientist hideout?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's that guy over there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a stunt double or a clone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A polymorphic spectre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well spectre or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's not getting my autograph…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, hands off my nephew, pal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Now you'll see what it's like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to mess with an old Special Forces agent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, we really need you Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get to… get to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… She's in trouble. Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris] Hey, what's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you not to ask any questions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All set Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, first let me program an overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks Jeremy. That was a close one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Move out, Aelita. Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey there, you little crab cakes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you miss us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can have the last one. Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! I love having seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get rid of that impostor now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one does that to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and gets away with it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, Uncle Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William and Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic mid-tempo music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you're trying to get a date with Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not so sure that's the right way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't have to be a math genius to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that there's one too many Jims here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Reminds me of the time I fought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against Hurricane Windstorm in Vegas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back in '94. In the third round,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just walloped--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'm sorry, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you guys doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got our hands full here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if this keeps up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Subdigitals are gonna need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a new drummer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're doing our best, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's get down to business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mantas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing digital beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll fight you every step of the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois, I want an explanation right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is going on, and what in the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is all this equipment for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would but I'm getting tired</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of explaining it to you, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause in ten seconds,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you won't remember any of it anyway.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so fast. First, tell me who Aelita is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I finally figured out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what was wrong with my demo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't push the second break</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a series of scratches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do a lot better next time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess in the end, XANA's attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ended up giving us another free afternoon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to work on our virtual ship, huh, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knock on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excuse me. I'm looking for Aelita Stones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… That's me, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really glad to meet you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I heard your demo</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I think it's really great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could we go over to the gym?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to hear it live.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to, but I'm not sure I can…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on. It's an offer you can't refuse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] By the way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how'd you get a hold of my demo?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Chris]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, one of your friends gave it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>