<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>UNCHARTED TERRITORY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elf panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolf growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elf gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolves howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolves howl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elf pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music crescendoes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolves howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolf grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elf shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Now… Let's see…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Wow, unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Jeremy, let's get a move on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There won't be any hot water left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Remember the Hermitage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Where Aelita had visions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Bad memory, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to check it out a little closer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I found out something amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What would really be amazing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that there are still eggs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when we get to breakfast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you a real walking stomach, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're a walking brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, we're complementary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[giggle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I researched the house owner,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I came across</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a restricted access site.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It took most of the night to hack into it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it was worth it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found a deed signed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by a Mr. Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems he is the owner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it has something to do with Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, there's an underground passage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the sewers from his yard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He must be linked to the supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, I searched "Franz Hopper"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and guess what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was a science teacher</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here at Kadic Academy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that weird or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] It's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] Every day, the same thing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it may go faster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now that Sissi's done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Shut up, kiddies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly and Tamiya mocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poor thing, you'll be here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for another two hours!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not go upstairs?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are some showers free up there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and not a girl in sight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boys] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The girls' showers are downstairs, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita Stones, hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go easy on her, Jim. She's new.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, well, new or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a young lady</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has no business in the boys' showers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I thought that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to hear your excuses!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do that again and you go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Principal's office!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Einstein, just like I said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a single girl in these showers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, we're sick of your bad jokes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so chill!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you give Aelita a break for once?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You knew she'd believe you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What can I say? Ulrich, sweety.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She has to adapt, doesn't she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] It's a jungle out there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm looking at a big baboon right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich, Aelita and Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Shut up, you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Sissi is such a brat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] And to think you kissed once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Cool it. That is ancient history.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, you think the owner of the Hermitage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the science teacher are the same?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finding two guys named Franz Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a radius of half a mile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a real coincidence!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, there is only one way to be sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After history class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have a study period in the library.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What if we do a little research</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Kadic Academy archives?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll go with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'd rather you didn't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were in trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the showers this morning!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Jim catches you in the archives,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be suspended!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll meet you at the cafeteria.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Are you all right, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't get used to living here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had another nightmare last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The same one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You haven't been here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a week, yet. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll feel better soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] E, F, G, H. H for Hopper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, shoot…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums] Shouldn't you be in class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, children?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming] We're looking for a teacher.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Which one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mr. Chardin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mrs. Mayer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boys titter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hopper, Hopper…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shuffling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Weber shrugs] At this time of day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you can't find your teacher,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means they're in class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's OK, I found Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Madame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy] Come on! Move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, fish and beans</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or steak and potatoes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs] Oh, well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry! We're starving!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods and shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy] My turn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] That was a close one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] No doubt about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I compared the teacher's signature</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the one on the deed I found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're the same!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if we look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around the Hermitage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find out more about this teacher?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Good idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't we supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to meet Aelita in the cafeteria?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll be a minute. She won't mind waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, going back to the great, white north?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not? At least I feel at home there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Still looks as creepy as ever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are we looking for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How should I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If this Franz Hopper is linked to XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe we'll find some information</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about Aelita's virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not much. Physics books,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Planck, Heisenberg, Schrödinger…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What's this doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Tunic Wars</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>? What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Punic, not tunic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The war between the Romans</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Carthaginians?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] We studied it, remember?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are lame in history.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You see these notes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure Hopper wrote them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet! Where is Aelita Stones?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, why isn't Aelita here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, madame. I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I do, madame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She went back to Canada.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Canada?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! That's what she told me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She said "I feel at home there."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Elisabeth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you disrupt the class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send you to your father's office!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's "Sissi," not "Elisabeth,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate being called like that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Madame, I don't feel well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-May I go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Of course, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we take him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… Oh, all right, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But don't dilly dally!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Jeremy, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think Aelita is there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She told Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she was going back to Canada.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think she meant</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I'm going back to where I came from!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She virtualized herself on her own!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's pretty weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why would she do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe she got homesick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does Yumi know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I left her a message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go to the scanner room. Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy gasps] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got the message at the pool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run to the scanner. Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Odd are there. I'll explain later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, don't worry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others are on their way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd. Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner and virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you see her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She's due north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants] Jeremy! I'm surrounded!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up! Aelita's fallen into a trap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Go ahead, Ulrich! With your speed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll get there first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Krab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Another one behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Battle stations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's bought some time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your move, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Nice, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Bloks are catching up to Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting? Call a taxi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Hurry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Vehicle materialization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They are coming to get you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? She's already gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She must really be mad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>This is not time for jokes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I lost Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean… She's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… I doubt it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She disappeared from the screen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if… Wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got it! I got a signal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A very weak one, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, that's strange!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's not in this sector anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She's not in any sector!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you explain that a little better?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No. Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's in a sector that doesn't exist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A fifth sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A fifth sector?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you gone bananas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I could just fix this thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Maybe I--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to Carthage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Will this take long, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I hope not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flutter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, oh… Now things are starting to buzz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what are we doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Wait, I got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>As long as is not a biggie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I need a password.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something to do with Carthage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Not the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a history lesson.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A history lesson?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's exactly what I need!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That's too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hannibal… Carthage…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>General…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His father, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Any day now…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hannibal's sister?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Salammbo?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The nemesis of Carthage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No dice!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Whenever you're ready, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm doing my best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we won't last longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll get this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No… I can't believe this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[flutter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm going around in circles…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to Carthage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to go into Carthage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to defeat Carthage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who defeated the Carthaginians?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scipio!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>S-C-I-P-I-O</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] The Hornets are calling it quits!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come back, cowards!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's that ball doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shrug]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I think the code "Scipio"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>made it appear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did you do that, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I got some help</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to Sector Five, everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What does it look like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] A sphere that--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums] It's probably bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Scyphozoa whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita is being attacked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you guide us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Take the footbridge behind you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Scyphozoa whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Scyphozoa whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there's this "thing" in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Destroy it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's taking Aelita's memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Something weird is happening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! That can't be good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Scyphozoa whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just in time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Now, what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Wait, I'm re-entering the code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Scipio"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've got your ticket out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy types]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And there you go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm bringing you in right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, get to the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll rematerialize you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Materialization Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Materialization Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Materialization Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You should have seen it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There were creepy things!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And in the middle,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this big jellyfish holding Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine! That thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was stealing my memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, for sure XANA wants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get something out of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what? That's what we have to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to go back to Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So much to explore!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'll go with you. It'll be awesome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Not so fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to study it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, it's uncharted territory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can be totally dangerous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums] You're not angry at me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for going back to Lyoko by myself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what got into me, I needed--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't have to explain, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We understand what happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we're not angry at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I promise to spend more time with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And I'll teach how to tell Sissi to go--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know what your filthy mutt did</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the shower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a pretty picture!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So, you found Mrs. Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, when you were taking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your third shower of the day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, a beautiful flower like me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>needs to be watered often.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You never know. You might sprout a brain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Morons!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can give Odd lessons, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] You sure learn fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>