<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>END OF TAKE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[film projector whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dramatic music plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Totally ridiculous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, that was great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the special effects were pretty good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but well, it wasn't scary enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come your teeth were chattering?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the sound effects?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy, Ulrich and Yumi laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dear students, your attention please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would like you all to give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a warm welcome</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the director of the film</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've just seen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and which we all found very...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And here he is now, James Finson,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who is honoring us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with his presence today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to discuss his work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the fascinating field of cinema.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[applause]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, that's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm also here to look for locations to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shoot my new film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[multiple] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Finson] In fact, I heard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's an old factory around here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that nobody uses anymore,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which I'm very interested in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A factory? Oh, no! Not ours!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kid] Great! Thank you, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] If Finson finds out about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our super computer, we're in trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that means we absolutely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have to stop him from using it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah sure we do, but how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. Nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come every time he says</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's nothing to worry about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get worried. And I mean, worried!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, I'm so glad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to meet you, Mr. Finson.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just love your films.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a big fan of yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh. Oh, really? Well, I can't argue</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your taste. I like my films too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Um. Why don't you just write</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"To Sissi, a rising star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who I'm going to give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the leading role to in my next film."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'm going to write</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"To Sissi, who's got a lot of nerve!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>...and a lot of talent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm very sorry, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the casting is over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The parts have all been distributed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, better luck next time, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Humph.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat] Uh, hello, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The factory you were talking about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was wondering</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you'd already been there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but I'm going to start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my scouting later today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you see I know the place inside out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and, uh, I really don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you could find a better guide.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] It looks like everyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this school has a lot of nerve.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Finson] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's even better than I thought!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah, it looks all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The trouble is it's falling apart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopefully, the ceiling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't fall on our heads.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great. I love a dangerous shoot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I always look for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An actor is always better under pressure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, Mr. Finson, you better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>watch out for your equipment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's crawling with rats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Finson] Rats? That's lucky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got some big scenes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to shoot with rats in them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Conclusion: Never trust Ulrich when</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he says there's nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, he tried to gross him out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Instead, he's even more excited.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're right, it's a great set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad about all that uranium</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they stored here for so many years.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe one day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it won't be radioactive anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmhmm. Do you know where</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this freight elevator leads to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that old thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, it stopped working ages ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, they say that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-when it was working, it...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ghost noises]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That noise? Oh, it's nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing at all. Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well, there is an old rumor that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this factory is haunted by ghosts,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't believe a word of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Although...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This place just keeps getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>better and better than I thought!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you seem to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>every nook and cranny of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How would you like to work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as a technical adviser on the film?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes! Do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you serious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Yay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Shh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uhm, well, it would be a great honor, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only problem is that the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would never let me miss my classes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me talk to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Sissi, your father will never let</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich miss even one hour of school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. We'll see about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing's gonna stop me from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>becoming a big movie star!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! He said no. Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I even promised</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to put his name in the credits.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Mr. Finson, can I talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi got a part in Finson's film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, in exchange for convincing her dad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to let me skip school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>working together on a film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This could be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the beginning of a great romance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She won't leave me alone for one second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your real job</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to be there, in the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>making sure that nobody discovers our lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not going to be as bad as all that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure it's not too heavy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts dragging a luggage]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I think that I'm about to become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a big star, and that you, Ulrich, honey,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are lucky enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to witness the event live!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Oh, I envy you. I really do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Uh, hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Finson is expecting us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you have cell phones by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, cell phones? Why of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could think we didn't?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Confiscated. Mr. Finson's orders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man assistant] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>During the shooting, it's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>forbidden to communicate with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the outside world without Finson's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's so there are no leaks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the script, or newspaper gossip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's also why everyone sleeps here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with guards at the entrance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blond man]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We shoot this one from above, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man assistant] Apart from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all that, it's a lot of fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but what if we have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get in touch with, uh,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our parents, for example?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In case there's a problem, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you shoot with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>James Finson, there's never a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut off from the rest of the world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's so incredibly romantic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's almost like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being alone on a desert island.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic. I can't wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's time for you all to meet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the main character of my movie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Prepare yourselves for a big surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Finson]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be shy. Tell me what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's my best monster yet, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And to top it all off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've invented a way to make him squirt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>slimy, disgusting threads of goo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll knock your socks off. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Funny, but it makes me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>think of the alien in that film, uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can't remember the name...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-My creature is unique, young man,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my movie will be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like no other ever made!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Humph.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hhh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Finson, I'm very anxious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get my script, if you don't mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to start working on my lines.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we professionals are very serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, why, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one second. Here it comes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Finson] There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aaaaah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got it kid!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be the alien's first victim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Twenty seconds on the screen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but twenty seconds of glory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Finson laughs] Gory glory, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crickets chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we can shoot that one in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem gonna be the next scene.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music keeps playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music turns ominous]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[inhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what're you doing in the lab?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They took my cell phone away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finson's totally paranoid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It won't be easy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>staying in touch with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Well, well!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of a weird place is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich, please tell me that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that wasn't Sissi's voice I just heard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Sissi, listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't explain this to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but, uh, you can't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell anyone about this or else...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or else what? A monster's going to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>squirt goopy goo all over my face, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[monster growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a big problem here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Follow me. Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what is going on? Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine slowing down and stopping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta climb up. I'll follow you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go. We can't stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Through here. Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>X.A.N.A.'s up to something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A tower's been activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm launching a scan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to localize the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll wake Odd, call Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll be on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic, ominous music plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] Who's the moron that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's you, boss. I'm sorry. [laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just composed it for the film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, all you lazybones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's go. We've got a movie to make.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Finson] Go get the alien.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[man] Boss!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Eh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better come and take a look. Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a little problem here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little problem huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You call this a little problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and find him, you understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He couldn't have walked out on his own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go find him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Finson, the two youngsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have both disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finson's alien monster...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's come alive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can a machine, made of plastic and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rubber, come alive like...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[splattering and growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hhh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna try and find Ulrich and Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll stay in contact, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd's about to make the plunge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do things look?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty bad. You were right, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>X.A.N.A. is up to no good again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've localized the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's in the polar region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman assistant] Do you really think it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was those two kids who stole the alien?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man assistant] If it was them, they</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>better hope Finson doesn't find them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy, I'm in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's on her way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the polar region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's where the scan localized the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll launch the transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Nice little place,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it could use a little heat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower plateau is in that direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go. If we run, it'll warm you up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get this at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why did he leave us alone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he could have just as easily...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm pretty sure he wanted to use us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as bait to attract the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you say the others, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you mean that whole gang of yours?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever you do, don't move a muscle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, aren't you funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi! I never thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd be saying this to you one day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm actually very glad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see you for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can kiss and make up later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or X.A.N.A.'s gonna get his way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Finson] Come out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And make it snappy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drama music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>X.A.N.A.'s sent his monsters out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just behind you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a swarm of them armed with lasers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Twenty life points per impact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] A little battle's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bound to keep me warm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Talk about a reception committee!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Odd, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's keep going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Yumi, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, answer me, Yumi. Please answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What have you done with my alien?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But... What...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Boss, did you find the--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't let them get away! Get a move on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop! I created you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to obey me, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hhh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. I did find them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but X.A.N.A.'s taken possession</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a monster who's gonna be here--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Yumi and Ulrich are in big trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's not much time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wow, that sure is steep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] But we have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wow! What a fabulous ride!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Woohoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I think I just might</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>settle down and live here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeehaw!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ahh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's at the end of this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, I, uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, I get the idea. Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Ahh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>At any rate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower is pretty close now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the info, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You think he's called it quits?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I doubt it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For once, I had a chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to show how talented I am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that mechanical monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has to go nuts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's more he decides to pick on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did I ever do to that plastic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>piece of junk to deserve that, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, you think you can get her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep still for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well Aelita, any sign of that tower yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but I may be seeing double.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there are two towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can that be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only saw one on the holomap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>X.A.N.A. must have done that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to confuse us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we've gotta choose one,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and pronto, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, have you got any news for us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what's going on? Answer me, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I know what you're gonna tell me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, for your information,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're not exactly having a tea party here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you've gotta choose</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of the towers now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold them off much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, I'm out of arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich struggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I happen to choose the wrong tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be all over. You know that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have faith in you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Argh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm sorry. I chose the wrong one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Great idea to use</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the factory for a movie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks. I must confess that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my ideas are...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I say this with great modesty,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>absolutely ingenious. Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It makes a great set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, you do know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that a film was shot here once before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, a science fiction movie with an alien.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] And a fabulous picture too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. No, I've given it some thought,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the factory is a good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, it wasn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my idea in the first place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How dare you accuse me of lying to you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can find another producer, you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Finson] I'm not upset!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>