<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE SECRET</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy, I'm on my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what are you doing up so late?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't exactly call this up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, I was speeding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get back to the dorm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I climbed the wall to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Skybreaker Four," but it was really lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The first three were duds,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why the big surprise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] I'm too much of an optimist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even things start badly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel they can get better with time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, but I've gotta go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that a good enough answer for you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me go, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but before I do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you got to kiss me good-night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-All right, but close your eyes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I guess my evening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wasn't a waste after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps dying away]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William screams] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I am, Jeremy. You can send me in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just in time to welcome Aelita, Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich from Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've already deactivated the tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what happened to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't your phone ring?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I oversleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at least three times a week.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course, with Ulrich always snoring,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's a question of survival!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not only my sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's beginning to bring me down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Mathias Burrel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emmanuel Maillard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Maïtena Lecuyer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Maïtena] Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, last night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you pulled a fast one on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one has ever humiliated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that before! Why did you do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Because I got sick of your Casanova act.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the beginning, it was pretty nice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but now, I'm really fed up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Buzz off, William, and leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] William Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm not deaf!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can see I'm here, can't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dunbar, to the library! Outta my sight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No swimming for you today, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I'd like to know what you had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do that was so important last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm gonna find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what your big secret is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] You can bet on that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna make a fabulous report.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better. It counts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the whole semester.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, what's the latest in the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Kadic Junior High today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Is Judith going out with Ronald?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who are Judith and Ronald?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How should I know? But they're going out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, no, a XANA alert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Not again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but the problem is Aelita and me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't get out of history class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't sweat it, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and I will get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you get there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can send us to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But finish your report</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as fast as possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Second grade Casanova, uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi is not picking up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on with her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last night, and then now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, is it OK if we begin now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, you may.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where are Odd and Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you see, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they had something important to do, and--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>More important than my class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I wasn't supposed to tell you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but they're preparing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a surprise for your class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A surprise? What kind of surprise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a big historical show in your honor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd never have guessed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll excuse their absence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And now sir, can we begin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell us about World War One.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] On 1914, a Serbian student</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>assassinated Archduke Franz-Ferdinand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nephew and heir to the Austro-Hungarian</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emperor, Franz-Joseph.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This took place in Bosnia-Herzegovina.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Political alliances were reinforced,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all of Europe got involved.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Serbia, Russia, France and GB were against</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Germany and Austria-Hungary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>More countries got involved.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Germany invaded Belgium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Italy, Greece, Romania</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the U.S. joined the allies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Turkey and Bulgaria</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>supported central Europe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The armistice treaties of 1918</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>put an end to the fighting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but peace treaties were needed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a definitive end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to "the war to end all wars,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>clearing the way for a lasting peace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finally, the victorious countries united</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a peace conference</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a two-fold mission</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of creating a "League of Nations"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the adoption of peace treaties</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sent to the defeated nations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope that wasn't too long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, may I go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've a bit of a headache.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I do too, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not feeling too well either</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of a sudden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Call Yumi again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's bound to answer sooner or later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Today, we'll learn synchronized swimming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means, no speed competitions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no stop watches, just pure grace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] But, since "a picture is worth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a thousand words,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here's a demonstration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Admire the finesse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what I think? That's about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as graceful as tractor pulling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I hope we get a good grade</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even our presentation was fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was "a one-page presentation."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He didn't give us any time limit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lately, XANA's getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more and more active.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're constantly on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry to interrupt, but would you tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who this XANA dude is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you are! We've already</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>started things up. Your turn, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's William doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have followed you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! What is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what do you guys do in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May I punch him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Try it if you dare!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Calm down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our priority now is the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After that, a simple return to the past,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and William won't remember a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't bet on that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I remember everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm great at holding a grudge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where's Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's unreachable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that's her secret!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A supercomputer hideout!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's incredible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why she didn't tell me anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to make do without her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't like this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can go and get her if you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope he won't rat on us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's not his style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, this is an emergency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's preparing dirty tricks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Aelita. Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita. Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here come your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is at the northern edge of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should be able to see its halo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come you're always right, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, Jeremy, we're on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relaxing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be like me. Remember my example, my grace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emergency, Yumi. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] XANA's launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dunbar, what is this gibberish?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You making fun of me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I mean, not this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To the principal's office, on the double!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because of him, I nearly drowned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me take him to the principal's office,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make sure he doesn't run away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good idea. Go on and take him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Miss Ishiyama.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's very responsible attitude</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on your part.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you could learn a lot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from her example, Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, you're right. I know that Yumi's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got a lot she can fill me in on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it. Kankrelats are behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'll take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many are there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A big gang of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks. Nothing like precision!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, guys, but I don't play favorites.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the same treatment for everyone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bomb beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, climb aboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go on, Aelita, hop off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ticking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Closing in on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! The Kankrelats will be overjoyed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We'll go separate ways</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and meet on the other side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on tight, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for some turbulence?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since when do Kankrelats</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have turbo engines?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Are you two okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still can't figure out what you do here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I can't figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why they agree to let you lend us a hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe, they trust me, not like--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's me, I'm--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're on the bridge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich are close</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! I came too late</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the party again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, is he one of your super heroes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I think he's more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a big super bad guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there's someone here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>possessed by XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so we might be a little late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell the others to hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That guy is your super enemy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An electric company worker?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's so lame. I was expecting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something more gory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I take it back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a super enemy electrical worker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go on, I'll take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was pretty sneaky to hit and run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you still there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but maybe not for long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This guy is a terror!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang in there, Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will get to the tower any minute now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] I'll take care of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, don't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Answer please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you've gotta get the job done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? I thought we'd do it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after tea time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've gotta tell you this, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is a very bad time, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] I can't swim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bravo, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, nice going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but it was a close call.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well, now you can launch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a return in time, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that "you know who" doesn't interfere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with us again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you know it's over?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The guy works for Explobat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If I'm not mistaken,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that company specializes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in building demolition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet he came here fully equipped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to blow your factory sky high.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you hear what William just said?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Relax, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When we return to the past, the explosives</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will disappear with William's memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, the Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Scyphozoa groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's got Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So launch a return to the past!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't know what might happen to Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we do it when she's in its clutches!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get back here now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll send you to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd, go find that bomb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Good luck, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You too, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Find that dumb bomb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so our factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't go up in smoke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think we should split up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, then let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] The Scyphozoa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has just released Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She's heading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy the Ice Sector</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to avoid that, at all costs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, consider it done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, almost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, I found it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's only one of the charges he set up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There must be a detonator somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to find it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you know this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My uncle worked in construction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On vacation, he used to show me how to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Family stories are all very moving,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we are kind of pressed here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Odd. So, where do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll find the detonator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, but that guy should know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, but he's out cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep searching. I'll try to wake him up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that blockade of Megatanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is closing in on the way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on Sleeping Beauty, wake up now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, it's your Prince Charming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man] What's going on? Where am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My dynamite!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are my explosives?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the factory, with a detonator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you recall anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Oh, my head!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful, Yumi, you don't have a lot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Look carefully.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To blow this factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where would you place the detonator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't think too straight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I guess I would put it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere high up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so the signal could reach all the charges.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, look for it somewhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over your head. Somewhere high up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It's okay Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got Aelita in my sights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think I found the detonator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Way up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't have any choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We found the detonator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to evacuate now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's gonna blow in a few seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't leave Yumi and Aelita on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Give me your belt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to defuse the detonator,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and shunt the electricity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How will you do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My uncle explained it to me once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Once?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Once is enough, if you're not too dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, get out of here. If it doesn't work,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be stupid for both of us to blow up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way. If you stay, I'll stay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That makes three of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another one and it's game over for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's gonna be the end</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Ice Sector as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ticking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, William defused the detonator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're saved.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Come on! Please?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear I won't tell anyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He deserves it. He could be a soldier.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he's proven he can help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let's vote. If everybody votes yes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William can officially become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a member of our club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad, William. There's one "no."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the big losers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was expecting this might happen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some guys just can't handle being jealous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That was uncool, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why'd you vote "no"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't look at me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not crazy about him, but he saved us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'd be a great Lyoko warrior.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't vote "no".</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if it wasn't you nor me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>either Jeremy or Aelita, then it was--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't think you can be trusted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>