<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's now or never.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[battle cry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Go on, Aelita, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd's on his way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mega tank approaching.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come and get me, you bowling ball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay. Aelita's in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>As usual, guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-great job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right. Another XANA attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>chalked up, another tower gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, get ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the return trip to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] And so, this equation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which you weren't able to solve,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-would have enabled you to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Class dismissed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don't forget your chemistry exercise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Actually, I prefer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's funny too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy] I got bonus points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for making level five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well guys, how was class today</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Ms. Hertz? Was it fun?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The same lesson as before the XANA attack,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so it was twice as boring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once, twice, it doesn't matter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll never be good in physics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, if it isn't Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[imitating Sissi] "Hello Ulrich dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we talk for a minute?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Ulrich dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we talk for a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, I'm not "Ulrich dear."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Second of all, I will not go to your room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to explain exercise B, page 52.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, how did you know that I...?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Jeremy snigger]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] A Sissi attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is as bad as a XANA attack,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and ten times more boring!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] For sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Anyone feel like sneaking out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and going into town for a while?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Count me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a heavy date with my pillow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm gonna work on my program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for materializing Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-One of these days, I'm gonna do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] And you, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna have an ice cream?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not tonight. I've gotta study.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm way behind thanks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to all these XANA attacks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ciao,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Yumi. See you tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Another exciting evening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy and Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ciao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to take a shower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It really relaxes you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yawning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me what your day was like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing special. Let's see now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had the embarrassment of my life</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in gym class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My shorts tore, you can guess where.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then I lost my pencil case in the library.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I had a fight with Marcy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's what my day was like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No, what I mean, is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you feel you've already had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same exact day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah, but that's normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget, we had the same French,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>English and Physics class twice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and on Lyoko, it was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Yoo hoo, it's us" for the seventh time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Yoo hoo, it's us?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I call our game plan;</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the one we use to help Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to reach the tower safe and sound.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why all these questions, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No reason. I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm fed up with all this: school, Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back to school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back to Lyoko and this is XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fifth attack in a week.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm also fed up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with what's happening to Yumi and me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once in a while, I get the feeling that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she doesn't really like me...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she doesn't have any feelings for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water dripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hi Emily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello, Ulrich. I'm looking for Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you seen him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Emily] That's okay. Good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich to self] I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does she have a thing for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Ulrich, if you're gonna sleepwalk,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do it in your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Hi, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Emily's looking for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[determined]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi to self] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's he doing with Emily?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They sure don't look bored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello. What kind of a game does</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he think he's playing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's just talking to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What, are you, jealous?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Me, jealous of Emily?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta be kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, she's a year older than him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess what? You are also</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a year older than him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you just forgot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah well, it's not the same thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm Ulrich's girlfriend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters] I mean I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm his good friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's been kind of down in the dumps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So if he wants to talk to another girl,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't make a big deal out of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting] Who says that I am?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This machine's gonna drive me bananas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] That's double big news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich without Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich with Emily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emily? How dare she!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The nerve of her going after him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Yumi's out of the picture,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm next on the list!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's not taking it too well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Neither are you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shut up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just got a really great idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's bound to make Ulrich all mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quite a romance going on there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two months already. That's not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, I thought you knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Doesn't Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell you everything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, you two are so close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've decided to give up on him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to forget him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, if I were you, I would do the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not me, Sissi, so save your advice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't mind! What a pest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] You didn't know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Emily laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Sissi, do you mind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>explaining your strategy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's launched another attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Are you feeling pulsations?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, in the desert</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>region. They're really strong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so active as he is now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry guys, you've gotta go back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and right away too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, as they say, when you gotta go,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you gotta go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[busy phone signal]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich has shut off his cell phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, he's too busy with Emily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on, I'll go and get him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi, no. Wait...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Emily] Wanna go for a walk, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] It's nice to relax...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come here for a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll be right back, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Emily nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate to disturb you, Romeo,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Jeremy's been trying to reach you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's just woken up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA, again? Go on, I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean, go on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool it, huh, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll cool it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me what's with you and her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like her. We get along really well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand the problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Unless that bothers you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bothers me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's just that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angrily] that you could've told me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about it! Like a buddy, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I get it. You think of us as buddies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wondered what you thought of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing] That's right, a couple of pals,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing more, and besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's the way you want it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not like Emily, huh? Oh, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, what do I really mean</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And be honest, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me be honest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and Emily have been together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for two months without a word,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you tell me to be honest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did you get that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emily and I are not...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not gonna defend myself to you. </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ciao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing and angrily] Yeah, right,</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ciao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all you can think of to say!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Jeremy. Yeah, I told him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's on his way there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me too, yeah. I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that act two is over,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the final act is all mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] All yours? But what about Emily?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For a pro like me, Emily's no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In exactly thirty seconds,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich will be in my arms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich, dear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to tell you something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can't wait any longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, "dear," under normal conditions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would take the time to tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go fly a kite,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but this time, I'll just ignore you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb laughing] Your 30 seconds are up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No, everything's quiet here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No short circuits,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no giant bug invasion,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no earthquakes. How about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm almost at the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but no monsters have appeared yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not for the pulsations, there's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no other sign that XANA's woken up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if this isn't a new tactic of his.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if the attack is aimed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at us directly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For example, this argument</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between Yumi and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suppose that XANA is just using Emily</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to mess with our heads?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got a better idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's using</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your ridiculous theories to distract us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just trying to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give us a break, Odd, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay out of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, stay calm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think one of you should do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little reconnaissance on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, who wants to be first?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't all of you answer at once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Send Ulrich. He needs to be entertained.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'd love to go to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ladies first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get her out of our hair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Look, I'm tired of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this quarreling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita needs us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's what I call an emergency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So head for the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All three of you are going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Help is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I better warn you, Yumi and Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are a bit, well, you might say, buggy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've been fighting again, don't they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guessed it, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna transfer you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the desert region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget you have to protect Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all three of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi. Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was a bug at the moment of transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are they...?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Everyone is accounted for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Safe, sound and ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno what it was. I'll run a scan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll see what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What is this mess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think the super calculator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has been infected with a virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that's the XANA attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's crazy. Why would XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>want to infect himself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you never know what XANA's got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in his head until it's done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless he's using it to modify a program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he doesn't have access to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But which one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't know, but it looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he wants to change the rules on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I've got a funny feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to take a closer look into this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] There has to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a deactivated tower not far from you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[intermittent digital buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you're not gonna kill each other</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I leave you two alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whiffle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy. Okay, I'm here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have access to the transfer program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is very strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Usually, the program doesn't include</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any of XANA's creatures. It's really weird</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] You go. You're the closest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I understand, Jeremy. It's a trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's sabotaged</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the devirtualization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, watch out for lasers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This monster can kill you for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can prove fatal to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't be devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or you'll disappear forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's lost fifty life points already!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Calm down, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's still here with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He just got hit by a laser.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That means he's only got...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita takes the same risks all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing's changed for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to be more careful, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] One thing is sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's really trapped us, and we'd better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not make a mistake this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll make the fight more exciting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to deactivate the tower fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before XANA has a chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to concentrate all his strength on...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the safest solution.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Hurry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but watch out for monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meanwhile, I'll try to get rid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Listen XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you think you can impress me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your cheap two bit virus,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you are mistaken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm never gonna get it to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has completely wrecked the circuits.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one possible solution:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>work directly on the hardware.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy to self] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's gotta be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an access here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I gotta do is find it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must be in the super calculator room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy to self] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, no way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On this floor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everything's locked up tight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA, you're even more evil</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than I thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy to self] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The access bays.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I adjust the winch,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should be get down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower! It's there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts] You don't scare me, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've just gotta replace the circuits</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you messed up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you'll fail again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like the other times.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we try to get through all this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're done for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just have to hang on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until Aelita enters the code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's "yoo hoo, it's us" time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you take the crab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and I will take on the mega tanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita, go on. Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters] Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hm. Be careful, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You too, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelps] Keep rolling. Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yelps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouting] Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were just...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[winch whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[winch whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yumi, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's okay. I got you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[romantic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewinding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Actually, I prefer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's funny, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy] I got bonus points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for making level five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quite a romance, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two months already, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Two months? That long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There's Yumi. So long now, Emily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Emily] Ain't love grand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, I was waiting for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So was I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two months is a pretty long time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Sissi was here to keep me company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humph]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bunch of creeps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about what happened on Lyoko...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, what nearly happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that you mention it...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uhm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather you didn't talk about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it to Odd or Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least, not right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I agree. Not a word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both giggle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget we've got Ms. Hertz's class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go to one more time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it wasn't all that boring on Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was it, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I learned something too...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something super important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>