<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Ants are social insects,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like termites or like bees.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A single individual is incapable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of any personal initiative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of the decisions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are made by the colony.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ants receive a few simple orders,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such as "search for food,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"mark the path leading to the food",</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and "follow a marked path."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As a result, we might have the impression</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that each ant is rather clever,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when in fact, this has more to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a collective intelligence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean that an army of Sissis</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could be intelligent?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs] I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Very funny. Shut up, birdbrain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[class laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Settle down please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I was saying, thanks to their numbers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they manage to accomplish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some fairly difficult tasks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such as finding food or</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>defending themselves against an attacker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It would seem that ants even wage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>full-scale wars between colonies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about killer ants? Do they exist?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yes, maybe in movies, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[class laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But there are, in fact, "army ants,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that destroy everything in their path.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's true</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you'd best stay out of their way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, do any of those filthy bugs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>live around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, fortunately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They live in South America.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Down there, the phenomenon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is called "Marabounta."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad I live</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a country where there's no danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Yeah, well, that only really…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[indistinct conversation]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Saturday's my favorite day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No school in the afternoon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I like Sundays better!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] No school at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You seem worried, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's on your mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper's notes, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last night, I decoded a really interesting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>part on a multi-agent system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a computer application</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which follows the principle of an anthill!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happens is--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Mrs. Hertz already</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bored us to tears with all that ant stuff!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you start now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Seriously! This time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might have found a way to weaken XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's meet up at the factory after lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, normally I'd love to, but I have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to finish my Italian homework!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nervously] No, I have to practice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a skateboard competition!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, I've got swimming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after school. Bye, bye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you doing anything later on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah, I've gotta be somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh yeah? Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The swimming pool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Well, since everyone else</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has better things to do…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll just deal with it myself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knuckles cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles to self]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[high pitched groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't that Ulrich Stern about to dive?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[board rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both boys grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Out of the way! Let me through!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Is he okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is he breathing? Is he hurt?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, call someone! He looks like he…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He needs mouth-to-mouth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get out of the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl 2] Is he breathing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl 3] I don't know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Let me through!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a first-aid certificate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim inhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There you go! Good thing I was here, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Now for the moment of truth!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything seems to be working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer prototype!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! Franz Hopper, you're a genius!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so am I!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA and his monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>better watch out now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something amazing to show you guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you meet me at the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay! Soon as possible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! And don't forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go and pick up Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's called</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a meeting at the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You coming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not in the mood. I'd rather be by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If you don't come, he'll get mad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, suit yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Both of you stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Both of us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and your bad mood!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch mechanism whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you are! But where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's sulking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what his problem is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's this program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Marabounta!</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>My own creation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what does it do, exactly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a multi-agent system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that functions according</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the same principle as an anthill.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But instead of ants,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have these little spheres,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whose mission is to search out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destroy XANA's monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get it! While the monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are being wiped out by your ants,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA leaves us alone on Lyoko. Is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You guessed it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, that's great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] But what happens if there's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a real bug in the program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember Franz Hopper was a genius!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right! What do you say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we go to Lyoko to check it out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If this thing really works,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing can happen to us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You read my mind, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go to the scanner room. I'll transfer you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If there's the slightest problem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll pull the plug! Promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You guys are South</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Marabounta.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take the path to your right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but you'll have to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't have enough machine resources</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring them up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And watch out for the bad guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA may have his hands full,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you never know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Roger, general!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A Krab at two o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Follow it. It's headed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the right direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you been crazy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about Ulrich for a long time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about Yumi for a long time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You've only been here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a few months.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you believe in destiny</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a capital "D"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two people who have never met,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but who are made for each other?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm not really into fairytales</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or cheap magazine-style romance stories.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had a crush on Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since elementary school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to go out with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's all there is to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it weren't for that stuck-up Yumi, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it weren't for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that big shot Ulrich, I'd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both chuckle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shall we go? I'm getting cold!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Target dead ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? I've got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can see the Marabounta.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well? What's it like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Aelita gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty scary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never thought I'd say it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I really feel sorry for XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll uplink you a visual, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's working even better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than I thought it would!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If you want my opinion, Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've invented a nasty piece of work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I've seen enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to come in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, okay, Aelita. I'll bring you back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head south-west.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a tower nearby.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd! Aelita! What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd! Say something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Your Marabounta seems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have it in for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is no time for jokes! I programmed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack XANA's monsters only!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, could you also program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some eyeglasses for it then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This can't be right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you do something special?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, except for firing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a few Laser arrows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That wasn't the smartest thing to do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, Odd didn't have a choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Marabounta was coming after me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can that be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Jeremy, idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's my fault!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the virus implanted in Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Marabounta thinks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's one of XANA's monsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Great! Nice work, Frankenstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought we had nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I was wrong!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, head for the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll kill the program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bleeping and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. Oh! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Whenever you're ready, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't deactivate the program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that the Marabounta</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't want to die!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Marabounta has become autonomous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll submerge everything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and everyone in its path!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll brief Yumi and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing? Will you pick up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! That guy can really pick</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the right day to sit and sulk!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean a "Chattanooga"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Marabounta!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't explain now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just get here ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Aelita are in big trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's at school, but I can't reach him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what's going on with him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I do. I'll get him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll be right over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we've lost your monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but now we're kind of lost ourselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… Uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take off in the direction…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Due West! The Marabounta</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hasn't hit that sector yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll find a way to stop it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't blow it! I don't want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to end up as chewing-gum!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was sure I'd find you here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I need is for everybody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to leave me alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, if you want to make a fool</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of yourself in front of everyone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't blame me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one asked you to spy on me at the pool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Spy on you? You've got to be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just happened to be there, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah. Right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What an incredible coincidence!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyways, do you mind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shelving your ego for a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Aelita need us on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Marabounta got here first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The Tower's unreachable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This won't take me long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll find a way to stop it, I promise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Ulrich and Yumi are on their way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least… I hope they are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopper! Help me out a little!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] If this goes on any</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>longer, all of Lyoko will be destroyed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's sending a monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That Krab just sacrificed itself for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA knows that he can't let Aelita die.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He needs her memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, what's the matter with them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're protecting me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's right. Use them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as allies to defeat the Marabounta.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ah! At last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alone with his pride.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna tell me what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time! Go straight there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hang in there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The cavalry's coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beam zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Marabounta's the one to go after!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is that horrible thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] One of Jeremy's bright ideas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Luckily, XANA is here to give us a hand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The world has turned upside down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi. I came to see how you were.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right. When you have a good chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to humiliate the competition</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you might as well go for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did I miss something here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're my problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'd be too easy, Ulrich. Let me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell you what's wrong around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My being around Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>forces you to ask yourself a question.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A tough question that you can't answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here's a piece of friendly advice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and talk to Yumi! From the heart!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or else, one day, I will!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then, I really will be your problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How you doing, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really the biggest loser</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ever to walk on the face of the Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You couldn't have known</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that my virus would be a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your virus. Virus! What if…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[excited]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That ought to work!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[substance gurgling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever you do, don't let it make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any headway. It'll attack from the rear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a really good combat general, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It takes strategy, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only thing stupider</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than a Blok, is two Bloks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, move it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things are getting a bit out of hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, I'm doing my best, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I think I've found a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy the Marabounta.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I inserted a code for a</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>deadly virus in one of your arrows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you hit a sphere with it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the whole colony will be infected, but--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wait! It'll only work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you hit the first sphere,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the one I transferred to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that created all the others!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's at the heart of the Marabounta.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! So how am I supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to reach the heart of the Marabounta?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On a camel's back?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Krab huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's the only way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Charge!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, would you mind telling me how</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find the right sphere in all this mess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll guide you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're almost there, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give you the exact location</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the first sphere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's okay. I think I've found it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You've only got one shot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser arrow blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Ulrich gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't buy it, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's right. The Marabounta is gone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but XANA and his monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are still our worst enemy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wants your memory at all cost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Next time you want to play</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at being a mad scientist,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>clue us in a little more first, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I really tried to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you all had better things to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you're right, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'Cause this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was a big zero from start to finish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You found a way out of it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what counts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if it isn't the whole crew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if it isn't the brainless frog face.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs sarcastically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You crack me up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way Ulrich, are you feeling better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after what happened at the pool?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Cool it, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] So, what happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the pool, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, out with it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Nothing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>