<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ T</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>oday, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>HARD LUCK</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd mumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, hey, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you're trying to clean up the room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd better find another system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There! That's what I was looking for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. It's not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't wanna be late for breakfast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you can steal an extra croissant?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well yeah, but also to steal Azra's heart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are my shoes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Uh, you just have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to follow the stink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're pretty wound up today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure this morning is the best time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah. She borrowed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my pencil sharpener yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's a sure sign</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she's totally crazy about me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So today's the day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Sorry about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means seven years bad luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, are you superstitious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding? No, not a chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get real, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four leaf clovers, rabbits' feet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>horse shoes are for old ladies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! In fact, I can feel it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Today is gonna be my lucky day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you think it's really funny</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>filling my shoes with cottage cheese, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just earned yourself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>eight hours of detention!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it wasn't me, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if it wasn't you, then who was it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm not a snitch Jim, but you might</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wanna check out Nicolas and Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the tip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's gonna cost you four hours of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>detention for selling out your classmates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you believe that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you, Odd. Seven years bad luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no such thing as bad luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Odd, but I guess you're out of luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not even one croissant left, Rosa?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What am I supposed to eat?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about some dry toast?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, give me some hot chocolate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to drown my sorrows in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do that, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The machine is on the blink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It never happened before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in all the years I've been working here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tea and dry toast, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you, sick?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But after I choke this down, I will be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Okay everyone, here's the plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to return to the military base</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destroy XANA's Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once and for all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it should be too complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is as long as XANA doesn't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything new up his sleeve.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Azra!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's have breakfast together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you can start drinking hot chocolate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through your nose again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, no. And besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the machine is busted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I meant is, uh,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna learn to speak Turkish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe you can give me lessons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you mean it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Sure I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, uh, we can discuss it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great idea, Azra. I can't wait to start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, why did you tell Jim on me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a snitch, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not only that, but it was your idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to put the cottage cheese in his sneakers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which was incredibly funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. Yeah, Odd, you just wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna get even with you for that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>someday. You'll see, you traitor!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't blame Herb. </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Budala</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Brouhaha"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dork! That's the word for "numbskull"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Odd, I guess you've just had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your first Turkish lesson!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Walking under a ladder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is like asking for bad luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In Japan, people avoid anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do with the number four,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it sounds just like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the word for "death."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you know that the word</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"rabbit" is bad luck for sailors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So is spilling salt when you're on a ship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I tell you that the only thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that'll bring you bad luck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is talking to an Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about dumb superstition,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cause all you'll get you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is being laughed at!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think you're smart,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'll bet by the end of the day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll be crossing streets</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to avoid black cats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Odd and Yumi, you guys ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for teleportation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then here we go. Energize Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energize Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Jeremy, we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a slight problem. Where's Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's still in his Navskid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What did I do wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't get it either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The teleportation failed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the first time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess it's bad luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, save your dumb jokes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or you'll have the bad luck of being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>forced to eat ten pounds of dry toast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What do we do now, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you want me to go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, you've got plenty to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dealing with the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Superscan has just picked up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an activated tower. I'll send Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just say when.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Energize Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hey, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where's Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Stuck on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Disappointed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No. I'm glad in fact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's really bad luck today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch your step.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If a tower's been activated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can be sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA's planning to counter attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about giving us the coordinates,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that we can go and deactivate it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Due west</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from you present position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-As deserted as ever, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's good news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here are your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, isn't Aelita getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the overboard with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Uh, you know Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>seeing how your day's been going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up to now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather you guys traveled separately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are all such lame-os!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tell you everything's cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you see that, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea. I'll check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys get going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Freight elevator over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll take us downstairs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Yumi. I never asked you this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you like fighting the least of all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Kankrelats. I really hate fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against big bugs! Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I hate most are Megatanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How about the--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The Kankrelats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know. You said that already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I mean over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kankrelats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish XANA had sent us a few Krabs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have preferred Hornets.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, do you read us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah. We just found out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why XANA activated a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's teleporting Kankrelats our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Yumi and Ulrich have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some visitors at the base.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You have to deactivate the tower fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] We're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can see a canyon in the distance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll check the area</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see if the tower is there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower is in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the center of the canyon. Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. You see that? Everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Superstition's for lame-os. I told--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Uh, you were saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Piece of cake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] The coast is clear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But not in back of us! Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's try to buy some time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Any news. It's getting rough here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there. Aelita and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are almost at the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Let's do our thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who said I was jinxed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You lost half your life points just now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's that stupid bug again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What… What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That'll teach you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to zap my friend down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm heading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita. Make it fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Ulrich have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got a huge, huge bug problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And what about the program bug.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know what's causing it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might be a virus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or some "made in XANA" thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whatever it is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're not having any luck with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no such thing as luck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of a place is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That's exactly what I said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the first time we came here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some sort of factory assembly line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but what do they assemble here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We might find that out in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like a control terminal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Check it out, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any info on XANA's tactics</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can come in handy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on with the tower, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita should be deactivating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any minute now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not going to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get off that easily my friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Guess I've gotta go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the rest of the way on foot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw it. The bug seems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be having an effect on you too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better deactivate the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fast before you disappear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm going as fast as I can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I read you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita can't deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower just yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's been affected by Odd's bug too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's not my bug, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just my name for it until</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we figure out exactly what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It better be, because I've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing to do with this mess, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just a question of chance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you say, "chance"? What do ya know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not becoming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>superstitious, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] I figured it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm? Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think it's an assembly line</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for mother boards and electronic implants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Electronic implants? But for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To control those spiders, for example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mean those cybernetic creatures</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the jungle lab?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. Makes sense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the big question is what XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is planning to do with all of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wish I knew the answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess you're just like Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not your lucky day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anytime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just located the Supercalculator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the southernmost end of the room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What about your end?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the latest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William just showed up on the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not just a friendly visit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, we're coming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Supercalculator room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Down there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The Supercalculator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will have to wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to solve the William problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to. Got any suggestions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We haven't any choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One of you has to be teleported back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from deactivating the Skid tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ok. What do we do, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want me to go, or you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can always play for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Paper, scissors, rock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scissors cut paper, don't they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready, William. We're good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy. I'm the one who's going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De-energize Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, wake up! William's coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm glad to see you too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, wow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, the Supercalculator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is infested with Kankrelats over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's holding Aelita up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's just about ready to enter the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I finally got here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great. Don't waste any time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Aelita just got devirtualized!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're on your own</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Kankrelats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I know I'm good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there are seven of these creeps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could go down on this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that'll blow the whole mission!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to hold out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until Yumi's finished her combat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If she beats William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she can come back and give you some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts in frustration]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was great, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready for another teleportation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich needs your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Uh, no, hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm all bugged up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe how jinxed we are today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this dumb bug anyhow?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That's exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I'm about to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's a Mandelbug!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A bug in the virtualization software.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the causes are so complex</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that its behaviour seems totally chaotic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And with no way to tell if the behaviour</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is really chaotic or only seems to be,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's impossible to differentiate it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a "Bohrbug" or a "Heisenbug."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Couldn't be any more clearer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's an extremely unusual problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Jeremy doesn't know how to fix it yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Why didn't you say so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, great! That's all we needed now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you want some good news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry, I don't have any.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To make a long story short,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're still on your own,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower's still activated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you're probably gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get the bug that I can't fix.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No. You've gotta work fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because XANA also sent in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some Tarantulas to blow up the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to rumble, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich just knocked off three of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how did he do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's only got two sabers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible! There goes another one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's on a lucky streak today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, get rid of the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry, you're fading fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The Replika's disappearing too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about the Skid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, no sweat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I made a little remote control piloting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>program for emergencies like this one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another Replika bites the dust! Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the man today, guys, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Luck, buddy, that's what I think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew you'd say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What'd you do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does it look like? I slipped.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess I can't deny it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since I broke that mirror,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been jinxed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Odd. Jinxes don't exist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Luck does, but it changes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, the only question is when.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha ha! Lady luck might</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be smiling at me already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tada! Azra's mobile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, she left it behind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on purpose just so I would find it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure I am. Now I've just gotta</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wait for her to call me to get it back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I'd like to get my cell phone back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet me under the arches right away."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you guys later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a date with Cupid!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great. Tell Cupid we said hi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's already good. So long!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd whistles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[someone whistles back]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Azra?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's Jim Morales.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sorry Jim, but you see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm waiting to meet somebody,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so if you don't mind…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So it was you who found my cell phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, you mean it's yours?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right. Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because, uh… I mean, uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean it's not your style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like pink. You got a problem with that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at the color that you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wear all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but pink with sparkles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a heart charm on it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that a bit too much?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Probably.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>