<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>WILLIAM RETURNS</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hear you very well, Mr. Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you trying to say that your son,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, has gone overseas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stay with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that he won't be attending classes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here until you bring him home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yes, that's correct, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see, but it's quite surprising</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he would leave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without even bothering</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell any of us here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It was a very sudden decision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how youngsters can be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at this age.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy in adult voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure your own daughter Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is capable of doing the same thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's very possible, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I didn't realize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you knew my daughter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and by her nickname as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Uh, that is… Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>actually, I don't really know her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>obviously, but well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you see, William talks so much</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's always Sissi this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Sissi that, and so it's almost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if I really did know her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, I didn't know that William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was such a close friend of Elisabeth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well, Sissi's a role model</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for William, an example.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And how could it be otherwise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, considering the sort</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of father that she has.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Mr. Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was delighted to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this little chat with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and please give William my best regards,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and tell him that we hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll return to school very soon,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that he'll always be welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I will tell him. Goodbye, Mr. Delmas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and many thanks for your understanding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're very welcome, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess I make a good grown up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but now all we have to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is find William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better get back to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It worked with the principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but what'll happen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when William's real parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>want to see their son?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's right, and I'm not so sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that voice synthesizer of yours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna do the trick, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who knows? Maybe by then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll have localized William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you gonna do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to the data we got from my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before he disappeared into the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and I have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just about recreated Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're recreating Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We may even be ready by tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and I have worked on it every night</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the last week.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, so that's why you look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a couple of zombies, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought that you looked like wrecks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause you were partying all night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was getting jealous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi, Milly. Hi, Tamiya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't mind if we sat here with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are they still sulking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did sneak out the bathroom window</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of an interview.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For ace reporters like them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that is pretty insulting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Being mad at me isn't as bad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as their being really mad at each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They had a massive argument</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the newspaper, I think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean the Kadic News</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has folded for good?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's the best news I've heard in a--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, it's not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How am I gonna know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's going out with who now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to console myself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by watching Jim dancing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to old disco music. He really…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, personally,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of all the season of the year,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like spring the best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like summer best,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it's nice and warm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet, huh? I can't hear anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you can't hear anything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we should speak louder, shouldn't we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dork! It's not you I wanna listen to!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, don't tell me you've been watching,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Paco The King Of Disco</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't help myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever I'm in a bad mood,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I put the film on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno why he's so ashamed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he used to be an actor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Most probably because the film was a flop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't see what makes their conversation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more interesting than ours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, me neither.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I do, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanted to see me, huh, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's she doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I was gonna say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I thought it was me you wanted to see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] Same here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, at least you agree on that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not much,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's a pretty good start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's all thanks to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which is why for the good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Kadic News,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've decided to become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the editor-in-chief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You've decided what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] Who do you think you are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The daughter of the principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the only person who can stop you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from printing that poor excuse for a paper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're so proud of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're not a real journalist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't even know the meaning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the word "scoop."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wrong again, little ones. A scoop, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about an enormous scoop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to be a party pooper,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there doesn't seem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be very much happening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The data that my father transmitted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wasn't enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess we must've been really crazy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to think that we could recreate Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey wait, look at that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's incredible! It worked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Jeremy, you guys are gods.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, almost but not quite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, all we've been able to recreate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is Sector Five of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've still got to work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to create the other sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we should be able to do that soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, but it can wait a night or two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys deserve a good night's sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Yumi's right, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to be needing every bit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of our strength to look for William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll start tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yeah, well, all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do you guys wanna watch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Paco The King of Disco</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It'll take your mind off things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock releasing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[brushing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A newspaper without much news?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me see that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You promised not to tell anyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And to think I actually trusted you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, I didn't give your secret away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must think I'm an imbecile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Do you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what Jim's gonna do to me for this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but I can't wait to find out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm sure that my readers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are dying to know, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Sissi, since when have you been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>involved with the Kadic News?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since I made myself editor-in-chief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, and since you're all together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as usual,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to ask Yumi a few questions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the next issue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you two waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, we're rolling!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our readers would really like to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how you and William are getting along.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, William? Me and William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno what you're talking about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you rather I asked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same question to William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He may not be as shy as you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As a matter of fact, where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The last time I saw him was a week ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gone abroad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His father called your father to tell him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh? How come you know that, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I, uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Are you talking about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I can remember is being virtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and being captured by the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a blank after that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is until this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I woke up in the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you doing, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're hurting me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just checking to make sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're not one of XANA's ghosts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No danger of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There isn't any activated tower on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William couldn't have been sent by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you can stop pinching me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyhow, you're just in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a quiz in math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Timing, huh? I haven't studied at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So? Since when have you ever studied?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both chuckle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The next problem is explaining</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's sudden return to Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you said it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I don't get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is why when Lyoko disappeared,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William didn't fall into the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to know how he managed to escape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gentle knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Hi Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not disturbing you, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We would really like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do a feature story on you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our next issue. It's true</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we don't know a lot about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you really Odd's cousin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And well, is it really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that cold in Canada?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why did you suddenly come here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of the year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our readers are interested.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you let her study in peace, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get going, all three of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've annoyed her enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, William, you came back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were overseas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get going, I said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] OK, OK, we're outta here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have been Sissi's next victim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and that's even worse than--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-…than becoming a prisoner of XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that what you're saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William only came back because of Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's a scoop, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to tell the news to Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see what he has to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There's no reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for him to know before our readers do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once we've printed it, then</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll ask Jeremy what he thinks of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William came to Aelita's room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure he did?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We sure are. We were there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, well, I think that… I know why!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna help him catch up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on what he missed in math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've gotta go now and take a shower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, you want a scoop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A real one this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK, here, I quit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So do I, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you couldn't possible do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Wanna bet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, there's something weird</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going on with William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Why? What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He left for the factory with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I picked up the signals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of their cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm pretty sure this is XANA's doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What makes you think that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just a hunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's strange</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he escaped the Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Meet you at the factory, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You get Yumi, and I'll clue Odd in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He's not with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd? No. As a matter of fact,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno where he is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Keep trying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure you can do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot better that that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[disco music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You remember the scene?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You told me that you watched</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the film a dozen times, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, Jim, I swear it's not my fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't tell anybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll continue</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until you know the steps by heart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless you'd like me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to change your class instead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of your pals will be so sorry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to have you with them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK, OK, I get the picture, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd was right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This film is incredibly funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[disco music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just when I was trying to chill out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible to reach Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've already tried three times.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet he's living it up somewhere,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just when we need him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can see that. They're in Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't like that at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Ulrich, head for the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll keep trying to reach Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We really need him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[disco music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's better, much better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a few more hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you'll be all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, where can Odd be, I wonder?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I'm ready, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, I'll launch the procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you've got to take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the corridor right in front of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there a key I've gotta trip?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. When we recreated Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-we got rid of that procedure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Step on it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while they're not too far away, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once you're in the core zone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll guide you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, where are you taking me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, having fun without inviting us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure have changed, haven't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be careful, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's sent some Creepers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super smoke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I thought this was gonna be easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Be very careful, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's coming after you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What's the matter with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower in Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hasn't been activated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it seems that William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is under the control of XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better get out of there fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanner room, fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Aelita really need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've been trying to reach him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno where he is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[airlock seals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[disco music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't take anymore of this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>honestly, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that, my friend,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is what you should've thought about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before talking to the press.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There he is! I told you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I recognized the music!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[music stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you doing up at this hour?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girls giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we just watched your disco film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's incredible, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean you liked it that much?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl] It's a masterpiece!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Would you give us your autograph?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yeah, why sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd be happy to, if that's what you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] To Lakeisha, is that right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] No, William! Listen to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich, better make it snappy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's taking Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>straight to the dome area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm doing my best.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creepers groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Obviously, my best isn't good enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yee-ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you could use some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guessed right. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword slices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On three, we attack. One… Two… Three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooms]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword slices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't get here too late, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What were you doing, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was taking a disco dancing class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going on a little trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Funky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[airlock seals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Manta!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's he trying to do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What's going on, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> It looks as if William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wants out of Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] But I thought you hadn't managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to create any other sectors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what makes it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so hard to understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the end of Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's nothing except…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Digital Sea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If he jumps into it with Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she'll be devirtualized for good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just like her father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll do all we can to stop him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But for that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're gonna need our vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. I'll see that you get them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in no time flat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicles zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better watch out. There are mines.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mines exploding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You okay, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Move it, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They just went into the tunnel!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Not a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Yumi, you have to stop William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from jumping into the Digital Sea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, Jeremy. I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate to cut in, William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but Aelita's always preferred</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the company of real gentlemen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but I hate being tailgated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosive splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think William's gone forever?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I think he just went back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to his new master…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why would William want to drag me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the Digital Sea? I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I think it's part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of XANA's new strategy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so, we've got to be very careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William could come back at anytime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now we have to think up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another excuse for his absence,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Delmas might not buy it this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya and Milly] Hello, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They don't hate you now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess they found someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they can hate even more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kinda like us and William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[children chanting] Paco!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right on, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's incredible. Jim's become a real star.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's mainly thanks to you, right, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[disco music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The guy's great. Incredible presence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A real super star.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>