<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give, all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE TRAP</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Aelita, are you connected?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy. Did you have a good day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing special.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which classes do you have tomorrow?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, we've got physics</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and chemistry with Ms. Hertz</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a math exam with Ms. Mayer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you do during an exam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You show what you know in writing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What a strange idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Lights out now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not really. We're not like you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your memory and ours aren't the same,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because yours is, well, infinite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our brains have limited memory capacity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't store as much data as you can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In other words, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>compared to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our hard disk comes up short.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you sleeping yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be in trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I stay connected. I'm sorry, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but... I've gotta go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't wanna have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to introduce you to Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll connect at noon tomorrow,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>universal time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[owls hooting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[the bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unlocking creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something wrong, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No. I finished, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students murmur] What? Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mutters] Yes, you have.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good job. It's excellent work, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All the rest, keep working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! Her birthday is today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[murmuring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Mayer] You may go, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispering] Thanks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could've stayed and helped me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I almost forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we met exactly a year ago today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd whispers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Aelita's birthday today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I forgot about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind your own business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Wow, a year since we met Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And I still haven't managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to materialize her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sips]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, but we managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to protect her from XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if we use our lunch hour</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to prepare a surprise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She'd like that, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! Let's go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go ahead. I promised Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd stop by after class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] We'll meet you there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[muttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I thought they would never leave.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your friends stick to you like glue, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not as much as you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to talk to you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we have lunch together? Just us two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry, Yumi's waiting for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi to self]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> It's always Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time he dumped her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[circuits flowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sliding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to find a present for Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why don't you program a digital cake?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Power cut, I guess. Let's check out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the fuses in the control room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Great idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what he sees in her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The coast is clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot what this place looked like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's really cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A hunk of junk to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll beat you to the elevator! [giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting] We'll see!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi laughing] I won.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's nice, they sent it back down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd must be in the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Nice little hiding place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should ask you that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanna know. Are Jeremy and Odd waiting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or is this your love nest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is none of your business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Why don't you leave?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shrugs] What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't wanna open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] It won't start off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know. It's blocked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elevator hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator rumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[elevator creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[they both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Better check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a trap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich! Are you okay? Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can't seem to move my arm. And you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I was lucky. I'm okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But not her. She's out cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll call Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hissing and buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you alright?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] In the elevator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was the noise we heard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] We're stuck in the machine room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're on our own, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta go back up. Get to the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With just one arm, impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, we can't leave Sissi alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, please, answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning] I just remembered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a slight fear of heights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on tight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don't look down. You can do it, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened? I can't...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The elevator broke down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're stuck in the shaft.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'm so cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll be out of here soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I think I broke my arm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let me have a look at it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water dripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've gotta get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No kidding, genius!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me go, you horrible...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drilling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Up here, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad this isn't Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least I have superpowers there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know Aelita's also in danger,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she'll need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do we reach the lab?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Via the boiler room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clunk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you alright?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Heading for the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's say I'm trying to cope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Look at the boiler.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's really after us this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's on her way to the lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>climbing up the shaft.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't trust that thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready for a hundred yard dash?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm better in math than gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Math won't help you now. Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting] Go! Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[murmurs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water dripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's that noise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't move. Wait... there. Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a real good nurse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not just someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who sticks to you like glue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[burbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita giggles] Bye, bye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Odd! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! Jeremy! Please, answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was so scared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We pushed the boiler hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It couldn't take it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[burbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich moaning] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is useless!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko Connection. Please wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[burbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is absolutely impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I launched a scan for the position</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I understand, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How is Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on. We're off to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, good luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The water rises,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich can't swim with a broken arm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't contact Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[burbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I've got the coordinates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I gotta...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, how are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tried to contact you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for such a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We had a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA set a trap for us in the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich is in danger. Yumi and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are going to Lyoko. We gotta hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in front of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dreamed of being alone with you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for so long!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But this isn't what I had in mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear if we get out of here alive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be nicer to you in the future.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy and the others</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will call for help, won't they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you can call it that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They better hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, we'll drown</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before you can be nicer to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi and Odd, we're ready to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Off to the desert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Yumi are transferring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on for a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Jeremy. It's getting tough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can hardly touch bottom!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay now, back to the virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Yumi gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] You missed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, it's time. Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll force our way through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run behind us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We gotta make it to the tower. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts] Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] Take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forty life points in two shots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're losing life points too quickly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting] Don't worry, I'll make it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Watch out on your left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your point loss is too high,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, 80. Yumi, just ten.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Clear the passage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Ulrich, do you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bubbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[burbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on? I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's something from our world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone] Happy birthday, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We're celebrating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's one year ago that we met you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I supposed to do something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Save me cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] One-track mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't listen to that glutton.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Speak for yourself, four eyes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Calm down, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a bunch of loonies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They celebrate their computer's birthday!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I think it's a trendy thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Buy a cake for tomorrow, to celebrate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the birthday of my makeup kit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[they both shrug]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're eating all the cake. Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm hungry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So is everybody else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hand it over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>