<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give, all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE ROBOTS</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I'm sure you've noticed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this sheet of titanium</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is much stronger than steel,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is why it is used by NASA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for constructing its space shuttles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should've used it for your robot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] I'm afraid this alloy would</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be a bit out of your budget range, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But since your friend</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>brought up the subject, let me remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the robot competition is scheduled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope you've all finished your models.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is yours ready, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And you, Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come and see my masterpiece</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after school, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machinery whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let me see it, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm waiting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... Well... [sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] Tada!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas and Sissi scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is that horror?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's our team's robot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Iron Sissi."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How dare you name</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that hideous monster after me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's a tribute to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides, it may be ugly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but watch how it works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, Herb! Herb, do something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] A couple of adjustments,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it'll be just fine [chuckles].</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It better be. If not, Jeremy and his pals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are gonna humiliate you again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's got to win, ugly or not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if it doesn't,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>say goodbye to Sissi's gang.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That goes for you too, Nicolas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb and Nicolas groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing to worry about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've thought of everything [chuckles].</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like you to meet Kiwi Two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanic clacking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That's cool. Kiwi's got a playmate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi yipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's as cute as the original.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Congratulations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's our nice little robot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You want a bolt or a nut?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[water splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Sorry, I didn't have the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take him out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He needs an oil change every day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's time. Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're bound for glory, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Call us if you see or hear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything suspicious on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I hope XANA gives you enough time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to win the contest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye-bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid snapshots]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the moment you've all been waiting for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, folks, the grand finale.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In this corner, Iron Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And in this corner, Kiwi Two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy versus Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, isn't that original.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the winner will be Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, what suspense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, both robots are forbidden</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to use any physical force.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shake hands now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's roll.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The first to score</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>five baskets is the winner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy. Can you hear me? Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi one, Sissi zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've never seen a robot so ugly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, please answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Way to go, Jeremy, way to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just keep it up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time out. One minute for halftime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're doing great, Jeremy. Keep it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Game ball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Kiwi! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready, set... [snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whistle blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crowd cheers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] We won!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! We really did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh... Well done</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and thank you to all our contestants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The robot contest is over for this year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And remember, Class Nine B,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got Phys Ed in five minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds and creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's okay, Jeremy. Don't worry about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can't win all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] We can show you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take a look at this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that was it. He cheated us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, am I still part of the gang or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess. We did win.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's till the ugliest robot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've ever seen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Herb, can I see you for a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Where did that come from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] I'm getting out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans and coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you doing in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you thinking what I'm thinking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it's true,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's probably been trying to reach us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! At last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's activated a tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Bloks are after me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we've got a humongous robot at school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's causing total panic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wherever it goes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how could XANA have ever made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a thing like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but one thing is sure, it's us he's after.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Ulrich and Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've gotta try neutralizing that thing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while Odd and I go to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give Aelita some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good luck you two, and stay in contact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it looks like our visitor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has already gone to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might be much worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] He could've been made there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Look at that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He won't quit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't access anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All the programs, the scanners,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the holomap, nothing. Everything's down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means I can't send you to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Got any ideas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We should try to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a specialist in robots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA made a robot on the assembly line</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he messed up all the controls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way of getting to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The time's come to eliminate the robot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy's too busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's not the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who knows about robots.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who have you got in mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We haven't got a choice, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick, we've gotta find him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, plug in the IDE.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Bingo! You're a genius, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're coming with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, where are you going? Come back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The school's being evacuated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb, we've got a favor to ask you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you help us disconnect that robot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you're not in my gang.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's a tremendous danger, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I said, "no."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what Sissi'd think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if she found out you were a cheater.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Milly and Tamiya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have it all on tape, positive proof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but if you tell her...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stay with Herb,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of this guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Come on, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you'd better find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to eliminate this horror.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I may have an idea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we'll need Mrs. Hertz's drill.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion in the distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasping] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I finally found the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can't go by yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I'll go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if the scanner management program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too late to test it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's give it a try.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The mountain region's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where you're headed, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine. I made it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's just a little further north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cranking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There we are. Let's hope the robot's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not made of titanium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We'd better make a little detour.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] XANA, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No. Don't hurt him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[retching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We got him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, only 50 life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Jeremy, but who's counting?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The second one is coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb, I've gotta hand it to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your droid worked miracles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I've gotta go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are a couple of things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, this isn't exactly summer camp here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell Ulrich and Yumi to move it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They'll be there soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's a nightmare!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We've gotta go to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how many points?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Only ten left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, you've gotta jump!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy, what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's losing all his life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's never gonna stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>concentrate on the rotation speed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Two monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gunfire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead, I'll take care of the last one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gunfire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd chattering, cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[applause]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle blowing] Game ball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, Kiwi Two!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready, set...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I now declare Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the winner of this year's robot contest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you two, I want both of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to shake hands, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] No way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a sore loser!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgive him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's nice every now and then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? You mind explaining?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Yumi laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, we'll tell you all about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a loser and so is your robot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] It's exactly as you are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>