<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give, all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>FRONTIER</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanner beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's fine up to now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll test this part here again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanner beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping and whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping faster]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer alarm rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why does it always happen just then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the external sinusoidal modules,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like I told you to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course! And I even defragmented</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the internal matrix.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] But... I already did that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The system is bound to screw up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if it gets the same data twice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we keep working against each other,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're never going to succeed. Never!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] No! I'm the one who's sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita. Forgive me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I shouldn't have got so angry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think we should stop for tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll see you tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, wait, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it looks like I'm not the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who'd rather have slept late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What were you guys doing? Studying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not exactly. Tetrix Annihilator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until three in the morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should have guessed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was something like that. Nice going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks. How'd you know I won?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How are you, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me? I didn't sleep even a wink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got an awful lot on my mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? The usual worries</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about materializing Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Well, yes, actually.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there's a lot more to it than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm off! Nothing like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little math class to wake me up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Meyer] I'll begin again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since it's a bit complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Meyer] Now, I want everyone...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's going on with Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, last night we had a bit of a fight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, about what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing. It was on account of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I yelled at her, and I think she got mad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I really have to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where to? The boys room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Meyers] Repeat what I just said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! Go on, help him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What? No way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Not for very long,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just for an hour.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could go at lunchtime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's not the problem, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem is the super calculator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the only one who can use it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but once you get the idea,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can launch a simplified transfer program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and explain the procedures to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't feel right. I'm sorry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had an argument with Aelita and I want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to ask her to forgive me in person.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA attacks while you're there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We just have to bring him back immediately</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and take his place on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, XANA's been pretty quiet lately.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I've calculated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the variable virtual mass,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you don't have to worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since I won't be fighting,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I used the default option</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the exponential memory transfer. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for the fractal encoding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the Bloks... Piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Piece of cake? Hey, this may be easy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you, but it sure isn't for us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You do all this every time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I take a nap while you're on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, we'll stay in contact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you have any trouble,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just check my notes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your scanner is waiting, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy to self] Okay. Be brave, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have a good trip!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm starting the transfer now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanner beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just scanned the data chain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi made a data capture error</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that blocked the system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Which means that the memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>used for transfers was deactivated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the worst time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wasn't transferred to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he didn't come back to you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so he's...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's out there and...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>blocked somewhere between us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. He's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to retrieve memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you in contact with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yes. Well, let's say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think what he thinks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as if he were part of my mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And can we get him back?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy says we have to recover memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the four passage towers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and redirect it to the three scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to complete the transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's going to take time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a hopeful sign. How much time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the time to go to each one of the regions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and do all the necessary manipulations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and reinitialize the system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of your afternoons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means there's no time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, Yumi, it wasn't your fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's the only one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who can run the computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without it breaking down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yes, I know. The big problem is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that as long as Jeremy's in limbo,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can't go to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if XANA attacks...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't sweat it, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's going to get Jeremy home soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm positive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA won't have time to do anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better go back to school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we're all absent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll get suspicious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here just in case.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Valerie?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Valerie] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy isn't here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitating] He's...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the infirmary, ma'am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to get unblocked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not surprising.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You children eat much too fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Hertz] Now for chemistry...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] What kind of no good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are you creeps up to now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>None of your business.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, with that kind of answer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now I'm sure you're up to no good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't fool you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well actually, Jeremy is working</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a new project</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for making worms intelligent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he'd like to test it on you! [laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Ulrich laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] Alright, quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm coming to the second tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ring beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Great, Aelita. Memory recovered.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two down, two to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] How are you doing, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Aelita just left the second tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things are going almost too well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm heading for the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you ought to relax a little bit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita'll be finished soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you go back to school?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll take your mind off it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we'll take over for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not missing class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're supposed to be in the library.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll see you guys later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm replacing Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yes, loud and clear, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost at the third tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is Jeremy okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] A little worried,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but yeah, he's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Oh-oh! Trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, we've got a problem here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I get the feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're not alone out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, Ulrich. I'm not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Watch out, Aelita! Better run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Three more monsters coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Careful, in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[radar beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita, on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a platform.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy would be proud of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I'll get you connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's three down. What do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Should we tell Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, let's leave poor Yumi alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We haven't needed her up until now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Gilles] By the 1950s,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>radio and television had become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the most important means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of spreading culture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In addition, the cinema had its role</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to play and did so very dynamically.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the 1990s,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>computers entered people's homes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and by the end of the 20th century,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there was a new means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of planetary communication,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the development of the Internet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm in the mountain region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one more tower to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Why is she stopping?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Ulrich, I'm at the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's being guarded by two Bloks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's got the message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's no way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can get through?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, none. And if I can't transfer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the memory from the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll lose Jeremy for good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's got to be a way, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy says that there may be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way of retrieving memory elsewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] But where? In another tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another computer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Another tower's impossible,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Jeremy's convinced</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that an external computer's power</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wouldn't be enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to operate the three scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one scanner? I'll check with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why only one? To bring Jeremy back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all three scanners are needed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think it over, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If one of us can succeed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in getting transferred to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will be able to get into the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Ulrich! Odd! I've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's becoming harder and harder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to contact Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm afraid he's starting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to delete himself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's disappearing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The computer is confusing him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with an outdated file.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to bring him back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps] Okay, we have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Gilles] Now, who would like to answer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers] Ulrich, how are things going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Trapped by some Bloks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy's computer? I'll go and get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, can I please go the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[running footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] There it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's always good to exercise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your mind after Phys Ed class, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nervously giggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[game console beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I wish Yumi would hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's taking you so...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, well I got caught red handed by Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hastily] No, look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, but I can't talk right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi got caught.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's in the principal's office,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she's got the computer with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're done for, now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's absolutely nothing we can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Listen, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really need your help this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, well, what do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm serious, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you've got to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's very important, Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't have any...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're completely out of your mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only way I would do something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is if you promise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be a little more cool with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And when I say "a little" that means,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>well, you know...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, look...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go out with you for a... week.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? A week!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To help Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the price is two months minimum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One month and a down payment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of down payment?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[romantic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students gasping and chattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I don't understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your story, Miss Ishiyama.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy couldn't possibly have asked you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get his computer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because he happens not to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in school today. It's noted here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he is on the school grounds, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's in the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, Yumi herself was reported</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>absent for part of the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And as for Ulrich and Odd, her two...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Enough of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You and your friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have accumulated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a number of reasons for being suspended</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in just a half day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you have to say in your defense?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I've got to speak to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, can't you see I'm busy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know daddy, but it's about Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Behave yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't warn you again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going to have to explain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to me how you did that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you mind if we don't see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot of each other for about a... month?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Watch out, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>One down. The others are coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Listen, Yumi, what I did was...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich, it's your problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] But it's not what you think,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If that's all you can think of to say,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't say anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the time being, I've got a computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to connect. So save it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well Odd, how is Aelita doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Pretty good until now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fortunately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she runs a lot faster than you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The big problem though</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is that she's losing contact with Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll head for the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe that you kissed Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you tell Yumi, you're dead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, all we can do now is hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's going to try and reach you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The computer's connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do I do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to configure the auxiliary port</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to transfer the memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here's how to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Aelita, I did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've just entered all the data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can transfer Ulrich now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Transfer, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well go on, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do it, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have faith in you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not enough memory! We came so close,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's just not enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] We need another ten bytes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, watch out behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Transfer, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clacking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crashes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry I'm late, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Odd, how did you do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A lot of the credit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should go to Tetrix Annihilator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hope you weren't planning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on playing it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I've got enough to do here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without playing other games.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, it's up to you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bring back Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've retrieved the scanner's memories.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring and powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone] Oh! Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you feeling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering and laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your crazy idea of going to Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gave us a real scare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've got to go. I promised Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you, her slave?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With that down payment you gave her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she should leave you alone tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Down payment?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's all this about, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Wait, I want an explanation...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Catch you sometime!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I was afraid you were mad at me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were mad, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I understood how you felt about me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you came to get me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, when you're really in love,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>does it mean you fight all the time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not all the time, but it can happen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to tell that to Ulrich and Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I'd rather stay out of that one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me talk!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing to talk about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm fed up with your lying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm not lying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing between Sissi and me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure. Good night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey wait, Yumi, let me explain!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you still there? Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>