<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DÉJÀ VU</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Was that you screaming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, what's all this about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Aelita Stones, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She isn't feeling well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you? You're not sleeping.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… She… woke me up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's… nothing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, go back to bed everybody, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It was daytime, there were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these men in black coming after me…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was horrible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must've had a nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You shouldn't get worked up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it happens to everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Happens to me all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dreamt I was on a date with Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you think of a worse dream?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of which,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how's your Internet dating going, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! There's this fantastic girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've totally flipped over, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I just found out that she's a student</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right here at Kadic Academy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's totally crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see her every day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I have no idea who she is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's worse, he stayed up all night</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>exchanging chat messages with her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't sleep at all, thanks to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She sends me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these messages that are so romantic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, like poems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to this:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Love… is not looking at one another"…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"It's looking together in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same direction," huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey… How do you know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a poem by the guy who wrote</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Little Prince</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] She may be romantic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she's not very original!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, time to get wet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you gonna cut swimming again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I can't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim has already warned me:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy imitating Jim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"No more dumb excuses, you hear?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! We'll finally get to see that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>buff athletic body of yours!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I can't wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may be surprised.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] The human body is made up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of 90% water,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that is why it floats.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because, contrary to what you might think,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>water floats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget Archimedes' principle:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Any body plunged into a liquid…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is…" [hesitating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Comes out wet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right… No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, no one has to be scared of the water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unless, of course, you're lost at sea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the middle of the Indian Ocean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In that case,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you would certainly have the right to say,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Wow, that's a lot of water…"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tania? Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] ...and what's more…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-it's only on the surface…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I know who it is! Yeah sure, it's Sophie!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She kind of fits the profile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of all those chat messages.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What makes you think it's a girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in our class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It might just as easily be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Milly or Tamiya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] …which reminds me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of when I was a salvage diver…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You used to be a salvage diver, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Azra? No…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way, she's not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a first-year student either, I forgot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe she's in Yumi's class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if it's Anais Fiquet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Next to her, you're a real shrimp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry if I'm boring you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, on deck!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Let's see what you can do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time it was much more detailed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There were still the men in black,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I was at the Hermitage…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The doctor said you passed out from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That may be but… What about the visions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are they coming from, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't the slightest idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although, I'm sure that it's no big deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The best thing is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you to get some rest now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll talk about it later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, I've got to go, I'm already late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Us too, Mrs. Hertz is gonna kill us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a minute!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just about to find out who she is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Odd, you can talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to your cyber girlfriend after class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take the computer with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in a bit, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll come and check on you after science.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[school bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Can't you look where you're going,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you clumsy dork?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sorry Sissi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mistook you for a doorpost!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, she's in our class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She said that she has science now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Mrs. Hertz!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, pass me the computer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I forgot to check something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Settle down and be quiet, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Open your books to page 99.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, an activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ma'am? Can I… go to the bathroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no you don't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's always the same with you three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should have gone before class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And put that computer away,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before I take it away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mercury freezes at 38 degrees</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>below zero Celsius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] At room temperature,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it is therefore in a liquid state.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] We use it in certain devices</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such as thermometers, for instance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because it expands with heat…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[eerie music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita to self] Calm down, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] It's also a very heavy metal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which means…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It means…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that a pound of metal weighs…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nearly a ton?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] Let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Warn Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go get Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll meet up at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita to self] Calm down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the Hermitage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you should be resting!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These visions are haunting me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta know where they're coming from.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, anyway, listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You oughta know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA is on the offensive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others are already at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't move, I'll come and get you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm big enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make it to the factory by myself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[man] Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come, quickly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is anyone there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[eerie music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music crescendos]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just 30 seconds more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you can head for the scanners!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's Aelita up to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She said she'd be right over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should've gone to pick her up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, there you are at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey Cinderella,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we said midnight on the dot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… had some more visions!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw a man… and it was…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know it sounds crazy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm sure it was him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What if this is XANA's offensive?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… These strange visions…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly! XANA is perfectly capable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of stimulating your cerebral cortex</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the virus that links you to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And from that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he can paradoxically simulate in you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an artificial sleep,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the involuntary psychic activity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that goes with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In short, you mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is showing you free movies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's not hang around to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go deactivate the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Odd first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is due south.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here come your vehicles!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, you're all there now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't waste any time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Coming, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's monsters up ahead,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you see them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd have to be as nearsighted as you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to see them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you handle the Blocks!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and I will</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>take care of the Tarantulas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ground and air attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Piece of cake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Transporter!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] But I didn't call it up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Jeremy, but I want some answers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to find out where these</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>visions are coming from!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, don't do it, it's a trap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Way to go, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's succeeded!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's gone to Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to get there, fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[suspenseful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hollister system, connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] The corridor is still there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's because the countdown</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is still ticking, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! The Scyphozoa is taking over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're almost there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Great, a leapfrog contest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think this is easy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At this rate, we'll never make it in time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, mind telling me what you're doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Saving the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd… are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sector Five is even worse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than Mrs. Hertz's class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Only ten seconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before the end of the countdown!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here comes the elevator!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as you get to the Celestial Dome,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get out of Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and head for the Desert Sector, fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what did I tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not getting any data!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to deactivate the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This will only take a few seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's one of XANA's traps!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He created these visions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to lure you to Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me the controls!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>drag her outta there by force!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What do you want us to do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>knock her out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It won't be necessary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll find what I'm looking for!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even if you do find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the origin of these visions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's the point if XANA takes your memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>away from you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich, we got trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa's got Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We gotta deal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Flying Mantas first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's about to lose all her memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time you deactivated the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The tunnel's open!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both exhale]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hi, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, any more visions?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see? It was just a trap, made in XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess… But I still would really like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to know where those memories came from.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA must've made the whole thing up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or maybe the memories</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>came from someone else,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>implanted in you by XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in order to scare you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That could be it…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's very strange though…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was really under the impression</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I was reliving the events</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I was seeing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That, however, can't be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Odd, how's your cyber sweetheart?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She is too cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've really got it bad this time, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm gonna meet her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-When?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, at the vending machines!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Later!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] So, Odd, your fantastic girl?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's she like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Surprising.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you meet your mystery</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>computer boyfriend? What's he like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he's a mystery, why would I tell you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you dork?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You act as if you never saw me before!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>