<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DOWN TO EARTH</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hang on. Let me get this straight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and Einstein spent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an entire weekend together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all you did was work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we had to work on the Superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah right, you guys are worse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-than Yumi and Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're always trying to convince us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you're just good friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all that stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, where is Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a little worried about him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since he found out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA had infected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hundreds of Supercomputers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around the world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's always at the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or in his room, and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah, that's him now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, right, I was beginning to worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right behind you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're so silly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein the comedian?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right to be worried about him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think he's all there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got some good news, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a little. I finally figured out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to wipe out XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Huh? Are you absolutely sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A multi-agent system?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yup, that's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I decided to go over</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of Franz Hopper's notes again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as well as all the data he sent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the network</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he was escaping from Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and of course, the data you gathered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you were traveling on the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's when I realized that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we wanna get rid of XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's through a system of multi-agents!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sounds pretty dangerous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, because XANA himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a multi-agent system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And don't forget what happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Marabounta.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Aelita's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Y'know Frankenstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that was a pretty creepy invention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you stop worrying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not gonna launch my program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I'm totally sure it's gonna work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now, all that I can destroy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are two or three Megatanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On the other hand…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, we're listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA made a really big mistake</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he teleported William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during your last mission</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Ice Sector Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the data I found in the tower…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Was it of any use to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Was it ever! Thanks to that data,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was able to imagine a program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-for freeing William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm? You mean for good?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You bet for good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's so simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All Aelita has to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is get to the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that corresponds to the Ice Sector Replika</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and run a program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the exact moment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that one of you devirtualizes William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, wow, that's simple all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Piece o' cake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's just gonna twiddle his thumbs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while Aelita enters the program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said that it was simple, but not easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You forgot one little detail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA sends us King Kong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like he did last time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who, the Kolossus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think of him as just another one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of XANA's monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you've gotta fight against.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe we should introduce you to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Then you'd understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, fighting happens to be your job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mine happens to be programming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You all know that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If there's a chance of bringing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the real William back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then what are we waiting for? Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, no reason to wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Everyone to the factory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What, like now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But they've got tuna casserole,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sauerkraut and sausages for lunch today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can have lunch tonight. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone ever tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we eat dinner at night?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girls laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't you hear me call you, Dunbar?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… I'm sorry, but I don't have a phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trying to be clever, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not that dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you think you can pull the wool</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over my ears, you're wrong!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your parents are here to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents? But who are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, would you stop acting so stupid,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're waiting for you in the principal's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>office, so get going. Go on now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I'm certain William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be delighted to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's changed quite a bit, as you'll see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>especially since that trip</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you all went on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What trip?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We didn't go on any trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[someone knocks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah yes, there he is now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come in, I said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't you hear me tell you to come in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did, but the door wasn't open.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh… Well, your parents are here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Dunbar sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is everything all right, darling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You seem to be a little out of sorts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I never had any sorts to begin with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right. He certainly has changed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holoweb system, online.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm sending you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Ice Sector Replika's coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm on it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Rotation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Rosa] What'll it be,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tuna casserole or sauerkraut and sausages?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… You wouldn't by any chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have anything lighter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sauerkraut's light, you'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, William, my boy, how's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It goes any direction I want it to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You kill me, William, what a cutup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, have some of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This'll stick to your ribs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't eat it if it's on my ribs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>High speed acceleration in three seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, Mr. and Mrs. Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, I'm really glad to meet you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, that son of yours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's really quite a piece of work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not just any piece of work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To be specific, I'm a digitally generated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>random, polymorphic energy field,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>controlled by a basic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>non-evolving, behavioral program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Chip off the old block, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well I'll leave you now, I'm sure you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lots to talk about together, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your father and I were wondering,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why you don't call us much at the moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right here in front of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I called, you wouldn't be home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've got a visual on the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Digital Key activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good work, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll let you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, no sign of any activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a tower south-southwest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can dock the Skid there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm gonna teleport you with Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, everything's cool,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're inside the base.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's great, make it fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's bound to rear his ugly head</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pretty soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After you, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell me he isn't your son?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>are </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>the parents of William Dunbar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of the real William Dunbar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our son is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a dynamic and rebellious youngster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who was expelled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the last school he attended</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for gluing stickers all over the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Including on the principal's windshield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't recall you ever telling me that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you enrolled him here at Kadic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what if I didn't?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not the point!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm telling you this child is not my son!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's true that your son has been behaving</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhat strangely these past few weeks…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I can assure you that this is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the one and only William Dunbar we know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me, sir… You said earlier</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that William had taken some sort of trip?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What trip were you referring to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, well, of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the trip he took overseas with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just before he came down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with that terrible flu.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What flu?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's crazy, I can't believe we're actually</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going to bring home</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the real William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but in the meantime, let's hope</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his clone is keeping out of trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I hope…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that when we set William free</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you won't be jealous if he starts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hanging around me again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… Why should I? There's no reason to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, we decided that we were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just good friends, didn't we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry to bother you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but speaking of William,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the radar shows him coming in dead ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Uh-huh, speak of the devil.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There he is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Try to slow him down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here come your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What bothers me most is that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is drawing energy from all the Replikas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm sure that means trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Odd, how's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We're coming into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the main room… Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's a lot more crowded</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than the last time we were here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? What do you see over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there are dozens of robots in here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all lined up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like an army waiting for orders!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] So that could be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's secret plan!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To use an army of robots</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to enslave all of mankind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get to the Supercomputer room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as fast as you can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Leave pretty boy to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're just supposed to slow him down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hi, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not much on conservation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Open up, Grandma!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Little Red Riding Hood…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pink that is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm working on the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's scary looking at</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all those robots standing at attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It sure is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! One of them just moved!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where? Which one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will you relax? I was just kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Oh! Dumbbell!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! One of them just moved!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not funny this time either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only it's no joke this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, tell us you found the right key</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause things are getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>kinda weird around here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I feel a storm brewing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last stop. Everybody off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The robots are firing at us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there, hang on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Easy for you to say!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's a nightmare!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to go to the Supercomputer room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see what the others are up to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and I don't like it at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So much for bringing him back home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's it, the Kolossus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why XANA was drawing energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from all of the Replikas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hurry, Einstein! Open up the door!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got an emergency on the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got you now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're not gonna bring him down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it, I was right on target.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He should have been destroyed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I saw another target on his arm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's not gonna be easy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>getting rid of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Concentrate your efforts on William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to give you a hand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Kolossus, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How are you gonna do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna launch the multi-agent program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Will it destroy him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. The program isn't finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it might immobilize him long</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough to devirtualize William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like it's working, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He doesn't seem to be getting anywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fantastic, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Kolossus is paralyzed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita, I'm back to you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Open sesame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'll hold them off. Get William home!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, there's a terminal next door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, Jeremy, I'm there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna dictate the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Enter it word for word,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll be just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready, Jeremy. Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's just you and me, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Go easy, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy said we have to wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we devirtualize William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but right now, it's him or me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey uglies,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't look so stainless now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Hey, don't go inviting all your pals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't entertain everybody!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's entered, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready to launch the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I give you the signal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-devirtualize William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, the Kolossus is breaking free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I know. The multi-agent system</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't have enough power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That hurt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, the robots are here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Victory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better luck next time, handsome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Welcome home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! The heap is already near the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do anything from here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I saw him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, get out of there, fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It's okay, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's here with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was never so scared in my life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lucky for me, I was devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Skid was totally destroyed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and what's more, we saved William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did a pretty good job, didn't I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Mr. and Mrs. Dunbar are right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are some really weird things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going on at this academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even your own daughter agrees with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth dear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At first William was more or less normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But ever since he started hanging out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Jeremy Belpois' gang,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he turned into a real space cowboy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know exactly what they've done</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to him…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…but if you ask me, Belpois is using him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as some sort of mini pig!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's guinea pig, dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure about this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I'm sure. After all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am your daughter, so I'm always right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd still like to know more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about this flu you said he had,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that imaginary trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the only way to find out is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk to this, uh… Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one's there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this nonsense has gone on long enough!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to call the authorities!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll run some tests</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see if he's my son or not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready Aelita? Now's the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay… Right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, try to calm down, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You calm down as well, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was here… And then he wasn't here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He evaporated!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But he's still here! Look, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] But I swear, he was here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then he wasn't here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] and now he's… here again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could use a day or two off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniggers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As you can see, I'm here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And yes, dad,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this nonsense has gone on long enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Wi… William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true that I haven't been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>quite myself lately</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm fine now, really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry I worried you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, darling!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] You think he can live</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a normal life after all this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] He's gonna have to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Luckily, he can't remember exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happened to him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>although he does know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that he was under XANA's power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, if you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna miss his clone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was a lot more fun at least.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't say that, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's just lost one of his most</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dangerous weapons: William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the meantime, we lost the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll take months to program another one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess we can forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about wiping out other Replikas now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what about those robots in Siberia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The army that XANA's created</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take over the entire world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why the only hope we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of ever beating XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is my multi-agent system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'll get back on it tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>