<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE KEY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've been looking everywhere for you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I spent the whole night</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>reading Franz Hopper's diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Listen to this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>June 6, 1994. Day 67.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Project Carthage" was a military program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>used to block enemy communications.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait. It's further down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…so I built the Supercomputer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>created Lyoko and last of all XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to destroy Carthage…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>June 6, 1994.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Day 639…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's still further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>June 6, 1994.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Day 1265.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone's watching me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone wants to get rid of me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeaking rewind]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to destroy the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destroy all the evidence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my activities.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's when I discovered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of its fascinating properties,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>returning to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It gave me all the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could possibly need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to perfect my great project,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the only thing that would allow me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to escape my enemies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeaking rewind]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>June 6, 1994.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz Hopper]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Day 2546.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the virtualization programs are ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a few hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I will go to Lyoko with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just like me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita will hold the keys to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we will be the absolute masters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will live together… forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The keys to Lyoko…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wants to steal from Aelita's memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what could XANA do with them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Escape from the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and take over the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should have stuck around 'til the end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't have time to tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the best news of all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It turns out I've been wrong all along.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] You have? Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA had given Aelita a virus,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I have been looking for an anti-virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But thanks to Franz Hopper's diary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I finally understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA didn't give her anything at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, he took something from her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He did? But what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't really know yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a fragment that belongs to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've located it in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could go and get it tonight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after the end-of-the-year dance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Awesome! It'll be our final mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then it's time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a well-earned real vacation!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Out of the question!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I refuse to set foot on Lyoko ever again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's gotten into you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father stole my life from me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was a totally crazy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>second-rate magician!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because of him, I'm nothing! I'm no one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of that's behind you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll recover the fragment that XANA took</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from you and shut down the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Then you'll be free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What if it goes wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA gets hold of the keys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Lyoko in my memory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Right, for all you party animals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with short memory spans,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to remind you that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was I saying? Oh, yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>During the end-of-the-year dance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any overly-suggestive dancing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wild behavior or trouble-making</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be severely punished!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] That's all… Enjoy yourselves!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So far, I don't have anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take to the dance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fortunately, I've got a way with women!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi! Wanna go to the dance with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I told you never to speak to me again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey… Who are you going with anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I was hoping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk to you about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I talk to you for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I get the idea now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Yoo-hoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What would you say to taking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the prettiest girl in school to the dance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, you mean Anais Fiquet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, she's going with Christopher M'Bala.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I meant me, stupid! Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay. I'll go to the dance with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps, stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Well, great! See you tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather look like a big loser and go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by myself than go with someone like her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Let it go, Odd, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure you won't come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the dance with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you going with another guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope so…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts] Have you seen Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no answer on her phone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Supercomputer's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not responding either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you think it's a bug?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe. I'm going to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Cover for me with the teachers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Odd. Did you find someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to take to the dance yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Yoo-hoo, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A surprise. See you tonight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? You are going to the dance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with William, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that a fact?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you really don't get it, do you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more of your stupid proverbs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you are dead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich has lost his head,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and should've stayed in bed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait! Wait! I got another one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go with Sissi and your future's gloomy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause you're gonna lose Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors opening]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on… Wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're insane! Why did you do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save the world! To save you all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll save it together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then you'll have your whole life</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of you, a brand new life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should get ready!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your girlfriend's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gonna be waiting for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Drop it, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm outta here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Who knows?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I'll bump into a lonely heart…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is Yumi home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Your boyfriend's here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beat it, Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not at the dance with Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't really like dancing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even less with Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why are you here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I came to tell you something…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't you going to get that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me. Are you at the dance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No. I don't want to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Glad to hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and I aren't gonna go, either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come to the factory. It's mission time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let Odd and Yumi know, too, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You… You haven't seen Ulrich, have you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, and he promised to take me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the dance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi. Wanna go to the dance with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right! My name's Carla!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd Della Robbia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The one and only!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh… I'm sorry…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm already seeing someone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you at the dance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… I mean… almost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Right. Urgent meeting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're taking the plunge!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, man! Just when I finally</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>almost found a girl to go with!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the big one, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna recover Aelita's fragment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get rid of XANA once and for all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I'll lead the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Ulrich! Transfer, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everybody all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better than all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi! Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm programming your vehicles, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There you go. The edge</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the sector is North-Northeast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Nope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you think that's weird?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. XANA wasn't expecting us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Enter the code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. All aboard for Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You feel like throwing up as usual?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I don't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I can't understand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Everybody ready? I'm going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to enter the coordinates of the room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where Aelita's fragment is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready! The wall is about to open.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have three minutes to find the key</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stop the countdown!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I see it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Out of reach, as usual!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi there, Creepers! Still ugly as ever?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Only one minute to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Supersprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yowling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go for it, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only ten seconds left, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna see how low you can go, guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were going to lead the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's something shining over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> That's Aelita's missing fragment!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creepers growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We better not hang around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy! Yumi and Odd are down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know. Get Aelita's fragment!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The whole room is falling apart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run for it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, it's getting worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no. It's getting better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're crazy! What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's Franz Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's controlling the Mantas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is amazing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a trap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There wasn't anything I could do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's… dead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What… What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA got what he wanted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He has the keys to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] He'll be able to get out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Did you see, mommy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hopper]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't go too far, sweetheart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, he's so cute!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What should I call him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What about "Mister Pück"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It means "goblin".</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you like him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, thank you, mommy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's like math.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me show you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mommy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bike bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rapid footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm going up to my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[man] All right, come out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The men in black are here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you remember where Mister Pück is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz Hopper] Come quickly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] This way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… Where are we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] My laboratory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz Hopper] Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] To a world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where we will be safe, you and I, forever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz Hopper] See you in a minute, honey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in a minute, Daddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's bringing Lyoko back to life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Look! It's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper is saving his daughter!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] To the scanner room! Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Would someone please say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something funny</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before I have a heart attack?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father sacrificed himself for me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we don't even know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if he's still on Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excuse me while I have my heart attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All those memories of your life on Earth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that was the fragment that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>took from you to bind you to him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Franz Hopper managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give them back to you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you're free, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But unfortunately, so is XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shutting the Supercomputer down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not gonna kill XANA anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Same as always, we'll fight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA may have become more powerful,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't think he's invincible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he attacks, we'll counterattack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We'll find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get rid of XANA for good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we'll do everything we can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find your dad, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right. The fight has to go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, fighting XANA is my job!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>our </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>