<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi! It's Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to come to the factory right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The super scan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>picked up an attack from XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like big trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Because there are five activated towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a bad feeling about this one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… Relax, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We'll take out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your five towers in no time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scrapes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got here as quickly as I could.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man hums] There you are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been expecting you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That XANA locks the door,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but leaves the window wide open.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, I mean, what are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm deactivating the towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without going to Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, who are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Haven't you understood, yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the one who created Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And XANA, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But then I lost control of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the beginning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was a program that I designed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to counter a military project</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>based on a multi-agent system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I created you to be the guardian of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I never thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd see you one day in flesh and blood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, where have you been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for these last few years?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's say I was a kind of prisoner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who managed to escape!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What now, then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to destroy XANA once and for all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd love to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but XANA has given Aelita a bug.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we switch the super computer off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita switches off, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll find the antivirus, you'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, but how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that, young man,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is why I came. I'm here to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's very fatherly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, in a way, he is my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's the one who created me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I adore my own dad,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he's sure no genius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But this Franz Hopper is a real genius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. That's it for me. I will get a bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, good night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good night, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[man] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? It's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Franz?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, Michael, your father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you know why I'm calling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Happy birthday, big guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Happy birthday, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>By the way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your mother is worried about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should call us more often.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Have you thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the school for gifted children?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Dad, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I have to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My friends just came in. Talk to you soon!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, a present.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting for? Open it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[paper rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, it's great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! And I drew it from memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you can imagine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how much effort it took!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, everyone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, how about going to the factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to see Franz again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You used the scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to virtualize human beings?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the only way we could find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate towers in Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The virtualization process</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wasn't ready for that yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] It's a very dangerous procedure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with serious side effects.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Such as?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cell degeneration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd seems okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] Ulrich, too. But Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer whirs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it, what a nightmare.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dr. Shrank transplants animal limbs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto human beings,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but compared to you, he's small time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't have known.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're sorry?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not going to help cure Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave me alone, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need to be by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You coming, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure there's a way to cure Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't even know what's wrong with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll work it out. I promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you've done enough damage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That everything's been my fault</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right from the start?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the brains</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this outfit, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scrapes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chair creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, Ulrich. If not</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the scanners, I wouldn't be here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slurps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not very hungry tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hiroki laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs] Ulrich, I love you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Ishiyama] Hiroki!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm going to bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're in the thick of it now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Of what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A teenage crisis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[owls hooting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi? It's Franz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have some good news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell the others and meet me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>first thing tomorrow at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay. We'll be there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] I now know how to program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the antivirus to free Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I need now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the data from Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! We'll go and get it, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought the scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were too dangerous to use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we want to get to Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then we have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It'll be our final mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then what am I supposed to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I were you, I'd stay out of the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not fair!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone blames me for everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, we turned the super computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back on together!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perhaps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you were the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who played the sorcerer's apprentice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who put your friends' lives at risk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who let XANA destroy my diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine. I get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] Right. Shall we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Dad, it's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You know that school you mentioned?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I want to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can you come and get me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>When?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] As soon as possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Belpois] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll be there tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz] Transfer, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Yumi. Scanner, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hey, we arrived directly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Sector Five!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Of course. There's direct access.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Transporter is a little outdated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[remembers Franz's voice]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> And you're</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the one who let XANA destroy my diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy to self]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Franz Hopper's diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how can he know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the diary was destroyed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Maybe you'll find out more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the owner of the Hermitage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Everything is encrypted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to decode it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And you're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who let XANA destroy my diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] How could Franz Hopper know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA took control of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He destroyed all of Franz Hopper's CDs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Apparently,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he had a problem with his notes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> And you're the one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who let XANA destroy my diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The countdown has begun. Clean up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll send Aelita over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants] All right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz, I don't mind cleaning up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we'll need industrial detergent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No problem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've programmed some new weapons.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't see what's new about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Wahoo! Homing darts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] There's the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich? How are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] It's a done deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well done, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's almost too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want more Creepers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Odd. It's not over, yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got more surprises in store for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you ready for virtualization?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clang]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita hums] Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Franz] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner. Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi? Ulrich? Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Franz, I'm not in Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz] Everything's under control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just came to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how you're managing, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're very clever, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you're too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! Wanna make this a contest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoever gets the most, wins.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on? Franz?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something's wrong!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Let's get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I get the feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've been double-crossed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your friends are in a little trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I fixed things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that they can never re-materialize.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more life points and it's bye-bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now for the grand finale.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well, there's only one thing to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz, we need help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not Franz. XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This must be the surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creepers growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creepers shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hello! Got enough?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creeper growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ciao!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Admit your defeat, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, not this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's the meaning of this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A decoy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creepers growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I often wondered how this would all end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, I know. This is it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi cries] No, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be so pessimistic, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I'm back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's start over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs] Nothing like my old gear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I managed to reprogram</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the materialization just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's home. Ready, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Yes, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All we have to do is deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Creeper shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! I'm entering the code "Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chokes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! What's going on? What can I do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm in the core zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Deactivate the tower. Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swish]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's in trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chokes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang in there, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy chokes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy chokes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy chokes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, buddy. Everything's okay now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Of course I'm not angry with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, I checked your bio schematic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during your re-materialization phase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no sign of alteration whatsoever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a relief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He really had me scared,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>false </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The real one is still somewhere on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready, son? Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, things have changed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Let me explain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're sure you've thought it over?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry I made you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>come over here for nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry about it. And don't forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give us a call from time to time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where were you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nowhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your father seems like a really nice guy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I love him. He's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like father, like son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>