<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>CRUEL DILEMMA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune fades into background]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Dear students,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this magnificent stadium</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is being built in close cooperation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the Board of Education.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon you will be enjoying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the latest in sports equipment,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I personally am delighted,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since my duty is to provide you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the finest work conditions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and in all areas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>both intellectual and athletic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since, as Juvenal said:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"A sound mind in a sound body."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wow, can he talk!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do we have to listen to all of this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really. You could've stayed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Jeremy if you wanted to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What's Einstein up to anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's glued to his computer screen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a big cyber conversation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with his darling Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft guitar music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just a couple</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of calculations to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and my devirtualization program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be completed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's going to work, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I have a chance of finally</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being materialized in your world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and becoming somebody like you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope so. Anyway,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's one thing that I'm sure of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never been as close</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the answer as now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, honestly, it's so hard to imagine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can be face to face</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the same room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can touch each other, even kiss.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters] Uh, yeah, that'd be...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nervously] interesting...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, well, I guess...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting the test program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] I don't get it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not the end of the world. I'm sure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, that one day, you'll succeed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm beginning to wonder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I'm up to the job...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I'm good enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for such a complicated program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. I'm just tired</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and jumpy, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I better go and stretch my legs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh? Jeremy... Hey, what's this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another one of Jeremy's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>materialization programs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, wow, candy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] How many times have I told you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not to touch my computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I'm not here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There are months of work in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Relax, Max.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I didn't hurt your little toy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! You're such a cosmic creep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now look what you've done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those keys are sensitive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, a little piece of candy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not gonna wreck your keyboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is really mega insane!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yes! It works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy laughs] Odd, you're a genius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make up your mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I a genius or a creep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] A creepy genius.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You didn't do it on purpose,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but dropping the candies on the keyboard,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>modified and relaunched my program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno what happened, but it works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who's an Einstein now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you gonna materialize Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem is I only get one try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because I didn't see what kind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of programming the candy typed in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah, so? There's only one Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and tell the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll announce the good news to Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh uh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, it's now or never.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We may not get a second chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] What if there's a bug?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to set up the program again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can't materialize Aelita like that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without making preparations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've boosted the scans.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got the program going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Everything's ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, in your head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come back to Earth, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try to be practical for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita has no parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or a birth certificate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, she's not enrolled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in any school. OK, that's no biggie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But all that together means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she doesn't exist in our world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine, "Hi, I'm Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I come from a virtual reality."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a one way ticket to the nuthouse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it doesn't have to be today. I can wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can put her up at my house.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My folks wouldn't mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you can plug</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the City Hall computers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and create a phony identity for her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Find her a new name... Whatever she needs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then you just have to enroll her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at our school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and try to put her in our class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'd be really cool, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we'll get started</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>first thing tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you asleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I asleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Jeremy, you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that virtual beings never sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't sleep a wink.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't stop thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and It's keeping me up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't imagine all the things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna discover in our world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You mean like sleeping?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That and all kinds of fun things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell me more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engines starting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you touch an object</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your fingers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have a sort of sensation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could be a feeling of softness,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or of heat, or it could be cold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I see. I thought that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you only sensed with your brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's a little more complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here on Earth, everyone has five senses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You, Aelita, only have two of them:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hearing and seeing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can only see and hear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Speaking of hearing...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Soon you'll be able to touch...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think I just heard XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's up to something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bulldozer engine rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's all that noise, I wonder?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's launched an attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, listen, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and hide in a deactivated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll contact you from the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd, wake up! XANA's attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was that? What'd you say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about carpet tacking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich, get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a XANA alert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said, it's a XANA alert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you always sleep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with those things in your ears?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Odd, always,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and one of these days I'll tell you why.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No need to look any further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time, he picked a real winner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's attacking us with bulldozers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, XANA. How subtle can you get!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, rush over to the lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and call Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and I are gonna try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stop these monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll take the front one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Got you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Yumi, get up. We really need you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you realize what time it is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bulldozers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What bulldozers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's controlling the thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what to do, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That makes two of us. You go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and meet Yumi and Jeremy at the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I can find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA wants to do with these monsters,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-that sure would help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, just be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eyes open, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where XANA's monsters are hiding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No enemy in sight for the moment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the pulse beats are stronger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower can't be too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells] Woah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator zooms]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd should be there soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope that Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich are on their way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? He's on the bulldozer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>trying to find out what XANA's up to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Bad news, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on the river bank, and I'm afraid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's target is the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's gotta be it. If XANA destroys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can say goodbye to our equipment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No more computer, meaning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no more communication with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget the scans.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without them, no more transfers to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And that means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>total victory for XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's just about to go alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'll do my best,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can't promise a graceful entrance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello, Odd. You're looking stressed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm okay, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I never know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I'm gonna find whenever I come here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come with me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower is this way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, let's go and check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bulldozer engines rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I've lost contact with Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Where was he</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you last spoke to him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] He was going to the factory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the bulldozers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] Right, I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll find him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Talk about a reception committee!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Usually,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>roachsters move in groups of five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like the committee</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is at full strength.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, roachsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, which one of you wants to be first?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, would you cool it, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your mission is to protect Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>remember?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wanna trade places, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Ulrich, get up, Ulrich! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud crash and thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, you've used up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>four of your ten arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here comes three more. Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you've gotta get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bulldozer engine rumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey Jeremy, can you give me a hand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What about the bulldozers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] It's a mess up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I wish it were only up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] How's Odd doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm starting to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little lonely out here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That answers your question?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Gotcha.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Odd, Yumi is on her way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's just say he's fast asleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He is? That must be tough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without his ear plugs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, figure out a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to slow down the roachsters</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're way ahead of Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Take care of the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of the roachsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see what the score is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three roachsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and three laser arrows left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, this is no time to miss your target.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser arrow blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jeremy, how many life points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have I got left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Ten. Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps getting closer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd whistles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's your buddy hiding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Uh-Oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yells] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy, I didn't make it in time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's game over for Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll back up Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in case she needs help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't want to stress you out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if the scans are destroyed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're on a one way trip, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No problem, I'll hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could use a little nap before class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it isn't the scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she has to worry about. I had a vision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I saw Yumi falling into the digital void.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualized forever?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hey, Yumi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I heard him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] I'll go and help her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Ulrich. Take a look at yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the shape you're in, it'd be crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, help me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales exhausted]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I saw it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's on her way to help you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me a visual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There it is! That's where I saw Yumi fall!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts and groans loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, I can't hold on anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's inside the tower now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't, I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[debris rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi, I'm coming! Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bulldozer engines cease]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I never would have thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was possible for one of us to become...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's all my fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I had been faster,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she would still be here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there is a solution,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Jeremy knows what it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The materialization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's operational, but Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has to give up her place to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you bring Yumi back here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but I can only materialize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one person.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One and only one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then choose Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's part of your world already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay. I can wait a little longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] But first of all, I need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to track down Yumi in the digital void.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's alright, Yumi. You're gonna be okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Welcome home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, how did you get me back here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm happy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and at the same time, I'm sad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why? At least you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the program works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just have to set it up again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, nothing to it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have faith in you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles to self]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One day you'll get me there. I'm sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey Jeremy, want some candy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing with that? It's mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I guess it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Okay, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>no problemo</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>. Here you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Come on, have one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Candy can fix anything...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even a broken heart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] If you say so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soothing guitar music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>