<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>HOLIDAY IN THE FOG</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pigeon cooing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[owl wooing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hey, what are you doing here, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] You dumb dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait until I get my hands on you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get you this time, you mangy mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whispering] Yeah! Way to go, Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[spraying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you're doing outside at this hour?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that! Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that supposed to be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[comical trumpets]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] If I'd had more time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could've done the eyes better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fly buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I hope this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will teach you a lesson, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A model student like you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should be ashamed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yes, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How did it go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What'd he say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, he gave me detention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the whole week of vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He really let you have it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As punishments go, you're a champion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure we couldn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have done better than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, XANA won't get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any vacation this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I dreaming or does Jeremy look happy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be punished for the vacation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it sure is weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd almost think he did it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cause he wanted to be punished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me neither.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And who's this XANA he was talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb is right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's even weirder than weird,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm gonna find out what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What're you gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to leave with your dad after school?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little change of schedule.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense violin playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Daddy, can I talk to you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a minute?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Sissi, dear, I'm very busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It won't take long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there's this girl I know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whose grades aren't very good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the best thing for her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would be to study over the vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But she's supposed to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>see her grandparents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I see, and who is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi shushes] I'm coming to that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She knows that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at her grandparents' house,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she won't feel like studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, what should she do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She needs your advice, as a principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, my advice would be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give up her vacation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stay home and study,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for her own good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, what's this girl's name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perhaps I could talk to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just did, daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you for the advice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise to study hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiss grandma and grandpa for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You get to go and see your parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the other end of the planet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's off for a vacation in the mountains</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and what do I get?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A week of math tutoring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] If they think they can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>make you a good student in one week,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>well, I say good luck to them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sounds like Mission Impossible,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you ask me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're sure you can manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on your own without us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat. And if XANA leaves me alone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to work on Aelita's materialization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, don't worry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's not gonna be alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm staying at school too, and I'll look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after him. I'll be his guardian angel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, Jeremy, are you lucky!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, young man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think this wall's gonna clean itself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[All] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get to work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling] now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on, laugh while you can, young lady.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your father told me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to monitor your studying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and that's what I intend to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay now, get to work and clean that up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi grumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know why, but all of a sudden my</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>math tutoring doesn't seem all that bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scrubbing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[pops tab]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water drips]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[burps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Come on, you can do better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than that. A little more elbow grease.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep scrubbing. Go on. You can do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's that math problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Making any progress solving it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I sure hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Um...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I'm a little bit stuck here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe if I gave Jeremy some help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father always says that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>manual labor is good for the brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess all kids aren't lazy after all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good idea, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay there. I'll go and get a sponge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, what a shame</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have to wipe all that off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess I'm not the first one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to recognize your talent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's really well done. A work of art.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, did you do it all by yourself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or did your friend XANA help you a little?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[suspenseful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I overheard you talking to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the other kids about XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She your girlfriend? Maybe I know her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on Jeremy, tell me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's the name of a rock group,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but with all the junk that you listen to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no way you know them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think I am, an idiot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Uh, you said it, not me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here, since you volunteered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to help me, it's time I took a break.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little more elbow grease! Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep scrubbing. You can do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, you can do better than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[owl wooing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, I ache all over, I swear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm telling you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never thought it was possible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be this sore. It even hurts to blink!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, you should go to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you kidding? I can't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if Jeremy tries something tonight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, but he's up to something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm almost sure this XANA is in on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight's the night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to play super spy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to find out the secret</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Jeremy and his weird friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I know I'm on the right track,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I need the computer in the lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to check out the figures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should go to bed, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA seems to be stable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't feel any pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's not the end of the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I stay virtual one more day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Uh. That's fine for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you don't come, I have to spend</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my vacation with Sissi and Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never survive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for everything you're doing for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snores softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[owl wooing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now don't tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you were sleepwalking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I've been working</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here for 20 years,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I've heard that story about...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, something awful has happened!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have a look in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Huh? It looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there was a hurricane.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This had better not be your doing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the smoke! It's disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird, not even a trace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Don't think about leaving this room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tomorrow, I'm calling your parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got some explaining to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't want to be in your shoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, come in please. Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've got a big problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're not the only one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's woken up but</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know which tower he's activated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the pulsations converge</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's even worse than I thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The spilled bottles contain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an extremely poisonous substance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the data from the computer is right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the gas can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even be deadly in cases of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>extended inhalation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get up young man. Time to face the music.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, oh... What's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where am I? Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm totally out of it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Jim, over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Smoke with arms!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This has gotta be contagious!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's all this about smoke anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! I don't see any...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! Holy Toledo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo! Aelita, I found it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirty-seven degrees south,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the forest area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm on my way, but I'm nowhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>near it and I'm gonna need some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know three volunteers who'll be happy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to cut their vacations short and help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll soon learn that mathematics</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is actually quite easy, young man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All you need is a sense of logic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-a little bit of common sense,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and of course, if you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>good concentration skills, and if you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>S.O.S. XANA. Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>...analysis, that will help as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I assure you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you apply yourself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's not at all complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct airport announcement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Come and have a look at this Charlie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it? Wow, that's incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is that, kid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, it's a... Looks like a skeleton.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but don't you see anything strange?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your skeleton is moving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh... Oh! That's Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi's my dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You do know that dogs are only allowed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the luggage compartment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah sure. Uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was supposed to stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With my grandma, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's gram!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were just talking about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you talking about, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, of course I know it's you, gram.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you've told me a hundred times</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you don't like me to call you, gram.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, okay. I'm on my way. Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll bring back the dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bye, gram!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We should have left over two hours ago!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how much she loves that dress.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't even know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what dress she's talking about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mom] I'm coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be down in two seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, I doubt that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mom] You're going to laugh</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>darling when I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I don't really feel like laughing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you noticed someone is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>missing in the back seat?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, I'm coming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the forest area now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should be there very soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are bound</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be monsters around there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better go back to the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim and Sissi might be in trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to warn them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Help us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yelling] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's no use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. No, we're not finished. Be brave now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy can't be far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll help us out of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's pretty reassuring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nice to know that the closest thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Bruce Willis is coming to the rescue!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi? Jim? Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll cut across through the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>boiler room. It's faster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Through the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Sissi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are still inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to find them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[struggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to go and help Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hang on, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you got here in the nick of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I only stayed at school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to try and find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the secret of Jeremy and his friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cause the truth is that I've been wanting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be part of their group for ages,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it seems so hopeless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you understand what I mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? No! All I understand is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's no ventilation in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna run out of oxygen soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I better stop talking then. Right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I can take a hint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Man on TV] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>...a strange and toxic smoke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whose origins are unknown.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ambulance siren wails]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The elderly and children are advised</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to remain indoors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[turns off television]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me get over to the computer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And get ready to dive in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop looking at me. Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Where do we go now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is over this way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you seen any monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess you didn't look very hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, do you copy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing] Still nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been through most of the building.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, get out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't stay in that smoke any longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] And they may be outside already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try one last room, then I'll go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jim! Sissi! Are you in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wheezing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, get out right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I don't want to rush you my friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's getting kind of urgent here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think we're doing, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Getting a sun tan?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh! [gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You okay, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No broken bones yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take good care of Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] You see, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you he'd come and rescue us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What the... ?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Oh! He came for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, he came to save me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just like I'd always dreamed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers fire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The only way to access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower is via a tree bridge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it happens to be behind the monsters,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so you're gonna have to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>find a way around them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I might have an idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for blocking the monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You take care of Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser flash.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[power building]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rock rumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If she gets hit one more time...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Welcome to Earth, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey look, a cell phone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Now we can call for help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, is that you? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you? And Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, we really need help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're starting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to run out of oxygen in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jim, what's happening. Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, what do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You take care of the monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water bubbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hey, you! That's right, you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser flash.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smoke hisses]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope it's not too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I don't understand why you insist</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on getting punished</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with detention again, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's not going to reactivate this soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could give yourself a short vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not as long as Aelita stays virtual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this time, to tell the truth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scoffs] considering what we've painted,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim can't be too angry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come to think of it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna stick around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything is better than another one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Miss Schmidt's math lessons,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts] Get back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>