<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DISTANT MEMORY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at my giant snowball, mommy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Schaeffer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay near the house, darling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hopper] Well done, my angel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolf howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Mommy! Daddy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolf growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mommy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mommy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mommy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music fades out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gentle music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're still having nightmares?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Well, yeah. They keep coming back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>every now and then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, they're always the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry, Jeremy. I'm used to them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita, it's not your nightmares</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm worried about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you that it's no big deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi won't be far for the holidays,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm staying here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep an eye on XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, there's no need to worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't care about XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just don't like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>leaving you here all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna tell my dad I'm staying here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No you're not!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should spend the holidays</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your families.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For me it's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not the same thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] At holiday time, my dad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gets more stressed out than ever,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which makes my mom hysterical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I'd rather stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, me too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My sisters drive me nuts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last year,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they locked me in the bathroom all night,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just because they thought it was funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They did?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's even worse than my kid brother.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought they were older than you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And they're a lot bigger than me too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's my problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita, Jeremy, Ulrich and Yumi laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that your dad's car over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, the show must go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you soon, everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May the force be with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See ya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's not all that long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try and have some fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] There's my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you sure that you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on now, hurry up. I won't be all alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got Kiwi for company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Goodbye for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, speaking of Kiwi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't feed him any cheese at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It gives him gas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's more powerful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than your Energy fields.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the tip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So long!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see you're still hanging around</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with that gang of good for nothings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I see you forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your happy pill again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your friends seem very nice, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, yeah, I really like them a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] They're my good buddies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That girl with the pink hair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the one you're always talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's very pretty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I get the impression she likes you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promised my mom I'd help her clean up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, see ya Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you sure you don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wanna spend the holidays with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll call my parents and tell them--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, I'd just be in the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could use a little time alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you need anything, you know my number.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Have a nice holiday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gentle music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, he's so cute. I love him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What should I call him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Hopper] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How about Mr. Pück?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the name of an elf.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Schaeffer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you like it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes! Thank you, mommy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Belpois whistling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistling continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're very quiet, son.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is anything wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, no, I… It's nothing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just thinking of something else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Stern] You disappointed me again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as usual Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought after the talk we had last month</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you would try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to make some kind of an effort.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Instead, there's been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>no improvement at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl making noises]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Plus all those unexcused absences.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you find that amusing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cars honking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chimes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[classical music plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[piano plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[turns off music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Expecting you here on Lyoko"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not on the network?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, rats! It bugged up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Ishiyama] Yumi, could you please</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>give me a hand in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon as I'm finished calling my friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your phone call can wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need you to help me right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not, I'll never finish</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the housework in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But mom, you've got a whole week to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and as usual,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your father's not going to lift a finger,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so a week may not be enough!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What did I do this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"There isn't much time."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not much time for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Here are the coordinates."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"See you in a minute, my dear."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in a minute, my dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What's that thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A simulation bubble?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can this be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[classical music plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[piano note plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've so much catching up to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and there's so little time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were lost on the network!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Lost? No dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When XANA destroyed Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I managed to escape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have information to give you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but first…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted so much to hold you in my arms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how did you--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had to create this simulation bubble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that I could finally--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is fantastic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything is just the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. This bubble will allow us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do many things, my dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like spending an evening together at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, come on! Pick up will you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what are you doing in here? Get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calling Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind your own business!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I ask you about Milly Solovieff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For how long of a time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her phone battery</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>might be dead, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think you can go over there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and check it out? Keep me posted, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Dad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, I forgot my laptop back at the dorm,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I, um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get the idea, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your laptop wouldn't have pink hair,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by any chance, would it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You know, I can understand that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was in love once too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were? With who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who else? With your mother!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car horns honking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! This traffic's horrible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[honks horn]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Getting all tense</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>won't get us there any faster, dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That you, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, something must be up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll let him know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll meet "you know where."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything is more fun than this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich! Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Stern gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To get a little air</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and to stretch my legs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, I'll get there faster if I walk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See ya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Stern gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[car horns honking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Aelita's not answering her phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet us at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, be right there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as I tell my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, are you flying today or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Adele? It's Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh huh. Oh! Sorry, Pauline.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, listen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you think you could ask Elizabeth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell Marie to say to Louise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she should let mom and dad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>know I missed my flight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What do you mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell them myself? Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, change of plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing like sibling loyalty!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Expecting you here on Lyoko?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, as long as XANA hasn't been defeated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't rematerialize myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you however, should be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to free your young friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was his name again?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to send a program to Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>via the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, how's your fight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against XANA progressing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're hunting him down on the network,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to our virtual ship,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Skidbladnir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Skidbladnir?"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a strange name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you know that name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's in the book of Viking legends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you used to read to me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before I went to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes of course, the Skidbladnir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could I forget?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Thanks, dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? Hurry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita virtualized herself onto Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? But why did she do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her father asked her to!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is anything wrong, my precious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why'd you ask me to come to Lyoko, daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because I wanted to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's been such a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA could attack at any time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not as long as I'm with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I said that everything here was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same as I remembered it, I meant it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad you like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted you to feel as if it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was your home, our home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true, everything's here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing's missing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Except for one little thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh really? What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My mother.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You remember, dear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your mother disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and I want to see her again</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>more than anything else in the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you know that. You've always known.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And since you're a perfectionist,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd have recreated her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here in the simulation bubble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is unless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you weren't really my father!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay away from me, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Something's fishy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm. What if it was Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who contacted Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] XANA's pulled this on us before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would risk this with his own daughter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is somewhere in the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a simulation bubble?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's in a what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A copy of the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A sort of ghost channel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's fallen into a trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready! You're going in right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better give up, Aelita. You can't beat me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you think!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go after her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I didn't land inside the bubble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I know. I can't virtualize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly inside of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You'll have to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your own way in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any idea how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Not really, but if you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's probably screening his guests.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For sure. He even left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a couple of bouncers at the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's twenty life points you just lost.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perfect timing you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head straight for the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Aelita are in big trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, but how about a little rundown?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll fill you in later. Now, get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible to escape!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>This bubble is your prison!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good to see you again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's your vacation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Short. Good to be back though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Somewhere inside that bubble thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's always</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gotta be different, doesn't she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Give up, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-All right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] You win, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't matter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You lose no matter what, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The simulation bubble's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go and help Aelita! Step on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you call us some taxis?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Coming up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi exclaims]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A Blok.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was it, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>A Blok.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess we'd better "unblok" the situation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The first priority is getting Aelita back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicles revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Manta!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Flying Manta! Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd exclaiming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanna leave? Be my guest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's too far away, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better bring her in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! This can't be happening! Not Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yumi, Aelita's gone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Romeo, this is really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gonna cost you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's he doing now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like he's waiting for something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I dunno,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but without Aelita, it's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, something weird is happening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I get the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Victory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what is that thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's what I thought!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I was right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Bloks whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, XANA's trying to destroy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a kind of brightly lit bubble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do we do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Protect it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That bubble is Franz Hopper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, then I'll go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and do a number on that Blok.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like he dropped something off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, he did. It was Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's great to see you again, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bubble chiming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hopper is losing energy! Take out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that Blok! And make it snappy too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're doing all we can, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super smoke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dad, you have to get away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William yelling] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Saying you gave us a scare</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is an understatement, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's gonna be really happy to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I hope this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he gives us the rundown he promised us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I dunno what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's pretty obvious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There he goes again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, when Lyoko was destroyed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopper wasn't spread out over the network.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He managed to escape!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He disappeared on purpose, is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, to get away from XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is why he's constantly trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to throw Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the Digital Sea all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He knows that's the only thing that could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get Hopper to come out of hiding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In order to destroy him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As long as my father's alive,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'll always be a big threat to XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And our friend XANA knows it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, before we blow XANA away for good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why don't we give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>each other our presents, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd wait till after vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, Einstein, this one's for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since XANA made us come back earlier</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than expected, why wait, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rubber duck squeaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's cool, Odd. Thanks a lot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but, um, what am I supposed to do with it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Nothing at all. That's what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>makes it fun, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not opening your presents?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. In Japan, you never open a present</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of the person who gave it to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that isn't all, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tonight, you're coming home with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents want you to stay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the holidays.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't want to bother them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's not bother at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're the ones who insisted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give you my room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll sleep in the living room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a really comfortable couch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Y'know, I'm sure that XANA could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>use a vacation too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you thinking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-About my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When he saved me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even in his virtual form,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could feel his presence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like he was holding me in his arms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>