<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>KADIC BOMBSHELL</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teacher] …and at the end of the play,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Juliet drinks a potion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which makes her appear to be dead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Romeo, thinking he's lost his young bride,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>poisons himself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And when Juliet wakes up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and sees the lifeless Romeo</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she drives a dagger through her heart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is so beautiful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That is so idiotic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[school bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[teacher] Don't forget to review</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the balcony scene for next week.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you on Monday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What didn't you like about it, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a wonderful love story, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's just it, Aelita, it's a story.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Killing yourself for love, that's dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's because you haven't met a girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who loves you enough to die for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, if you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nobody would die for love.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you be ready to die for Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well… That is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, what are you guys talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, about tragedy and true love</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich was just saying--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That it's totally idiotic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Aelita, I think I figured out a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for improving source logarithms and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could use your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That sounds great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But first, let's have lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think Aelita and Jeremy would be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ready to die for each other?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For love, I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They might die of boredom though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey look, what's that all about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's your name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How long are you here for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can you speak English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy] I'd love to show you around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, gimme a break.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who is she?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi's overseas pen pal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's visiting for four days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her name is Bringa Erad…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Erud… Whatever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bringa Erinsdottir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And she's from Iceland.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Sissi's just eating it up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to Bringa,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's getting lots of attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, only this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the boys aren't interested in her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, the show's over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take Bringa to her room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time to wake up, you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm awake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What'd you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you saying then that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your program lets you modify gamma waves?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which means we can have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a much faster virtualization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and more… Wow…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you let me through!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She said thank you to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder what the boys see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that string bean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at the girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're all chasing after her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find out her beauty secrets.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to sit down, if you don't mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me through, will you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Sissi, this seat is taken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm holding on to it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because Bringa promised</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that she would sit with me during dessert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhaling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, this weekend is R and R</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for me: rest and recuperation, yes sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not going to the pool tomorrow</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Ms. Iceland? Seems everyone's going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I've got better things to do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like hours and hours of sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch where you're going, huh, creepo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, one of these days,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>someone is gonna…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I tell you, she's something else!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gorgeous and slim</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and her hair's like gold.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And did you see those deep,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>clear green eyes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Absolutely incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! And, did you get a good look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at that beautiful soft skin she has?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bringa's not just beautiful,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>beautiful's not the word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's, I dunno, she's well… She's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You mean, ugly?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You talk about her as if she's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the eighth wonder of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Those are the words I was looking for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bringa is the eighth wonder of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, are you sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't have a problem with…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-…a slightly overheated brain?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, that's what I meant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not my fault I caught Bringa's eye</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you didn't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She really has fried your brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you see that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she comes on strong to everyone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're just jealous, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, there you are, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are those your friends?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to meet them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why sure, Bringa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita… Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bringa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich… and Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you the one whose name is Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look very intelligent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you're the one who likes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do martial arts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perhaps you could give me a demonstration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd be… I'd be…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is nice to get to know all of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shall we go for a walk, Odd </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>elskan</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elskan</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>… that means sweetheart!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really wonder what she sees</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that shrimp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bringa needs somebody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little more intellectually developed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys realize you're talking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about your friend?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jealous, both of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Talk about fried brains, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you take the cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're wrong, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just working out the statistical</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>probability of a girl as pretty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and charming as Bringa falling in love</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a guy like Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since that blonde ice cube showed up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've turned into a doormat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? I have not!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I don't know why you should care.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, we're just good friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What is it with girls this year?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're right, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That Bringa's really started messing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with our heads.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming to himself]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did I miss an episode?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, we have to talk seriously.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true. Ever since you started</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going out with Bringa,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's been a lot of friction</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in our group and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's not very good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for our mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your girlfriend is coming between us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we think the best thing to do is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to break up with Juliet now, Romeo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You actually want me to stop seeing Bringa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just because you guys can't get along?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not her fault or mine either!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem is you and your jealousy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, wait, it's a big problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe for you, but not for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In fact, I have a date with your problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So ciao!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Bringa] You look a little upset.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't want to go out…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure I do, it's just that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my friends are acting so lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The program'll run all night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to wait till tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still thinking about Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was wondering</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if our little gang will survive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this eighth wonder of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Honestly, I wouldn't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's romances last</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an average of two days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think that girl has turned our Casanova</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into a Romeo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Bringa]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have such a sad face all night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not happy to be with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure I am. I was just thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the fight I had with my buddies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Sometimes you make friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sometimes you lose them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll make new ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, they're not just any old pals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're real friends, and real friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>count a lot more for me, Bringa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is true, but your "real" friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have made you very sad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that we are together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't need them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm? No, it's really different with them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, explain it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you trust me, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you see, we're kind of like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an army… of warriors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Warriors?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, nothing. Forget I ever said it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought that you trusted me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-but you don't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bringa, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let me show you something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you'll see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why my friends are so special.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you've gotta swear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep it a secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we are… Ta-da!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, this is incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's kinda complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure I understand it all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're pretty top secret</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scientific experiments,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ultra secret phenomena,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>digital kinda stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Bringa, don't touch anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I'm not an idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the Supercomputer was doing something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? Nothing at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I hardly touched the keyboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, I think we'd better go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I haven't seen anything yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go. Please, Bringa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? What's going…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta get up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated tower, in sector…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There isn't any activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Ulrich, you can go back to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>False alarm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sure you heard the alarm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure I'm sure, and I don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my computer's gone paranoid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that's why we've gotta hurry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and find out what's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still no activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now let me check the log…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo! There's a system alert all right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but not from this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was at 12:36 last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Interesting…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is getting weirder every second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look! The Supercomputer says that there's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an activated tower in the Desert Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But in terms of digital activity,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing's going on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the cause of these false alarms?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think it's a virus?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could've been a problem with the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we launched last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I don't get it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I checked everything out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here are my calculations… Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it? What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The program has been modified!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some sort of parasitic foreign data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was entered into the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone came here last night for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Uh-oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like Odd made a big, fat mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I think his mistake is more like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>skinny and blonde.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Bringa, don't touch anything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only you're too late, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, no need to look any further, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd gave away our secret.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was Bringa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By touching the keyboard,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she modified my program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what messed up the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you fix it, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but the problem is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it might take a little while,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and of course, during that time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA could…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Though it could be another false alarm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but we can't be sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Send me to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-uh, too risky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But not knowing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA could be up to is even riskier.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You need someone there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like before we had the Superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you're probably right. Get in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The activated tower should be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the northwest part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Forest Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you made a mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sent me to the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I didn't make a mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I virtualized you in the Forest Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We really have a huge problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must be with his Icelandic icicle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd took the eighth wonder of the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the factory, and guess what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She tweaked the Supercomputer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, you haven't seen Odd around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure have!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's in the park with my pen pal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't feel any pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think there's a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna bring you back in right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't like your being all alone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another major problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Believe it or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in the Mountain Sector!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm not alone, either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll warn the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, hi guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] How was the movie last night?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which one was it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jurassic Experiment</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? You sure it wasn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two Rats in a Factory</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, what makes you say that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because Jeremy's got the whole film</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on video.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The actors are the spitting image</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of you two lovebirds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything to say for yourself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, listen, it's not what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was gonna tell you about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's in that head of yours, sawdust?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Supercomputer is on the blink!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you have just betrayed your way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of our group!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what is the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, we visited your mysterious laboratory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's not the end of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For your information,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it could be the end of the world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had enough of these stories,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to the swimming pool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Odd, are you coming or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I'm really sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things could be better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? But why did you send her out alone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think everyone's gone crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang in there, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Yumi are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be finished fixing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer really soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a couple of minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A couple of minutes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Survival out here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a matter of a few microseconds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cease fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! At last, just the two of us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're here, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you're going in right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's in big trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Just a second, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you plan on sending us there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if the Supercomputer's all messed up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No idea. I'm trying to fix it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we have to risk it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita'll be at the mercy of William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another crazy idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It gets better and better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, didn't you say the Mountain Sector?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Speaking of bright ideas, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chill, Ulrich, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not Jeremy's fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget, we could've wound up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Digital Sea, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can always try to bring you back in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then send you to the right sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, we can't take the chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll find our own way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just point us in the right direction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, the Way Tower is due south</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from your present position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're almost at the Way Tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Aelita. I'm almost through fixing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm not okay at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA's finally going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have your company for good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When are you gonna learn</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we never abandon our friends?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] What do you say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we go for a swim together later?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are there beaches in Iceland?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, would you like to have a fantastic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-breathtaking experience--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Shut up, Poliakoff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich, Yumi, go real easy, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you guys get devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before I can fix the program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure that I can bring you back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Earth again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're telling us this </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>now</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot. What's the bad news?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could I possibly ask for more?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna get three birds with one sword.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll see about that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's been seen to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you use my help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not exactly welcome around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have no time to chat with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's great,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then let's not waste any time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and virtualize me right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our friends must need help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But with the Supercomputer down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you could be virtualized anywhere at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's my problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the moment of truth, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think I'm afraid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of that popsicle stick?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I know just what you're gonna say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I betrayed you and I'm a total lame-o,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I should be kicked out of the group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're right too, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should never have shown</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer to Bringa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's unforgivable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well no. You simply forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that inside that head of yours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there happens to be a brain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not the only one who was lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were just too jealous of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. We all went a bit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>too far because of Bringa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I forgive you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… You saved me from William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well… Still friends?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, still friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There is a way to fix the mess I made.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little return to the past, hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that won't be necessary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students wishing Bringa good-bye]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Can you believe that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] She completely forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to say good-bye to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, now do you see why I'm not worried</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the Supercomputer, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who cares about her anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no shortage of girls around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hey, Sissi, I thought that Bringa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was gonna stay here for four days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let's just say I convinced my father</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to send her out of town,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to my cousin's place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She wanted to see the countryside,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess for you that's a real relief,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause now that Bringa's gone,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she can't steal the show.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may not believe it, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it was really a pleasure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I sometimes envy you two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because being surrounded</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by guys all of the time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could never happen to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, now that's the Sissi we all love!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could I have flipped over Bringa?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get away from me, creepo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi, wait! Wherefore art thou, Juliet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Uh-oh, Odd's gone bananas again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better watch out, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>