<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>FINAL ROUND</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You swear not to reveal the secret?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now for the final step: the scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to record</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a virtual image of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Afterward, you'll be immune to the returns</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the past. That'll make you part of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, you ready? You scared?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me? No, why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Were you scared the first time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh yeah, right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wasn't scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I guess I mixed you up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with another Ulrich Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can still change your mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you kidding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to the club, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, how do you feel now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to take on XANA and his monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I just can't wait to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I look like on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get real. XANA is much more dangerous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and devious than you can imagine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And, before you can decently fight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's gonna take a lot of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At first, you should hang back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to check things out and to try to learn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay, don't flip out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't try to steal the show.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm hoping that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't attack tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm enrolled in the inter Academy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>skateboard championship,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I am gonna win it too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not someone who likes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to steal the show either!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's right, in life,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you should always aim for the top.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Why not? If you fall back down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you crash a lot harder.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Thanks for coming with me, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Somebody's gotta pick you up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and dust you off when you fall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, what are friends for, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Good afternoon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic Academy is proud to welcome you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to this grand skateboard championship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure all of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are going to knock us out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your Nollies, Ollies, kick flips</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and other Smith grinds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! You're really up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on your skateboarding, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I sure am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I was a roller derby champion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the seventies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a shame you don't talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I'd be glad to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't have the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, into the pipe, all of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yee haw!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] There you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The perfect mix of exceptional skills</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and incredible elegance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a word, classy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd. Great run out there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sam? How are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that was real class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to this program, we'll be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find your father on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's check it out in the lab now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this is the room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of our man of the hour, Jeremy Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding! Did you forget?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're filming you for a whole day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Kadic's special edition:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"A day in the life of Jeremy Belpois."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are? I did forget completely.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, but I have too many things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! We wanted to film our valedictorian</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during his busy day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly]You won't even know we're there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. I'll go to the lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and call you when I've tested the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'm all yours now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm glad to see you, Sam,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but aren't you supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be living on the coast?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am, but I also signed up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the championship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm only here for the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Samantha Knight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My turn. Don't move. I'll be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How weird is that to run into her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd almost forgot</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how cool and pretty she is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And how you're really in love.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you like somebody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without being in love?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure I can, but you're in love,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For breakfast, do you like juice or milk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hot chocolate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Eggs or toast?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cereal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Butter or jam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maple syrup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure your readers care</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about this stuff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm the reporter, and I know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what our readers want to read!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has launched an attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the chamber of the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, tell the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be there as soon as I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] If you're the reporter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right. Those are stupid questions!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you have better ones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what stops you from asking them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are! Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ladies, I have an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can do this interview later on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after you two have finished fighting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're staying until you answer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all my fascinating questions!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, that Odd, he's so--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So messy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what his room looks like!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's like me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My room's a permanent disaster zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that you two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were made for each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita? No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell Odd, and we'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Ulrich Stern!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone here wants to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dad, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, emergency. XANA's attacking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the chamber at the core of Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, not today!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents are gone for the day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to look after my brother.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-OK, I'll sneak out when he's not looking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki] Dream on, sis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm worried about your grades.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the reason I came.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we have to talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, but today</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not a very good time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think the time is long overdue!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wasn't expecting to see you and--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I wasn't expecting a report card</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as bad as yours was!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come with me. Mr. Delmas was kind enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to lend us his office.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can you give Odd a message for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell him to go to the "he knows where."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes? Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool! Great! I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, this is what I call fun!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, where did Ulrich go, Sam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He didn't say anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but tell me, how was I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, you really rock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Come on, Hiroki, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me go, and don't say anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll make it up to you. I promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll make it up to me how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, want me to give you my disc man?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll find you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the entire saga of Surfer Zombie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Johnny just lent it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do all your homework for a month!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Including my math homework?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, interesting… but no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA's monsters destroy the sphere,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko is gone for good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and without Lyoko, we can't fight XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I read you loud and clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the others to get here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll meet up with us later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's not waste time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, that's the reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you recruited me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mycology's a complicated science.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the branch of botany</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that deals with fungi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are several species,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they range in form</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a single cell to a mass body</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of branched hyphae</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>producing specialized fruiting bodies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The kingdom includes yeasts,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>molds, smuts and mushrooms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's that an interesting question?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My question was fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The answer was boring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry. I'll take back control of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sure, that's just typical.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-When I ask a question, you get angry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Completely untrue!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No it isn't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's right, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Saving Lyoko takes top priority.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be there as fast as I can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to transfer Odd, Ulrich and Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when they show up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, don't drag your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on. Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] That's the way it's gonna be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ladies, I have to go to the bathroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You weren't planning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on filming me in the bathroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The virtualization process will bring us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly to Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We only have a few seconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get to the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How long will you shoot this door?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's interesting to know how long</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>good students use the bathroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, that's some pretty classy gear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you? No weapon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You fight with your bare hands?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your super power?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't a video game, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have an important mission</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to accomplish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay, sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, where are the monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow me. We have few minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to trip a key lever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that gets us into the chamber</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Killer! This is ten thousand times better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Galactic Battle</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a movie set! Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The key! It's over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] I'm on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's that noise I hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Creepers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Creepy crawlers! I love this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You take care of the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of these guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it. They can be really tough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Works for me. So can I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Stern] I want to understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why your grades are so consistently poor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just that I can't seem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to concentrate all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Remember when you were my age.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! At your age, I had straight A's,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and was preparing my college application!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am the man!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, William, come over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, just one or two more of them, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is too cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where are the rest?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How would I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They're not in the computer lab?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, a weird looking creature</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just showed up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like some kind of giant jellyfish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You have to get to William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry! You have to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around the outside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take the next hallway on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster, before the Scyphozoa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>goes after William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take the corridor on the right. Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, get out of there! Do you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not afraid of some dumb jellyfish!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>William, just do what I say!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what the Scyphozoa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wants with you, but it can't be good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Take the next hallway</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on your left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not much further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, get out of there right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>William, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, the Scyphozoa hasn't moved an inch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Must be scared of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's been captured</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the Scyphozoa! Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, XANA's possessed William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm concerned about your friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think they're a good influence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How would you know? You don't know them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't even know me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We haven't spoken for a year!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I still know what's best for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah? What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That you respect your work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Need I remind you that I'm the one paying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're costing me a small fortune!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy. Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not finished speaking to you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I've finished listening!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take one more step,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll tell Dad everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a coincidence. It's dad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on and tell him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Daddy, Yumi wants to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's not dad, it's Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, did you get to the computer lab?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why should I? I'm in the finals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But didn't Sam tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to see you top that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sam, why didn't you give me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's message? It was important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Important? I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just really wanted you to stay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're lucky to be together again</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a day. I'm leaving tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know how you feel, Sam,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have to do something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even more important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than hanging out with me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unfortunately, yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The next contestant is Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Creepers growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>At last! Get to the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain everything on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've just lost the first shield layer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] If the second one goes…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko will disappear forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And William along with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At last, they're there now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] He doesn't look happy to see us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yep, looks like me when I saw my father.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If we lose Lyoko, I lose my father too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that the program I started a while ago?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! Unbelievable! It really works!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found Franz Hopper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Run the rematerialization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>program, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not very nice</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack people from behind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew it was a bad idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to bring you into the group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Nothing can stop them anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're going to destroy the sphere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't rematerialize Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't have enough time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've lost everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] William as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have no other way to fight XANA now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The entire world is in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's impossible even to imagine it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And William, you think that he's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is horrible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was really hoping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd see my father again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm sorry. I did everything I could.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I know you did, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laptop beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what the-- This is incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, tell us. What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just received a coded message…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A message directly from the Internet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's signed…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who? Tell us, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Franz Hopper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>