<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>STRAIGHT TO HEART</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Welcome back, campers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two weeks without us. Not too long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you miss me a little, ladies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could've stayed away three weeks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA attacks: zero.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well, a nice quiet summer, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kind of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since XANA discovered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to leave the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to access the World Wide Web,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we haven't heard anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No news is good news, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] That's what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I trust XANA as far as I can throw him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which is why I just reprogrammed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] From now on, we'll know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where the big bad wolf is hiding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but how's that gonna help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, first of all, we can try to find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how he plans to use the Internet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool, and then you send us in after him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so we can crack a few heads.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But wait, getting you into the Internet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't all that easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So first,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let's get a handle on what his scheme is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let me remind you:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have to pick up our class schedules</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So let's move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, wait a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did a lot of thinking during the summer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I have something important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tell me, I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you later, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Something important to tell you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think maybe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she wants you to ask her to marry her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right. I was gonna ask you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be my maid of honor, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No class on Saturday morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>meaning that on Friday night…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We can go to the movies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Forget it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It means I can go to the movies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're in the same class again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If cool means our worst nightmare,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Being in the same class is really cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have yourself a good laugh, Odd. Enjoy it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get it out of your system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because in a few seconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna be crying!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you real soon, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, why so sad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not in the same class as we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA attacks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what'll we do without him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was already complicated with Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now it's gonna be impossible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get organized!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not gonna be able to copy off you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My grades are really gonna go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>down the tubes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there's only one thing to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah, what's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Go for broke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, while he's going for broke,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll go for lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What was it you wanted to tell me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wanted to say that I--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Hey, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's really great to see you again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you have a good vacation?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you later, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really have to see him, ma'am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's a matter of life and death!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Delmas is not seeing any students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not here as a student,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm… here as a friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A friend?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes… I mean as a friend of Sissi's.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something really serious going on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I've got to speak to the principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>man to man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see what I can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd Della Robbia insists on seeing you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jim wants to start up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a basketball team this year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Seems he played pro ball…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[others] …but he would rather not talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what did you wanna tell me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki, what do you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just wanted to say hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Hiroki] Aren't you gonna introduce me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool it, sis! I was gonna introduce</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my new pal, Johnny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen Hiroki,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just because you're in junior high now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't mean you have to follow me around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>okay, bro?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better be nice or I'll rat on you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you come home late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a dork!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your sister's really gorgeous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're outta your mind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, it seems my Elisabeth has a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well sir, when she found out that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we weren't in the same class this year…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she just flipped!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see… I suppose I'll have to try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>reasoning with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's not much else I can do about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry to contradict you, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you see, all you have to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is put us in the same class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and presto, problem solved.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible, it's far too complicated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to change the composition of classes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In addition,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Morales was quite clear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when he requested that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, Belpois and you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should be separated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim? But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea. Why not ask him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Superscan has located XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm off to the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gotta find out more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait up! I'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay, what I wanted to say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, during all last year, I'd see--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just got here and you're leaving?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Guess!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jim, can I come in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As usual,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's never there when you need him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty funky there, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, nobody'll bother us here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we've both been running</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around in circles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One day we're together,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the next day we're not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one day you're jealous, the next day I am,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's why I think that we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to clear up our relationship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can be friends, but that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Uh-oh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] What's wrong, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We've got company.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has sent a ton of monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] He's probably mad</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we found him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that could be it… but then what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is he planning to do there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with all of his troops?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll head for the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll warn the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… what's that supposed to mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"friends, that's all"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Isn't it clear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, okay. "Friends and that's all."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fantastic… that's just great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, fantastic. That's just great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… yeah, we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim Morales…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Disco… film… enter…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[disco music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Paco, the King of Disco."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I see why you'd rather not talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about it, Mr. Morales.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our gym teacher really burns up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the dance floor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we're gonna burn it on a little CD!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Just the man I wanted to see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Oh really?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] About… disco.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I love disco!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was even pretty good at it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back in the old days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can see that… groovy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you know all about the film…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-"Paco, the King of Disco"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[record scratches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… never heard of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a fantastic film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was gonna submit it to Gustave Chardin</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for his film club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not sure that dud is worth showing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at a film club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, so then you have seen it, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got interested in the film club</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I'm pretty lonesome</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now that all my friends are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a different class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you get what I'm driving at…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, gimme that right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey you guys… what's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there a problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nope, no problem at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're the best of friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, that's a relief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's there already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] About time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone else is waiting for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What took you so long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I found a way to get back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into your class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did? How?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's easy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I decided to blackmail Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Blackmail Jim? But with what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know a secret</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he'd rather not talk about,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that he doesn't want anyone else</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk about either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think blackmail's really lame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since when did you get so high and mighty?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The end justifies the means, doesn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, thanks for your support.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet you'd be happier</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without me in class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're at the edge of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great. Now get into position,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'll enter the code "Scipio."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holosphere system, on line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] So, where are all these monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, what do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're all in a room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just below your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen that one before,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we haven't been there yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… what are they doing in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How am I supposed to know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the ones on-site.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Listen, instead of talking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>head for that room, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can we get in through here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, access is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the celestial dome. Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the countdown…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or you'll be back home a lot sooner</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You've only got a few minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Key in sight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought I had my A game going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go and get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Five…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>four…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>three… two…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>one…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you all better get here ASAP!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your hand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Looks like you got your Z game--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Lay off, will you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you talk to her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're at the elevator!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are more and more monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that mysterious room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a bad feeling about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] We're here, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where do we go now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to crack some monsters heads?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the south pole of the dome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's where you can get into the chamber.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Vehicles, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Coming up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, maybe that's where XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has his annual monsters' ball…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause up to now, we haven't seen any.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But look there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bull's eye! There's the A game!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get real, man, that was me who got him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is no time to compete</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with each other… move out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hang on, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're there. Can you see the access?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's pretty hard to miss, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great, go on in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you guys doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Aelita are already</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the passage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we know that! If Odd didn't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his XYZ game going, we'd be there by now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If this monster would just stop flying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a few seconds… ow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I get the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give you some more laser arrows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, ugly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now we'll see what you're made of!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nut case!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got a full supply.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich are in the tunnel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At last,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now we can trip the mechanism and go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, how are you ladies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little impatient.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think we're here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you see the monsters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are they doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're firing at some sort of blue ball!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA wants it destroyed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then it's gotta be important!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then it's down with the Creepers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Right! Go on, I'm gonna try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find out more about that sphere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle those two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you head for the sphere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Forget it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Concentrate on our monster friends!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, this is not just an A game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's more like an A plus!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super Sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, listen. Whatever you do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got to stop the Creepers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-from destroying the sphere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because that is the heart of Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The direct access to all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the core programs of the virtual world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the monsters destroy it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's game over for good for Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sphere has only two protective layers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the first one just blew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, it's your turn now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her turn for what? She can't do anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how could Aelita have done that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita developed some new powers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the vacation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's perfectly capable of fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like you can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, look at that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] She's been devirtualized!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you saying that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come on, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, do you realize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you almost gave me a heart attack?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would someone tell me what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it seems that even if Aelita loses</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of her life points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she won't disappear forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She won't? How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was too dumb to think of it before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ever since you recovered your</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>human memory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're exactly the same as us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't need Code Earth</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anymore to bring you in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'll really help now that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is determined to destroy Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep us from finding him on the Net.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a full-fledged Lyoko warrior</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from now on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Just friends"? And that's all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh… and what did you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I said, "Okay, fantastic."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Okay, fantastic"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'll never understand you two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To see Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? Be careful, good buddy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A bad deed can backfire on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I got news for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you came here to blackmail me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'd better think again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone who thinks he can pull</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the wool over my eyes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-is gonna be in for a surprise, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Blackmail isn't really my thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm very sorry, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you mean you did it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just to be with your pals?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… boarding school is tough enough,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but without your friends…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me see what I can do to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Okay, thanks Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're a real pal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… after all, I was young once too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No kidding! I wonder what you were like.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had blond, curly hair and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I would rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now get outta here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>