<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>BIG BUG</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children voices and birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And so my mom says: "I'm not gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let you go out dressed like that."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then she says: "Just look at your t-shirt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can see your navel!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you know me. I tell her:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Listen, mom, everyone dresses like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the latest style."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So then she says...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold it a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Ulrich. Just look at him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, how can anyone be that handsome?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Hello, little ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aren't we a bit wet behind the ears</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be looking at boys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it. Look at yourselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've even got a drop of milk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from your bottle on your cheek.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers] She believed you, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not only is she a baby,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she's also dumb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Nicolas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you should defend her, not insult her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You dumbbells ought to stick together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, girls,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're setting your sights much too high.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's way out of your league.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you just go back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to your dolls and stop dreaming?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think that because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're a few years older and play the snob</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that all you have to do is snap</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your fingers, and he'll come running?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think. I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There isn't a boy in school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's not dying to go out with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stick around and learn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Hi, how are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's Miss Conceited in person.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Nobody asked you, creep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So Ulrich, when are you going to stop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being so shy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and finally tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how you feel about me, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're wrong. I'm not shy, not at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just allergic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to anyone who's stuck up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And in that category, you win hands down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[only Nicholas laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet she's been telling you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how nobody can resist her charm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's right, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just take a look at the two "nobodies"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's always hanging out with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicholas growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Take it easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, you ought to be a dog trainer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you grow up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, laugh all you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Show your friends how clever you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] But I see the way you look at me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when they're not around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think she's hallucinating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Speaking of dogs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to go and feed Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna come, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promised Jeremy I'd stop by and see him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi Yumi, come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm working on a new program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sort of catastrophe alarm system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The idea is to rate non-natural disasters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a scale of one to ten,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and once I've got it finished it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna get it onto every website,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or information network, if you like,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and any time the system registers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a disaster that rates higher than five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it automatically informs me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And then what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's the surest way for me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to identify a possible XANA attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, that's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's on your mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's... it's Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you think he likes Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi? You're kidding. Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never would have believed it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you're really jealous, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[angrily] What? You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can you think for a minute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I could be jealous of that dimwit?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is ridiculous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, eat a little slower, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look like Nicolas in the lunchroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't insult my dog, huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His manners are ten times better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than that sloppy airhead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles] I've got a great idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that might be fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you say we take our friend Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>down a peg or two?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing in the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would rather do. What's your idea, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A message:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"You're the fairest of them all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't resist you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet me in the garden shed."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[male tech 1]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you read me? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't contact any aircraft!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[female tech 1]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The traffic lights are all blocked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The city's gonna be in total gridlock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[female tech 2] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The trains aren't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stopping anywhere. What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[male tech 2] I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I've got a sort of eye on the monitor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The train switches aren't responding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The trains are out of control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[female tech 2]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you contacted the conductors?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[male tech 2] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Most of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem is that trains 3611 and 9432</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are completely automatic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're on a collision course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I can't stop them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[female tech 2] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They're freight trains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How long before they collide?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[male tech 2]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Twenty-six minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the 3611 is a special convoy train,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>carrying a load of highly toxic chemicals!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] One last adjustment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the program should be ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now there's nothing left to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but wait until XANA rears his evil head.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A mysterious and powerful virus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>infected all of the country's main</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>computer systems just a few minutes ago.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The infrastructures affected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are very numerous and vital.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They include communication, banking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>subway systems and air traffic control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The most imminent danger however,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the probability of a major train crash.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For more information, here's John Swamp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you Ellen. That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two freight trains</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are on a collision course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and one of the trains</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is carrying highly toxic chemicals,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which if spread into the atmosphere,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would cause an unprecedented</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>environmental catastrophe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[train horn blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ellen] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>John, is there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any way of preventing this disaster?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>None at all, for the simple reason that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the trains are both computer operated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and therefore impossible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to control at this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll take a miracle to stop them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The authorities are considering</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an evacuation of the local population.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You try to warn Ulrich and Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll head over to the lab to contact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and prepare the transfers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh-oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's trying to reach us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna blow our cover.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gotcha. I'll shut off my cell phone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on with them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of you's gotta be able to answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm here, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans disgusted]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what is going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Irresistible Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not even a dog can resist your charms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey don't knock it, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a step up because Herb and Nicolas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are no match for Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles] Sorry, to drag you away, Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd whistles to Kiwi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll pay for this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's okay. soon as you're all dry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>send us the bill.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ciao.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi. go home now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Go home, boy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's a shame</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we didn't take a picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah. Imagine the headline</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Milly's and Tamiya's newspaper:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Sissi and Kiwi. An Impossible Romance."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] I seem to recall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a school rule that says:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Pets are strictly forbidden on campus."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rules must be obeyed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[train horn blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was working on your latest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>materialization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no time. We've got a big problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you noticed anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but I'll go have a look around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, were you able to contact them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, they've shut</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>their mobiles off. I'm looking for them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where in the world can they be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it. Go beddy, bye now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you horrible little mongrel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Yumi, you got here too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You missed a great show.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi's got herself a boyfriend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Although "boy" is not exactly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the right word. Anyway, they're in love.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I've been trying to reach you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for fifteen minutes. Thanks, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has just launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, I read you. It's urgent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim shouting] Hey, you there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as if we didn't have enough problems!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So it seems you forgot the rules</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here at school, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pets are not allowed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, we know that, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you're not gonna make a big deal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of a little dog, are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's for the principal to decide.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're even a worse pain in the neck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than I thought.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could she do such a thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She got her revenge, but we can't worry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about it now. There's no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>C'mon, there are too many lives at stake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The situation remains unchanged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The two freight trains</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are completely out of control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Army units have begun to evacuate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the people in the immediate area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now for other news around the country.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The capital is in a state</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of total gridlock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huge traffic jams are creating chaos,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the police are totally swamped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and unable to help,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and since all alarm systems are down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a tremendous amount of looting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Got anything new, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, I do, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've picked up pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that the activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the desert. I'm on my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, where's Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's in the principal's office</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause Jim found out about Kiwi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you two,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get ready for immediate departure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do we really have to stay here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be like that. Come on, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard the principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta stay in the study hall</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until your parents get here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and pick up that mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm gonna stay here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and keep an eye on you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Yumi grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's cool, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The transfer was successful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem, and Aelita's here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Great, and no monsters in sight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Any news from Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] No, not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm try to contact him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snores]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? Well, what do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Huh? What did you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uhh... nothing, I uhh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to go outside for a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dogs have well...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they have certain "needs,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you know what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it. What he needs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to get some sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs disappointed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower is there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, looks like a real XANA trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you see anything on your screen?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing, not even a single monster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Kiwi, come on, wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Want a biscuit?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi wonders]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A nice big doggy biscuit? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's the matter with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I warned you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I don't take him out for a walk,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna have some mopping up to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] You think I'm stupid, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon as you're outside,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll take off, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Me? I wouldn't do that, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay now, stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't pull that one on me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna take the dog out myself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you're gonna stay put and not move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[train horn blows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fourteen minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just 14 minutes left before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the two trains collide with each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember, one of them...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Alert, you're surrounded</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by four monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are they? I don't see any monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita and Yumi grunting and yelping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[intense beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Ulrich, get out of there now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're losing too many life points!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great idea only how do you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>suggest we do it? Sprout wings, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are a lot of rocks on your right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try and lose them in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yumi, take Aelita away with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll handle them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But Ulrich...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Don't argue. Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and inhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triplicate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact! [yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, are you gonna do it or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How're you doing, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Walking your "wittle" doggy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly and Tamiya laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you had your chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going back now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, did I miss the party?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess you could say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich has the grand total</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of ten life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about the trains?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eight minutes to impact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better get a move on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan and gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Telekinesis!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts] The coast is clear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on. Odd is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Welcome back to our world, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales exhausted]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm sorry, I did what I could.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're crazy! What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get out of there, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal chant]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rocks rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! I was sure she'd do that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans in slow motion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Just in time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Alone at last, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just the two of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb, what the...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi, I love you too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb smooches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you out of your mind or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I got your text message.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Meet me at the garden shed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love you. Sissi."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna give Tamiya and Milly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a real scoop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess who's gonna make the front page</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the next school paper?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just keep dreaming, you creep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've got some explaining to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when my father hears about this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi, wait a second!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's really such a shame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've just seen the beginning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the end of a beautiful romance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>