<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>JUST IN TIME</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Interface transferred... activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtual memory... activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Code management... configured.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanners... activated and verified.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Targeting... okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time it's going to work!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping and scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, Kiwi! Go on, fetch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone seen Jeremy this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think he spent the night</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the laboratory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was working on something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crack]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I thought it was time out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Guess I forgot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys, guess what I did last night!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see now, it's got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something to do with materializing Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, how did you guess, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well guys, I finally did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I decided to tackle the problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a different way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] You wouldn't believe it, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, tell us. Did you do it or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You materialized a test tube?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, airhead. Look inside, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A hair? You mean you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>materialized </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>one </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>hair?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right, Odd. To be exact...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's a hair of Aelita's!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Odd gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What, a real hair?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how did you manage that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well, I chose a hair because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's a simple anatomical structure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but which contains Aelita's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>complete genetic computer code,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to a well-known fractal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whose recurrences</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are comparable to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the genetic code of a human,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which enabled me to make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a physiological number transfer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto one part of the program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>already pre-targeted and defragmented...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] And that's that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Simple enough, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Do you follow?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's not simple enough,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or no, you don't follow?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"No" means that we take your word for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem. It'll become clear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when Aelita's here in flesh and blood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better get ready, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] You're going to materialize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not going to wait until next year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The hair was just a test before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we do the whole thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, making a hair appear is one thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materializing Aelita is not the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look. You want to spend</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your whole life fighting XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Once Aelita's been materialized,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can unplug XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once and for all, and lead normal lives.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] So, I say it's worth trying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can that be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I had planned everything so perfectly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You're almost there, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a few days, you'll be all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, guys, if we don't materialize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a couple of minutes in the classroom,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're not going to last a few days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have sworn that it'd work this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, if the computer gene code of the hair</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gives you enough information</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find the parameters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for materialization,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then, what's the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I knew. I'm doing something wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The only way to find out is start over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] No, don't do that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're only a "hair's breadth" away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Can't you ever be serious, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Odd, speaking of hair,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your dog sheds an awful lot of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Most of them end up on my bed, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the big deal about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>two or three hairs?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two or three? With all the hairs he sheds,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could knit you another Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Hello. Did you say "dog"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really adore dogs. Hey, can I sit down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I'm so crazy about dogs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I'm ready to keep my mouth shut</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the one Odd's hiding in his room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is if you promise to be nicer to me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen Sissi, I'm warning you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you say anything about Kiwi, I'll...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You okay, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There we are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Dorothy] It's nothing serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The cut isn't very deep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, put this on it please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's incredible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I barely squeezed the glass.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're pretty fragile, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Fragile, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not talking about Venetian crystal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lunchroom plastic's more like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I know what I'm in for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I get on your nerves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both titter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[romantic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich's phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a disaster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I was trying to figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why the materialization didn't work,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I realized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's program is full of bugs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I materialized the hair,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hit a button I shouldn't have,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so I damaged the annex programs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Annex? That doesn't sound so bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The part of the program linking Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the towers is screwed up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Aelita enters the Lyoko code,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she'll be completely reformatted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meaning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She'll disappear forever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You know, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a program can be debugged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can do it together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA attacks before we're done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means you got to work fast, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>make up a story to tell to the teachers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not leaving this computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until I've solved the problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You think they can do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've got two geniuses at work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Odd, if you don't get Kiwi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to calm down, they're going to find him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi yelping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, quiet, Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You heard me, quiet down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking frantically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[window pane cracks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Did you smell something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Did</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> you</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, maybe it was a ball that did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] And you, of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't see anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't have seen anything, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because I wasn't here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe so, but since all the rooms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are off limits during the day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how come you knew about the window?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, clean up your bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's hair all over it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] I don't know...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim didn't spot Kiwi, but it was close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi will have to stay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Jeremy for a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if you scanned</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the STR connection blocks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I already did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not where I went wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop chewing my slipper!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, sorry Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was talking to the dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When he's around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's hard to concentrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi panting and barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans] Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Give that back to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give it back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] That dog! He took my...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>handkerchief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans] Take him away, please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] That mutt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I was just passing by and...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I always said Sissi's head</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was full of plaster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm heading for the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the dog barking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the school falling apart,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't work in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope he finds the right solution</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before XANA attacks again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you guys tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hello, anybody home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] All these things happening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First Yumi's glass breaks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then the window gets shattered, and now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the ceiling. You think it's XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe it's just coincidence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm back, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, I don't believe it! Not now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we can get back to work... Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's XANA! He's launched an attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning and stammering] Are you... sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no, it can't be! Not now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I've never seen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such a thing in my entire career.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Do you think humidity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could have caused it, sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It doesn't look very damp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been after him for a long time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What the...?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim! We have to evacuate the building!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] It's XANA for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah, it's him. How does he do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your guess is as good as mine,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you heard Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi began barking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just before the ceiling fell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That might be a lead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the window, it was the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe Kiwi can feel the attacks coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Or, maybe he can hear them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a kind of ultra sound.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich's phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>XANA alert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's what we thought. Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Warn Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's real this time. XANA has woken up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas through school intercom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your attention please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Due to a danger of a structural accident,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>please evacuate the building calmly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and leave the immediate area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one will be permitted to enter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the building until further notice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi! He's in Jeremy's room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll go and get him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you at the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hello. Hi Ulrich. What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm not really ready yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi! Where are you? Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muffled voices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly groans] Didn't anyone ever teach</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you to knock?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't you hear the principal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to get out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] The whole building may collapse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] Come on, cut it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No, I swear. I'm not joking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] What's wrong with your dog?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing and banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About face.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, how are things going over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are cracks in the school building.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It may cave in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's using</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some kind of ultra sound system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ultra sound? That's possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] He could be using</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the electrical sockets.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, he might attack the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd's on his way, and I've warned Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope XANA gives me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough time to repair my program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich's phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I'm stuck, right...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Milly and Tamiya, if you must know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The firefighters will be here any minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So I can't meet you right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, don't wait. Go to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[plaster cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girls scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No time to lose, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm not finished fixing the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd is in danger. Transfer me right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dogs howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking and rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes] They're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>There's nothing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on my holomap for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things seem pretty calm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That's not what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the pulsations say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we follow them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're bound to lead us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the tower XANA's activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] What happened here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi sobs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd. He's stuck inside...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with Milly and Tamiya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music and cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Why aren't they here yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, we can't stay here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to cross over to the other side.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you out of your mind, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's at least a ten-metre drop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trust me, okay? I can't tell you how yet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we're going to make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] In the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we've got to get across</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where we'll be safe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem! Your turn now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sobbing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're coming to the parallel paths.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how many life points do I have?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on... 70, no, 60.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make up your mind, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to know. Take cover Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I can't do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a million things at once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dodge the lasers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you won't have to keep count.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi! Immediate departure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Aelita need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] The pulsations are separating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in two directions now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Then head east!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The monsters you managed to dodge before</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't very far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll try to find another path.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Need a hand around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here you go. Okay, your turn, Milly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, I'll never make it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Sure you will. Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good going, girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girls groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts] Get back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's pulled out all the stops.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're not going to last long, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A little patience, guys. I'm almost done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Aelita can enter the program now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's safe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're all set. Hang on Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up the repair program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just in time, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's getting kind of hot around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. This can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[banging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I've got to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, give me a little more time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start over again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you know there's no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be reformatted and disappear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! I can't let you do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you ready for one last run?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita! Don't do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be in front...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly and Tamiya groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> No! Don't do it, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Goodbye, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it wasn't your fault.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was. And all that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a strand of hair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, the hair!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, didn't you say that the hair</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>contained Aelita's entire genetic code?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Her computer code, yes, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it possible to reverse things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and recreate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's code from the strand of her hair?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It works! The codes are getting restored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Let's hope that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready for my materialization now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita! It worked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, did I miss something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why is there water on your face?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll tell you later, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time, we only missed... by a hair!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>