<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>SWARMING ATTACK</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[TV beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping rapidly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs, clicks tongue]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hello, is anyone there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy] Mrs. Hertz caught us red-handed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She made us give up our cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[increased buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you really look wiped out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did you do last night?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I worked on a little program;</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an advanced research engine of sorts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a... it's a browser,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which I'm trying to make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to help Aelita look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for more info on materialization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Lyoko towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just imagine all the things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's gonna learn when she gets here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna be amazed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think about it all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait for that day to come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, it's gonna... It's gonna be great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay guys, it's time for us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to work up a sweat. So long, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, wait I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah. Why are you asking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just... just...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>asked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Ulrich, move it, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Ulrich, I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to tell you this, so I'm writing it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've always admired you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been wanting to tell you for ages,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I didn't have the nerve.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Also, I wasn't a hundred percent sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But now, I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love you. Yumi."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] How could that have happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, don't take this badly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but your playing was kinda weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can say that again. Why even Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was better than you today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-My mind wasn't on the game. Lay off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll lay off as soon as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you tell us what's wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's just that... well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got this letter from a girl...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the kind of letter a girl sends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she's...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's in love!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's in love!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the problem. I'm not in love.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I... I'm not sure I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't even manage to talk to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And can you tell us who the lucky lady is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not telling anyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more thing, not a word to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want this to get around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Hey, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-did I really play better than him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Milly or Tamiya?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] No, they're too young.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Claire?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Sandra?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] No, no, much too young,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're so, you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're... they're too uptight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Emily! Hey, yeah, it's her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm an expert with girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's pretty. She's the outdoors type.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-She's the one who flipped for him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Oh yeah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Who has Emily flipped over?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Jim. Emily's crazy about Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jim? You're kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, they say that love is blind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers] Oh, I'm... I'm... sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking, panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi sniffing loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who did that to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Kiwi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi whimpering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] He doesn't look well at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think it's serious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Don't worry, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll be back on his feet in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, back on his paws.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knock on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I brought some pills</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and anti-venom compresses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Yumi. Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This'll make you feel better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Yumi, come over here please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to tell you something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They say Emily is in love with Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] With Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd told me all about it. Weird, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a class now. See you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's that all about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Then I heard this buzzing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>coming from the trees.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There must be dangerous insects up there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for the information, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Bennett yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help! Help! Get them off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll try to attract them to us. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Bennett groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta get him to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] That way! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Yumi grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs, gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you're... you're hurt, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh... It's nothing serious, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a scratch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I think we can go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well, Mr. Bennett was lucky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more bite and...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that's right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he's still not in great shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The principal sent for help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're gonna get rid of the nest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what you guys think, but I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you think it's XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Come on. Cut it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hornets' nests have always been around,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and accidents happen all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, but these hornets...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they were after us and nobody else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I say we check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to contact Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going back to class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but keep me posted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you realize the damage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>these bugs can cause?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are thousands of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA is in on this attack,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we could have a very serious problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't you think so? Hello!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts] What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Yeah, right...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you wouldn't happen to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a crush on this secret admirer of yours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you? Hmm, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, you could be right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Emily clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's all this about me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>being in love with Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[smack]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Emily] Start that rumor again</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and even your dog won't recognize you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are things in the real world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got a problem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we think it might be XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Have you noticed anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least here in the desert,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>things are calm, but if you want,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can check out the other regions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And in the meantime, I'll run a scan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see if there's an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chime tinkling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, the scanner's spotted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an activated tower in the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'm in the forest now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to find it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Alert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has activated a tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Aelita's trying to find it, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks as if something's up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy wants us to go</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the factory right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No. No, wait, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to... to tell you something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's about your... about your letter.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, let me finish.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You said in the letter that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>certain feelings for me and...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted you to know that...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I feel the same thing for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There, I've said it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I never sent you any letter, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi, Herb and Nicolas laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] Oh, that has got to hurt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Kind of embarrassing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you ask me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Forget them. Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't care. Leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow. Nice going, XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any suggestions would be very welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Get away as fast as we can?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We're trapped!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, you got any other ideas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jump!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[coughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is your idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Insects are very sensitive to smells.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not the only ones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd sniffs, groans in disgust]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, I think it worked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Looks like it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] What's that smell?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Ask Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We left you a message. Didn't you get it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't feel like checking my messages.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I think we should talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what you're gonna tell me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't wanna hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, this is all on account of Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you think I know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But because of her, I'm confused.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Every time I see you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't what to think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] So just leave me alone, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's losing it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. I found the activated tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's guarded. I can't access it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry. Help is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey guys, hold on a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The bugs have blocked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the factory entrance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I would rather stay out of that sewer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm way ahead of you on this one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what's the deal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping, whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty clever, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This thing generates ultrasounds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of about 30,000 hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like all insects,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hornets are capable of receiving...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fascinating, but we don't have time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so let's move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing, whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[firemen grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[fireman one] Get inside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[kids screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fireman two] Come on, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Headquarters, we've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're at the junior high school. Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your thing stopped. How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Battery's dead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd and Yumi] Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're on our way. Hang in there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time to lose. To the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come in, Aelita. Aelita, answer me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no, this cannot be happening!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you see her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] No, not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, talk about embarrassing situations,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure that Ulrich's not about to forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this for a long time. What a genius I am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] You could say something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb and Nicolas scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping, grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Wait up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Careful, three swarms</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of hornets converging. Get ready!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Less than 20 life points left,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi. Be careful, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, 80 life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wake up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, two enemies at three o'clock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Aelita! [groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, Yumi! Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, I'm fine, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[kids screaming and crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it! They're coming back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you've only got 20 life points left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd, you have hardly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any life points left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, are you with us or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you're unhappy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there's no reason to be.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our friendship's stronger than that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You can't let Sissi's dirty tricks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>break us up, can you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So forget all about that, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two head for the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'll take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's about time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Aelita grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triangulate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts, sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Go on, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you're the greatest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[kids screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Get away! No! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rapid rewind whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] I was just passing by and I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's see now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's a...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's a pretty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>embarrassing situation, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I... This wasn't the right door</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure isn't. Why not give it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to Nicolas or to Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They'd be delighted!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Yumi laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>