<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TEMPORARY INSANITY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What took you so long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I almost didn't wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just having a word with Lucy Anne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Lucy Anne?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, you know, Lucy Anne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love giving nicknames to the monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I blow to smithereens.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess she wasn't too crazy about her name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta take better care of your stuff,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'm trying to collect more data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Franz Hopper</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can't access the sub-systems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Flying Mantas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>coming your way at ten o'clock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mantas shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how's everything going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because around here, things are kind of…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…heating up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not great. For now, I don't have any data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that tells me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how to locate Franz Hopper, I'm afraid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to hold out a little longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Easy for you to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm about ready to access the sub-systems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many life points do we have left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not many. If you get hit by one more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Flying Manta, it'll be game over, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Same goes for you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Buckle up, Shirley.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ethel, Yvette, get back here right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, cut it out with your dumb names, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why aren't we devirtualized?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beats me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They shot at us and this is what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You guys okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All in one piece, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, I think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Two great legs…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a swell torso, two limber arms and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a good-looking head. No, nothing missing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, what happened out there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to look back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the quantum sequence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to track any possible abnormalities</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the access data.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mind translating that, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He has to carry out a full check.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way, there's not time. We've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rehearsal in exactly five minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rehearsal? Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I completely forgot about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chardin is gonna kill us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We want our money back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We want our money--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poliakoff, do you mind using</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your head for once?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can you get money back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a show that's totally free?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[kids chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We would have to give you back nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which, if you ask me, is too much.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, try showing some respect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Theatre, don't forget, is sacred!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids mumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Believe me, I know from experience.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Years ago, I even wrote a one act…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, actually,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was more of a one scene play.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, really? What was it about, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Phew, there you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, everyone, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Mr. Chardin,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what made you choose Cyrano de Bergerac</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for this year's performance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The elegance of the text, I imagine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or the tragedy of unrequited love?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or perhaps it appeals to your true</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but hidden romantic nature.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Lack of money.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since we had no choice, we had</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to use last year's Romeo and Juliet set</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the costumes. I had to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another play that had a balcony.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Cyrano.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Roxane!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who calls me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It is I, Christian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Today, your words are hesitant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Night has come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the dusk, they grope their way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find your ear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But my words find no such impediment.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They find their way at once?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, small wonder that, for 'tis</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>within my heart they find their home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Bethink how large my heart,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how small your ear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And from their fair heights</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>descending, words fall fast</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but mine must mount, Madame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] They need more laser arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[audience mumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Methinks that your last words</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have learned to climb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With practice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such gymnastics grow less hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] In truth, I seem to speak</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from distant heights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Two kankrelats, dead ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>True. Far above at such a height,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'twere death if…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, okay, I'll get them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, Della Robbia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you babbling about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, sir. Keep it down. Don't you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cutting edge theatre when you see it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a modern approach,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere between </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The Bald Soprano</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a deadly karate match!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that, you old Krab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[audience gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, help me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm hit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bravo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super sprint!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut it out! Your gag is not funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's lame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You made me miss the Megatank!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Odd, what's gotten into you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Out of the way, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't see the Krab!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time, you've gone too far!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>One more word out of you, and</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's the disciplinary committee, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wait, please, Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd isn't himself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does XANA have a broken hard disk or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Krab sounds a lot like Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, watch out! A Blok at four o'clock!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] A Block?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the blockhead, Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick, someone call an ambulance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern and Della Robbia</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have totally lost it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, reload me. Two Tarantulas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are getting the better of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're stuck in another of XANA's traps!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi, do something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So this is what happens</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you spend hours playing video games</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and watching cartoons on TV.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rehearsal is over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They are stuck in another of XANA's traps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go follow them to the hospital.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see if I can figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's happening in the meantime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Did you give them something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to calm them down?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, tell me, are you having some problems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the moment?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal] Are you sleeping well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal] Nightmares?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal] Restless nights?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal] Troubles at school?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With your parents?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that, you rotten old Blok!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[imaginary gunfire]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Rotten old Block," interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me at it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sorry, young man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm a tenth dan in Aikido.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, XANA is definitely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>behind Odd and Ulrich's madness.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only one way to make them normal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's to get them to a way tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>somewhere on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Then I can launch a program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get their head straight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean we have to spring them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the hospital?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello. We're here to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich Stern and Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but they're both under observation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No visitors allowed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Thanks a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry we interrupted you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in hushed voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet! Listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The two young men in room 237</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are fighting imaginary enemies</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they call Blocks, Megatanks and XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where do they get such crazy names from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you think, Prof. Hornet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Typical of today's youth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now we know what room they're in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave him to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, excuse me, ma'am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you need any help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm… I'm… looking for my room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>room 216.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nurse] Come with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, watch out for the Krabs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What Krabs?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The ones blocking us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's one down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That Krab just wouldn't let go of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think it was love at first bite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nurse] Here you are, room 216.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you for showing me the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[granny] Game of tiddlywinks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've located the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go. We'll cover you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoever wins</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>gets to take the other person's medicine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps, stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No thanks. Another time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you didn't come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a game of tiddlywinks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then what are you doing in my room,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>young lady?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You little rascal, you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[granny] Get out! Or I'll call the nurse!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, now that you're here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can go to the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell dings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, right. Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, let's get going then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I sure hope that this is gonna work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where do you think you're going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The Bloks caught up with us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Chantal] Out of my way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Is this police headquarters?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, no! That's all we needed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The core is being attacked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Will you pick up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is attacking the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope they get here on time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a little further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower's not far now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[police sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of the Megatank.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich! No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this crazy kid trying to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, tell us what it feels like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be part of the evening news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That should take care of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where can they be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There you are. It's about time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only one more shield left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>protecting the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would you mind sending me the overboard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'Cause I'm getting tired</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of running around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any idea how we can get them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into the scanners?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave it to me, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, guys. You made it there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now head for that way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd. Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, wow, it's empty out here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not a kid in sight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess they're all in the lunchroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Your turn, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is getting worse and worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now they think they're at the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, Aelita. You lead them to the way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tower. I'll head for the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Let's go to the…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Lunchroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I'm starving!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcoming committee</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>straight ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be careful, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[monster shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi, in a bad mood?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you break the scale this morning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] They put Sissi and her pals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a display case or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm here, at the edge</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the sector! Can you send me a taxi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You bet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A big white stretch limo is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the dork that pushed me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into Sissi's arms?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holosphere system connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm in the core zone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi, great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The countdown's started.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got less than one minute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to activate the key.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think we're on Lyoko or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something just stung me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry up, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've only got ten seconds left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nine, eight, seven, six, five, four,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>three, two, one… Zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Nice job, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now head for the Celestial Dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I'm on my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm programming your Overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, the lunchroom is that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to me, both of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna do exactly as I say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and no questions, you got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm in the dome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now get in there. That's an order!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Ma'am, yes, ma'am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope this works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see if this program is operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you guys feel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what are we doing inside a way tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shouldn't we be in the lunchroom?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it worked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but the core is still in danger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna need some help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's on the way. By now, Ulrich and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should be close to Sector Five, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up! Yumi needs your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! The last protective shield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is about ready to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm doing all I can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful. All the core shields are gone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it takes one hit, just one,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko is gone for good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you guys along with it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice work, guys! Time to bring it back in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what? Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just kidding, ladies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Right. Well, it's a good thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that while some people are clowning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around, others keep working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Methinks that your last words</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have learned to climb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With practice,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such gymnastic grow less hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In truth,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I seem to speak from distant heights.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>True. Far above at such a height,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'twere death if a hard word</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from you fell upon my heart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stop, stop, stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you're not there, not just yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What you're missing is a bit more…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>More passion?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no, some…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some popcorn?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some more funding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That'd be good. But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A touch of insanity?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly, yes! That's it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>