<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give, all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>CLAUSTROPHOBIA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita speaking through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, Jeremy. Hi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All alone? Where are the others?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] They're out playing soccer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I was feeling tired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tired? That's interesting!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how do humans know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when they feel tired?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you feel like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't have any energy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like having weak batteries,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so we rest a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And... is resting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something you like doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I used to find it really boring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But ever since I met you, Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's such a pleasure hanging out together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It is for me too, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hey Ulrich, pass it over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You won't get by me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both] Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Another goal! Seven to one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is turning into a romp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] It sure is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay guys! It's getting late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've gotta head for home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay. So long, Yumi. See you tomorrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys are so bad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a couple of losers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you guys need a little help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Theo. I'm new around here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just moved into town.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! And I like this school already!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both chuckle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi, my name is Sissy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm-hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And these two friends of mine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are Herb and Nicolas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The worst soccer players you ever saw.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice to meet you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd is the name. And he's Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi Theo! Welcome!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you play?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I sure do. Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which team should I play with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't need you, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought you were down seven to one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you think, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why not? Yeah, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure can't get any worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Theo] Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Theo clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] All right, Jeremy. I'm here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy speaking through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're looking for the tower where part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the scanner programs are stored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's at thirty degrees north, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm on my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>As soon as you're connected,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll download the data that you find.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll help me understand</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>materialization better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, guys! We've gotta stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time for dinner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nine seven, we beat them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think, princess?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Theo saved you guys from humiliation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who cares about soccer? It's a dumb game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Herb's got it in for Theo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great! Peas and carrots</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the umpteenth time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mystic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, why don't you eat with us, champ?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks a lot, but I can't abandon my team.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, stop trying to worm your way in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not in our group,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so go take a hike.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah, I know, Herb, but I'd love</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to join your group, or should I say...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi's group, is that it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do I have to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you've gotta pass</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our initiation tests,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're very really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dangerous and hard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Much too hard for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Initiation tests?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell me a little about them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Test number one! You have to clean</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the toilets with a tooth brush.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That sounds like a pretty dumb test.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like the kind they give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a ten-year-old at summer camp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So I'll pass on that one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay! Since you refuse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to pass our tests... Ciao!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Since when do you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>decide on the tests?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you what you have to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna mummify the skeleton</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we use in the science room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now that sounds cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb grunts and mumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>did you manage to gather all the data?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I did, but it won't do any good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not unless I can pirate the access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>codes for the scanner programs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>But that's almost impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, Aelita! I think it can be done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog making noises]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay! They've left their rooms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm-mmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll tell you all about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Operation Theo later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here I go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still a long way to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you gonna do, Herb?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna warn our old friend, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll kick Theo out of school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we'll be home free…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What was that weird sound?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunt in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Nice work, little ghost!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What're you two guys doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay. We were gonna tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dog grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, things look serious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between Sissi and Theo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, they sure do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh... You finished lunch already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but I want to see Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a while before class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't mind either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go together. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Leave your trays.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a shame to let good desserts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go to waste.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd, don't you ever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stop eating, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts] Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are gonna explode</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you keep this up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mmm... Nah... [slurps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electric explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Which region are you in now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just in the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I thought I sensed some pulsations,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm not sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] I'll call Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, weird things are happening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the lunchroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could be XANA's doing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why? What's the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are short circuits everywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, could you check things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll launch a scan to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if XANA activated a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! I wasn't mistaken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Tower localized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, there are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>very strong pulsations in the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, the scan confirms it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Odd and Ulrich are trapped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the cafeteria.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I'll head for the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Warn the principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then meet me over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocking on the door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Come in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I see you for a minute,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>sir, please? It's important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jim, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] Oh, Jim, say something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Are you all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to cut the current now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, is that you, dad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't know what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There's electricity everywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're trying to break a window to get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans] Ulrich, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're prisoners here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the cafeteria, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send Yumi to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll do our best over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have a lot of time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told the principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm at the passage in the park now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles continue]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is this? I just cut all the power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With no effect at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The firemen are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting] Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I have no idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what XANA wants to do this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about in town?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have any of the other buildings been hit?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that's why I'm worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll get out of this. Don't worry, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let me go, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girl crying]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Everything'll be okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Help is on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There, you see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] We could try the roof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Theo] It's probably the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's worth trying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Theo] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Out of the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like a prison.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how come XANA's set his sights</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the cafeteria?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It makes no sense at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You can't get access to the city</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He probably has other ideas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, I think I understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the four of us he's after!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Us? You sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and I left lunch before dessert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If not, we'd have all been there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wanted to catch us all together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA hasn't missed a trick this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're never gonna get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You've gotta play for time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna need every second</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she can get to protect Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll do the best we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the pulsations are really intense here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The tower can't be too far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Stay where you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I programmed the position.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi's on her way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital and electric sounds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pulsations radiate in two directions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, any news?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Give me a little time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to analyze the terrain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm getting contradictory signals.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impossible to tell which path</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is the right one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well, we have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Each of us will explore one path.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll stay in contact via Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tamiya] You see? This way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if the walls cave in, we'll be safe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The roof won't fall on top of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thumping sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! [gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Theo] Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sissi, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer me, child! Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how are things going with Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing to report for now, and no monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in sight. That's really strange.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Should I go on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll call you back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in thirty seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A quick analysis of the surroundings.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I gotta get out! I gotta get out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, no, don't Herb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The electricity! It's live!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Take it easy, Herb! Calm down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm stuck. [gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This tunnel has got to lead somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's got to lead to the path Aelita took.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I go. [gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two monsters are on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You're surrounded by two crabs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It's impossible, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I cut all of the wires, chief.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I doubt that. Nothing's changed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have the firemen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really tried everything, daddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're going to keep trying, dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Theo gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Theo] We'll be okay, you'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, have you got anything new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm trying, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay out of sight, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi will get here on time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know she will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have faith in you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have faith in you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I call getting carried away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi darling, you mustn't give up hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The firemen are going to make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an opening in the roof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all whining and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all whimper in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's got to be a passage leading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the path that goes to the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roof cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all over now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for what you did before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was pretty awful to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, this is urgent. Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it, a third crab is on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] There it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] No, leave him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on now, hurry. Don't worry about me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Good shot, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he's only damaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>But you took</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>twenty life points from him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more shot, and he'll be done for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's entering the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb screaming and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, Ulrich, pass it over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't get by me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Goal! [laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unbelievable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You losers!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay guys. I've gotta head for home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If you want, I'll walk you back home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, I'll go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So long, Odd, and thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, which way do we go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a lot better than having to get up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tonight to scare Herb, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong? Come on, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're toast, dude. Hmm-mmm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're never satisfied.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got a better idea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No? Well, me neither.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>