<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm just about through with Norbert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Don't tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're still giving them stupid names?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you have any idea what kind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of attack it is, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but with a bit of luck,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we were onto</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it faster than XANA anticipated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right. When Odd checks in,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA checks out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's not fair, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd glitches] I don't know. I can't move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm coming. Supersprint! Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see it, but I can't figure it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Norbert, you're not gonna--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, I'll try to distract them away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches and moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Krab is bugged too. Go for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Great job, Aelita. Nice one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That was so weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As if everything bugged up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know what could have happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that might've been XANA's attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? That's all you can come up with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you better start working on your A game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I suppose that was your A game</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against your pal, Norbert?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got some routine checks to carry out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just to be sure it was XANA's attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on and eat without me. I'll catch up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can I have your portion?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shepherd's pie tonight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and it's also boys' dorm inspection,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so don't be too long, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This'll take a few minutes, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, Kiwi, tonight you stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The last thing we need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is for Jim to find you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-My little diggity dog.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now then, let me remind you that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your rooms should be in impeccable order.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keeping your room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>neat and clean is a sinequa…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… sine… qua… How do you call it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Cine…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-…matography?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right! No, that's not it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… Anyway, it's an important part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a good night's sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He who sleeps well lives well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that is why man wasn't meant</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to live in a garbage dump,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause you can't sleep well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a minute… Hey, where's Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… In the bathroom, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? You mean all this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shepherd's pie doesn't agree with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dog groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is all this stuff about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh-uh, it's getting weirder.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is sabotage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Somebody's been in here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sabotage?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes. By Michael Reilly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>possessed by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what yesterday's attack was,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the bugs that prevented you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were caused by the drop in the calculating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>capacity of the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a mess! Think you can fix it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but I've got to do it fast</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or else we're in real big trouble guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We are? How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's simple.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The internal circuit has been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>badly damaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now, the Quantum bytes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are collapsing one after the other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The drop in computing speed will</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>become more and more serious,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-right up until the--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Stop. Reader's Digest version.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How much time do we have?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Three hours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you absolutely sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the whole thing will be destroyed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Definitely.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's already lost a lot of speed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I even tried to launch a return</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the past to see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way. I've gotta pick up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some stuff from my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then I'm gonna head back over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As for your classes, you'll have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to think of some phony excuses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, guys, but I've got to go now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chardin is taking us to see an exhibit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep me posted, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh no. The inspection!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you have time to clean your room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You mean, since last week?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I looked for you everywhere last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yours is the only room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't inspected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get up. Come on, on your feet. Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-So you can't eat shepherd's pie either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's he talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What on earth do you call this, Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… It's called my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An excellent student like you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You ought to be ashamed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are not leaving this room until you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>make it a hundred percent spic and span.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And these things, what are they?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Huh? Computer magazines.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our Einstein, really is a geek, isn't he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what do you think you three</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we thought he might be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>able to use some help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gonna do it himself,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without anyone's help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go to your classes right now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and double time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim's gonna get off Jeremy's back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'til he's through cleaning up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and in three hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's adios</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I can try to fix it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I'll be that's what Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>meant when he gave me this box.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you think you can do it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-At least I can try to limit the damage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Besides, we don't have much of a choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go to class, and tell them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got sick from hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the shepherd's pie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll let you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if I come up with anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Good luck, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, huh… the bus is late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When's it gonna come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There isn't any. We're all going to walk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything for art, children.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim groans] Straighten her out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna hover in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you see you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an F-4 Phantom on your tail?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Yeah, what do you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We heard that one of the students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>failed his dorm room inspection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could you tell us who that might be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… I certainly will not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When it comes to our students,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I refuse to divulge any names.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Especially when we're talking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about Jeremy Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both] Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! XANA is on the attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, where are you? I finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it okay if I go now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, okay, we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going in. I'll tell Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Breathe deeply.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing like taking in a breath of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fresh air before taking in some fine art.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which part of the museum are</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you gonna visit first, huh, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The impressionists or the pop art?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Neither. The gift shop. I'm gonna try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get something there for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What would you like, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Well, as usual, she couldn't wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give me the slip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think that Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got the thing fixed yet, huh, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll find out soon enou--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and whimpers in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Got any sunblock?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, now get to class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and hurry it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Jim. See you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[things fall]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Belpois, get back in here right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I did what I could in the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I don't know if it'll hold up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The others? No, nothing yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then, hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, try to free my hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What, are you joking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, I'd like to be able to move my own!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Here they are! Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty good timing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh, watch it Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>coordination's never been your thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey. Ulrich, run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Join Aelita, and try</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where are the others?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy and Odd are kind of "tied up."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to do without them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi isn't here yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Same here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These stupid roots are blocking the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Don't wait for me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi! No time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's in trouble, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll start up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a self-virtualization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you manage to fix the Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, just temporarily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to get out of this one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just like we said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we didn't say anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why we have a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on, I think I may have an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great. I'm dying to hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time, but when I give the signal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've gotta try with all your might</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get yourself free. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should try to get free, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could've thought of that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gotta trust me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you think of something more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>convincing to say for once?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, two Tarantulas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not exactly the end of the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Should we use force?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is there any other way?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Our brains?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't have any.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Supersprint! Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantulas growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roars]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since I'm in black and white,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>might as well fight the old fashioned way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>En garde!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Touché!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantula growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This time, we've had it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tarantula roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Tarantula growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what happened?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nothing special.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The bugs also affect the monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that kind of makes things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even for once.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The signal…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Quick, let's get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[roars and glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get to the scanner room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How many life points</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do you think you have left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Definitely less than you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, so you'd better watch it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you're there! That's cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes, and Odd's coming to the rescue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triplicate!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good job, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Any last words</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before we both get devirtualized?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's what I wanted to hear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good to see you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Coochy coo! I guess</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're not ticklish under the claws.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Here's a little something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get around with. Saddle up, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone out there? Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>losing more and more power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to go on foot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't have time to finish the repairs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know, Aelita, but you did a great job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, I can finish it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Do it as fast as you can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's bugging up more and more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we still haven't heard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anything from Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll do whatever I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just worry about that stupid tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here comes another mega problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There. That ought to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, that is so uncool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How are you doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein? It's killing us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We can't take a step without bugging up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, all I have to do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is reboot the works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better step on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough juice to reboot the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we could only deactivate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I could use its energy to restart</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the whole system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's fine, Jeremy, but over here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can't deactivate the tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unless you reboot the system.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There is one way to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, I'm listening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Destroy the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good old Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even during the worst of times,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she keeps her sense of humor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? You mean you weren't kidding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, that's crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, it's the only way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to recover some energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>and avoid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>total destruction of the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if that happens,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko disappears, and us with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't have a choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, that would automatically</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's right. Go on, do it Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I restart the system,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't be able to rematerialize you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You'll have to manage on your own.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both groan and scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants] Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you take care of Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you zap me… on three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We zap each other on three, or do we count</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to three and then zap each other?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You always pull this on me, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, we zap each other on three. Okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-One…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, don't miss, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita and Ulrich] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] One… Two… Three…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower's disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Reboot system!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, the repairs are only temporary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but at least they'll let us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>keep fighting XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We managed to save the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You did a great job, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi's right to call you Mrs. Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget that this last</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>little adventure of ours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cost us the Ice Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that is a shame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to have to find a way to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>virtualize you directly into Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from now on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's okay, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As long as the Mountain Sector</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stays together, there's still hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but for how long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't know you had the solutions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Bug Fighter Attack. You mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Careful not to knock anything over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim's coming back tomorrow morning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do another inspec--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[things fall]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… You were saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>