<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>PLAGUED</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water dripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rat shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't speak any louder.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in the library now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's a library, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A data bank</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where everything's printed on paper,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you can't make any noise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because you need silence</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to concentrate on studying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and so as not to miss</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the match point!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hm...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Game, set and match.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, is that what you call studying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In case no one told you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is not the schoolyard!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are here to work, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And work means silence!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No more games from now on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well if that's the way you wanna play,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can play just as hard as you can play,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>little friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling] You! Two hours detention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm... oops, sorry about that, sir. I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you come to my office?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to talk to you. It's important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rat shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The principal went on and on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He says the school psychologist</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has been observing me for a long time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he thinks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm an overly gifted student.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that all? But that's nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were scared the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>found out about the lab. Big deal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's worse than you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The shrink's decided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to take all kinds of tests tonight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to determine what my IQ is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the tests show</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I have a really high IQ,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the guy's gonna see to it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I get sent to another school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Huh? Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's gonna send you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a school for future Einsteins?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That is serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you're not here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can never go to Lyoko again,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and XANA will be able to do what he wants.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not just that, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to leave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because of you all. You're my friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on, cool it. Don't panic, OK?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They can't force you to change schools.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not that easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The psychologist creep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>couldn't wait to talk to my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He told them that at that kind of school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd be entitled to a big scholarship.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My folks aren't gonna pass up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a chance like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[water flowing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What's the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mess up on the tests,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they'll think you're a moron.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nobody'll know, and you're home free.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure, I thought of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only there's a problem,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because tests like that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are full of trick questions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you wanna mess up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and make mistakes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you've gotta be very clever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the cleverest kid around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, okay. I'll do my best to flunk,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can't promise anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll see you guys later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep me posted, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy. Do you recognize me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm Mr. Simone, the school psychologist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it true that you're planning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get me transferred to a school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for gifted children? Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents are gonna be glad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what we're here tonight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To start off, I'm gonna give you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a multiple choice test.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a test in which...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, I'm sure you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Me? No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] What's for dinner?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Some kind of hash.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They all taste the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it can't be! My brand new Gooki dress!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, so you're the savage that did this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rat shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, take that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? Jeremy, listen!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's woken up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must be preparing an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sir, don't you think we ought to stop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, but that would be silly, ah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tests are almost finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the lights are bound to come on again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Simone] Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] What kind of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a two bits school is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrieking loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi yells] Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's enough!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get back to your seats right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and quiet down! Go on now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The lights'll come on again soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now stop clowning around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Understand? Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rhythmic thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich shushes] Quiet down! Listen!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muffled squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Hey...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids yell] Rats! Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We better get out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Uh, don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Rosa] Take that! And that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Move, move! Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Don't panic. Get out of my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Rosa shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh, oh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] We're trapped.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The rats all waited for night time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they attack us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as we're all in the cafeteria.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that you, Ulrich? Huh? What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After the test,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can make all the calls you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's the matter? Why doesn't he answer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] The extinguishers, Jim! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammer] Don't panic, just don't panic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Pass them down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, outside everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeak]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There're too many.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll never hold them back all night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Help, help! Over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! What's she doing here anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to help her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or she's gonna get eaten alive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That noise is unbearable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, this racket has got to... Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Simone] Oh, rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're rats, a whole army of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're trying to eat through the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to barricade it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, here she comes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Your carriage, Cinderella!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Sissi yell]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to the rat pack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, keep going alone, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope this will hold them back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>long enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has activated a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've spotted where it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on my way there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try and get a closer look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, the rats have attacked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, right. We'll meet at the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to find a safe place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where? The rats are all over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I know one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only place with no access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the sewers is the science building.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, we're the rats in a trap,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't like it at all!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get a move on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The extinguishers are nearly empty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] C'mon, easy does it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student] Hurry up, move!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do I do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go up to the roof.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the rats get in, we'll be safe there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[loud crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy will meet us there...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as soon as he can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great, but how do we get there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I go. Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait, come back! What're you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, come back. Come back. Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Too late!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No choice. We have to go over the wall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Simone] Not rats! Anything but rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Simone stammers] When I was a boy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a rat came up to my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rats shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Bingo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay here. I gotta get to the photo lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rat squeaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasping] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's thought of everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Care for a little cruise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up. Faster! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door slamming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Simone gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rats shriek]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It worked! Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If they come, use this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll chase 'em away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay. Please, don't go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Simone] I'm afraid of rats. Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I'm in the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to contact Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and virtualize Odd and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Explain to me how to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, that's done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found the activated tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I've located Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's got a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Speak louder. I can hardly hear you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to type in the coordinates?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say that again... 19 degrees West.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's it, isn't it? 19 degrees West?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said 79 degrees West... 79 degrees West.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen. The rats've invaded the city.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>D'you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'm ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich. Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's okay. You did it, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you see Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No. She should be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around here somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't enter the right coordinates.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I virtualized you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>too far away from Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's okay. We could use the exercise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get warmed up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Smile!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Do you see her now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I see her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] She's here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The only problem is she's not alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oops!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hello, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just managed to get away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your two knights in armor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have come to protect you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, this is kinda weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Ulrich, what is happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ground cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's a good question.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It could have been my mistake, although...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Oh, it's XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's changing the slope of the plateau.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hang on tight!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Well done, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Two crabs, a battery of lasers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ten life points lost per impact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, cover Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's lost too many life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll attract their attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, get out of there now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Need any help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ah, Jeremy, you're finally here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd has just been devirtualized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich has hardly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any life points left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well, you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what you've gotta do now, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shuddering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, Aelita. You're there now. Go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rats squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say... Say cheese.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[kids screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewinding sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy... Did you figure out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to flunk the test?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I know all the questions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I shouldn't have trouble</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>giving the wrong answers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure it's gonna work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I've got a way of flunking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna get all of my answers from Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snickering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! Laugh your heads off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you might be in for a big surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[playful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme song]</c.bg_transparent>