<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>MUSIC TO SOOTHE THE SAVAGE BEAST</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Now pay attention, children.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An electrical charge flows</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through a section of conductor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The current's intensity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is expressed in amperes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the source of the tension</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is measured in volts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This gives it the energy needed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to maintain the current.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the tension given out from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the source is constant,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a continuous current flows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There isn't one ticket left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Completely sold out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I absolutely have to find one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's gonna give us each a ticket.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's the opening act at the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's got comps for all of us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that. The problem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is I need two tickets for tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you made a girl a promise</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you didn't know you could keep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd never understand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd! Would you repeat what I just said?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What exactly is an electrical charge?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… It's the amount</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to pay for electricity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not exactly an enlightening answer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know someone else</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's more stressed out about tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Won't you come to lunch, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I came up with a new program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that will help us to locate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>new Replikas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just have a couple calculations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to work out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] See you later too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got an important errand to run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Matthias, do you have a ticket left</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for tonight's concert?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You mean it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the last one, and it's all yours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna love these guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aerosmooth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're an incredible group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aerosmooth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Subdigitals…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I liked them better as the Subsonics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I like their new name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, ready for the big night?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't even talk about it. I'm so scared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to stardom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen to this: "In our next issue,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an exclusive interview with Aelita Stones,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kadic's brightest new star."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you know about this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Milly and Tamiya haven't stopped</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>hassling me for that interview,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I didn't promise anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what those two are like…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Always looking for a little gossip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget about it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and think about the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever I do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get butterflies in my stomach.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I could stop thinking about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to get my mind off it for a while.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go and see if Jeremy needs any help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't believe this. I'm jinxed!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The last tickets slipped right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>under my nose!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, Aelita's got a free ticket for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but that's not enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for his little harem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laugh at me, go on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but wait till you see Kelly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll know why I've gotta make</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this date perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're going out together?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, let's not get into all the details.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a shame I can't count</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a little help from my friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Try my brother. He must have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some sort of connection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki? You're right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hadn't thought of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a genius!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you really ought to go out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… You and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are just friends, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, we're looking for Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're interviewing her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know where she is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both] She went to the gym!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just supporting school journalism.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft piano music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas] We've been looking for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Can we have your autograph?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Dorks! Look, she's just dying to!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] I'm on to you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Einstein thinks she's a big star,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now that she's a cover girl!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I didn't know about--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Everyone knows</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I should be the opening act.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna be a total fool tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't wait to see that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you will, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna have enough time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to watch from the audience,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause Aelita is gonna be on stage,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Idiot!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Am I disturbing you, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just finished running</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my initial calculations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks to my program, we'll find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the last Replikas with no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! That's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See Jeremy, about tonight…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, right, the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I bet you can't wait to get on stage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Alone at my mixing table, I'm fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But in such a huge auditorium…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be great Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more, Yumi, Ulrich and Odd</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will be cheering you on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>till the calculations finish running,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I've got a couple of things to do,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I might be a little late,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'll go as soon as I'm done.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? As soon as you're done?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have stage fright and you say that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're going to be late to my concert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that isn't exactly what I meant…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I meant to say if it's really important</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you, then…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Important? I'm here telling you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I may not be able to do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that important enough for you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here's your invitation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can give it to someone else</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't find the time to come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cries]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hiroki… You've gotta be kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take it or leave it, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can get double the price</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm asking you from other kids.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't take an IOU</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from your sister's best friend, would you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See ya.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] If I catch you groveling again</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in front of that stuck up, pink haired</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mouse, I'm taking back those comps!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what that mouse thinks of you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? You wouldn't have a bunch of comps</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for tonight, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you think? Being the principal's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>daughter has its advantages.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you wouldn't have an extra one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I do… But not for you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb and Nicolas laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then again, if you can convince Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go to the concert with me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not with that skinny crow,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ping pong balls bouncing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ta-dah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How was your hunting expedition?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It was cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd the Great wanted a ticket,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he got a ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Odd didn't pay an arm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a leg for it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, and by the way Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to ask you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a teeny weeny favor, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ask me a favor? Go on, what kind of favor?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no big rush.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we talk about it later?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, there you are. I came</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give you your tickets for tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, it's nothing, it's on account</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein wins another first prize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in diplomacy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs] Yes, I guess you might say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Oh, relax, princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna bring the house down tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-For sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, don't get there too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The crowd's gonna be big.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd chatters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We came to see our favorite star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before she gets too famous to see us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be so silly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm really glad to see you all…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't Jeremy come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sure he did, but we lost him in the crowd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know Einstein, a great head for math,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's always in the clouds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, he'll be out there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cheering you on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I hope so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[female voice] Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're on in five minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Time for me to start concentrating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay then, we'll take off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look beautiful tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You gonna knock 'em out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, there you are, Kelly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Yumi and Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, hi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hey, Sissi, how're ya doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why is that skinny crow here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humphs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I gave you a ticket</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in exchange for a date with Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, uh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-In that case, gimme back my ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kelly, you can have mine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you told me you spent your last penny</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>buying tickets to this concert,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not that you were wheeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dealing with Delmas! Loser!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kelly] Keep your ticket!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wonder if she bites.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Odd, what was that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>teeny weeny favor you wanted me to do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, can we ask you a couple</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of questions for the Kadic News?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You couldn't have picked a worse time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you're on in two minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm afraid you have to leave now, girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The concert about to start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita was crushed not to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I didn't realize how late it was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one more calculation to run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Aelita's turn now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sophie… I'm ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sophie distorted] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>So am I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Chris] Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sophie] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Chris, Aelita's not well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She can't do the first part</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll have to begin without her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's sick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We won't have an opening act.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a real bummer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope it's not serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, let's go get 'em!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[presenter] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ladies and gentlemen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Subdigitals!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone screaming] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rock music starts playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But… Why didn't Aelita go on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA's just launched an attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They cancelled Aelita's act!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That sounds like XANA. Check it out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then meet me at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA alert! Let's go backstage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and see if Aelita's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There she is. Over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think they're angry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because they blew a scoop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to distract them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys go and get Aelita back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good luck dealing with the press!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girls growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rock music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, a woman's taken Aelita away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's heading for the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll try to head her off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys better hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts and moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sophie] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sophie through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm surrounded.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you're there, answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lateral crossing pattern</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and pincer strategy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's that in English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sophie and Odd grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sophie moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts] Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] How was that for strategy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Guess we beat you here, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where's Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's already virtualized on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants and shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy, at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This isn't where I was expecting you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm happy to hear your voice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] S</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>orry about the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] We'll talk later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] William is here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm sending in the cavalry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi. Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[machine buzzes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Nice one, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you! Ready for the tall,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dark, bad guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, I think we have an audience.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're stuck. No way to reach</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita without some transport!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you'll have your vehicles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[girls scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Awfully sorry, ladies, but no interviews.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Flight pattern and pincer strategy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you speaking English?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Close one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This time, we're on your own!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No help from the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We're bombing on this one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna have to change the music!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Trampoline spinning top action.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Game over for you Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] For you too, handsome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] I was in the mood for fish today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Manta shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rock and roll!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rock music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ They told me that I was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No good at all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Such a waster</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>… ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Get your distance from the star,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Okay, let's go princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ What should I do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stuck to this chair… ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here and now today ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here I am</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I said ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ I can feel you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Such a waster" ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ It's okay I don't care ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Didn't want to stick with the fools ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Skating down Park Avenue ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ I realize my time is now and here ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Ready to go ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Being sensible</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is just not sensible ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Gotta break away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ It's not my style</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I gotta get away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ We'll win it all the way! ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd screaming] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewinding sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[knocks on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Come in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wanted to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how you were doing, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have less stage fright,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess it's because I've already</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>been here, if you know what I mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way I was going to miss</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the concert for the second time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I didn't mean to blow up at you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I put too much pressure on myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe it was insane</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to want to do this concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, sometimes the sanest thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to be insane.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[presenter] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Now, let's put 'em together</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a brand new DJ, Aelita Stones!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electronic music starts playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's your girlfriend?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dumped me. No big deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb, Nicolas and Sissi laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>