<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE GIRL OF MY DREAMS</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Time to launch the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring and beeping slows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it. Not again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Darn it, I'm so useless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm never gonna do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> And I'm sure you will, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Thanks for the encouragement,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm useless, I tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, do you think we'd get along well</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the real world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, as well as we do now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, of course. Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, because I'm not so sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to have a best friend</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's useless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha ha, very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, get a move on, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll be late for school again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow. Is it that late?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll be right there, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyhow, useless or not,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna try one more thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I get the picture. See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This, whatever it is of yours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>weighs at least a ton!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not a whatever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's been in my family</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for hundreds of years.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[suspenseful music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] When are you going to unveil</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your thingamabob?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the very end of my report. You'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's gonna be a smash hit,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a real show stopper,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and worth an A, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you sure wouldn't find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a thing like that at my house.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First of all, your whatchamacallit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't go with the drapes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the living room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Whatchamacallit, whatever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I like most about you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, is your rich vocabulary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly] Don't look now, Tamiya,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I smell a big juicy scoop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So do I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] Okay, rolling. Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fellow middle school students, hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is Milly and Tamiya</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the seventh grade,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>reporting the school news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may not know it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but just behind your backs,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something strange is hatching.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this, my friends, is a part of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In our constant quest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be the first to report the latest news,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're bringing you this exclusive exposé</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of what's hidden under this drape...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[camera whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tamiya, listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there any reason</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you filming your feet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Tamiya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya] I'm sorry. It scares me a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] Oh no, time for class already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, most people</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>use the night hours to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was trying a new program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for materializing Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With this last one I was trying,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I almost succeeded.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was nearly there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And what are you gonna say to her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you do succeed?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never knew how to talk to a girl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With Aelita, it's not the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right, it's not the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good morning, everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Before the start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your first class this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would like to introduce</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your new classmate. Come in, Taelia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure your fellow students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are anxious to meet you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, here's your chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Imagine she's in front of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in flesh and blood.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What're you gonna say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh, wow...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Beep! Sorry, your time is up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could use a few pointers in flirting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh wow, this is...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She does look like her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if it really is her,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she ought to recognize us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not necessarily.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She may have lost her memory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when she was materialized.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, talk to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's the only way to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if it's not her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, watch an expert at work and learn.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi there, Ae...Uh, I mean,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Taelia. My friends and I were...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we thought you looked familiar,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like we'd seen you before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on. That's the oldest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pick up line around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Hey, who said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I wanted to pick you up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was just making conversation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>do things like the virtual world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or crabs or buzzing monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mean anything to you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, well yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It means that I'd better be moving along.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, wait a minute. Don't go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you from?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you have a family?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not in the mood to talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's not her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's only saying that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because he just got the brushoff big time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch and expert and learn, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, if it is Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's for sure she's got amnesia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a second. Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's say it's her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it's really her, I mean for sure,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then she can't still be on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can check it out later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Now we have a date with Ms. Meyer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wish me luck for my report, everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi internally]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks for caring, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Meyer] We have here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a simple equation with two unknowns.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to check out Lyoko now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I can't wait any longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, we'll go together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Ms. Meyer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Excuse me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, what is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need to go to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't feel too well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel uh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel really sick.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ms. Meyer] Of course. Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, I'll take him there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean you never know, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We're almost connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jim's gonna catch us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Jeremy, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She doesn't answer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but she might be in one of XANA's traps,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like in a storm or snowbound,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you can't pick her up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if the last calculations I tried</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>were the right ones?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could really use a night's sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I say, you're nuts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm positive. I did it! I did it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Taelia is Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[oriental music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Of course it's just a glimpse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my country's culture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To explain it all would take me hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm not sure you're ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to put up with me for that long, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To end my report,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to show you something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's been in my family for centuries.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a living symbol of Japan,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's a...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A...?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A drape?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[repetitive bass drums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hey you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what're you doing here? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of a costume is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what's wrong with you, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you outta your head?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Maybe one of the kids took it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't forget the electric plugs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, if XANA is in on this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd better not count on Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't reach her on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, we can't reach her on Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause she isn't on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry you guys, but I can't believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that that girl is Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I know somebody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's dying to believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Give me your attention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Several of your fellow students,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as well as our own Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whom you all know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and whom you respect, I know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's not go overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Their attacker was a person who...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A person who was wearing armor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the armor of a samurai.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this individual is still at large.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any information you can contribute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the police</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would more than welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't wait any longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to go to Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>find Aelita and deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When are you gonna get it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into your thick heads</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that if the samurai is controlled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by XANA, then he's after Taelia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It makes sense, doesn't it, huh,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because Taelia is Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, wow,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's really flipped his lid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[policeman] Excuse me Miss.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It seems that this armor belongs to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, listen to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's launched a new virus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's managed to take control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a samurai's armor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You're his sworn enemy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's after you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have no choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You absolutely have to hide!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As a pickup line,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's a lot more original</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than the one your friend tried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, please listen to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's definitely the materialization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that gave you amnesia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The shock made you lose your memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you have to trust me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, get your hands off me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't trust anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's stark raving mad!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[armor clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Taelia gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, XANA! You won't get her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't let you, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Taelia whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, follow me! Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster, Taelia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, this samurai's armor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>does belong to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yes, to my parents.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you have no idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who might have stolen it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, we can't do anything here for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to tell Jeremy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to meet us at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy's voicemail is on now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Taelia] Wow, this place is weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Follow me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The virtual world where you once lived.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Doesn't that ring a bell at all?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this XANA you talked about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Does he also live in this same world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got total control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Taelia] But if he's so dangerous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why don't you destroy Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because you're part of...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because you were part of this world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Taelia] You're totally crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Taelia] This whole story is crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what I think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If all this stuff is so dangerous,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's time you destroyed it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once and for all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you really think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Have you gone mad or what, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if Aelita is still on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But she isn't, I tell you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, she's there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's right in front of you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I know you've dreamt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of seeing Aelita in reality for months,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but please come down to earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't be sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if you were mistaken?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're ready to take the risk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of destroying Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-by destroying XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've got to make sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to let us go to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if Aelita's not there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's gonna deactivate the tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to take the risk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The last time I saw Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she was in the mountain area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can you see anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yes, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mountains, lots of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting the scan to trace</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower that XANA activated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to understand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Taelia, if you're not Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then we've got to...Taelia?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Boy, oh boy. Finding someone around here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna be harder than finding</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an idea in Jim's head!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I just saw Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In a kind of flash vision.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, hi, Yumi. Well, is everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, they finished questioning me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I just saw Taelia,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she looked like she was in a hurry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go and see the principal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, that can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is awful, horrible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I took Taelia to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna tell the cops everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Ulrich, the tower XANA's activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has been localized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at thirty degrees north in...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the forest area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's not gonna do us a lot of good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, there, that ball of fire.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's exactly what I saw before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's inside it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we found her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That ball</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is what's blocking communication.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's a guardian,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same monster that imprisoned Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Right. Aelita saved her</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by convincing the monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he had the wrong prisoner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Aelita is the prisoner this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So now the only solution is to use force.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sparks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is anyone there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know you're there. Show yourself!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sparks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, nothing's working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's like the machine's invincible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, wow, XANA must've designed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a program...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, it's a program!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if it's a program,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should be able to...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what are you mumbling about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got an idea, I hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe, but give me a couple of minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, no problem, man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got all the time in the world!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts loudly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To think I blew our whole cover</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by talking to a perfect stranger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means the samurai wasn't after Taelia</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at all. He was after us! Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Just a little more time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey, how about that idea of yours?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here goes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Making a clone of Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, personally,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a bit skeptical, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Patience, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] A decoy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you're the greatest!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Get Aelita to a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's got to regenerate herself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's got her life points back again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs] Oh, you found me at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about the guardian?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You mean that big fat fire bubble?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He won't bother you anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're off Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Destination: the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heart beating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, you'd better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't reach Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm afraid she's having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>problems with the samurai.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no time to lose. Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] While you're at it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you got any other good news?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, plenty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Taelia saw me punch in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the access code to the lab,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the principal</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the police are here now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, and XANA's monsters are around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two Bloks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch out for their laser gel guns</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or it's game over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey Bloks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>cool, my favorite monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There! It was this computer right here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was this XANA thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I dunno how,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it seems</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he wants to destroy the planet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think you owe us an explanation.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd, take care of Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay here and cover you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>alone, well, almost alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Triangulate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser zooms]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Impact! [screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring slows]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Your turn, Princess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come along, now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but my friends are in danger,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I can't abandon them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No don't! Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't do this. Let me go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You always pick the wrong time, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal chinks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy shouts] Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewinding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheerful flute]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And this is Taelia your new classmate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure your fellow students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are anxious to meet you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I heard Sissi say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the new girl was an orphan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's why she didn't want to talk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about her family.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well anyway, if you look closely,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can see their eyes aren't the same.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The nose is different and so is the hair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not similar at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could you have possibly thought</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she was Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you just say that we thought?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He sure did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You'd have to be blind to think that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[oriental music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And now to finish my report,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to show you something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's been in my family for centuries.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a living symbol of Japan. Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, man, that's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gosh, Yumi, she's so cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's the best report I've seen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of the whole class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>