<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'D RATHER NOT TALK ABOUT IT</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, let's move it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little faster. Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's trying to kill us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting and groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[clicks stopwatch]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You guys are ridiculous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're way too slow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a bunch of snails.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Except for you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even a snail runs faster than you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since when does the least athletic person</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the world think he's better than I am?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's true. Getting a little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>carried away, aren't you, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't blame me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The stopwatch doesn't lie, you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] That was even worse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than the last time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you expect to beat XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if all of you don't speed it up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a real comedian, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All you ever do is time us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anybody can do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One thing is for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you guys don't get into shape,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're never gonna get stronger,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and XANA's gonna beat you hands down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But if you think you want another trainer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be my guest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe there's a better…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A better way of getting in shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get it. You're just badly trained.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you guys can't keep up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's my fault!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, fine. I may not be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the best trainer in the world,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you have to admit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you don't exactly listen to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's true, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe we need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find someone else, a specialist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A specialist? You mind telling me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where you expect to find one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, just what do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't a man get a little peace and quiet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even on a Saturday?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's simple, although you might</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>think this is a little crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing can surprise me ever</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since I orbited the Earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Spit it out, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Well, we heard that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were once a special forces trainer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, Special Forces, the SIF,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Secret Intervention Force.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, those were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the good old days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But that being said,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you be willing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to train students, like us, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Train students?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, for a kind of commando camp,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like you…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like your special intervention</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thingamajig.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Deal! Meet me at the Red Cross Trail</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>crossroads at fifteen hundred hours sharp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Dressed for sports.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean like today? Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It touches me that students recognize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and want to benefit from my experience</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and skill, especially you, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never imagined that anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could ever turn you into a man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A real one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, you don't understand. I was talking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about training the others. Not for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This training course is for everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fifteen hundred hours,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I want you there on time, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This will do wonders for you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you'll be able to put your stopwatch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>away for a little while. All right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This is stupid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't do a commando camp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a ton of things on my plate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I think you're afraid of sweating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA attack while we're training?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bring your computer with you, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Jeremy. Jim's commando camp</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't possibly do us any harm, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] With Jim, you never can tell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have never seen a weaker pack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of legless slugs in my life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fifteen hundred hours sharp does not mean</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fifteen hundred zero two</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or fifteen zero three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, we're not gonna split hairs</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over a few seconds? My watch--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your watch doesn't wash with me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I give the orders around here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so straighten up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll make our way to the combat clearing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where we'll start in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with some basic training, like pushups!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, I wonder if it wasn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a mistake to recruit Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Aelita, it wasn't just a mistake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was a huge, colossal mistake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hold that fifteen! Hold it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold it I said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right. All right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one, two, three, four, on your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>On your feet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Breathe in. Breathe out. Easy does it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Easy does it, two, three, four, five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Jeremy, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Not really. I feel awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, what do you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're doing, Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is only the beginning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the time I'm through with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're gonna be a man, so get up now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, don't you think you're overdoing it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We want training, not torture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wrong again, young lady.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys are all participating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in Jim's boot camp,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that means two things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You sweat and you don't complain,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>unless you want ten extra pushups.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>From this moment on, we live and die</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>together as a group. Got it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Okay, no need to get carried away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got it, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Sir, yes, sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, let's move. Three mile run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[military drum beats]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, two. One, two. One, two.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, my poor stomach!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should never have taken seconds</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the tuna casserole</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>after the beef stroganoff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get those knees up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you soft shelled crabs! Go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Belpois, you couldn't even</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>outrun a one legged chicken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Left, right. Left, right. And left, right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At this rate, we'll need at least a week</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to recover from Jim's camp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's kinda useless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Young lady, it's adversity that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>creates strength and courage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's the shortest path</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to fame and glory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Hup. Hup. Hup. Hup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut the clowning, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is not a circus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, don't be a wimp.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got nothing to be afraid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of except a sore bottom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No use hanging there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a wet sock on a clothesline!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it. Get the lead out and crawl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Stones, I said on top of it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad for the first time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, let's take a little break here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then we'll start a new workout.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you know what, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd love to hear about your past life.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that you usually don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>want to talk about it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but since it's just between us members</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the same commando group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, then, listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exceptionally for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give you a quick rundown.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It all began when I completed my training</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a physical education instructor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was also a licensed scuba diver.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's why</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Marines recruited me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for their Special Forces.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>NASA heard of me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and since I was now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a Special Forces diver,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they had me test</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out their space suits under water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, after having received</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a medal from the President,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was then appointed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Secret Service.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] …and believe me, Rosita Banana</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't just play the accordion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She was also a heck of a pilot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I arrived in Buenos Aires</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my cameras,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her biplane bowled me over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Break time is over now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A quick trot to shake off the rust.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hup. Hup. Hup. Hup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all sighing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Let's go people. Move it out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta end this circus right now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? They're already way ahead of me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, you can do it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[animal snorts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar snorts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of beast is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How about that? A wild pig!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's huge! Let's go another way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, relax! It's nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I handled much worse than this</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I was in Burma.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita, Odd, Ulrich and Yumi yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim yelps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar squeals and growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Did you see that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, listen Jim, be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It isn't a normal animal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not a wild boar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Like I said,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's just an overgrown pig, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come to Jim, little piglet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, little piggy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm telling you Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd be much better off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-getting out of here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Careful, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out, Belpois!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, are you all okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. Yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's the other guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar squeals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Nice shot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Ulrich, you've got a great arm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll create a diversion.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Good thing you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fast legs, too. Go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA sent this thing after us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get to the computer lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita can manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the virtualization process. Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better stay here with Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles deliriously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if Ulrich can't join you guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then all three of you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are gonna be needed on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim! Get up, Jim! I'll help you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes! Mr. President, the mission</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has to go on whatever it takes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even if it costs me my stripes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way. It's a short cut.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting and gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's not so hard</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a little training.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come on! You can do it, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squealing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm okay, but the boar is heading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>back your way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm off to join the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hangs up phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to conceal our hiding place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll camouflage it with some branches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me a minute to get my strength back,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I can help you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My leg is fine. I'm ready to walk again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans painfully]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No coach, don't move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, this is horrible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel completely useless</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with this stupid broken leg I got.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your knee's really swelled up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll need an X-ray to see</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whether or not it's broken.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to have to immobilize it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or it's gonna hurt even worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ripping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants] We're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Just one last sprint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The factory's not much further.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretty good splint there, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't seen work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like that in a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never worked with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Magyar Commandos, did you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's just a question of common sense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An injured joint won't get any worse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if it doesn't move.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You would have made</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a good soldier, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If only you had a little more muscle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you don't know this, Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the brain is kind of like a muscle,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's the one in particular</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I've been exercising the most.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on. Every second counts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm on it,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm not as fast as Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has sent William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and some monsters into the core chamber.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Fire!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[bleeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You two get down to the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to protect the core of Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about the tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess I'll have to manage that alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No, not alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Old reliable Ulrich is here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I shook off the wild boar,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it went back into the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm afraid it could find Jim and Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better not waste any time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's got a funny smell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Peppermint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents have some in their garden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bad news, Jim! Our camouflage is useless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The boar's sense of smell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna give us away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It sure will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a good chance of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A better than even chance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta find a way to hide our scent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I've already called up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They'll be standing by for you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Celestial Dome. No time to lose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we had a little caribou poop,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we could cover ourselves with it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Did you say "caribou poop"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, it's an old Indian trick</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I used to use in Quebec</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to surprise arsonists in the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, we're not in Canada,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that means no caribou poop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way am I going to smear myself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with any kind of poop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-On the other hand, I'll be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch mechanisms clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I've started</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the delayed virtualization program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's the activated tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the Forest Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Valet parking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's classy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on Ulrich, rev it up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Listen, Jim. Take some mint.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rub it on yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It should be enough to hide our scent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a nauseating odor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like it much better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than caribou poop, don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I feel a lot better on this machine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than on Jim's ropes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, now all we can do is wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better hope that the others manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to deactivate the tower on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, are you delirious or what, Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just daydreaming, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you tell me about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you were in Canada.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah! Well, now that is a long story.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, where'd the tower go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must have made a calibration error.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without Jeremy to guide us,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this won't be easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unsheathes sword]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, anyway, with all these troops</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>around, the tower can't be that far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicles zoom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powers up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing and crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa! Beware of falling objects.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, isn't that your boyfriend up there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not my boyfriend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mantas screech]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a little clingy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for me anyhow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that was when I found out that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as far back as a century,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I was a full blooded Indian.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like your little trick worked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, the mint smells strong</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough now to trick him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but how much longer will it last?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, anyway, one thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about caribou poop. It lasts a long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Still nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Alright. We have to go back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to where we started.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower has to be there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Okay, here we go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Krabs growl]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[unsheathes swords]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts and yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Holy hogwash! He found us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey, what are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Follow me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That kid doesn't have much muscle,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he sure is big on guts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, the first shield layer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is about to give!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to do something!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I've got an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Oh yeah, and what's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams] Sky diving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans in disgust]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Attack!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go get them, guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mantas screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slow footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! I better get it right this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slam]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tell me where the tower is. Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should be next to it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's impossible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't see it. How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's pulled this one on us before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar growling and squealing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That was a volley shot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all over for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I would call that wishful thinking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, dear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar huffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar squealing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise never to eat pork again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs and squeals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, then, you piece of overcooked bacon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You thought I'd let you off that easy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, Jim, but you never</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should have left the cave.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me tell you kid, you've got guts,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I abandon my men under fire,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't know good old Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar squealing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come and get me if you dare!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boar growling angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[squeals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boar grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales relieved]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods and chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you didn't do a return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure Jim has forgotten everything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just the opposite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He remembers everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that is the best insurance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that there is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To him, our wild boar was a crazy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and dangerous animal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but a completely normal one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita, Odd, Ulrich and Yumi] Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, hello there, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're glad to see you back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on two feet again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>More like three, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it isn't too serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a bad sprain and a nasty bruise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be good as new in two weeks' time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For us, it's really a shame.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just one day of boot camp</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for two weeks of recovery.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That one day was very enlightening for me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You may not have been up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the commando level</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you showed great spirit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really did.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as I'm back in shape,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll organize lots of other</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>training sessions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I hope to see you all there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita hesitates] Um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not me. I'm booked to the end of the year.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a sleep session.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Honestly Jim, it's too much of a--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A horror…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too much of an honor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy chuckles] I'll be there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all in disbelief] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I owe you one, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excellent, Belpois.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew I could count on you, kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must be dreaming. "I'll be there"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow. You could have come up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a better answer than that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"No" for instance,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or "never" or </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>"nein"</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> or "</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>nyet</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must really like Jim's torture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim's voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Let me tell you something,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>kid. You've got guts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>