<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>DOUBLE TROUBLE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, let me get a good grade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just for once… I'm begging you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, you might have better luck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you studied before an exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It beats praying for them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excellent work, Herb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not surprised either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I gave you an A minus as usual.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The minus is to show</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can always improve.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well done!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thank you, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it. How can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such a good student be such a nerd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But then again, you did crush Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's even nerdier than you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keeping with a time-honored tradition,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've saved the best paper for last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm the only one left. He did just</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>say "the best," didn't he, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hate to burst your bubble,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it sounded like sarcasm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich Stern, there were</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so many spelling errors in this assignment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that at first, I thought it was written</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in some obscure and primitive language.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But no, in fact it was in English.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unfortunately, I've given you an F plus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The plus is to give you room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do worse next time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That wasn't just sarcastic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was bombastic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door knocks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Come in</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, Miss Ishiyama!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I must say I'm flattered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you answered my request</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to come and see me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Given your constant lateness and repeated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>absences over these past few weeks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am absolutely flabbergasted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you actually decided to show up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To what do I owe this great honor?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, sir, I really am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Perhaps, but not as much as I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sincerely sorry to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to say this to you, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but unfortunately,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't leave me any choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I hear that you are absent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or late just one more time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I shall be forced to expel you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the Academy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Expulsion? You're kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, Delmas was dead serious this time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] This can't go on much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's getting harder and harder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to keep up with our school work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-and fight against XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Better believe it, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is trying to wear us down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there is one thing that we can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we could recruit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one more Lyoko warrior,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it would give us some breathing room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And who did you have in mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There's William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's already shown what he can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way. We've already been over this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's too much of a hothead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, he can't be trusted.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As far as I'm concerned,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's right. It's a good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's very bad idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, we're all really tired.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we talk about this tomorrow?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's take advantage of the fact</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA hasn't attacked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get a good night's sleep?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll stay up a while and work on a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to virtualize you directly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into Sector Five, okay guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got some calculations to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what you call</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>getting some sleep, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't need all that much sleep,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and besides, I'll sleep a lot better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>once we defeat XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We all will, Aelita, not before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, I have to talk to you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What are you so excited about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I finally found a way to virtualize</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all of you into Sector Five directly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We have to run a test right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on. Let's go to the computer lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we have a physics exam this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You and I have fabulous grades, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We can afford to skip one exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't think we should.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, we have to tell the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! No way we're skipping the exam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need a decent grade to bring up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my average.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's more if we're all absent,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're bound to suspect something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm sure to get expelled.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Some adventurers you all are!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't be like that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go after the test is over Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at lunch time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. Go ahead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll meet you in the lunchroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to go back up and get some stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[water moving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's the answer to question number one?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is Aelita done yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How should I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ask her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, Jeremy wants to know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you're finished yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, would you like me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give you some help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, gee, thanks Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure could use a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had quite enough of watching you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>copy answers left and right, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… But, ma'am, no, I was just…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, have you completed the exam?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, ma'am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good. Well then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you will please escort</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your classmate to the principal's office.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time Odd was punished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Why wouldn't you let me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>copy off of you this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We wouldn't be here now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if you studied like everyone else,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we wouldn't be here now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, A, Not everyone else studies,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and B, I am not like everyone else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I am special, unique…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Like you by the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's me, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm? Today isn't April Fool's Day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Odd, listen to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has created a clone of me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from a polymorphic spectre.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We fought at the factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he tried to drown me, but I survived.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't know what he's planning, but--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wouldn't believe me if I told you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right next to you, isn't he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through phone] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Huh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah… I mean… I don't know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look in his eyes, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you see the sign of XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning in doubt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted voice] You didn't answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammering] Jeremy, I think you're right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do I do now, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electric whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing. There's nothing you can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through phone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Odd, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Answer me, will you? Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May I remind each of you not to spend</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>too much time in the darkroom,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>printing your photos, since the darkroom</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is for everyone to share.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's nobody's personal darkroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I remember when I was a war photographer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We had to develop our prints fast,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while bombs were falling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were a war photographer, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but I'd rather not talk about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Yumi and William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the first up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know I had another dream</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about you last night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was this giant computer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this huge room, like in a factory,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you know? And then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>both you and I were on this bridge,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>fighting against some factory worker,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who was doing these wild acrobatics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really dreamed that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been having that same dream</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a really long time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's totally weird. Then again of course,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's only a dream,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're always a little bit weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Shall we go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] This light means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that your classmates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have started the developing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you see that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>absolutely no one should open the door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The light would ruin the pictures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen Jeremy, if I skip class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one more time, I'll be expelled,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you get it? What'll we do then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what's going on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you can always get out through here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Leave it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He won't notice a thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just don't be too long, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would you do that for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's just say that in my dream,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really enjoyed helping you out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, why not try it in real life?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Might be just as much fun.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, Jeremy, I'm coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Find Odd and go get Ulrich and Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to need all of you to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower that my evil twin set up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of whom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wonder where could be right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I found Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a little woozy, but he's okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to try to get Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Ulrich, and then we'll meet you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start setting up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your transfer to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted voice] Well, what do you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You actually survived.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're a real swimming champ.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm almost proud to resemble you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the exception that I am</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>far more powerful than you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mobile vibrates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through mobile]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, we have to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like there's an emergency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, emergency or not, I'm not moving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I need the grade, and this time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm off to a decent start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but I'd better go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meet up with us when you're finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy's clone grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are they doing in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's taking so long?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, William, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're almost done, Jim. Wait 'till</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you see the prints. They're fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] They're taking long enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to see them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so hurry it up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Believe me Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going as fast as we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what does Jeremy's evil twin look like?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Well, just like Einstein,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except with muscles and super powers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Where's Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll be here as soon as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he finishes his exam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, get down to the scanners</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the double, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start up your transfer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where did your nasty twin go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea, but the faster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we deactivate the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the faster we'll be rid of him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right. Let's get going.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, what are you waiting for? Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay. Let's go then.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, time is almost up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One more minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm just not sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should have looked him in the eye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure it was him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aren't you, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Female intuition. You can trust our flair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-If you say so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy's clone through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll transfer you as close as I can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm starting up the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy's clone through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi. Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy, bring on our vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're raring to go over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy's clone in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry Odd, but I have another plan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Such a great plan that you guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are gonna just flip out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've been had by Jeremy's twin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing like female intuition, huh, girls?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, what's he gonna do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want a little male intuition?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Something very nasty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy's clone laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[keeps laughing evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's happening to us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] He's bugged you up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why us and not you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There's your answer. Look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, Yumi, that's it, you hear now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Open up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William] Can't Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're working on the contrast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how important the contrast is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, you know better than we do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we open up now, we'll lose everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Yumi, why do you leave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the talking to William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm right here, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guarantee you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be worth waiting for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William and I are making</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some incredibly beautiful photographs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But hurry it up, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We will, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no, it didn't work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] At this rate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there isn't gonna be any winner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, knock yourselves out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers in fear]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Oh, no, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We can't do anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>bugged up like this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta defend yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] It's horrible not being able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now she's gonna make a dash</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This can't be!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Given the circumstances,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's not much we can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I take back what I said.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not even half as smart as me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As a matter of fact, you're a stupid dope!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy's clone laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy's clone distorted voice] Sorry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but one of us is going to have to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right, and I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's gonna have to be you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I think I need glasses</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause I'm seeing double.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks Ulrich. You got here just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on on Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wish I knew.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, is that you? For real?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can vouch for that. It's him all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going for you over there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you could say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we're all bugged up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And a little ridiculous too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, I'll take care of that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is under XANA's spell,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and she's heading for the way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We could lose the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sending you Ulrich as backup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sorry, major problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This might take some more time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy's clone laughs evilly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up the debugging.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope this is gonna work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the main man, Einstein!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks! Now, go catch Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before she enters the XANA code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm bringing up your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's great to have my svelte body back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Things are heating up over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Almost at the tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you can still catch her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on, Yumi. I'll cover you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explodes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd groans] Yu-hoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope it's not gonna be too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was nothing I could do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're going to lose the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget to bring Aelita and me in.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, now it's the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna rematerialize you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer keys clatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glitches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Mountain Sector is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>completely disappeared.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no way of getting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>into Sector Five now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now XANA can attack the core</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Lyoko at any time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and destroy it for good, and there will be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nothing we can do against him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lyoko's gone for good,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and without it, there's not a thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can do to fight XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These are the results of the calculations</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I made this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What about them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I might have found a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to virtualize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly into Sector Five, at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean the struggle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against XANA goes on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not rid of us yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If that's the case,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then we are gonna need somebody else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After what's happened,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we don't have a choice, it seems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? I changed my mind… So?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Right now, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William and Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to open up this door,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and don't think I can't do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I used to be a safecracker.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean a locksmith.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We told you not to come in, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now you've ruined my pictures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, our pictures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yumi! Where's Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Here I am, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's so uncool for our prints.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We worked really hard on them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you're saying my dream</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really wasn't a dream?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It really happened. Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're also sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you need my help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] You think he'll say yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course. If Yumi asked him to dive off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a cliff, he'd do it in a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, how did your physics test go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it went really well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who'd have thought that studying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a test would help?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ullrich turning into a good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>student for once,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William turning into a Lyoko warrior…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our little group is going through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a lot of pretty huge changes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all nod]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both chuckle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>