<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>SEEING IS BELIEVING</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Delâcre]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Our heating plant uses</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>energy supplied by a nuclear reactor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to which,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we produce thousands</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of megawatts of electrical power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here is the cooling tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the turbine, the alternator,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and finally, the reactor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This plant is one of the</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>most powerful in the world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As chief engineer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm particularly concerned with safety.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[seagulls squawk]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dr. Delâcre] And to guarantee</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this safety, security measures have been</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>applied at every level of production.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The plant's design,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>its functioning, and problem phases.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We call this combination</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of safety measures, "in-depth defense."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be glad to answer any questions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Uh, sir?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ms. Hertz] Yes, go on Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to know if an atomic process</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>exists for fusing virtual particles</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and materializing them in the real world.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Son, that is in the realm</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of science fiction. Sorry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy is an excellent student,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but a bit of a dreamer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[other students laugh mockingly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student blows raspberry]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[power cuts out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, now, what's happened here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh. It's certainly nothing serious,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just a blown fuse, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy and Odd] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniggers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm saying that maybe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is behind this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't get so excited, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was just a short circuit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've thought it over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can form your group. The, um...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"Fox Trot Fanatics"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's The Pop Rock Progressives, sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it must be open to anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who wishes to play. Is that clear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problemo</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>, sir!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! Let's hear it for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the god of rock and roll!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we step on it ,we can photocopy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the leaflets before lunch, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you know, Odd, I'm not into rock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, I want to check on that outage.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Okay, see you later, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing fast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hi. Is something wrong, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know, if you ever have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a problem, you can talk to me about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why can't I hear anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's check this out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, do you read me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Loud and clear, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We had a power failure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in class this morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the school electricity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>system seems to be having problems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zoom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And?...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think XANA's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>behind it, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you noticed anything in Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Everything's quiet here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, I'll do a scan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA's activated a tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll find out soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To the cafeteria.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They've got Brussels sprouts today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you know what they are?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but I don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what they taste like. Are they good?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're gross. Ugh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Odd, what are you up to now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're holding auditions for our group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, if anyone is interested,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we need a drummer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here you go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Let's see now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hot chocolate? No. Soup, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The soup tastes like dishwater.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, you pressed soup!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, it's not that awful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soup drips]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, this miserable machine's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the blink again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe it's another power failure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you worried?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll keep checking things out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you need us, we'll be in the gym.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to hold auditions.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[frantic drumming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ugh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yeah, you got a lot of style.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's heavy metal, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mike] Oh yeah, for sure!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really sorry, Mike, but we're looking for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something more traditional, you know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Next!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks and closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello guys!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, how are you, Naomi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't know you played the drums.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well yeah, a little. Besides, I've always</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>dreamed of being in a band.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay then, go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drumming badly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[messy drum hits]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, Naomi! That was fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I mean, come on, we're not going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find anyone better, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Four hundred thousand volts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at a high-tension pylon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Got anything new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Well, not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping and cutting out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh? Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sparks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is XANA's doing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm almost sure of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The current's cutting out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all around the school,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the pylon outside is way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the voltage limit. It could explode!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would XANA do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your guess is as good as mine, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's obvious my friends and l</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>aren't very welcome, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My father did say that the band</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was open to everybody, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh but, don't worry, l don't want to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a group of deadbeat weirdos.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Nicolas just loves the drums.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A drummer, huh? What does he play?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>His mom's pots and pans?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay guys, I'm off to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep you posted!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drumsticks click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drumming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[steady drumbeat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing and clapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggling] Looks like you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>found yourself a drummer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas? The drummer in </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>our </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>band?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't care how good he is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the answer is no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, Sissi set this up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just to give us a hard time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe for once she was trying to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you 've got to admit that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas can really play the drums.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better than Naomi. That's for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's only a beginner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She needs a little more time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-huh. A couple of years should do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well if that's how you feel,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then listen up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you want Nicolas to be your drummer,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you better find yourself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another guitarist!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I say if you don't take him,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you better find yourself a new singer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If Sissi's idea was to cause trouble,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she's done a great job.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[slide trombone plays]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would you guys need</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a slide trombone by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch closing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry about the outage. What's new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were right to be worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's woken up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? The scan's picked something up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower XANA's activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the desert region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be careful, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I will.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ugh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim plays slide trombone]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, what do you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, the fact is, we're a rock band,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not a military brass band.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[muffled voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, be right there. We're going to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have to audition you another time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no you don't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're not going anywhere unless you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>agree to take me as part of your group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're on our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch buzzes and cracks open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here's what XANA's up to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once he's stored enough voltage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in that pylon, he'll unleash it all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Unleash it where?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess! On the nuclear plant!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-...creating a short circuit and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't manage to cut the power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've tried everything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen such a weird thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The pylon can take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one million volts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once it's all accumulated,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA can blow everything up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nuclear sabotage! That's a little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over our heads, wouldn't you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah. What do you mean?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Think about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we fail in Lyoko,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the whole region will be wiped out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to warn the authorities.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Are you crazy? There'll be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an inquiry and we'll be questioned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to tell them everything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if they discover XANA,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll pull all the plugs out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> And we'll lose Aelita...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But we're talking about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a nuclear disaster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's take a vote.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who is for raising the alarm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Against!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Against.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Aelita, but I also think we can't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>take this big a risk. I vote "for."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's report it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, then. Two votes for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and two votes against, it's a tie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We don't tell anybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think it means that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we should tell everybody.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Don't I have the right to vote?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, sure you do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way there won't be a tie.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In that case, I vote "for."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want thousands of people</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to die just to save me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch buzzes and cracks open]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going to make it, huh, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope so, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I've got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The scan has located the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's in the desert region,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>near an oasis.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I know where it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That way, on the other plateau.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it. The plant</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is functioning perfectly,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the city is in total darkness.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No need for alarm, though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're working on finding the reason.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry to disturb you, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's really important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to trust me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know it's going to sound crazy, sir,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but please hear me out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The nuclear plant</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in danger of blowing up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't believe this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Where is this tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can't see it now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's here all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at XANA's pulsations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They all converge here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, you can do it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't be too far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got to find it fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pylon is going to be overloaded soon.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the principal and Dr. Delâcre</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't believe me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're going crazy here too, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pylon is 85 percent charged,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and we can't find the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital splash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-l found it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] We've been tricked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no water down there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just a surface layer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go and have a better look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I hate those horrible crabs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, it's you they're after.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Ha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical crab explodes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you for saving Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But things look bad here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Up to 95 per cent! Soon XANA will be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>able to attack the nuclear plant.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing and electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Fireman] Could you repeat that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The voltage that built up in this pylon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is going to be used to blow up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the nuclear power plant, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can you just stand there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do something before it's too late! Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>you</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> know all that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go on, go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich clones grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fusion! Come on, you only get one shot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Ulrich, are you out of your mind?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The pylon is over 98 percent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, it's up to you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Fireman] A super computer in a factory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A virtual world?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, l swear! You have to believe me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's going to work!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping frantically]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling ceasing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for a return trip to the past, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, hit it! Three, four!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rock music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[drumming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Mystery girl from another world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ She wanted happiness</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and not a lot of stress ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slide trombone playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ A strange affair that's true ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! [clapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪ A love affair for you ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat rock music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You were right. He's doing great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who you talking about? Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slide trombone playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your energy is super nuclear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going to make this town explode!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[applauding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>