<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>SAINT VALENTINE'S DAY</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, stop! Let me go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[knocking on door]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] What could…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mysterious music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tick tock]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Hey, you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] No one's allowed in the dormitory</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without my authorization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did you get in here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sizzling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Plain, but not bad.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I wonder who gave it to me…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] and why.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might have an idea…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know what day it is today?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tuesday!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but not just any Tuesday!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Saint Valentine's Day!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The day all lovers celebrate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lovers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, and I can guess exactly which boy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>might want to give you a present,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, there's Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You know, the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I see someone in the morning,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tend to say "Good Morning."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But then again, maybe I'm a little</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>old-fashioned.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For the necklace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The… necklace?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your Valentine's Day present. It's lovely.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you're welcome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's only natural.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in History class!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You didn't give it to her, did you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Was it that obvious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but luckily for you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>love has made Aelita blind!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[smirks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Most historians believe Valentine's Day</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is associated with the Roman…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey Ulrich, it wouldn't be you who gave</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her that necklace, by any chance?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You out of your mind, or something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't even know it was Valentine's Day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Gilles continues talking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An important day in ancient Rome…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What rhymes with tulip?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Microchip? Paperclip? Hypocrite?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, never mind.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What're you writing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A poem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Is it for Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's… biology homework.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Biology homework that rhymes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Odd… The necklace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't you, was it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I have to remind you that Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is supposed to be my cousin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Except that we both know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>she isn't your cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, what if it was me? Aelita isn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your property, as far as I know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, you admit it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't admit anything.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You just said it was you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, have you gone bananas?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your eyesight's not great,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but your hearing's worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Gilles clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you have more important subjects</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to discuss than today's lesson,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I suggest you do so in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the principal's office.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In your case, Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this comes as no surprise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] But you, Jeremy…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A model student in all areas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I simply don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two hours of detention should help you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to find some more convincing arguments.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're lucky it's Valentine's Day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or I'd have given you at least four.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm still waiting for an answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Why don't we call a truce, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Was it you who gave her the necklace?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes or no?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, then. No truce.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Come on, Einstein! It's stupid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to fight over such a little thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's right. Odd has every right to give</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita a present if he wants to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could I talk to you for a second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only if it's really important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] For me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is this for Valentine's Day?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's for Christmas…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course it's for Valentine's Day,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what do you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, open it, stupid!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A ticket to the Subsonics concert!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Isn't that your favorite group?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Well, yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I must be dreaming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got something for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I must be dreaming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I wrote you a little poem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"To tell you how much I flip,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if not with a tulip,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how I'm a victim of your charms,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and long to hold you in my arms,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With you I never feel gloomy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my little… Sissi!"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Ulrich… It rhymes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's so beautiful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, your bouquet is beautiful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How did you know that I liked roses?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I didn't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I figured</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were like all the other girls…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gulps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How romantic, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[guffaws]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a bit awkward… Thank you, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You couldn't have made me happier!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[water splashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Look, it's ridiculous</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to fight over such a little thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William had every right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to give Yumi a present,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and so did Sissi with Ulrich, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're the one to talk right now, okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, does anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>know where Aelita is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Settle down and take your seats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please open your text books to page 27.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer] The anatomical structure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of muscles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where were you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I looked for you everywhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think we could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>go to Sector Five after class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know where find the data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for making the antivirus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The one that will free you from XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You mean to say it just came</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you, just like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's just say that your necklace</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>inspired me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The problem is that given</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everybody's bad mood today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I doubt that Odd or Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or Yumi are going to want to go with you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can go by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's too dangerous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't forget XANA's ready to go to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any extreme to steal your memory, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please, Jeremy. I'm positive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on the right track.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And with an Overboard, I'm sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can get away from the monsters,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>even the latest ones, like the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Please…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grins]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's two more hours.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four hours of detention. I'm going to have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to suspend you if you do anything else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim seeing Spiderman stuck to the ceiling,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my best pupil is acting like a clown,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Valentine's Day is making everyone crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi says she'll go with me to Lyoko!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After everything that's happened today,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be nice to get</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something accomplished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metal grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical door clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[necklace blinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready, ladies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm starting up the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Yumi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Vehicles for the ladies coming right up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Materialization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] You need go due east</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get to the edge of the sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No way. I'm heading north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're supposed to go to Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zoom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yumi, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd be lying if I said I was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's gotten into her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't know. She's lost it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've absolutely got to stop her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's headed due north!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll try,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm going to need some back up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'm on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[keys clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jeremy, we're supposed to be doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>two hours of detention now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speak slower, I can't understand a word.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An attack by XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that all you can think of as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an excuse for us to make up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, listen to me! It's an emergency!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just come over here now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No cell phones in detention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Where is Jeremy Belpois?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, can you hear me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The latest Subsonics CD, look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not bad for getting in the mood</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before going to the concert.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[CD starts playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Listen…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's not talk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's listen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, Jeremy… Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll take care of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! Where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy just reminded me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a really important thing I have to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well… Leave.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door slams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[huffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy, I see her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, do you know how</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita got her necklace?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I think she found it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on her doorstep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think XANA could have put it there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm launching a superscan.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll know in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In my opinion, it's that dumb necklace</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that gives XANA control over Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wants to lead her straight to</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Scyphozoa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's exactly what I was afraid of…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like XANA's activated the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've just about caught up to her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I was about to say this was too easy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[fan swooshes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't want to sound pessimistic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but if Ulrich and Odd could hurry up…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You see, Aelita's got 104 fever,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so naturally she wants to see her cousin!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He's her only family here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A minute ago, it was 103!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. Her temperature keeps going up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by the minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do you take me for, an idiot?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Excuse-me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… Well, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim doesn't believe me…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>About Aelita's fever!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay… Put him on, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here you are, Jim. It's for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes… Of course… I understand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mr. Delmas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy using Mr. Delmas's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you hear me, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let Della Robbia see his cousin!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very well, whatever you say, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, when you have time, could I speak</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to you about a personal matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> It's about Suzanne Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A tunnel! We're about to get cut off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did you manage that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the principal?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wrote a new program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern! Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy using Jim's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up! Things are getting hot here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's one down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's one fan down as well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, tell me you've reprogrammed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the new vehicle!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Don't worry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Give me ten seconds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you still have a visual on Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She took off for Sector One,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Ice Sector. Use a way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] On the Overboard?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you absolutely sure about that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, yes. There's no reason you couldn't.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you're wrong, I swear I'll…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You swear you'll what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical grating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Can't do without me, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You won't get mad if I save Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, let him, Ulrich. He's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was being stupid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't blame you, Jeremy. I understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I'm a pretty charming guy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's only natural you'd be jealous of me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Transfer, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Transfer, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crash]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you must stop obeying XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Leave me alone!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, could you just remind me what'll</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>happen if I fall into the digital sea?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> If I were you, I'd avoid it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, then, if you could help me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of here, I'd appreciate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm bringing you back…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's going to take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a couple of minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I was afraid</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were going to say that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Happy to see me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I sure am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Move it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold her for long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm doing all I can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, Yumi, what did you think of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my poem for Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, this is really not the time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because, in fact,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I actually wrote it for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remind me to boost that program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Odd's about to need your help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita! It's me… Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich, hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You okay, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Brilliant, as usual!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That bad, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's cheating!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[slashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! We're never going to make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You've got to think of something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I do have one idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's awfully risky!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Odd, aim for Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! Don't forget that if Aelita loses all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>her life points, she'll disappear forever.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA wants her memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He won't risk losing that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Deep down,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he wants her alive as much as we do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No… But I can't think of anything else.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay, here I go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Only thirty life points left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You want me to stop?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! I just hope I'm right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's given up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa is at it again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was too good to be true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only ten life points left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why are you aiming at me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[necklace blinking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going to study this. You never know…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might be able to get some interesting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>information about XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, Aelita, from now on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you don't take any presents from anyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Promise! You know, Jeremy saved my life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] And that's the nicest Valentine's</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>present anyone could hope for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, but that won't save him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from being suspended</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for missing four hours of detention!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The principal's not going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be too happy about that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, I'm sure there's a solution!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! What are you looking at me for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'm really happy to be going</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the concert with you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you won't forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to talk to your father beforehand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Don't worry,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get Jeremy out of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, that's a real friend,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ready to sacrifice himself for his pal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Are you sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's sacrificing himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as much as all that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He doesn't seem to be bothered by it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Maybe not…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it was for me that he wrote the poem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poor Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>