<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tal</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>l ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>BAD CONNECTION</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Odd, knock it off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and open this door right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Stern, what are you doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>walking around half naked?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's a pretty awful imitation of Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't Delmas. It was Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what are you dressed like that for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been out here for 15 minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd refuses to open up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But how come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Who knows? He won't even answer me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me handle it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, if you don't open up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this door right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can forget about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my portion of meatballs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice try, but it's not going to work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lock rattles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Never fails.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] After you, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it because of your film?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yes. I mean, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a film of mine will be screened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-for an audience of ignoramuses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Then, what's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My parents are in town,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're coming to see my film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's really nice of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] No, it stinks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You didn't have a fight with them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, just the opposite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is it then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] A weird relationship problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Teenagers are always having</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>lots of conflicts with their parents,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>generation gap, except for one: me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My mother and father are always cool</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and understanding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're perfect.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Bummer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll trade yours for mine anytime.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] If only there was something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we could fight over,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so I could finally be a normal adolescent!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a major drag.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really feel sorry for you, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We can feel your pain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't want to be in your shoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I knew I couldn't expect you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cheer up. With luck,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll hate your film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that would be too good to be true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Della Robbia] How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Couldn't be better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, it's really so good to see you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you look wonderful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've still got that great appetite?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And these must be your friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd talks a lot about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How do you do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hello.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're really delighted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to meet you all at last.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a present for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can wear it to the screening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you try it on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, but later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm much too busy right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Guess he's a uptight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because of the screening.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's understandable.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After all, it is a premiere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] You're absolutely right,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd is undeniably talented.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's very creative, intelligent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He participates orally in class, but--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's true, he is intelligent.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When he was barely two years old,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he managed to completely take apart</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>his uncle's stereo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure if he were four at the time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he would have been able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to put it back together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I happen to be quite</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an electronics buff myself, and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As I was saying,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your son has many fine qualities, but--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You needn't tell us that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's got qualities coming out of his ears!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He eats well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He has a wonderful sense of humor.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even when it's not funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's a daredevil on a skateboard,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he has an excellent ear for music too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Undoubtedly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No doubt about it, no. However--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If he wanted to,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd could be at the head of his class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he's just too modest for that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Della Robbia] You were saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've been very reassuring.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know better than I do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that young people today</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't work hard enough at school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's true.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They have trouble concentrating.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we don't want to keep you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any longer, Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You must have a lot of work to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Yes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[parents] Good-bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door closes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] What's the matter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with this piece of junk?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Something wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, it stopped working!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It did? I paid a lot of money for that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you to buy the higher priced model!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[foot tapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth, Let me have a look at it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll fix it for you in no time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You know how to do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas] Of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a true gift</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for delicate work like this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I was your age,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my nickname was Mr. Circuit Breaker--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Fixer, that is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[plastic snaps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is this thing still under warranty?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, hold on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good evening. There are some empty seats</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the first row.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, we'll have a large popcorn, please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, sorry, I don't have any.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I just might have half a box</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Nibblejacks lying around somewhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I was only kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh yeah, sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So was I.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm putting it to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd would kill me if the Superscan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>went off in the middle of his film.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's not much chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that XANA would launch an attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the three minutes the film lasts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi, what's the matter?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't look so great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd has made fun of me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in every single one of his films!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughing] Yeah, that's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Keep laughing, Nicolas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the whole school's gonna find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what happened to Mrs. Hertz's hamsters!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But where is Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better go see if I can find him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very well, now we can begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome cinema lovers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to this special screening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Mandibles and Purple Mauve</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the latest creation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of our own Odd Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Please do forgive me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for not having seen this work yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I understand, however,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the film cleverly combines fiction</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with documentary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>truth in short.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But, in the end, what is truth?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where could he have gone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet, you'll give me away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is ridiculous.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your parents are looking for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know. I'm stressed out enough.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got the answer to your problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get off your butt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get to a seat inside!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why don't we all listen now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the film maker himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about his latest work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you have the floor!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hello, first of all,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I would like to--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll start the screening as soon as</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the director's father returns.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Is this some sort of a joke?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who was it, darling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't you keep quiet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and stop batting your eyes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at that old goat?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Let's not fly off the handle here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the fly that needs handling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm onto your game!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Have you lost your mind, darling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I prefer losing my mind to having yours!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, it's for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, hello? What is it now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phones ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since when do you keep your cell phones on</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a movie theater? Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, take the wax out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your ears and listen!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Mommy, is that you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If it's okay with everyone, we can begin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does that little brat want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe he wants us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to shut his trap for him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wouldn't do him any harm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something is going on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I don't like the looks of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just what I was afraid of:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like XANA is using cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you get a call,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whatever you do, don't answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at that coward,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>slinking away like a little rat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are we going to let</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that snot nose take off like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[crowd angrily shout] No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's not very polite to sneak off</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a thief in the night, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He needs to learn a little respect</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>whether he likes it or not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shout] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's no need to get all worked up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll give each of you an autograph.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He deserves to be taught a lesson,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doesn't he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I vote for voting against him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, man.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't just stand there like a bunch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of house plants. Go on, hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, are we looking for</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little spanking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There he is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This time, he's not gonna get away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shouting angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep up the pace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna get him this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's wrong with everyone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is it something they ate?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, my boy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how would you like a loving spoonful?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, Rosa, but I'm not very hungry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's he doing? Where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought he was behind us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have been held up by his fan club.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll check out what's happening</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by locating their cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, I found him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Where is he?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take a guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chewing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm… Meatballs!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come to think of it, I am hungry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks pretty bad for him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's totally surrounded.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We've gotta rescue him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-How? The whole school's out to get him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'd be faster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we deactivated the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what we've gotta do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head for the scanner room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're going in now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's hope that Odd can play for time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gravy? There isn't enough gravy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[elevator whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock seals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[low humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[airlock seals]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[click]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[low humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical sparking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower in front of you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the end of the path.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Any suggestions, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like a ladder maybe.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without vehicles forget about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You could have virtualized us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the summit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, but there's a bug.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't do any better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I can't even bring up your vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA threw a virus into the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All I can get you is the overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Send it anyway. It'll have to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Coming up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wanna keep me company?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[vehicle zooms]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sword slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just in time. Thanks, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb] He's gotta be in here somewhere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch, I'm gonna sweep him away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll be biting the dust</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when we get through with him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Nicolas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thought you could hide from us, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Lunchtime!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't touch me! I'm invulnerable,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>thanks to my shield. Go on, keep trying.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Nicolas groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is awful, wasting perfectly good food</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on a vegetable like him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah-ha, alone at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metal clangs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Incredible, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is happening? It looks like everyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at school has gone crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's because of the cell phones.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How come you haven't gone bananas too?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] 'Cause my phone's a piece of junk.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] The one place we haven't checked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from top to bottom is the lunchroom!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's split!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There he is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what is my daughter doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with that little scoundrel?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must've forced her to be on his side!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Children become monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when they're not instilled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a sense of discipline!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shouting angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what are you waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Reprogram the overwing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not working.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll try the overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got a problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] You're not the only one! Hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Manta screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold on any longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi and Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Whew! Here at least,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we might have a little peace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gardener] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Peace, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eternal peace is what you'll get!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd and Sissi screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, thanks, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Just great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's happening with Odd's board?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's loading,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it'll take time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We could try to climb up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The rock face is much too smooth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd never make it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still scared of heights, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all shouting angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can't get good gardeners nowadays.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I do not think it's a very good idea</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to frighten these poor children</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your garden tools, sir.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, that's a pity!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rest assured,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're not the type of parents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who would ever shirk</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>their responsibilities.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We promised you a fitting punishment,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you're going to get it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise never to complain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about not having conflicts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with my parents again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers firing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like shell fish are back in season.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, welcoming us with open claws.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Okay, I'm on it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser charging and fires]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna try something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you just lost</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>forty life points, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and I can feel it too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try my best not to take another hit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[robotic whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[airlock releases]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, what an idiot I am!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're not getting anywhere here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>overboard in two or three seconds!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here I go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! How does Odd manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to pilot this thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's not afraid of falling.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm afraid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Anything but this!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Della Robbia]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Trust us. It's for your own good.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a little step forward</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you won't be afraid anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Obey for once in your life!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't we get a last request?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They do have the right to that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like one last club sandwich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with organic mayo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, one club sandwich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but forget the organic mayo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I would like a purple parachute</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go with my top.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, okay, time out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Last requests are gonna have to wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>until later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich shouts] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword slicing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The coast is clear!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think these children could use</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little parental guidance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Absolutely.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get this over with.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we doing up here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know better than to get so close</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the edge, don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? I wonder who could have pushed me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the edge?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And here we have a splendid specimen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a dung beetle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now, we have a magnificent</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>field grasshopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, he's saving the worst for last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] But what could</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this strange creature be?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A spring roll?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, no, it's an enormous larva.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] A caterpillar,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>metamorphosing into a lovely butterfly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>