<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>BRAGGING RIGHTS</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[running footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] To think, this was supposed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be a piece of cake!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[narrator] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Several hours earlier…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I'll say it once more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for those of you who were daydreaming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, run up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two, jump onto the springboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Three, push off of the horse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four, pike vault… And five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>land feet together on the mat.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You got that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I didn't get it all, Coach.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So would you mind giving us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a demonstration, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with you, Pichon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing to it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only a halfwit couldn't manage it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, two, three…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He got to five without doing four.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pichon… Funny, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see what you can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] And don't forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>those five golden rules.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That horse</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>oughta be in the rodeo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia, front and center.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's your turn to fall flat on your face.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[clears throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student 2] Perfect!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student 3] He's so cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, how was that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're right Jim,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>only a halfwit couldn't manage it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls to himself]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Perfect! Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I do a vault worthy of the Olympics,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and bam! Four hours of detention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that the kind of payoff I deserve?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Well… Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on Odd,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the way you spoke to Jim was…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Was what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Obnoxious, pretentious…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Pretentious?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one's more humble than I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Who are you trying to kid?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your middle name</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>oughta be "braggart," Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's for sure. I can't remember even one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>day that you didn't sing your own praises.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that is so wrong.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I can prove it to you, too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I'll bet you a week of desserts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you can't go 24 hours</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without bragging.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know someone who just won himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>some yummy seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Nuh-uh, me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No, me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hey, are you guys all through?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I ought to remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we're supposed to be blowing up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA's Supercomputer tonight after class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-In the jungle?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean we're going back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, and we don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be a problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Odd knocked out the energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>field protecting it last time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And once again, where mere mortals</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>would have failed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd demonstrates his great…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um, modesty and humility…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So thanks to our non-bragging hero,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's gonna be a piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hatch squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[brakes screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm entering the coordinates</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the Replika.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Holoweb system connected.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should be able to see it now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got it on radar.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Affirmative.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Skid in position in front of the entrance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Digital Key engaged.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beam charging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beam blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic squeaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Tower in sight, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Docking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Gotcha. I'm activating</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the tower for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you ready?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through intercom] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Teleportation Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Teleportation Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're the greatest, Jeremy. It worked!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your teleportation is pretty accurate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're in the middle of the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cut the flattery guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>before it goes to my head… Like Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I do not have a swelled head!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That being said,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>considering</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my extraordinary exploits last time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't see why I wasn't teleported over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Gotta give everyone a chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to have fun, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And if the only dessert you want</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to eat for a week is humble pie,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just keep it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay Jeremy, which way is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Head east. You'll go through a door.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then go straight</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and a little further on, at your left,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you should see the door</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Supercomputer room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Got it. We're on it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bingo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great, all you've gotta do now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is open the door</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and trash the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We told you this would be no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, why can't I get the door open?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh right, the last time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita used her digital power to open it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll figure out something.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me handle this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Uh, Ulrich… Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great. Now the panel's dead</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the door is still locked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What an idiot! I said to wait, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You should've said it sooner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What do we do now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hold on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ah, I've got an idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys have to cut</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the power to the door's electromagnetic</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>locking mechanism.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know where the generator is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yeah, I'll guide you there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll stay here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as it opens, I'll go in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get rid of the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Ulrich, turn around and go back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the first intersection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then, take the corridor on the right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'm on my way, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, can you hear us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Uh… Just a little problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No sweat. Everything's cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure? Because I'd love</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go and help Ulrich and Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Modestly, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Sorry Odd, but you've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your work cut out for you already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just spotted an activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're on it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through intercom]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get ready to disembark, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Disembark!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical whirring and crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Einstein, could you send us a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] What were you saying, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh, nothing. Thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Uh-oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a little problem here, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer bleeps and beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I see William and three Hornets!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should Odd stay here and fight them off,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while I deactivate the tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No, the tower's too far away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Odd could never handle them alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four hornets and Sir William the Lowlife?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Four Laser arrows and it's game over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd? Forget your bet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs nervously]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That isn't bragging,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's the simple truth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You see? Lucky for us I was here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, it's easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just hold off William long enough</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for Ulrich to neutralize the generator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll only take a few minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] No problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, do you read me? Where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>In front of the generator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great. Tell me how it looks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's this huge machine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with a bunch</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of flashing thingamajigs all over it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy laughs] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, just neutralize the commutator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that powers the lab doors.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The commu what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>The button!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you see a little red button?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] There's not just one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are millions of them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This thing's lit up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a pinball machine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Just proceed by elimination.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm gonna do this my way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your way, huh, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Like smashing up the generator</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your saber</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and short-circuiting the Supercomputer?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You guessed it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Give me a minute to think it over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This way, kiddies!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[intermittent swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[glass shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screaming] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If I tell them this,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll say I'm bragging again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[glass shattering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi]Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doors hissing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, remind me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of what there is in a vivarium.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Cybernetic spiders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spider chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You guys are ugly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've had enough of your cyber-spider web!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy, those cyber-spiders</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are being controlled by XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and they're just behind me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not for long. The Supercomputer should be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>off-line in just a couple of seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, your idea isn't big on finesse,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it should work.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical crackling and crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Hmm.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[machine powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whenever you want for that short circuit!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clanging]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where'd it go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, even my looks blow them away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's happening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We did it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Already?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Energy field!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Replika is disappearing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better get airborne!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] That was what</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you call a real "swan song" dive.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you this'd be a piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can head for the Skid now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your mission's over, guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Are you ready, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm teleporting you back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hold on. I think something's up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The power's back on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[machine powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh, Jeremy? Is the Replika</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>supposed to be regenerating?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's not supposed to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, there's gotta be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a backup generator somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even I could've figured that out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only, where is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] How do I know?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm looking for it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Better hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm going back to Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, how come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you haven't teleported me back yet?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's that alarm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Oh, just a little hang-up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing important.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] I see!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Not so fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, Jeremy, where is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this backup generator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] I still can't find it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Better take care of</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>those spiders before they take care of us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you have to deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you stay and protect the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no! Why do I have to stay</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while everyone else is having fun?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wasn't bragging.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[menacing music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[relieved groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Somebody just showed up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and he wants to play with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Feel like playing tag?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[heavy thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To think this was supposed to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a piece of cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, better hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Yumi are in a huge jam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm doing what I can!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy breathing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still got a ways to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heavy thud]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] For me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[William screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stings, doesn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super smoke!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sword swishing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whistles and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, did you just blow William away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by yourself?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Yep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No boasting?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What do you think I am, a braggart?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hmm…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Ulrich, I just located</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the auxiliary generator!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alarm blaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, but it's a little too late.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming] Yumi! Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened to the two lovebirds?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hmm… Interesting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I get it. They knock each other out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well Jeremy, we kinda blew our mission,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found the auxiliary generator,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but the problem is there isn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>anyone around to take it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I don't wanna seem pretentious,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, get back into the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll teleport you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Roger, but once I succeed,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't say I did it just to show off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm ready to go, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I read you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Teleportation Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get out of the lab</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and watch out for spiders.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I can't see any hairy legs yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I can, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical roaring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you gotta get up and fast, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the Skid goes, so do you. Get up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting and exploding]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jeremy, I'm out of the lab.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which way now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go left. You should run</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>right into the auxiliary generator.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Uh-oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That generator's a really popular spot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Because it looks like</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a full house.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[spiders chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to deactivate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that tower right away!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a few seconds more.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wings buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Oh no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming and moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs frustrated]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe it… Let me guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on my own from now on, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry about that…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Better make it fast too,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or else we can say goodbye</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the Skid, Ulrich and Yumi for good!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, Odd, it's now or never.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Geronimo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[howls and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I need ammunition!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on a second.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm reloading you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay, you're all set.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's that for a pike vault?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you've got just one arrow left.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So take good aim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One arrow is all I need!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical buzzing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[crashing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't say I didn't aim well.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>De-teleportation Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosions]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, nice place you've got here, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's… going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing. Things are cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go back to sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rumbling and crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can come back, Odd. It's over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[triumphal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Skid swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical creaking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosions]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You were right, you know.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You couldn't have asked</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for an easier mission.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He took out both William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Supercomputer on his own?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's crazier is that he hasn't bragged</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about it even once!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Who knows? Maybe he's changed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You mean</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he's suddenly become humble?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Miracles happen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He might have become</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sensible, responsible kid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yelling] Yee-ha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forty point one seconds flat!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You are now looking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the new world record holder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the fastest shower! How cool is that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Gimme an "O"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gimme a "D"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gimme another "D"!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who's the man of the cen-tu-ry?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you're handsome, too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I love it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you break records like that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Odd…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, right, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can have my desserts!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you don't even care?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess I gotta face facts. Yes,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a braggart and I love it that way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Svelte, but muscular, don't you think?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>