<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>LYOKO MINUS ONE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[up-tempo rock music playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, will you kill that dumb alarm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here are the photocopies</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you asked me for, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You wanted 31, is that right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's right, 31, thank you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rise and shine, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The birds are chirping away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy… Odd and Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are going out with each other.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? Oh, it's you, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Awful joke. Anyway, what's the time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the story? You've given up sleeping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a bed, or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I was trying to find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to send you guys into the internet</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so you can track XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you figure something out?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Just look at you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No one's gonna vote for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not voting for a zombie</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the year but for their student rep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] It's not about how you look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's all about what you have to say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least you're optimistic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It can't hurt, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, you've got one thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're up against the lamest candidate</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the galaxy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Now, how about giving me the smile</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a real winner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A smile of victory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi scoffs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We'll never win at this rate.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb] Why don't you run, then, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't! The principal's daughter</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>isn't allowed to be a class rep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Therefore,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the new student rep's gonna be you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and definitely not Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do I make myself perfectly clear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's what I like to see,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a nice winner smile.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not a smile, Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're crushing my kneecaps.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Take a copy of my platform.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Platform? But for what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My platform.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're looking at the next student rep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're running, Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why didn't you say anything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because surprise is the secret weapon</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my election campaign.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the second weapon is poetry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you all want to have your say,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why not give the nod to good old Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I love lines that rhyme with Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I'm warning you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone tries to pull anything, detention.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can join that smart aleck,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William Dunbar, in the study hall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you've made yourself clear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Roger, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, I mean Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fine. Let's not forget</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what we're going to be looking for.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The purpose of our field trip today</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to witness the early effects</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of pollution on our ecosystem</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and especially in the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Effects that might someday</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>mean the end of our forest</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and all animal and plant life, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you saying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there won't be anymore bunny rabbits,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or little birds or trees or mushrooms,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they'll all disappear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow. I love that perfume.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[light music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] And so I ask you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why should good students</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>represent the bad?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why not let a near dropout like me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>speak for all the other near dropouts?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[class mumbling in agreement]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you're not smiling, Jeremy. How come?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because I don't want to look</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as dorky as you, Herb, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does Belpois and Pinchon know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about our problems?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They always get A's and B's, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They don't know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the fear of getting left back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're not capable</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of defending our cause.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Bravo! Good point, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, near dropouts.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's time for all of us to take a stand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[overlapping conversations]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy 1] Odd sure gets my vote.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy 2] Odd will be a great</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>student rep 'cause he knows what we need.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right. Now quiet down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[class clapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert sounding off]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic rumbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[kids groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[boy] What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] Go on, Douglas,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't be scared. You gotta put her down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you're in the jungle. Hey…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter? Are we already…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In conclusion,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I promise to put lots of pretty plants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in each and every one of your classrooms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Won't that be nice?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah! Bravo! Bravo! Way to go, Herb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Clap, stupid! Go on, go on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna vote for Herb, aren't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your turn to bat now, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, this is not a game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Being elected as the class rep is really</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>serious with lots of responsibilities.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you don't think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm capable of handling them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I never said that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, but that's what you're thinking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, answer it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's probably some think tank</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that wants your precious advice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello? Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm in real big trouble!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My whole bus has been Xanafied!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you don't mind, Belpois,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're all waiting for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, look, I've gotta hang up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's just launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, if you're still a candidate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>speak up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's your platform?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… I… I had some notes but I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I left them back in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go… and get them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go with him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To keep an eye on the competition.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we better go too,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to separate them if they start fighting.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Vote for me, everyone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't believe this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[animal howling in distance]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Attack confirmed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has activated a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, where are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] At the Red Trail crossroads.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold out much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, you head for the forest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And we'll see what we can do</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>about the activated tower around Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs deeply]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim shouting in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> The activated</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tower is in the Forest Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to get you in</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as close as possible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita. Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Okay. We're here Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower is due north.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You should be able to see it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from where you are.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Can't miss it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here's your taxi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hop aboard! We're off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital scanning, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is sending you some monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How original can you get.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He hates it when we're bored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, let's be polite.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll say hello to them first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Odd, take care of yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If anything happened to you, I wouldn't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have any competition except for Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Einstein. I'll take care</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of them and then I'll go after you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser Arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's turn around.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You better be careful, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lots of tarantulas are on the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just can't stay away from me, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It looks like they can't either.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[birds chirping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing maniacally]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dial tone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on, Yumi, pick up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps approaching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are you following me for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I heard it all. Yumi's in trouble.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I came to see if I could help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know what you're talking about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now do you know what I'm talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to keep them busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As soon as the coast is clear,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>head for the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When you gotta go…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monsters groan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Wait, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're still too close.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim laughing maniacally]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, that's Jim shooting lightning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of his fingers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is this a nightmare or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, do you want to help Yumi or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Then don't say anything</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and do what I tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monsters shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What, Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is heading for the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She should be shutting it down</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in about five minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good, because I'm getting ready</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do something risky with William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William? What are you and William</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>doing together?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you two guys buddies now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Nah, he's giving me a hand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I've got a big problem!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scyphozoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita through computer] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's already got all of the data Xana</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>needed from me. What can it want now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know, Aelita. But please don't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>stick around trying to find out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, change in the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower's not gonna</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>get deactivated right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess we can't count on you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How are you doing zombies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, I know I'm not welcome,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I love strolling in the woods.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim in distorted voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After him!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[chuckling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Yumi…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, try to hit him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the energy field.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Scyphozoa’s attacked Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, she needs your help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd love to help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But my new playmate doesn't seem to agree.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks like the Scyphozoa has implanted</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>something into Aelita's memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Almost there, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wheezing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita is alive. I don't understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, you gotta wake up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yoohoo! Hey, come on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can take a nap later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, got a problem here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Something's wrong with Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, answer me, it's Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wake up, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Find your overboard, and follow Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what about the tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music fades out]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Fifteen against one, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been through worst.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what's going on with the tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm back and ready to go but it's Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who's in trouble this time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's only a slim chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of deactivating the tower right away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi through headset] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>How slim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To be honest, none at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready to fight, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[inhales, nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning in pain]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yoohoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Grab that girl!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] Banzai!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Go after him, right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi whistles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi shouts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You taught us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that wood doesn't conduct electricity!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you hear me, Odd? What's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got the feeling that Aelita is heading</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the way tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just what we needed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[echoing beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing, beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] What is going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd… what happened to me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you about it later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Right now, let's run for it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's happening now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The sector's disappearing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rematerialize us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi and Ulrich groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William's not in great shape.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, did you manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get the tower deactivated?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I didn't. It deactivated itself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because the forest sector</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the process of disappearing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Jeremy, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[both screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Rematerialization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what happened.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, for one thing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was a pretty close call.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Otherwise, I don't know what happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>either. But I'm sure Einstein can tell us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all moaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim and Mrs. Hertz groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Look over there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That moss must be the result of pollution!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I love science field trips.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door creaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[snoring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, nap time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but don't you dare dream about Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a nightmare!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It's no use.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Forest Sector doesn't exist anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has totally wiped it off the map.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If only I hadn't gone into that way tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and if only I hadn't punched in that code.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't you see? XANA used you, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He launched an attack</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>just to lure us to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But why would he do that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If the surface sectors disappear, we won't</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>be able to get to Sector Five anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean that XANA's gonna destroy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the sectors?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] He sure is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If only I could find a way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to materialize you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>directly into Sector Five.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like I've got plenty of work ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's a good thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not gonna get elected class rep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you know that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Easy, 'cause we're all gonna vote for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Fumet] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>And your newly elected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>class representative is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd Della Robbia!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cheering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't tell me that you voted for Odd too!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Take that grin off your face, dorkhead!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student 1] Odd, now that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're our class rep…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[student 2]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think you can get me out of gym class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey! Cool it, calm down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One at a time, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>