<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>TEMPTATION</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say, Odd, why do you always have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to wait for the last second?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because it's more fun, that's why.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that what you call "fun"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks more like "insanity" if you ask me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, really? You mean there's a difference?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Thanks Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't mention it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Aelita, you're only a few minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Bummer. I was just starting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to enjoy myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Careful! Behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Well, lots of action!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Aelita, we're gonna have to jump.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry. I'll cover you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Scyphozoa shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Good job, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All done, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower's been deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay. I'll start the return</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and get you all home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Really? Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA didn't even have time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to launch an attack on earth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You can't be too careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… May I remind you that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>going back in time makes XANA stronger.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I know what I'm doing, all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Well, if you know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>then explain it to us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just trust me, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that's not the point.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>That's my final answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past, now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy's really becoming a pain.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He just flies off the handle</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for no reason at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's like a time bomb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who knows? Maybe he's got family problems.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or else, he's only just realized</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he has a split personality</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that when the moon is full,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he becomes the son of Doctor Schrank!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Capable of grafting animal body parts</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>onto human beings!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And he now knows that he must face up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to a fate worse than death.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've been watching</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Horror at the Hospital </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>again, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How can anyone pass up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such a fantastic program?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all grunt softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Whoa, there he is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's life, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where were you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In my room, why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is there a law against it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Chill, will you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We were worried, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm a big boy now so just get off my back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you might just have something there</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with your Dr. Schrank theory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ha! You see? I told you so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bell ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right, in the meantime,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've also got a fate worse than death.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Mrs. Meyer's class.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer] Thales theory allows us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to calculate length.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For example, in a triangle marked ABC.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With straight lines called RS and BC</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which are parallel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First we calculate X, then SC.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hypothetically, ABC is a triangle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>R is a point on AB.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>N is a point on AC.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Meyer] …equals seven times eight,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>10x equals 56.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And that's it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's rather simple in the end.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ma'am?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh… Yes, Jeremy? Question?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May I go to the infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yes, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you want me to come with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Jeremy skipped history class?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And gym class too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And now he's skipping lunch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Gym class and lunch, I can understand.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But skipping history class</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is not Jeremy's style at all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna check his room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[typing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I brought your notes from the classes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you missed this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Put them down on the bed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, if there's anything wrong,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you can talk to me about it, right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's up with you guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing wrong with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just working, that's all.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I've almost found the antivirus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which will free you from XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Isn't that worth spending some time on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, of course, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've been acting strange recently.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You should take a break from time to time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah. Does XANA take breaks? No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So what do you want?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You want him to steal your memory?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't want to lose you, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I can hardly recognize you anymore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's something I have to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you XANA never takes a break!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You sure you're done now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone ringing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>SOS XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, Jeremy. We're on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hurry up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has launched an attack.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in distorted voice] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>You over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sit back down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich and Odd] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said, sit down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd] Whoa!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting angrily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I shouldn't have said her mashed potatoes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>looked like barf, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me, this looks more</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>like a xanafication.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cover me. I'll try to reach Aelita</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and Jeremy at the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problemo. Ulrich, on three.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>One, two, three!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready for another round?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not every day we get the opportunity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to break up the place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is in the Mountain Sector.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, we'll just have to wait</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>What on earth are they doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-They're doing what they can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA has possessed Rosa.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll have to make do without them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start the virtualization process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scanning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>should be straight ahead of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We can see it, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But there's also</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an army of monsters blocking our way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a funny feeling</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we should take cover. Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, Aelita, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We'd be a lot better</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you could materialize the Overwing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, coming up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going on your end?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Because over here,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're starting to run out of ammo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, you better hustle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>May I remind you that Rosa's specialty</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is chopped sirloin?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, ladies, get a move on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd and Ulrich are in a really bad way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No kidding! All we need here</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are some sandwiches for a nice picnic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll never get through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold on a second. I've got a little idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Little or big, it doesn't matter,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as long as it works.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here she comes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I know</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what Tweety feels like against Sylvester.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what are you guys waiting for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita's in the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just hang in there for another 30 seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thirty seconds? That's like an eternity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Rosa groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, I think this calls</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a return to the past, don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right. I'm launching it. Get ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's he up to?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He should be here already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why don't we go check his room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[dramatic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, wake up! It's terrible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita has fallen in love with Herb!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No reaction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-This is really serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Right. I'm calling the hospital.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look! His eyelids are moving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[melancholic music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must be dreaming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[footsteps echoing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[loud whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What could've happened to him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something must've happened</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during the last return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's worth checking out the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Should we search Jeremy's room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I really don't wanna do that, but…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Nothing special,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>except that I just found out that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy still wears underwear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with kangaroos on them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to tell him to move onto boxers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No activated towers,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but there's a ton of files.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Hey, I can't open this one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's called "My Journal."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The logs are all normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There certainly was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a major discharge of energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>during that last return</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the past, though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But they're no different from</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>any of the previous returns to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We need you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Can you meet us in Jeremy's room?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] There! And… I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>got it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't easy, but I got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These are video files.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just open the first one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Today, I have decided</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to start a video journal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a bit like the diary Franz Hopper kept.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way, if anything happens to me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>others might be able</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to continue my research.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My search to find the antivirus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which will free Aelita from XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has never been closer to total success,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's thanks to Franz Hopper's diary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and thanks to the data recovery</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Sector Five</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that I was able to decode</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>part of his diary</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that explains how to use</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the returns to the past</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to logarithmically increase</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your intelligence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I immediately tried it. It's amazing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as if my brain</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>suddenly had the processing power</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of ten computers linked in series.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A neuronal headset.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Open the most recent entry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] This one's from yesterday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Every time I use the headset, my mental</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and physical health gets worse and worse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I'm moving so far forward</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in my research,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't stop this close to success.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-That's all we needed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is there anything we can do to save him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's go to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll meet you there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, I have to stop by the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I want to make sure that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attack isn't directed at Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come with me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there are papers we have to sign.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both men] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey! My ambulance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Is Jeremy in there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yes, but he isn't driving it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hi, Aelita. XANA is taking control</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of Jeremy's ambulance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm gonna try to do something</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'm really counting on you guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll go as fast as we can, I promise.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, Ulrich, are you in position?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization in 30 seconds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[static zapping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The tower is that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] I'm sorry</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I couldn't materialize the vehicles.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to go on foot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revving]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[repetitive thuds]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sirens wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi echoing] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi echoing] Jeremy! It's me, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi echoing] Wake up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy… Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just huge problems, same old routine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Before we can do anything else,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have to get out of here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey. Don't you think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we ought to stop the ambulance first?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, of course I do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But do you mind telling me how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make it fast because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we are heading straight for the river.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] There!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe you shouldn't have said it so loud.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got an idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I love it when you say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yowling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[siren wailing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting] Hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, darn it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tires screeching]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help had better be on the way, like now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Got any other brilliant ideas, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Uh… well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Man, that was not cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps] Watch it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[growling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monster shrieks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, Odd, Aelita, are you there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To tell the truth, no.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now the problem is how to reach the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Jeremy have gone for a dip</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in an ambulance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the bottom of the river.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Just a little tarantula</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get rid of first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shield!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, leave it to me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice one!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, we got it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich through computer]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita has deactivated the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Super. Now we can drown in peace.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're still at the bottom of the river.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The only thing that can save us now</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is a return to the past.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But I have no idea how to do that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Put me on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I need you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do exactly what I say, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, right, huh… Yes, wait, wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not so fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where's the button? I don't see it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Quickly!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-On the right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>On the upper right</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of the keyboard, the "jump button"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-in Ultimate Blaster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Uh… Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I got it. Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't tell me he's out cold again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I checked the calculations I've done</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>over the past few weeks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>most of them are wrong!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you were destroying your health</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without even improving your brain power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't call that a very good deal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you think that XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>had something to do with it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He certainly put me on the track.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But the information did come</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Franz Hopper's diary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In some way, then,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we have not just one but two enemies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hopper is certainly not an enemy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But his discoveries are out of our league.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I think we'd better be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For now, the important thing is that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you get back to being your old self again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's for sure. Seeing you so grouchy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you were getting to be like Dr. Schrank.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Or even worse. Huh, Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! I am not… grouchy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah right. Give me a break!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Well, all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>