<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>NEW ORDER</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've really done a good job, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA better behave himself</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>now that we've got these things!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gleeful scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be careful all the same!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, Einstein! I know how to ride.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way I'm gonna let Ulrich beat me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wahoo!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Oh, no you don't!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[revs engine]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, I didn't have time to perfect</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the program that calculates trajectory…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, yeah. There's still some work</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do on the overboard, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Maybe it's the rider</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who needs work!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened Odd?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You miss a step?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very funny. I'd like to see you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on an overboard.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I guess surfing's not my thing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Sorry to interrupt</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your fascinating conversation,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it looks like XANA has spotted you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-There's something coming your way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's really weird!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't tell what it is!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey! What's that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it looks like trouble, big-time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've never seen</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a monster like that one before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA must have just created it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In any case, it says here that</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's got more life points than the others.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how about reprogramming our vehicles?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm on it already,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's gonna take time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-On my signal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I'll go first!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I'm going to keep it busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's a deactivated tower not far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Direction: North by northwest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get out of there, and come and meet me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But hurry up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, you overgrown spider! Looking for me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrieking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, you just lost 20 life points!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's got a powerful laser.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What does it take to destroy this thing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Vehicles… ready.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well it's about time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, I'm doing my best!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Let me go first.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Go on, we'll be watching you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser Arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] This thing is really unbeatable!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Need a hand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Laser Arrows!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA's gonna start programming</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>new monsters,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it means our troubles, guys,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have only just begun!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, Einstein, one thing is sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You're gonna have to program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>our vehicles faster.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Otherwise, we don't stand a chance</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against those Tarantulas!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your aunt what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Tarantulas. The new monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like to give my enemies a name.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What worries me is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that our friend XANA has obviously found</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to increase his power.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think he's still evolving?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Maybe so…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In any case, from now on, we have to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>ready for anything and everything!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I'd better get back to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If XANA activates a tower,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd better be there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy hesitates] Should we tell her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita] Hmm?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well of course we should tell her!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Why keep good news like that a secret?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Keep what a secret?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Would someone please tell me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what's going on?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Over the past few weeks,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've spent all of my time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>developing the vehicles and an antivirus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to free you from XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I also perfected a whole new program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for detecting activated towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A super scanner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Much more accurate than the old one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] With instant detection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Meaning, you don't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to stay on Lyoko all the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So I'm gonna live…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, with us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've already enrolled you as a boarder</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>at the school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything's all set up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We wanted to surprise you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] This is so wonderful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] And… this is your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not very big,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you'll like it here, Miss…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stones…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita Stones. Like the rock group.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm Odd's cousin from Canada.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah… So, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Breakfast starts at 7 a.m.,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and dinner's at 7 p.m.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] It's against the rules to be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in your room between 8 a.m. and 4:30 p.m.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can ask your friends</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia, Stern and Belpois</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to fill you in on the rest of the rules…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is if they can remember them!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] I don't want to hear</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>another word about the school newspaper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] This excursion is for 8th</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and 9th graders only, is that clear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi, stop wiggling around!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Five more minutes</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and you can run around all you want to.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, is everything okay, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you all settled in?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes I am, and I love my room!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And what's this field trip</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>everybody's talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna make a biodiversity scrapbook.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz wants us to take pictures,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and to draw plants and flowers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That kind of thing. You and I</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have been paired up to work together.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Anyone seen Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's under the arches.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think he's waiting for Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich to self] Okay… Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's something I have to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that doesn't sound right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, there's something serious</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you and I have to talk about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, she'll freak out if I say that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right… Yumi, you and I have to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… I have something to tell you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[boy] Yo, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Mrs. Hertz said okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can work together on the field trip.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey… William… Do you know Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh… Oh, you're Ulrich Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi mentioned you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ready to go?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Didn't you have something to tell me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll tell you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Hey, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everyone's leaving.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to be back by six.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who is that guy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, who, him? That's William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] He's the new guy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He got kicked out of his last school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's totally cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you know that trees grow new branches</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from one year to the next according</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to an exponential ratio of 1.6?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] 1.618 to be exact.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] It's the golden ratio.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say… Do you think nature obeys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>non-linear equation systems?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Can you believe those two?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who do they think they are anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Mr. and Mrs. Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Who?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi, where are you going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The woods are this way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, but the stores are that way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… we're supposed to draw plants…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a florist in the shopping center.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] There aren't any monsters</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in these woods!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That only happens in fairy tales</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or in silly horror pictures.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The kind that Odd likes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] You don't like horror films.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I find them inaccurate,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scientifically speaking.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I don't have time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go to the movies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got my work cut out for me with XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Oh no, I don't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I left my laptop in my room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA attacks?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We'll run back and get it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll just keep working by myself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with the drawings we've already done,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sure we'll get the highest grade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Yeah, be right back.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Bye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[zooming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Oh, stop freaking out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know Yumi's crazy about you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That's what you think.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't figure you guys out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you going out together or not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitates] Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's complicated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right now,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll bet he's completely snowing her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wouldn't really call myself a rebel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm just a little… rebellious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Well, you did manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get yourself kicked out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your last school</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>putting posters all over the place.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[William] I object your honor,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>extenuating circumstances.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They were love letters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You mean love makes you crazy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Makes me totally insane.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[bushes rustling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wind howling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita to self]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Monster's only exist in fairy tales.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[wolf howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[wolf howls]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[animal growling nearby]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just what I was afraid of,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alert blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think I have to remind you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that we haven't done a single drawing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since we got here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't even want to think about the grade</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're gonna get.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go ahead, you draw…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] …you're better than I am.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm at school. XANA's attacking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll head to the factory but you guys</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>have to pick up Aelita on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No problem, we'll go and get her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I left her on the Red Trail.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Is Yumi with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather you call her yourself.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See you in a minute.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, I don't do anything half way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No way, it's all or nothing with me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just can't bring myself to be sensible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But hey…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Being sensible is just not sensible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You stole that line from the Subsonics.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You listen to them?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, they're awesome.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's about time we got back to work, huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] "The Hermitage"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[music crescendos]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is anybody home?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Are you sure this is the place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That's what Jeremy told me.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Let's follow him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He may be a little dumb</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he does have a good nose.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nervous, aren't we?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a warm welcome… Nice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yumi, we can't find Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[classical piano playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music crescendoes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't tell me you haven't found her yet!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What have you guys been doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She may be in big danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Chill, Jeremy, okay?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're doing everything we can.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Who knows,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe Aelita just went back to school.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Kiwi led us to an old house in the woods.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're gonna take a look inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll call you back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we have any news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door slammed]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] It's locked.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] No signal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] That way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] You thinking what I'm thinking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, and that means Aelita must be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps] Hey, Odd, watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Looks like XANA's trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to lead us somewhere.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all] Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry princess, we're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich… It's a trap!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA! He's going to…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get Aelita out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] You'll be cooked alive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we don't get you out of there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all straining]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd, run to the factory with Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Deactivate the tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's our only hope.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] I knew it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now we'll have to go above ground.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Wait!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[eerie music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd… There's a passage over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I… think it leads to the sewers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is no time for jokes, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm not joking, Odd… I'm sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow… Incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did you know about this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, I, um…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Forget it, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I should've told you about William sooner.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, that would've been better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was really worried.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No time to lose, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Otherwise,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Ulrich will end up like dim sum.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, head for the scanners!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll start the process.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whoosh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Aelita, the Overwing is for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our taxis are waiting for us. Let's go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tower, dead ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be careful!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've got two tarantulas guarding it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll never be able to fight my way</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through two of those horrors!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Maybe I can lure away one of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, what are you planning on doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>She's gonna steal the show.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Go ahead.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't look.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Well, my little monster friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did you miss me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Yoo-hoo…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Surprise!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>They're not all that invincible.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[weapon clicking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh-oh. Jeremy, I'm all out of ammo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Okay, I'll reload you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be patient.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] We're gonna have to keep</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the monsters busy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Wait for my signal to run.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Gotcha!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yu… Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting] I, um… What's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>really going on…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>between you and… William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing at all… He's… just a friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Done! You're fully loaded!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Great, Jeremy! I'm breaking off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[rewind sound]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Congratulations, Ms. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You found an Amazonian Yucca</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>here in our woods?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Uh… Yeah, and it wasn't easy, either!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I think it's going to be much easier</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>grading your work… Zero!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, did you manage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get any drawing done this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah… But I had to drag Ulrich far away</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Yumi and William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Going back in time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>didn't change anything there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I went to check out that house,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Hermitage? Nothing to report.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's gone back to being a normal house.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Abandoned, but normal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's so weird…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All those visions I had there…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not to mention the underground passage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that you knew about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[eerie music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's as if I'd already seen that house…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a dream.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A new mystery to solve for us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is for you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's to keep us one step ahead of XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This way, we can always stay in touch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought that pink would suit you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow, looks cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It matches her hair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thank you, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] There you go,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're like a regular school kid now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>