<c.bg_transparent>[theme music starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>AMNESIA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[monitor whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[humming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Here we have the "nanosphere"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that the Nano Tech Services company</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was kind enough to lend us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who can tell us</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what nanotechnology is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[geeky groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy, go on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's microscopic size technology.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are nanomotors,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>nanocircuit boards and nanogears.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Herb and Sissi hum]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the medical field, for example,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scientists are developing "nanodoctors,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tiny machines which will be able to travel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through our bodies to combat disease.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scientific research however</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>still has a long way to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are these robots capable of fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pimples, cellulite and things like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yes, they can, but the priority</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is for more serious illnesses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And nanotechnology</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't do a thing about stupidity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poor Sissi, what a shame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mrs. Hertz] All right now, quiet down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] So, this nanosphere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is used to make microscopic devices.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Strange, it hasn't been cleaned properly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's gelatin inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It looks like the greasy stuff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd puts on his hair every day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since you think you're so clever, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why don't you take a sample</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for us to examine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The gelatin is used as a culture</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where nanodevices can develop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It looks an awful lot like jam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Sorry, but I just couldn't resist.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I'll get you for that, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] This is a science class,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>not a comedy club!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This nanotechnology is incredible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now there's a field</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd like to work on in the future.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have enough trouble with normal size</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>technology, much less microscopic.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, that looks good. Can I have some?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I warned you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[everyone laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah... [laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But taking advantage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of my sweet tooth wasn't fair.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I said I'd... [groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning] It's my head! I...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Hey, Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich passed out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take him to the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim plods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-He was just fine this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I know. It's really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dorothy] All right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get some rest now, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi gasping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dorothy] What are you doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I wanted to find out</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>how Ulrich was.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Much better. He's asleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Just a second. Can I see him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hesitating] I don't know, I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You see, I'm his best friend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hesitating] Eh...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Dorothy] All right, but not for too long.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi tittering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs joyfully]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're so handsome</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi surprised]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Where am I anyway?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the infirmary. You passed out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-The infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What infirmary?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who am I? What's my name?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Eh... Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You must've hit your head</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when you fell down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And who are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Me? I'm Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your sweetheart.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Watch it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, when are you gonna admit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're mad about me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're kidding.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm allergic to anyone who's conceited.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're your own favorite fan club!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>My sweetheart?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Dorothy] Our patient is awake, I see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ulrich, how are you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich hesitates]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, much better.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take him to his room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure you're all right?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim plods and groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] What is this, an epidemic?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Come on, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Herb and Nicolas surprised]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Milly] Well, what d'ya know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] See those three kids there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're your worst enemies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] But why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, it's Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's going on? Why is he with Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You feeling better, good buddy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Who are you? Huh? Leave me alone, creep!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on, it's me, Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's enough. Can't you see?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He doesn't wanna know you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So stay away from us! Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[they sigh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter with him?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Jeremy grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, these are your good friends,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas and Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] He forgets things.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'd better remind him! [grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm very thirsty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] You know what would be good</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for you? A walk in the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here, thanks.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He didn't recognize us. It's crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Could be amnesia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Let's go see what the nurse says.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Good idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta bring him back to his senses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi and Ulrich? Can you believe that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Here. You need the energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, what do you feel knowing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're with the prettiest girl in school?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, to be honest, nothing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi] What did you say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What I mean is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you're really not my type.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At least, he's not completely</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>out of his head yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Hey, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Spying on me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I was just...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're a liar!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Ulrich, cut that out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're buddies, remember?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's not what she says,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so get outta here, and make it fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, don't get all worked up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, are you all right? Come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich and Sissi! Just the two of you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This could be the beginning</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a big romance.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, forget it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's gonna be a pain in the neck</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the whole time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] Come sit down. You need to rest.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sorry, but...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I need is to be alone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whimpers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi munches]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The answer is no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can't you see I have no time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what's happening,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it's an epidemic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy and Yumi grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Tamiya groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] We can stay and help you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The best way to help</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is to stay out of my way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Maybe Odd had more luck.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No doubt about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich's got amnesia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought he was gonna slug me just now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a real epidemic,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>according to the nurse.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But you don't catch amnesia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's not contagious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something's really weird.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'd better ask a doctor about it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Too bad that nanodoctors don't exist yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nanodoctor...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now I understand!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ominous music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Mrs. Hertz!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Oh... where am I?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] You'll be all right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Look at this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] It's the gelatin from this morning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[expressing disgust]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are those ugly creatures?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What I was afraid of.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're nanoviruses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And XANA must have crated them</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack memory cells.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That means that it is contagious!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Like all viruses, you can</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>catch it from food, contact, sneezing...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Soon the whole school will be infected,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>including us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] A world without memory...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Under XANA's control.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Let's go to the factory fast.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita must be in danger on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And Ulrich... we're gonna need him.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, Odd, it's Ulrich who needs our help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He'll only get well</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if we can deactivate the tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Besides, if he can't remember anything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>he won't be much good to us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Excuse me, is my room around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Has everyone gone crazy around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Third door on the right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts] I…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know who you are...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it seems we're friends.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[background laughs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[everyone pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly and Tamiya grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Not a minute to lose!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's going on around here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[principal groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[annoying noise]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, I'm so glad you came.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You really know how to cheer someone up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts intensely] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't seen anything to worry about</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>either in the forest or the desert area.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, beam yourself over to the mountains.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send Yumi and Odd to the glacier.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower's gotta be somewhere!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting from far]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready for the North Pole?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>We're on our way, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Through the tunnel in the park.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ten seconds to transfer time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic door opens]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Odd.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi and Odd grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, take the access on your right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Right, boss.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita, anything new?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I haven't been all over yet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but still no vibrations.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Odd are pretty far away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, you just lost 20 life points.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we've got a welcoming committee.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't panic. There's just one crab,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the activated tower can't be far.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll warn Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>He's coming towards you, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Don't worry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He just wants to play hide and seek.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Playful little beast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Wow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What am I doing here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What kind of place is this?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't tell you now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got an emergency.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I can't remember anything,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I have something important to do here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Tell me what it is.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well uh... Sure, why not?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Once you're on Lyoko, you'll have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to do something, amnesia or not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What's Lyoko?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's… Look...</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>See that pillar behind you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You've gotta slide up one level.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Uh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll see a few scanners.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Get into one of them, and then just wait.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You'll get all the answers you want.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Yoohoo.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Over here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Crabby.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Target hit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two things guys: one, Aelita's waiting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the other side of the glacier.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-And two?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Two, Ulrich's on the way.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Ulrich? I'll wait for him here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi panting] Better hurry.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Transfer Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to the virtual world, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] What is this place?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What are we here for?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To fight, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-To fight?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I don't know how to fight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But of course you do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You just forgot,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I'll refresh your memory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd mutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Okay, come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I found the activated tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Lead the way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're just dodging my blows.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Don't you have a weapon?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a few arrows,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I prefer to save them for now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And I don't wanna hurt you with them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Oh yeah? No kidding!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] We're almost there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Yeah, it seems almost too easy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have a funny feeling about this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm sick of always being right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] That way!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Four against one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, it's better than five or six.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Hang in there girls.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll try to send you reinforcements.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>First, let's get rid of two of them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, it's not gonna hold for long!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts] Hey, you ought to save</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>your strength. You're gonna need it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Why? Are there other levels?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I like it here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-It's a video game, but for real.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah, but now it's time to stop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and Yumi need you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich hums] Who said that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jeremy, come on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Hey, wait,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we haven't finished the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich runs and grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Again? Yumi, be careful.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've only got a few life points left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] Ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Nice going, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi] One to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry, Yumi! The wall's not gonna last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] There. I win the game.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Yeah, but you beat an ally.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now that you know who your friends are,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's time to meet your enemies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? Enemies? What enemies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're crabs. Monsters created by XANA.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, I can't explain now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi and Aelita need our help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And right now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich and Odd grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita surprised]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To get rid of them,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you have to hit the thing on their shell</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that looks like an eye.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Sounds easy enough. Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blast]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What happened to her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nothing serious.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've gotta protect Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's good to see Ulrich</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with his memory back again.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're wrong. He's still got amnesia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ya, ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[strong effort]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Thanks</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for clearing the passage!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Eh? She's leaving?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers] Not exactly total recall.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy, I'm coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, I'm Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Here we go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[resonant voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sighing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] Laser arrow!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Impact!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great guys. You're one heck of a team!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is that it? No other players?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, we can go home. The game is over.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Huh? But how?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Magic! Watch.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Exactly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In the medical field, for example,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>scientists are developing "nanodoctors,"</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tiny machines which will be able to travel</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>through our bodies to combat disease.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scientific research however,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>still has a long way to go.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are these robots capable of fighting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>pimples, cellulite and things like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs] Yes, they can, but the priority</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is for more serious illnesses.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And nanotechnology</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can't do a thing about stupidity.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Poor Sissi! What a shame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] All right now, quiet down.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This nanosphere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is used to make microscopic devices.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Strange, it hasn't been cleaned properly.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's gelatin inside.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] It looks like the greasy stuff</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd puts on his hair every day.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Since you think you're clever, Ulrich,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>why don't you take a sample</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for us to examine?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's used as a culture</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where nanodevices can develop.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, it looks an awful lot like jam.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's try to cook it. You never can tell.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Milly grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] Ulrich, what are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How dare you destroy school equipment!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll have to punish you severely for that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And it's going to be a punishment</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you won't forget!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] I hope not, Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I sure hope not.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stammers]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>