<c.bg_transparent>[theme song starts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital typing and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Today, make evil go away </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, be there when you call </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Code Lyoko, stronger after all </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>THE LAKE</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can take your hand luggage</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the bus with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And the rest of your stuff goes down here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if XANA attacks while we're away?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>After a week of working day and night</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think we deserve this weekend,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>don't you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It'll be the first time</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we go camping together too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What program are you talking about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita thought we should shore up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the protection shields on the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-We haven't tested it yet though.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You two are incredible, really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>As if we didn't have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>enough homework…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia, weren't you listening?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta store the suitcase.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You said that carry-on was okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, I'm carrying it, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi, what are you doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with all that stuff?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's my baggage, Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You were told to only take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what was strictly necessary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now get a move on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and take all that junk back to your room.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But Jim, my party dresses,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my shoes and all my makeup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi] I can't possibly go without them.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And my hairdryer too.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now listen, Elisabeth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>This is a camping trip</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's only two days.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your bicycle too should be left at home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do you want me to tell the principal,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my father,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that sports activities are being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>discouraged on school trips?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, but make it snappy now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You're kidding, Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's wrong?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How could I leave Kiwi in his room</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while we're getting fresh air?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Speaking of being cooped up,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi got stuck with a test this weekend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not one. I've got two tests today.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You lucky dogs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I wish I were on that bus with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd have loved to sneak you on,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but we got a lucky dog already.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know who I'm talking about.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the torture session's about to start.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll speak to you later. Thanks, Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Elisabeth! Put that strap higher up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Seat belts weren't meant for puppy dogs.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Huh?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shushes]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet Kiwi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or they'll know you're here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, somebody looks very guilty.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What do you got inside there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In there?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Um… Some things to keep with me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the trip, like…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh, imagine that!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must be that stray dog</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that everybody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>saw running around near the campus.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He sneaked on the bus, I guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You went and bought him</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a collar marked "Della Robbia."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, it's… just a coincidence.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must belong to a very distant cousin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There are plenty of Della Robbias.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a common name, like Morales, or…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Knock it off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All animals are forbidden anywhere</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and everywhere on school grounds.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's great because</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're not at school now are we, Jim?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't try to be a wise guy with me,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've been caught red handed.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] As soon as we get back, you have</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an appointment with the principal!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quiet please.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For this exam all you need is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a sharpened pencil</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and your logic and concentration.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're lucky. As a computer program</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this math test should be</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a real piece o' cake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's a math test and a piece o' cake?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold it! Slow down!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sniffing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I told you not to keep him on a leash.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh yeah? What if he bit</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>one of the other kids? What then?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here we are. This will be our home</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and our laboratory for the weekend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>An unspoiled haven</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for all lovers of flora.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A field trip to a true garden of Eden.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In short,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an ecosystem unequalled</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the region.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And you are looking right at it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What? That microscopic island is</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>where we're gonna camp?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you think that's small,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wait until you see the rubber dinghies.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[indistinct chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I was afraid of this.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't get a signal here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I won't be able to access</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't worry, for the time being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can still call out. I'll tell Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Rats! The factor of minus x</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was the right answer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Looks like I'm in for another lousy grade.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Inferno here. Everything okay in paradise?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not really.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy can't seem to get on line.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're gonna have to check regularly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to see what's happening on Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You've gotta be kidding. I've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a huge French test in five minutes and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hello?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's it. I've been cut off.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-But I think she got my meaning.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[classmate] Hurry up, Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Be right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've gotta… go to the bathroom.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Remember to pitch your tents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>very carefully,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because if you don't,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the smallest gust of wind</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and poof! Down it'll come.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Actually, that reminds me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of when I was living in a teepee</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the desert near New Mexico.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, this might not be the right time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't know what you're missing,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, I want you all</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to read the instructions</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for the setting up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of your tents before you start</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if you don't wanna find yourselves</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up the creek without a paddle.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, get going!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Do you know how to set this up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Yeah sure, no problem.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Follow the instructions,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and just holler if you need any help.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… Thanks a lot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich, honey,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I thought maybe we could pitch our tents</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>side by side</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so we can talk together tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sorry, Sissi, but I didn't come camping</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to gossip or talk about clothes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'd rather sleep.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, I would be glad to set</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>up my tent next to yours for tonight.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sure, Herb.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Really? Oh, that's fabulous, fantastic!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>By the way, where's your tent?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let me know when you've set it up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing we can do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Without a connection,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it's totally useless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's just hope that XANA doesn't take</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>advantage of it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi is watching the store at home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, now let's see…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] The flower called</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>campanula insularis</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>can only survive</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on small islands such as this one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since it's protected from ruminants</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by a barrier of water.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, in your opinion,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what would happen if the lake dried up?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We would be able to walk home.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, everything seems okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No open window, no activated tower…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I might even get higher</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>than an F on my French test.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! I guess that's that.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Still no connection.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are they on a desert island or what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mrs. Hertz] The presence of so much</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>campanula </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>insularis </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>contributes in turn</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to the proliferation of a rare</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>species of butterfly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as we will soon see here in the woods.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Nicolas] I don't see what was so funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean, what's the use of a boat</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>if there isn't any more water?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, there's a lot of pollution</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in this lake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry up, come quickly, Jim, Mrs. Hertz!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's in a state of shock,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but he's breathing.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There was this thing in the lake.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It was black,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it shot a lightning bolt at Nicolas</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then it was gone.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It must have been an electric eel.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] I've seen them before.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>When I was a forest ranger in Quebec--</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim, enough chatter!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Make yourself useful</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and go get the first aid kit.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right away, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't an eel,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it was much bigger, it was huge!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ma'am, I really think</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we're in great danger here.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, don't worry, Jeremy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>These things happen.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Nicolas will be just fine.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[children scream]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[students]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But what's going on, Jim? We're scared!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stay where you are,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>let me go check it out.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah, the ambulance!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Suzanne?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What is happening here?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh no! XANA's attacking the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what to do!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, answer please!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] We absolutely have to find</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a way to get back to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] One step off the island means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>electrocution for sure.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] If we create a diversion</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>maybe one of us could get away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, you and Ulrich do that,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while we try to get in touch with Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If we only had an antenna.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, how big an antenna?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[girl screams] It was a horrible monster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panicked chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Calm down now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't know what that thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the lake is,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but I can tell you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that had better watch it</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>'cause he's gonna have to deal with me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and sparks will start flying and…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That is…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, there already are sparks…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you know what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, to begin with…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We've got to help Mrs. Hertz.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Suzanne…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Say something, Suzanne.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[slap]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, that's all we need!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The Lady Killer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy! About time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey listen, we're here playing </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Survivor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>with an aquatic monster</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that likes to electrocute anyone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who comes close to the shore.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anything on your side?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm totally helpless.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is really well protected</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and the Skid is in the process</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of losing most of its energy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Does it have many life points left?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>At the rate things are going with</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the ship, it's gonna be over in no time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Listen, there's no other choice.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ready or not, we have to test the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, do you have anything to write with?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll dictate what you have to do.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I oughta have a pen,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>since I've got a French test right now!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Go on then, shoot.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] That's the first time I slugged</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>someone without getting a reaction.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You have to give her mouth to mouth.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, mouth to mouth, of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim! You come even a hair closer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and it's the last thing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>you'll ever do on this earth. Understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, I cured her.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now, "shift the energy of the lateral</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>shields to the side under attack."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The left one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, the other left one.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, what are these commands?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you sure it's gonna work?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She'll never make it on her own, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy, we're all set, but we need Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi, the others are trying</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get to the factory.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Until then, you'd better get things</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>prepared for going to Lyoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Feeling better?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, obviously.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, you've all been through</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>an awful shock.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's the matter now?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help me, Jim! It's my dog!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He's in terrible danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Only you can help me save</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that poor defenseless animal, Jim!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, I heard you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Don't overdo it now, Della Robbia.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look, over there!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, holy moly…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How did that hound ever get into</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a mess like that?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was playing in the canoe,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and… Well…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A wind came up and carried him away.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, Jim, save my Kiwi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, okay,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but you stay right here, understand?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughs softly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Kiwi barking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim] All right doggy, come to Uncle Jim.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come here, I said!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You hairy hound, get over here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But… That's that sneaky Ulrich Stern.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come back immediately, will ya!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Stern, I'm responsible for…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Two on one…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tough guys.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jim] Stern!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come here, you slime ball.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't scare me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got rubber soled NASA issue</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>astronaut space shoes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jim moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It… smarted just a little.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see how fast I can pedal.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There we go. The place needed a cleanup.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got good news and bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The good news is that Aelita got through.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>My good news is that I finally managed</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to get connected to the Supercomputer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The bad news is that our black,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>muddy sludge monster is on the prowl.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You can never beat us, XANA, you hear?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're a Lyoko warrior, you swore to it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You swear to keep our secret?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I swear.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Good answer, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[student] I wanna go home!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[children screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Watch out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panicked screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Now if Aelita can just get there in time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we can launch the program.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You can still change your mind, William.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Are you kidding?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well, how do you feel, William?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All ready to take on XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and his monsters.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted moan]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Why, of course!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] The program's almost complete.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is the Skid beyond hope?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No, not yet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted grunt]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William, listen, it's me, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted exhale]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>William!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[distorted laugh]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, it's launched.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… We should feel proud of ourselves.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Our program is operational.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>how are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Aelita, at last!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold on much longer!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Give me time to set up</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a delayed self-virtualization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and I'm there.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electricity crackling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay, everybody, hurry it up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run to the antenna over there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>it'll be our lightning rod!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just in time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Is something wrong, Yumi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>For a second there,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the real William came back, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] That means</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll bring him home someday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] The electrical discharges</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>are getting more intense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Given the enormous rate of ionization</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>against the dispersion factor</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the ground,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>they're going to reach a highly</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>critical mass in…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's see, just about seven minutes.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Meaning?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>In seven minutes everything on this island</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is gonna turn into one big barbecue.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[children screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[powering down]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[all gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, Benjamin Franklin.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think Aelita will remember</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to program a return to the past?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Go on, Yumi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Return to the past now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] So, I regenerated the shield</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>by activating several towers</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a few seconds at a time,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and that's what saved the Skid.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So that's what you've been doing</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while we were gone?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What a fun weekend.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyway, it's effective, isn't it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Obviously, it requires too much energy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to be able to use it all of the time.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hey, how come you're</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so cool all of a sudden, Einstein?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA attacks don't scare you anymore?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're still scary,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but since he never makes the same mistake</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a second time, and since</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita and I have been working nonstop</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for all of this week,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'd like a little…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Okay, we get the picture.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Hey, what'd you do with Kiwi this time?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Well, let's say that I found somebody</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who learned</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what a dog's life really means.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on Kiwi, hurry!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to get to my exam!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>