<c.bg_transparent>[theme tune intro playing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital sputtering and beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat synthesizers come in]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[whooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Going far</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To save all that we love ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ If we give all we've got</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We will make it through ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Here we are, like a star</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Shining bright on your world ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Today, make evil go away ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we'll reset it all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, be there when you call ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, we will stand real tall ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>♪ Code Lyoko, stronger after all ♪</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer blipping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Come on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[alarm beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I am so darn lame!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] Hi, Einstein.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You look awfully down. What's the problem?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've been spinning my wheels for days</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on Aelita's antivirus</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and trying to decode Franz Hopper's diary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Just a question of time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You think so?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Even with the latest data</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>from Sector Five,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't moved ahead one micron!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What if I'm just not good enough?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Okay!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think I know someone</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who needs to air out his neurons!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here's how to do it:</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>tonight, Odd is screening his short film!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone seen any of it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He wouldn't let us.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Do we know who's in it, at least?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Humbly speaking,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think it's unfair to say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>that this first role</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>will reveal to the world</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>my true star personality.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Can you sum up the story</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a few words for the Kadic News?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… That is… It's a love story.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And at the same time, it's a thriller.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With suspense.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And of course, it's got a good dose</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of psychology… and it's very funny.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[giggles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A real comedy. Quite satirical…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So you have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cartoonish boing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've got to go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Someone's calling me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both giggle]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible chatter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Chardin clears his throat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Welcome to the Kadic Academy</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cinema Club's Short Film Night.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Charlie Chaplin, Dziga Vertov, Tex Pincho.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of them got their start…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How's it going, Odd? No butterflies?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. I'm cool.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You never guess.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…to full-length features.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Which is also why…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Chardin] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I'll be keeping…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Relax! You'll be great!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks, that's sweet.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But move your hand,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or lose it at the elbow.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cartoonish boing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>…the short film is, was</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and always will be an important art form</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>which can say</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>as much as a full-length feature.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Chardin] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Our first film</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>is by Odd Della Robbia and is entitled,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>rather poetically, </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Natural Grandeur</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi titters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Chardin] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>No one has seen it yet,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>but it isn't hard to imagine</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>a subject, perhaps,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>on the fragility</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of our ecosystem, which…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[film projector running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Chardin shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[projector keeps running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister drums beating in film]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[moans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[projector running]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Mr. Delmas hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Help! Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's awake! Oh, no!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[imitating Jim's voice]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What's all this racket about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs and grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We have to get outta here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's coming!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I tell you! She's as big as her ego!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's impossible!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You know how big that would make her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you've lost your senses!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right! Let's go to the infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[stamping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's too late! She's found us!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[in slow motion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh, rats!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I just broke a nail!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I didn't know you could be so funny!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd yells] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Help!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Oh!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[projector stops]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groaning]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling] Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-You are nothing but a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[struggling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You're nothing but a…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[murmurs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Something wrong, sweetheart?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi stutters]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take care of this, Mr. Delmas.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I think you've lost your senses!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right! Let's go to the infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All right, children. I want you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to go quietly back to your rooms.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jim… Take care of the students!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll take Sissi to the infirmary!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] You think it's…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. No activated towers.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA's got nothing to do with it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The nurse said</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi received an electric charge.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She's in shock but fine,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>there's nothing to worry about!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Oh! Poor Sissi.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I have to admit her acting</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>was really electrifying!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Right… False alarm!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We can all sleep easy now.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yawns]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That works out just fine,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>because tomorrow's Sunday.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And on Sunday…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shouting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We sleep in!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door squeaks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi stutters unintelligibly]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible stuttering]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! What has gotten into you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[scribbling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[door clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What's this racket about?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi? You should be in the infirmary.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Your father's going to have my head again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grumbles]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Jeremy! It's Sunday!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK… We're coming.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[sinister music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] A message in code…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>written by Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I ran the Supercomputer</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all night to translate it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look at what it turned up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible distorted voices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can help you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It has to be a trap by XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He must have managed to possess Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>without activating a tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I don't think so.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Otherwise, Sissi would have gone after me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>She would have tried to get me onto Lyoko</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>so that the Scyphozoa</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>could steal my memory!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita's right.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>If you ask me, someone, or something,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>wants to contact us through Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's not XANA!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well then, who is it?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No idea… To find that out,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>we'll have to talk to Sissi again!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>OK. I'll bring her over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Anyone care to join me?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I will! I'm your man!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I mean… You know what I mean.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go take a look around on Yoko.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I still want to make sure</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA isn't setting a trap.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll go with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>With the Scyphozoa and everything?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's risky!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy… Stop worrying about me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Transfer Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Transfer Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Ulrich!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Scanner Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Great timing! Nice work, Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Thanks… OK, make it fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's a reconnaissance mission!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We know. Relax! We won't go crazy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine accelerating]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasp]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells] Yeah!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[siren]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy. Bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi's going to the hospital!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No! We have to bring her back here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-No sweat! I've got an idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone beep]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Are you thinking</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>what I think you're thinking?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yeah, good thinking!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich? Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything OK with you guys?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>To tell you the truth… I have no idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Has the superscan</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>picked up an activated tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Still nothing. Why?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Well… Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll send you a visual!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] What is this white tower?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I was about to ask you</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>the same thing!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich] Do you think this tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>has something to do with Sissi</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or with the being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who is trying to contact us?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>I don't know!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Come on! I'd like to see this close up!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[engine revs up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! Behind you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Faster!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[engine revs up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-I've got it floored.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Turn left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow… Are you sure?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's nothing to the left!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[both breathe heavily]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well done, Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>But it's weird they didn't come back</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>to attack you!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Something's not right!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It wasn't us they were after!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>They're trying to destroy the white tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hold them off!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Feel like a little game of bowling?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-A what?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Forget it. It's a bad joke.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sometimes I really crack myself up.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[revving up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[cracking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[soft music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Mr. Delmas] Well? What's wrong with her?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I haven't the slightest idea.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>We'll keep her under observation</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>for a few hours, and then we'll see.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Very well… Let me know at the first sign</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>of a change in her condition!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Of course.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeping continues]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[woman] Such a sweet patient.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>He was lucky.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[man hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-What did the girl at reception say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Room 237.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[phone rings]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Jeremy?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I've just located an activated tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>XANA is on the offensive!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Jeremy… I'll call you back!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doctor screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams] Stop!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doctor grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasping and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screaming and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[doctor exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Poor thing! She had hypertension…</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doctor exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Not anymore… Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>It's OK, Jeremy! We've got Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Great! Bring her to the factory fast!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>It won't be that easy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>There's a doctor possessed by XANA</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who doesn't seem to like the idea!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Ouch!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich! I've got some bad news.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hang on.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts and screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So, Jeremy, what were you saying?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Activated tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in the Ice Sector!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What should I do with Aelita?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Protect this tower</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>or deactivate the other?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ulrich.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Jeremy? What do we do?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doubtful] Protect the white tower.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can go deactivate that tower!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All alone? No way! It's too dangerous!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll get rid of this one</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>and then, we'll go together!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[nods and gasps] Look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita! Stay next to me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>No. Aelita, don't do it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[revving up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Let's get outta here!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Here comes doctor Doom!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I hope she was wearing her seat belt.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[groans]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[sad music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hum]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing and panting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[electric whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Cool!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doctor grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd] Phew!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Ulrich?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Relax. I'm fine!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That's gotta hurt!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[thumping]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Ah… Finally!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Yumi… What are you doing?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'm buying time!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi! I believe that… Hey!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Sissi? What's the matter with you?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wait! Let her go!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[revving up]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer alarm beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Aelita! Look out!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Aelita yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Get to Lyoko! Quick!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[tense music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[metallic clanking]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[evil laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Yumi screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[doctor grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Ulrich grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting] Jeremy!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't hold out much longer.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Sissi yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-Sissi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Sissi exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps and pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Virtualization!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[gasps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[explosion]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Run, Aelita! Run!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[action music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] Watch it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You lost 80 life points!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-One more hit and it's game over!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Odd] </c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent>Relax! It's part of the plan!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Something wrong with the elevator?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I'll explain later.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Hurry on up to help Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laser blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[mechanical footsteps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Get on!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[lasers blasting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants and yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunting and yelling]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Odd yells]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screams]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[electrical whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[grunts]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[screaming and grunting]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>-[Ulrich] Yumi!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[ethereal music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[digital whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[heartbeat]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[exhales]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Aelita] Tower deactivated.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[swooshing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[hums]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Wow! Great job, Aelita.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[upbeat music]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[pants]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[door clicks]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Everything OK, Sissi?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>How do you expect everything to be OK</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>when I'm surrounded by big fat losers?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy shrugs]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Did I miss something?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughter]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Come on! Tell me!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Odd just offered Sissi a role</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in his next film!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The story of a girl</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>driven by a mysterious being</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who tries to make contact with humans.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>All of which takes place</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>in a virtual universe full of danger!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What did she say?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>That no one would ever believe</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>such a ridiculous story.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[laughing]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>You don't say.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>What about you? How's it going?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Finished.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>The computer deciphered</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>all the lines of code Sissi spoke</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>while she was "spellbound."</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>So? What's it say? Let's hear it.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Tons of interesting stuff.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>A lot of elements that are gonna help me</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>find the antivirus for Aelita!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>And do you know who this mysterious entity</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>who wants to get into contact with us is?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>Well… Take a look!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[whirring]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Jeremy] I'm warning you,</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>this is completely crazy.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[computer beeps]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[unintelligible distorted voices]</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[male voice]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I can help you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I want to enter into contact with you.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>I can't believe it!</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[Franz]</c.bg_transparent><c.bg_transparent> I am Franz Hopper.</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>"I am Franz Hopper"?</c.bg_transparent>
<c.bg_transparent>[theme music]</c.bg_transparent>